Chapter 102: Spring comes after the winter winds

Fang Yuan arrived at the internal affairs hall and turned in the golden honey wine.

The middle-aged male Gu Master in charge was very surprised. While holding his pen, he asked, "You completed the asset mission already?"

"What do you think?" Fang Yuan retorted.

The middle-aged male Gu Master frowned, this was the mission he chose specifically to make life difficult for Fang Yuan. To think he completed it so quickly!

He looked at Fang Yuan, his eyes threatening, saying solemnly, "Young man, answer whatever I ask you. If you do not reply honestly, it will affect your evaluation. Let me ask you, did you complete this mission alone? Say the truth, we will investigate thoroughly."

"Of course I finished it myself." Fang Yuan replied.

"Good, I will note that down." The middle-aged Gu Master recorded while laughing internally, you're just a newbie, how could you complete it alone? Such a falseful report, the clan would definitely investigate. You will have trouble then.

But unexpectedly Fang Yuan continued, "But this situation is slightly peculiar. That day I only went to scout out the area, but to think the bear was digging the beehive. Using that chance, I retrieved this honey wine."

"What?" The middle-aged man's pen stopped, raising his head to look at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan shrugged, smiling, "What, did you think I could accomplish this mission alone? To say the truth, this is all thanks to you, finding this mission for me."

The middle-aged Gu Master was stunned on the spot, a complex and unexplainable feeling in his heart as he laughed dryly and continued to record in the book.

Fang Yuan stared at this man calmly, knowing full well that his extremely difficult asset mission was all 'thanks' to this man. Unfortunately, he had already completed the mission; even if the clan investigates, Fang Yuan had the appropriate set up already. He could stall Fang Yuan no longer.

Even if this matter was handled by him.

This is the grief of being in the system. Your status is the chain that restricts your actions.

"Alright, your mission is complete, you can inherit the family asset already. Except, your asset is all controlled by your uncle and aunt. The internal affairs hall will retrieve it for you, come back in three days." After recording, the middle-aged man said.

Fang Yuan nodded, he knew this rule, but he stared at the middle-aged man's record paper, saying, "According to the clan rules, the internal affairs mission record needs to be confirmed by the accomplisher on the spot. Please let me see this record."

The middle-aged man's expression changed, he did not expect Fang Yuan to be so familiar with the process. He snorted lightly while handling the report to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked at the record without any problems. A few hundred words with the final evaluation—Good.

He could immediately see the relationship between Gu Yue Dong Tu and this Gu Master.

This evaluation was definitely fair, showing that the middle-aged Gu Master did not give up on his work ethics just because of Gu Yue Dong Tu; the reason he helped Dong Tu was only because of their friendship and the transaction between them.

It was the 'taking money to settle problems for others' type of transaction.

Giving the report back to the middle-aged Gu Master, Fang Yuan left the internal affairs hall.

Outside, Gu Yue Dong Tu was already gone.

Fang Yuan could not help but laugh coldly. Gu Yue Dong Tu's influence was not big enough to affect the internal affairs hall. Even if Gu Yue Bo the clan leader wanted to do this, he would have to go against the immense pressure from the clan elder circle and pay a huge price in his political career.

There was a phrase on earth, called 'those who live in the society has to follow its rules.'

There were rules in the society, and that is a form of system. Those who follow the rules, being anyone's pawn piece, restrict each other, and it is not up to them to control.

Unless an individual's strength has reached the point where it can oppose the entire organisation, otherwise, joining an organisation and wanting to retain freedom was a pointless dream!

Borrowing the power of the clan system, Fang Yuan had already affirmed the truth of getting back his assets.

Regardless of Gu Yue Dong Tu or the clan leader, they will not pay the political price for interfering with such a small matter.

In the guest hall.

"Brother Dong Tu, there is nothing I can do anymore." The middle-aged Gu Master sighed, standing in front of Gu Yue Dong Tu.

Gu Yue Dong Tu's face was grim as he remained silent on his seat.

"Are there really no more methods?" Beside him, Aunt fearfully asked in an anxious and indignant tone.

The middle-aged man shook his head, "The results are set in stone and have entered the internal affairs hall's procedure. Unless the two clan elders in power or the clan leader interferes. Brother Dong Tu, this internal affairs hall's inventory list states clearly the inheritance items and amount, please return them all and don't make my life difficult." Saying so, he took out the inventory list.

The inventory had a ton of records, from expensive items like estates to cheap tables or chairs, other than that there were also the Gu worms that Fang Yuan's parents had left behind.

After a Gu Master dies of battle, their Gu worms would be retrieved as an inheritance for their successor. This was a political move by the clan.

Aunt took a look at the list, before losing her composure, "Damn it, you cannot do this! This is all ours, OURS! Hubby, say something, think of something. Without these assets, what do we have left? Even our servants will be gone by half, we cannot afford it! "

Slap!

Gu Yue Dong Tu stood up and sent his palm flying towards Aunt, sending her to the ground from her seat.

"Noisy bitch!" Uncle flew into a rage, scolding in an agitated tone, "Frog in the well, the clan rules are there, you think you can choose not to return them? Dumb, ignorant!" Aunt used her hand to cover her cheeks, beaten into stupidity, lying on the ground in shock, staring at her husband blankly.

"Hmph!" Gu Yue Dong Tu grabbed the inventory list, gritting his teeth, scanning through.

His eyes were filled with blood traces as he breathed heavily, saying with hatred, "Return! All these things... I will return... NOT A THING LESS!!! But..."

His veins popped from his forehead, the muscles on his face twitching, his expression full of ruthlessness, "But Fang Yuan, I cannot stop the internal affairs hall, yet I can deal with you. Don't think everything is well and alive now that you have these assets, hmph!"

Three days later, Fang Yuan walked out from the internal affairs hall with a stack of house and land deeds and sold human contracts in his hands.

"To think this inheritance is so abundant." He was slightly stunned.

Even though Fang Yuan had some estimations, after receiving this asset list, it was way out of his expectations.

Over ten mu of farmland, eight family servants and three bamboo buildings, and a wine tavern!

"No wonder uncle was so insistent, thinking of all ways to stop me." Fang Yuan could understand Gu Yue Dong Tu's actions.

With such a large family asset, even in this world, one could live like a king.

Ten mu of farmland, eight family servants, put this aside first. Those three bamboo buildings were property assets—even if they were only rented out, every month, the rental amount was enough to support Fang Yuan's current cultivation.

Other than that there is also a wine tavern. Note that there is only four wine-selling areas in the entire village.

Such an asset, if on earth, would be equivalent to having several mansions and a hotel, it is an aristocrat life with multiple servants.

What's worth mentioning is, this world's living conditions was way more ruthless and difficult, thus the village being the safest location, priced the property assets even more expensively than on earth.

"It is said that my Fang family, three generations ago, had a clan elder who held power and left much inheritance for his future generations. With these family assets, the seven Gu worms aside, even if that number doubled I can still afford them! But the crucial point isn't this. It is this grass Gu!"

At this point, there was a grass Gu lying quietly in Fang Yuan's palm.

It was dainty and delicate, the emerald green roots resembling a ginseng's beard. There were some semi-transparent stolon that was like jadeite. Nine pieces of round-shaped leaves that were jade green covered and reflected each other, forming the shape of a round plate.

This was the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, the healing-type Rank two Gu worm.

If it came to normal healing, it had no difference from the Life breath grass.

The true value of the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass lay in its leaves - Every one of the leaves torn from it was a vitality leaf.

Vitality leaf is also a type of grass Gu. At rank one, it is an expendable type, disappearing after one use.

It had another flaw, and that was when a piece of vitality leaf is used to heal injuries, within the next hour, other vitality leaves had no more healing effect on the person.

But, all in all, it was easy to refine, and instantaneous healing together with the easy feeding of it made it the most popular healing technique among Rank two Gu Masters.

Healing Gu Master, every group needed one. But in times where multiple Gu Masters were injured, what can a single Gu Master do? If the healing Gu Master was the one who died, or got lost, what happens to the rest?

Thus, Gu Masters always prepared some healing methods for themselves, and the vitality leaf was the best method. Every Gu Master that roamed outside needed to prepare at least one or two.

"After I refine the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, every piece of leaf torn out would be a vitality leaf. Using the primeval essence to inject into the grass, I can make it grow new leaves. Thus, this Nine Leaf Vitality Grass can be said to be a moving goldmine. The most important asset of all... without exception. Having this Nine Leaf Vitality Grass is an avenue of business. In this dangerous world, which Gu Master does not get injured on their missions? They have a perpetual need for the vitality leaf."

"No wonder Gu Yue Dong Tu was known as the 'hidden elder' even after he retired many years ago; he still held great influence outside. So the reason was this Nine Leaf Vitality Grass."

Gu Masters needed the vitality leaf, and Gu Yue Dong Tu sold the leaf. With such a relationship, it is no question that his influence remained.

Fang Yuan was enlightened.

"Only in this world are clan relationships raised to such a level, restraining Uncle and Aunt. If this was earth, with such a conflict of interest, Fang Zheng and I would already have had been killed by them. This is not good, it seems I have some trouble ahead, Uncle and Aunt will not let go so easily."

"But I have already grown up with Rank two cultivation. If they want to deal with me and also consider the clan regulations, they would be highly restricted. Hmph, regardless of what they do, just show me what you've got. Dealing with it as it comes, I will handle them all."

Fang Yuan walked on the street, his eyes glimmering in brilliance.

A gust of winter wind blew on his face.

It was still far from spring, but Fang Yuan knew that 'spring' (start of his new life) had already come.

Chapter 103: The larger your ambitions, the smaller the world

The wine tavern wasn't big, but it was in a good location; it was at the eastern side of the village near the eastern gate.

The flow of people was the largest at the eastern and northern gates. Thus, the wine tavern's business was pretty good whether it was day or night.

"Young lord, please take a seat." An old man lowered his head to Fang Yuan.

Few waiters wiped the benches and tables with a fawning and flattering smile towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan shook his head. He didn't sit, but walked around the tavern, sizing everything. He thought inwardly, "This is my wine tavern."

This wine tavern only had one floor, but it had an underground wine cellar.

Huge and square black tiles covered the floor. There were eight square tables; two tables were set against the wall and other six tables were surrounded by four benches.

A dark brown, long sales counter could be seen immediately upon entering the wine tavern. There were papers, brush, ink stones and also an abacus on the counter. Behind the counter was the liquor cabinet where all sizes of wine jars were displayed. Some of these were large wine jars of black pottery, and some were small and bright porcelain wine bottles.

Fang Yuan was walking around as he wished; the old man and waiters didn't dare to sit, they could only follow close behind.

They were restless, the news of the landlord changing was too abrupt. The previous landlord Gu Yue Dong Tu was cunning as a ghost, he was strict and acrimonious; they were under a lot of pressure. This boy in front of them was actually able to take the wine tavern from Gu Yue Dong Tu's hands. Such a method of snatching was shocking. So these people's gazes towards Fang Yuan carried unease and fear.

Fang Yuan suddenly stopped, "It is good. But this store is a bit small."

The old man immediately walked forward and bowed to answer, "Young lord, we put sheds outside every summer and lay tables and benches. But it is winter now and the wind is biting cold, no one would sit outside even if we put up sheds. So we took them down."

Fang Yuan slightly turned. He glanced at this old man, "You are the shopkeeper?"

The old bent his waist even lower and said even more respectfully, "I dare not, I dare not. Young lord, this wine tavern is yours, whoever you choose as a shopkeeper is the shopkeeper."

Fang Yuan nodded then glanced at the waiters; they all seemed to be competent.

If it was on earth, he would be anxious that this shopkeeper and the waiters would team up and scheme against him, the owner. But in this world, Gu Masters were high and mighty, killing mortals would only require a thought. Even if Uncle and Aunt egged them, these mortals wouldn't dare to go against Fang Yuan.

"Alright, bring the accounting books and bring me a pot of tea." Fang Yuan sat down.

"Yes, young lord." The shopkeeper and waiters moved hurriedly.

There were as much as sixteen account books, and every book used bamboo papers which had a light green hue. The bamboo papers were more brittle than Xuan paper and were suitable for the damp atmosphere of the Southern Border.

Fang Yuan casually picked up a few books and skimmed over them, asking some questions occasionally.

The shopkeeper gave prompt replies; soon, his forehead was covered with sweat.

Fang Yuan had created the Bloodwing Demon Sect and taught countless people in his previous life. He was rich in experience and his eyes were shrewd. Others might be confused and dazzled when they see the account books; but in his eyes, all the doubtful points were as clear as crystal.

This wine tavern was the second biggest asset after the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass; Fang Yuan naturally wanted to firmly grasp it.

There were only some small problems in the account books which could be attributed to mistakes and negligence. These mortals didn't dare to be presumptuous.

However, when Fang Yuan turned to the last page, he saw that this month's income had already been taken by Gu Yue Dong Tu.

"Young lord, the previous landlord personally took it. We didn't dare to resist." The shopkeeper replied while wiping his sweat. His aged body was already trembling and his face had become very pale.

Fang Yuan was silent, he put down the account books on the table and glanced at the shopkeeper.

The shopkeeper immediately felt a huge pressure as if a mountain was pressing down on him. He was scared witless, kneeling on the ground.

Seeing the shopkeeper kneeling down, the waiters also astutely knelt down one by one.

Fang Yuan calmly sat and turned his gaze towards them.

The waiters immediately felt like they were in a world of ice, they couldn't resist Fang Yuan's aura. They were all silent.

To these mortals, the wine tavern's work was both stable and safe, the ideal job. They didn't want to lose this job.

Fang Yuan stopped upon seeing that his authority had been established, going too far could end up being detrimental. He slowly spoke, "I won't bother about the past matters. I saw that your wages are somewhat low; waiter's wages will be raised by twenty percent and the shopkeeper's by forty percent from now on. Work properly and you will get more benefits."

Fang Yuan stood up and walked to the entrance.

The group of people kneeling on the ground were stunned for a good while before coming back to their senses. All of their eyes brimmed with tears that flowed down their faces.

"Thank you young lord for your great kindness!"

"Young lord is compassionate, we will definitely work with all our strength!"

"Young lord, you are our benefactor, please take care."

Tearful sounds came from behind, there were also crisp sounds of forehead smashing on the black tiles from continuous kowtowing.

Use might alongside mercy, this was the only way the top controlled its subordinates no matter in which world. Might was the foundation and under this might, any small kindness would be magnified by countless times.

A benefit without might would only give a title of a good samaritan. But as time passed, people would no longer feel grateful for such kindness and it would instead result in greed and disaster.

"But these ways to control people are all unorthodox methods. It would be highly esteemed on Earth, but in this world, raising one's own strength is the one true way. No, even on Earth, strength is first."

Fang Yuan thought of the Scarlet Red Imperial Ancestor[1].

In those days, the Scarlet Red Imperial Ancestor had gone through and experienced a trial and he had come to a conclusion: Political power comes from guns!This was the naked truth—strength was the foundation of any political power. So-called authority is only an accessory to strength.

Actually, not only authority, wealth and beauties were also derivatives of strength.

Fang Yuan headed towards the three bamboo houses after leaving the wine tavern.

These three bamboo houses were rented out by uncle and aunt; they were practically full.

This world paid attention to more birth. To the ever-growing huge population, the space in the village seemed narrow.

The clan had the system of the eldest son inheriting the property. Other sons and daughters would have to rely on their effort. Even if a lot of people relied on clan politics to get a meager split of the family assets and work hard outside, they might not even be able to save enough to buy a bamboo house in their whole life.

On one hand, raising Gu consumed a lot and on the other, the village had limited space, so the house prices were very expensive.

They could naturally build houses outside the village but that wasn't safe. Wild beasts and snakes would always roam around and could intrude into the houses. Above all, every time a beast tide occurred, all the houses outside the village would be destroyed.

Extending the village was the only way to solve this.

But extending meant the area to defend would increase and the village wouldn't be able to defend against beast tide's attacks. Moreover, if the area was big then it would be difficult to guard against and search for infiltrating Gu Masters of other villages.

Gu Yue village had extended several times in history but had been devastated by beast tides. After learning from this lesson, the current village size was already the largest.

Fang Yuan skimmed through it and after understanding some situations, he already got the picture.

These three bamboo houses were operated very well by Uncle and Aunt. The rent was also customized to get more profits, so he might as well just let it run like that. He calculated that the earnings from these three bamboo houses were not as much as the wine tavern but the difference was not much.

The overall situation was much better than Fang Yuan's original expectations.

Just the day before yesterday, he was left with nothing and had become so poor that his primeval stones count didn't even reach five. But now, all of a sudden, he rose to the list of richest people in the clan.

The female tenants in these rented houses were all Rank two female Gu Masters in difficulty. After knowing Fang Yuan's identity, their gaze towards him turned amorous.

If they could be near to Fang Yuan and get married to him, then they would no longer have to rush about facing danger; their lives would be smooth and steady.

Such a life was what they were pursuing and using all their strength to fight for.

That is to say that if Fang Yuan wanted, he could retire and live a rich life now like his uncle used to.

With a tap of a finger, many female Gu Masters would flock to him.

"But that is not what I want." Fang Yuan stood at the second floor of the bamboo house, letting female Gu Masters' provocative gazes fall upon his body. He frowned as he held the railings and gazed afar.

Far away, stretches of green mountains went on continuously, looking like a sleeping giant with the gray-blue sky as its quilt.

The endless rivers and boundless earth, when can I move unhindered on them?

Amidst the winds of change, dragons and snakes rise from the lands[2], when can I look down upon all living things?

"Since rebirth, I have been drifting with the waves like a rootless duckweed. I spared no effort to get the family assets; with this base, I can be said to have become independent and gained my footing. Next would be to unearth the Flower Wine Monk's inheritance and put all my effort into cultivating to Rank three, then I can leave this village and go out to the wide world!" Fire burned in Fang Yuan's deep black eyes.

Qing Mao mountain was one of the countless mountains in the Southern Border. And the Southern Border was only a corner of this world.

Too small, too small! How could such a place sustain his lofty ambitions?

Compared to his ambitions, these family assets—which others were cracking their brains to obtain, which was a thing of yearning—was as tiny as dust.

"Brother, come down, I need to talk to you." At some point in time, Gu Yue Fang Zheng had reached the bamboo house. He looked up at Fang Yuan and yelled.

"Hmm?" Fang Yuan's train of thoughts were broken, he looked down at Fang Zhen with an indifferent look.

The brothers' eyes met; it was silent...

Younger brother Fang Zheng was downstairs and was shrouded by the shadow of another house. He was facing up; his eyebrows were raised and his two eyes were flickering with light.

Brother Fang Yuan was upstairs; sunlight shone on him, his slightly drooping eyes had pupils as dark as night.

Similar faces reflected in each other's eyes.

As to his little brother's appearance, Fang Yuan wasn't surprised. Fang Zheng was a weapon of Uncle and Aunt to fight for family assets.

And yet, so what?

Fang Yuan looked down at Fang Zheng, sighing inwardly. A grade aptitude, but nothing more than a pawn... truly insignificant.

[1] It's referring to Chairman Mao. Writing his name directly in chinese texts will be hit by the censors. Back

[2] 龙蛇起陆—It's along the meaning of 'an earthquake is about to happen, and all kinds of living creatures feel fretful and uneasy, they start to move about lively. It's a visualisation description. Back

Chapter 104: Want to buy the liquor worm?

Eventually, Fang Yuan did not go downstairs, and his brother did not go up.

The two persisted, and the distance between the floors indicated that the distance between the brothers were enlarging.

The talk was not smooth.

"Brother, you are just too much! To think that you are such a person!" Downstairs, Fang Zheng stood, his brows creasing tightly as he screamed.

Fang Yuan was not angry, but laughed lightly, "Oh, what kind of person am I?"

"Brother!" Fang Zheng sighed deeply, "After our parents died, Uncle and Aunt adopted us. They have the gratitude of raising us. To think that you are so heartless, returning favor with revenge. Brother, is your heart made of stone?"

Saying so, Fang Zheng's tone was slightly trembling.

"So strange, this inheritance is rightfully mine, what is there to be said about revenge and favour." Fang Yuan retorted unenthusiastically.

Fang Zheng gritted his teeth, acknowledging, "Yes! I know, this inheritance is from our parents. But you cannot take them all, you have to at least leave some for Aunt and Uncle to let them enjoy their life in retirement, right? Doing so, you really are making our hearts bitterly disappointed, you let me look down on you!"

Pausing, he continued, "Did you ever return home to see the living conditions that they are in now? Half the servants at home were already retrenched, they cannot afford it. Brother, how can you be so cruel!"

Fang Zheng's eyes were red, clutching his fist, he screamed at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, he knew that Uncle and Aunt had controlled the assets all these years and must have amassed a huge fortune. Even if this was not so, just with the profits at the end of the month from the wine tavern, they would be able to afford all those servants. They are only pretending to be poor so Fang Zheng would come and find trouble.

Fang Yuan used his gaze to size up Fang Zheng and said directly, "My adorable little brother, if I insist on not returning the assets, what can you do? Although you are sixteen, you have already acknowledged them as parents, don't forget that. You have lost the rights to the inheritance."

"I know!" Fang Zheng's gaze had a divine light, "That's why I am here to challenge you to a written war challenge[1]. On the arena, let's have a match to decide victory, if I win, return a portion of the family asset to mother and father."

This world's Gu battles were like the Earth's martial arts competitions.

Between clansmen, if they had unresolvable conflict, they could use this method to settle the problem. There were many types of Gu battles—1 versus 1, 2 versus 2, battle of arts, battle of strength, and life and death battle.

Of course, Fang Yuan and Fang Zheng would not be so serious as to fight to the death if they had a Gu battle.

Seeing the brother's determined expression, Fang Yuan suddenly laughed, "It seems that before this, Uncle and Aunt specifically told you huh. But, as someone who lost to me before, you have such confidence of winning me?"

Fang Zheng squinted, unwillingly thinking of what happened not long ago—the humiliation on the arena.

Ever since, every time he thought about it, rage would rise from his heart. This rage was directed towards Fang Yuan as well as himself.

He hated himself for being useless, being frantic at the critical moment. As a matter of fact, he had underperformed in that battle. His tempo was taken away by Fang Yuan, and he only thought of using the Jade Skin Gu at the last moment. In the end, he lost abruptly and very indignantly.

Fang Zheng's anger towards himself fuelled even more intense indignance.

Thus, unavoidably, he had such a thought —"If I could redo it, I can definitely perform better and defeat my older brother!"

Thus, when Uncle and Aunt complained to him, Fang Zheng not only wanted to take back the inheritance for the two of them, but also wanted to fight Fang Yuan again to prove himself.

"Things are different now, brother." Fang Zheng looked at Fang Yuan, his eyes burning with determination, fires blazing around him, "Last time, I performed badly and lost to you. This time, I have successfully refined the Rank two Gu worm Moon Raiment. You cannot break my defense anymore!"

Saying so, he emitted a vague light blue fog around his body.

The fog enveloped him, and in the mist, it eventually formed into a long floating ribbon.

The ribbon[2] looped around his waist and coiled around his two limbs. The middle section of the ribbon drifted above his head, causing Fang Zheng to give out a sort of graceful and mysterious magical breath.

"Indeed, it is the Moon Raiment, how foolish, revealing your trump card like that." Fang Yuan stood on the stairs, seeing this scene, his gaze twinkled.

Moon Raiment was a Rank two Gu worm with defensive properties. Although the defense was slightly lower than the White Jade Gu, it could assist others in defending and had greater contribution towards small group fights.

With this Gu in his hands, Fang Yuan really could not break Fang Zheng's defense with his bare fists. Sending the fist over was like hitting cotton, absolutely losing its kinetic force.

Even if he used the Moonlight Gu, he could not breakthrough unless it was the Moonglow Gu. Thus if Fang Zheng wanted to fight and invited Fang Yuan to a Gu battle, according to the clan rules he has to accept. Without revealing the White Jade Gu, Fang Yuan might really lose.

A grade is A grade, and with the clan leader's nurture, Fang Zheng is growing rapidly. It could be said that, during the academy phase, Fang Yuan suppressed Fang Zheng. But now he had to admit, Fang Zheng was starting to show the brilliance of a genius and was showing imposing threat to Fang Yuan.

"But, you think I did not expect this?" Fang Yuan stared down at his brother, his lips curling.

He said to Fang Zheng, "My persistent little brother, of course you can challenge me. But have you gotten the approval of your teammates? If during the battle, your group has to go on a mission, how would you choose?"

Fang Zheng paused; indeed, he did not think of this.

He had to admit, his brother was right. The group had to work together, and if teammates wanted to go on individual operations, they would need to report first.

"Thus, you might as well go back, find that leader Gu Yue Qing Shu of yours, and explain the situation. I'll wait for you guys at the northern gate's wine tavern," Fang Yuan said.

Fang Zheng hesitated slightly, then gritted his teeth, "I'll go now, brother! But let me tell you, delay tactics don't work."

He came to Gu Yue Qing Shu's residence, and the family servant led him in.

Gu Yue Qing Shu was practising using his Gu.

His body was moving around in the garden's arena stage, extremely agile and fit.

"Green vine Gu," he lightly said, and from his right palm, a green vine shot out. It was around fifteen meters. Qing Shu grabbed the vine and used it as a whip, splitting, coiling and sweeping around.

Pow pow pow!

The shadow of the whip swept across the floor, sending the concrete on the broken ground flying.

"Pine needle Gu." He suddenly kept the vine whip, and flipped his long green hair.

Immediately, from among the hair pine needles shot out like rain.

The pine needles hit the wooden puppet not far away, piercing its entire body and creating close and numerous pinholes.

"Moonwhirl Gu." Next, he placed out his left palm, and a green-coloured crescent insignia glowed in a bright green light.

With a flick of his wrist, the green moonblade was sent flying.

Different from the trajectory of a normal moonblade, this green moonblade was more curved. While flying in the air, it travelled in an arc, making it harder for enemies to predict.

"As expected of the number one Gu Master among the Rank two, Senior Qing Shu! With such an attack, I can't even last for ten breaths. He's really too strong." Fang Zheng stared with his mouth wide open, forgetting his original intention in the first place.

"Oh? Fang Zheng, why are you here. The previous mission just ended, you have to rest more, got to keep that balance between work and rest!" Gu Yue Qing Shu upon noticing Fang Zheng, kept away his fighting aura and smiled gently.

"Senior Qing Shu." Fang Zheng bowed to him respectfully.

This respect was sincerely from his heart. Ever since he joined the group, Fang Zheng had been attentively taken care of by Qing Shu, and in Fang Zheng's eyes, Qing Shu was like an elder brother.

"Oh Fang Zheng, it seems you have business with me?" Qing Shu wiped the sweat off his forehead while going towards Fang Zheng with a smile.

"It's like this..." Fang Zheng said his intentions, as well as the entire story.

Hearing so, Qing Shu's eyebrows slightly rose. The truth is that he had heard a lot about Fang Yuan, and when compared to Fang Zheng, he was more interested in Fang Yuan.

"Might as well meet him for once."

Thinking so, Gu Yue Qing Shu nodded, "I have something to discuss with your brother as well. In that case, let's go together."

Fang Zheng was overjoyed, "Thank you senior!"

"Hehehe, no need to thank me, we're in the same group." Qing Shu patted Fang Zheng's shoulders.

Fang Zheng could feel warmth in his heart, his eyes unwillingly turning red.

The two got to the tavern. A shop assistant had been expecting them all along, and brought them inside.

On a square table by the window, there were several side dishes and two wine cups, and a pot of wine.

Fang Yuan sat on one side, and when he saw Gu Yue Qing Shu, he smiled and extended his hand, "Please sit."

Gu Yue Qing Shu nodded to Fang Yuan. He took his seat, then said to Fang Zheng, "Fang Zheng, go take a stroll around, I'll talk with your brother."

He was a smart person. Upon seeing only two wine cups, he knew that Fang Yuan wanted to have a chat alone.

The truth is, he had such intentions as well.

Fang Zheng acknowledged and left the shop indignantly.

"I know you, Fang Yuan." Qing Shu smiled, opening the wine pot skillfully, pouring a cup for Fang Yuan and one for himself.

"You are a very interesting, smart person." Saying so, he raised his cup towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed and raised his cup as well to return the toast.

The two drank it in one shot together.

Qing Shu poured another for Fang Yuan again, as well as for himself.

As he poured, he said, "There's no point beating about the bush when talking to a smart person. I'll be open, I want to buy your Liquor worm, how much would you sell it?"

He did not ask Fang Yuan if he was selling it, but asked directly—How much, showing his immense confidence.

He was the number one Rank two Gu Master. At a young age, he reached Rank two peak stage, overpowering the Rank two upper stage Chi Shan and Mo Yan.

Once he appeared, he took the initiative and poured the wine and toasted Fang Yuan.

His confidence together with his gentle smile formed a unique aura. It was not overbearing and forceful which could make people disgusted, but it made others feel his persistence.

His long green hair, and the winter sunlight shining through the window and unto his fair, gently streaked face. This let Fang Yuan subconsciously think of the bright and beautiful radiance of spring.

"A truly talented person. What a shame," Fang Yuan thought.

He was not bothered by Qing Shu's act of taking over the initiative. In fact Fang Yuan was slightly appreciative of him, and he sighed lightly.

[1] Written war challenge—SHAOLIN SHOWDOWN!! Gu battle showdown basically. Back

[2] If you really have no idea what it looks like, perhaps this link might help (tell me if it ever gets broken?) https://vignette4.wikia.nocookie.net/valkyriecrusade/images/0/0e/Celestial_Raiment_H.png/revision/latest?cb=20170718080803 Back

Chapter 105: I will lose extremely terribly

Gu Yue Qing Shu was also an orphan like Fang Yuan and Fang Zheng.

His parents had died in a wolf tide when he was young.

He was personally raised by clan leader Gu Yue Bo.

After he was tested to have B grade aptitude, he received Gu Yue Bo's personal guidance. His aptitude was outstanding and could be said to be at the top among the B grades, it could even be called 'false A grade'. Gu Yue Bo had been raising him as a clan leader candidate.

Gu Yue Qing Shu had a warm temperament and was amicable. He was highly praised and well received by the clan members. He was also very loyal to the clan; Fang Zheng's arrival cut off his hopes of inheriting the clan leader position, but he was instead happy and wholeheartedly took care of Fang Zheng.

On Earth, Yue Fei[1] Song Dynasty patriot and general.], Wei Zheng[2] Tang politician and historian, notorious as a critic, editor of History of the Sui Dynasty.] and Bao Zheng[3] Northern song official renowned for his honesty.] were people with such characters.

Unfortunately, in the wolf tide a year later, the Northern gate would fall; to block this gap and protect the clan members, he stepped forward. In the end, he forcefully used a Rank three Gu with his Rank two cultivation, becoming an impenetrable fortress and successfully defending the village.

However, his aperture was destroyed because of this and he finally turned into a treeman and died.

Thus, Gu Yue Qing Shu had left a profound impression on Fang Yuan.

When he saw Fang Yuan sighing, Gu Yue Qing Shu naturally didn't think that Fang Yuan was looking back on his death and thought Fang Yuan was vexed due to the Liquor worm.

He smiled, "Fang Yuan, you should already be clear on the limits of Liquor worm. The Liquor worm is only a Rank one Gu worm and can only refine Rank one green copper essence. But you are already a Rank two Gu Master; the Liquor worm has no use towards red steel primeval essence. Although you have a wine tavern now and can easily raise the Liquor worm, why would you vainly raise something that has no use to you?"

He switched the thread of discussion, "The Liquor worm has no use to you but it is useful to other Rank one Gu Masters. Especially in the awakening ceremony next spring, there will be a new batch of students and the Liquor worm will be of great help to them. So, you might as well just sell the Liquor worm to the clan and contribute to clan's strength."

Fang Yuan didn't reply.

Qing Shu pondered, guessing Fang Yuan's intention, "I understand now. You are reluctant to part with the Liquor worm, you even want to fuse it. If I am not wrong, you should be thinking of going the route of the Rank two White Chrysalis, then the Rank three Mist Perspiring butterfly fusion route, right?"

"This is the most widespread and also the most practical recipe. The Mist Perspiring butterfly is a great Gu worm. But the White Chrysalis has no ability. This fusion route wouldn't have much value to you. You have C grade aptitude and now have Rank two cultivation; White Chrysalis doesn't have any ability and will only squander food, it will be of no help to you."

"What is the possibility of you reaching Rank three? Even if you succeeded in advancing to Rank three, you will probably be middle-aged by then. Will you raise the useless White Chrysalis for tens of years? It will be better to use the expenses of raising White Chrysalis on nurturing Gu worms. That is more practical and will be more helpful to you, am I wrong?"

"Liquor worm's true value lies in refining primeval essence and raising a small realm. If you go through this fusion, you will only be treating the Liquor worm as a material, won't that be a pity?"

All Gu worms had only one ability.

For instance, the Spring Autumn Cicada was a Rank six Gu, but it only had the ability of rebirth.

The new Gu worm that comes from fusion usually took an ability from one Gu worm and enhanced it. White Jade Gu, for instance, took the defensive ability of Jade Skin Gu and enhanced it, while losing the White Boar Gu's ability to gain increased strength.

That is to say, if someone obtained White Jade Gu, it would only help in defense and couldn't increase the Gu Master's strength.

Qing Shu was correct, the Liquor worm's value was in refining primeval essence and raising its stage by a small realm.

To Gu Masters, this was another form of increasing their primeval essence reserves while also being an enormous help in nourishing their aperture and increasing their cultivation speed.

If one went through 'White Chrysalis, Mist Perspiring Butterfly' fusion route, the resulting Gu worms won't have the ability to refine primeval essence which would truly be a pity.

In fact, Flower Wine Monk took this route and refined the Mist Perspiring Butterfly from the Liquor worm, using it to enchant women and commit evil acts. After his death, the Mist Perspiring Butterfly continued to degenerate due to not having sufficient food and finally reverted back to Liquor worm.

Qing Shu's eyes flashed upon seeing the silent Fang Yuan and continued, "Actually, our clan has a recipe; this recipe raises Liquor worm to Rank two Moon Harbinger Gu then the Rank three Seven Fragrances Liquor worm. Seven Fragrances Liquor worm has the ability to refine primeval essence."

"Fang Yuan, if you don't want to sell the Liquor worm, then we could change it to a business transaction. You will sell the Liquor worm to the clan and if the clan can refine it to the Seven Fragrances Liquor worm, you will have the right to use it for five years. If it fails, the clan will compensate for it. What do you think?"

Doing this meant the clan will bear all the risks for the fusion. With such a superior condition, others might eagerly agree to it.

But Fang Yuan only sneered coldly in his heart.

He knew himself.

With his 44% C grade aptitude, advancing to Rank three was almost impossible. In his previous life, Fang Yuan had stalled at Rank two for over a hundred years before finally and coincidentally obtaining a talent-raising Gu worm and becoming a Rank three Gu Master.

Five years of using rights sounded wonderful but to Fang Yuan, it was like trying to catch the moon's reflection in water.

Gu Yue Qing Shu had said so because he saw Fang Yuan's ambitions to charge to Rank three, so he intentionally threw this sweet bait to lure Fang Yuan.

But he had miscalculated from the start!

In Fang Yuan's memories, there was the best recipe for the Liquor worm fusion.

First was advancing the Liquor worm to Rank two Four Flavors Liquor worm then to the Rank three Seven Fragrances Liquor worm. Whether it was Four Flavors Liquor worm or Seven Fragrances Liquor worm, both had the ability to refine primeval essence.

However, it was not easy to refine the Four Flavors Liquor worm.

First of all, its fusion required two Liquor worms; Fang Yuan only had one currently. Next, the fusion required four types of wine, and these four wines should be of four different flavors: sour, sweet, bitter and spicy.

Let's not talk about the difficulty in purchasing a Liquor worm with there being hardly any supply of it in the market.

Let's look at these four wines first.

Spicy wines were the most common, ordinary white spirit wine were all of this type. For sour wines, you could get bayberry wine and grape wines; rice wines could fit the sweet wine criteria. But as for the bitter wines, it needed some thinking to be done.

From what Fang Yuan knew, there was a type of green bitter wine which was brewed by using Ai grass. Unfortunately the Ai village was immeasurably far away, how would he obtain it?

Fang Yuan had detained the Liquor worm not because he wanted to wait and sell it for a high price. Rather, Fang Yuan had all along wanted to go through this fusion route; using any other fusion routes could be counted as ruining the Liquor worm.

How could Gu Yue Qing Shu know what Fang Yuan had in mind.

Seeing Fang Yuan not making any moves to agree at all, he threw his trump card, "Fang Yuan, if you sell the Liquor worm, I can mediate between you and Fang Zheng. At least, he won't use the family assets to challenge you to a Gu battle. You also know the clan rules; the challenge must be accepted. Even if the Gu battle request is not approved by the higher-ups, it must first be accepted. Even if you are sure of your defeat and don't want to go to the arena, directly throwing in the towel, you still need to accept the challenge."

This world promoted martial spirit; clans didn't need cowards. If there was a challenge, Gu Masters must accept them. Accepting the challenge proves that you are not a coward. Even if you admit your defeat in front of the public, that too would be a conduct of courage.

Under the oppression of the ruthless environment, this had automatically turned and formed into a system of values.

The clan's higher-ups would arbitrate according to the results of the Gu battles and resolve any problems and disputes.

The premise of a Gu battle was to have a reason. The challenger should be in the right and the challenge should be reasonable, or the two parties could both make an agreement similar to betting, only then would the Gu battle be approved.

"Fang Zheng's Gu battle request is reasonable and fair; it will be approved. If this happens, no matter the result—whether loss or win—will be judged by the elders. Who do you think the elders will side with between you and Fang Zheng?"

Qing Shu's smile became bigger, he looked at Fang Yuan with a burning gaze and continued to add pressure, "Fang Yuan, if you win, you will simply have to part with a tiny bit less of the family assets. But if you sell the Liquor worm to the clan, you will be contributing to the clan. The clan will remember you. I can also guarantee that Fang Zheng would never challenge you on the basis of family assets."

The implication was that Fang Zheng could still challenge Fang Yuan for different reasons.

This was one of the things Gu Yue Qing Shu and Gu Yue Bo would be happy to see. They hoped Fang Zheng would defeat Fang Yuan and break the shadow in his heart to build up his self-confidence.

Fang Yuan suddenly smiled, he had been listening to Gu Yue Qing Shu's chatters from the beginning. And now, he finally spoke.

"You think I will lose if we fight?" Fang Yuan asked Qing Shu.

Qing Shu also smiled, "Fights are full of variations, no one can foretell what might happen. However, I need to remind you, Fang Zheng has already refined the Rank two Moonveil Gu; you won't have much of an advantage."

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan shook his head, and the smile on his face became bigger, "I will lose, I'd definitely lose."

Qing Shu stared blankly.

Fang Yuan stared into his eyes and continued, "Not only will I lose, I will even lose very miserably. I will hand over all my parents' inheritance, and from then on I will sleep on the street and wander about begging in the village."

"You...." Gu Yue Qing Shu was smart, he understood Fang Yuan's true intentions. His expression became grave; no longer was it confident and graceful.

Fang Yuan's words were a bare threat.

Fang Zheng was being raised as the next clan leader; if it was made known that he had recognized others as his parents, used his cultivation and aptitude to bully his brother, snatching the inheritance, then there would be a devastating damage to his reputation.

Even on Earth, a person who did this would be shamed and disdained by people. Let alone in this world where the values of family love was raised to a whole new level.

It wouldn't be anything if Fang Zheng wanted to become a devil. But he was going to become a clan leader, a leader of the righteous path, and that meant he needed to uphold virtue and cherish it.

For a moment, Gu Yue Qing Shu looked dazedly at Fang Yuan. He discovered that despite hearing a lot about Fang Yuan, he had still underestimated the latter.

The dominance that he built up from his many sentences since the moment they met, had now crumbled with a bang.

Fang Yuan hit the nail on the head, directly indicating the main part to Gu Yue Qing Shu.

If it was another person, Fang Yuan would have spoken differently. But Gu Yue Qing Shu was someone who had extreme loyalty to the clan and in Fang Yuan's previous life, he would rather sacrifice himself to protect the clan. Thus, he had no choice but to worry because of Fang Yuan's threat.

However, he quickly calmed down, his eyes staring at Fang Yuan as he spoke between clenched teeth, "But you won't do this. Because the inheritance has been your goal all along, how will you cultivate if you give up the inheritance?"

Fang Yuan wasn't afraid. He met Qing Shu's gaze, his lips curled up in a smile. "That's why I believe you will give up the notion of buying the Liquor worm and also persuade Fang Zheng to not challenge me, am I wrong?"

Others might not be able to persuade Fang Zheng, but Gu Yue Qing Shu had this capability.

Fang Yuan had no doubt on this.

The situation was in a deadlock.

After a moment, Gu Yue Qing Shu lowered his eyes.

He stared at the wine cup in his hand for a while and suddenly laughed.

"Interesting, we will do just that." His tone carried a hint of melancholy.

[1] Yue Fei (岳飞)—[1103 AD—1142 AD Back

[2] Wei Zheng (魏征)—[580 AD—643 AD Back

[3] Bao Zheng (包拯)—[999 AD—1062 AD Back

Chapter 106: Half his life-savings gone to dust, only his vitality remains for eternity

A day later.

On the futon, Fang Yuan sat cross-legged.

A large face-sized white light was an arms' distance from his face, silently floating.

Fang Yuan took out piece after piece of primeval stones from his money bag and threw them into the light ball.

The white light contracted, but became more eye-piercing.

When it shrunk to a fist-size the white light was glaring, and Fang Yuan could only squint his eyes to observe it.

"Probably the last piece..." Fang Yuan played around with the primeval stone in his hand, knowing that the critical moment was here.

He tossed the primeval stone into the light ball.

He could vaguely see the primeval stone floating around in the light ball, like snow dropping into boiling water, constantly melting away.

A large amount of rock powder fell on the ground.

The primeval stone vanished, and the light ball exploded!

With a bam, the three Gu worms flew in three directions. One fell on the bed, while the other two flew to the walls, and then dropped to the ground.

Refining the Moonglow Gu had failed!

Fang Yuan's heart sank. He quickly moved his finger, calling back his Gu worms.

The Moonlight Gu and Little Light Gu wavered their way to Fang Yuan as they floated around, slowly landing in his palm, but the other Little Light Gu had no response.

It laid on the ground, its milky-white five star-shaped body gradually dissipating into the air.

After a few breath's time, it had completely vanished with no lingering traces.

This was the price of a failed fusion—according to the different fusing recipes, the Gu worm might get injured as a result, or when unlucky, might even die.

Even with his rich experience, adding on to the fact that Fang Yuan could multitask and had the right recipe, there was still a chance of failure.

Fang Yuan was not upset, he had seen such an event many many times. He had already performed to his best, and if the result still failed, it could only be attributed to luck.

"Luckily, it was not the Moonlight Gu that died, but the Little Light Gu. I can just buy another one from the shop, it is easy to replenish. If the Moonlight Gu died, it would not be easy trying to get another one." He had lots of cash now, even if one Little Light Gu died, he could just purchase another one.

Next, he inspected the Moonlight Gu and the remaining Little Light Gu. On the surface of both Gu, it was slightly dimmer than usual. This was the result of an injured Gu due to fusion failure.

"Once a Gu worm gets injured, the chances of a successful fusion would drop drastically. I have to wait for them to recover before I continue trying." Fang Yuan knew that haste does not bring success, and quickly kept the two Gu.

He estimated the time, around at least three days later would he be able to perform another try.

Cultivation did not end there.

Fang Yuan opened his right palm.

His left hand was pale, and on his palm, there was a green insignia with a grass pattern, like a dark green tattoo.

Fang Yuan's thought moved, and the primeval essence in his aperture began to move, like light red fog flowing towards the insignia on his left arm.

The green insignia was instantly brought alive. From Fang Yuan's palm, the tip of the grass emerged, followed by the round leaves of nine dark green leaves, lastly followed by the jade green transparent stem. As for the roots, they were not exposed.

On his palm, the original dark green tattoo was gone, only leaving behind traces of dark green lines. It represented the intertwining of the grass with Fang Yuan's palm.

It was the Rank two grass Gu—Nine Leaf Vitality Grass.

Right now, Fang Yuan's palm was like a piece of land, and a Nine Leaf Vitality Grass was growing on top of it, like the exquisite art made of jade stone carvings.

Fang Yuan stretched out his right hand's finger and plucked the leaves.

With every piece of round leaf that he plucked, Fang Yuan could feel a slight pain himself, like the feeling of pulling his hair.

After the nine pieces were plucked and placed at the bedside by Fang Yuan, there was only the bare stem of the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass left on his palm.

Fang Yuan continued to deploy his primeval essence. The light red-coloured Rank two primeval essence continued to rise from his palm like a cloud of mist, and covered the jade green stem.

The stem continued to absorb the primeval essence, and eventually a bud started to grow from deep within the stem.

This budding was pinkish green, small, delicate and very fragile, breaking upon contact.

Fang Yuan continued to use his primeval essence, and the bud grew bigger, its colour deepening. Eventually it grew into a piece of dark green colour, a completely mature leaf.

"I used up 20% of my primeval essence." Fang Yuan inspected his aperture and concluded.

He only had 44% primeval essence in his sea, that meant that he could only create two vitality leaves at one go.

After creating another piece, Fang Yuan grabbed a piece of primeval stone and rapidly recovered the primeval essence in his aperture.

When the primeval essence rose to 40%, he nurtured the vitality leaf again.

Rinsing and repeating like this after half a day, he had finally made the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass grow back to nine full leaves.

He did not pluck the leaves this time, but with a thought, kept the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass back into his left palm, turning it back into a green insignia.

He took the leaves that he plucked and placed them into a small bag, bringing it with him.

A piece of vitality leaf was a Rank one Gu worm, each worth around fifty primeval stones in the market. This meant that with just these nine leaves, it could allow Fang Yuan to earn four hundred and fifty primeval stones.

Of course, he incurred costs in creating them, but excluding costs, he still profited around four hundred primeval stones.

Among all of the family assets, the most valuable one was no doubt this Nine Leaf Vitality Grass. Owning it was tantamount to owning a gold mine! And this Nine Leaf Vitality Grass had an advantage too—it was easy to feed. It only needed water and sunlight to survive, thus there was virtually no cost in raising it.

To Fang Yuan, he could give up all the other family assets, but for this Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, he needed to grasp it firmly in his hands!

Of course, this type of Nine Leaf Vitality Grass Gu was not owned by Fang Yuan alone. In the village, others held this grass Gu as well.

In fact, there were five Nine Leaf Vitality Grass Gu that was collective property owned by the clan. Everyday there were specialized Gu Masters whose missions were to create large numbers of vitality leaves.

To Fang Yuan, this is a good thing.

If he alone had the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, the clan would definitely strike and buy this grass Gu by force. Just like how Gu Yue Qing Shu represented the clan and came to buy his Liquor worm.

Precious Gu like Liquor worm, Black and White Boar Gu and the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, the clan higher-ups all wanted to control it and make it useful for the whole clan.

Three days later.

A light ball under Fang Yuan's supervision suddenly exploded, and a new Gu worm floated in midair slowly.

It was sparkling and translucent, bent like a crescent, resembling a piece of water blue crystal. In a nutshell, it was like the Moonlight Gu that was enlarged in size by twofold.

Yet it was not the Moonlight Gu, but the higher-ranking Rank two moonglow Gu.

This time, Fang Yuan's fusion succeeded.

The Moonglow Gu is made by fusing a Moonlight Gu and two Little Light Gu. A Little Light Gu can raise the power of the moonblade by 100%, but two Little Light Gu still raised its power by 100%, this boost was not additive.

But the refined Rank two Moonglow Gu, its attack power reached three times of the Moonlight Gu!

Actually, there are many different recipes to refine the Moonlight Gu, and it has many advancement paths.

Fang Yuan took this path to raise the moonblade's attack power to the limit. The attacking range remained unchanged, it still had a scope of ten meters.

There was a route—using the Moonlight Gu and the Stone Scar Gu to perform fusion, the result would be the Moon Scar Gu. Its attack power remained unchanged, but the range doubled, reaching twenty meters.

There was another common route, which was using the Moonlight Gu with the Whirlwind Gu to fuse, creating the Moonwhirl Gu. Using it, the moonblade turns from blue to green, and at the same time its attack trajectory becomes curved. Gu Yue Qing Shu took this path.

As for Gu Yue Fang Zheng, he used the Moonlight Gu and Jade Skin Gu to create the Moon Raiment. This was a rare route and had an upper limit of Rank five, becoming the Moonlight Treasure King Gu.

However, having a Rank five recipe did not mean it was definitely possible to create a Rank five Gu worm.

Many Rank five Gu Masters did not have a single Rank five Gu in their possession.

What causes this awkward situation is not a lack of ingredients, but the success rate.

Gu fusion was not a 100% success rate. The higher the ranking of the Gu worm you are trying to refine, the lower the success rate. In his previous life, Fang Yuan's Spring Autumn Cicada had a success rate of less than 1%, and it failed countless times. Sometimes, he was lucky and less Gu worms died; other times, all the Gu worms died together.

To refine the Rank six Spring Autumn Cicada, it needed all Rank five Gu worms. Once these Gu worms die, all of Fang Yuan's hard work and accumulation would go up into smoke, becoming an illusion.

Fang Yuan failed countless times and started over many times, fusing once again and collecting Gu worms and special ingredients all over again. Eventually, he caused too much of a commotion and incurred a public outrage, causing the will of the people to become disorganised, and many deaths forming seas of blood and floating corpses.

He was lucky though, as he finally succeeded and obtained the Spring Autumn Cicada.

But once he obtained this Rank six Gu, all the righteous cultivators who were eyeing his Gu all along came to attack, and before he even got a chance to familiarise himself with the Gu, he suicided.

Thousands of millions of years, it was because of this disgusting failure rate that caused many high-ranking Gu Masters to waste their efforts, and go back to square one.

The only way was to slightly curb this failure rate.

And that is —

Vital Gu.

No matter the fusion result, failure or success, the vital Gu never dies. At most it gets injured.

Why?

Many people guessed that it was because the vital Gu is the Gu Master's first Gu worm and is linked to the Gu Master's life, forming a mystical relationship and connection.

As long as the Gu Master is alive, if the vital Gu's fusion fails, at most it would be almost dead.

Of course, the other Gu worms used in the fusion had a possibility of death.

Even so, a portion of the Gu Master's fruits and labour can be preserved and accumulated.

The vital Gu is the Gu Master's greatest fortune and fallback. Whatever the vital Gu is, it can to a large extent affect the Gu Master's development path. Conversely, Gu Masters also find new recipes aggressively to raise the level of their vital Gu.

Some Rank two and Rank three garbage recipes, to Gu Masters, it worsened their future prospects.

When Fang Yuan found that the Spring Autumn Cicada had become his vital Gu, why was he so happy?

This was why.

The Spring Autumn Cicada was an extremely rare Gu worm, allowing others to rebirth, it was a heaven-defying ability. No matter how it is refined, it will not die. If this was Fang Yuan's previous life where the Spring Autumn Cicada was not his vital Gu, if he continued refining, it could potentially die.

Spring Autumn Cicada was Rank six, something many Gu Masters would never be able to reach in their lifetime. An extremely large number of Gu Masters did not even have a Rank six recipe, and are still desperately searching!

Spring Autumn Cicada, although unable to be used to its full potential by the current Fang Yuan, was still his greatest treasure. The Flower Wine Monk's inheritance compared to this, was a difference between heaven and earth.

Chapter 107: Skillfully earning primeval stones, ill-intent customers come to wreck havoc

The cold snow came to an end, and spring wind took its place.

Without realising it, winter had already passed, and the days of spring arrived.

The frozen mountain creek began to flow again. The ice cones under the eaves of bamboo buildings and trees were sparkling and translucent, dripping water in the sunlight.

In the morning, the wine tavern was quite empty, there were not many drinkers.

Fang Yuan sat inside at the seat near the window. According to his request, the surrounding was covered by wooden plank screens, creating a small room for him.

A gust of wind blew in from the window, and the fresh and fragrant smell of the earth was wedged between the air, letting people who smelled it feel carefree and pleased.

Jiang Ya sat opposite Fang Yuan, his face full of smiles.

"These are the primeval stones this time, please confirm it." He took out four money bags, placing them on the table and pushing it towards Fang Yuan.

What was inside the money bag was naturally primeval stones.

Fang Yuan did not open them one by one, but checked their weight by holding them in his hand.

He had over a hundred years of experience making deals and transactions, so he could easily tell the number of primeval stones in his hands. One less and he could immediately tell.

This was nothing special, to be honest.

On Earth, there was an oil seller who placed a coin on the bottleneck and dripped oil inside, where the oil dripped in a line and entered the bottle through the tiny hole without any spillage. There was another divine shooter who could shoot tree leaves at 100% accuracy from a hundred meters away. There was also a butcher who worked for many years, using his hands to check the weight, he could tell their exact weight and when scaled, was exactly as he said.

How to train such a skill?

Nothing else but 'practise makes perfect'!

Accumulation of experience, when enough, can stir up a miracle.

After his rebirth, this kind of experience was naturally brought over as well. Fang Yuan used his hand to check, and on finding no problems, he then took out a small cloth bag and gave it to Jiang Ya.

Jiang Ya received it with both hands and opened the bag, checking the quantity carefully.

Although Fang Yuan had nine vitality leaves in his possession, he did not plan to sell it himself. If it was Gu Yue Dong Tu, he would rather do this to sustain his social relationships and increase his influence.

But Fang Yuan was reluctant to do this. It wasted too much time and effort. Thus, he sold them all to Jiang Ya who was a shop owner, so Jiang Ya could sell the Rank one healing grass Gu to the clansmen.

Jiang Ya is Jiang He's brother, and when Fang Yuan was searching for the Liquor worm, they met before. His brother was even Fang Yuan's half-alliance mate, thus, having him take over the transaction and sell to the clan, was a reliable method.

"One, two, three... nine. Indeed, it is nine vitality leaves." Jiang Ya counted three times before closing the bag and carefully keeping the bag close to his body.

Next, he raised his cup, toasting to Fang Yuan. "Lord Fang Yuan, happy doing business with you, let me toast you!"

His gaze towards Fang Yuan carried deep admiration, even turning into a hint of jealousy.

A year ago, when it was also spring. The first time he met Fang Yuan, the latter was still a student at the academy, not even having the rights to wear the Gu Master's battle attire.

But now, Fang Yuan was not only wearing battle attire, his belt was also red colour, and a square steel piece in the center of the belt—a Rank two Gu Master!

However, he himself was still a Rank one, carrying a green coloured belt.

Nevermind that, what made him jealous was, after getting the inheritance, Fang Yuan turned from a pauper into a tycoon.

He owned the wine tavern, bamboo buildings as well as the nine leaf vitality grass. It was all fortune that Jiang Ya would never be able to earn throughout his lifetime!

But, Jiang Ya did not dare to show his deep emotion of jealousy.

Fang Yuan sold the vitality leaves to him and allowed him to earn the difference in price. Fang Yuan is already his money tree, and Jiang Ya no longer dared to offend this junior.

"Sigh, comparing among people is odious....." Jiang Ya held the cup. His face was full of smiles, but in his heart, he was sighing deeply.

Fang Yuan raised his cup and drank it in one shot.

Jiang Ya's expression although secretive, with Fang Yuan's old fox wits, how could he not tell?

Fang Yuan did not put it to heart, for if Jiang Ya was not jealous, it showed that he had much greater heart, and that would make Fang Yuan think more highly of him.

But, he stared at Fang Yuan's small fortune and got jealous, this showed how little his world was, insignificant. Drinking with him was solely because he still had some value to exploit.

Jiang Ya put down the cup, excitedly saying, "The clan's vitality leaves are sold at fifty-five primeval stones a piece. I followed your instructions and only sold our grass Gu at fifty primeval stones, and the demand is overwhelming! Lord, why don't you make more leaves daily, that way we can earn much more!"

Fang Yuan listened and slowly shook his head, rejecting outright, "No, creating nine leaves is already my limit, it is already wasting much of my cultivating time."

This was the difference between Fang Yuan and a mere frog like Jiang Ya.

In Fang Yuan's perspective, primeval stones were just a cultivating resource, a tool. It is all for his cultivating needs. However, Jiang Ya treated primeval stones as his life goal, thus he cultivates in order to earn more primeval stones.

But even if Fang Yuan only made nine leaves a day, he could earn four hundred primeval stones daily, and with the accumulation, the fortune in his hands also grew to an amazing level.

Seeing Fang Yuan's rejection, Jiang Ya did not dare to push his luck, only moving his lips in pity, then continuing to pour wine for Fang Yuan enthusiastically, and then for himself.

"Indeed." He exclaimed, "Lord has such great fortune, you do not have to waste time and effort daily. In my opinion, why does lord have to stay in that poor old rented flat? Why don't you empty out a bamboo building and stay there yourself. Then marrying a beautiful wife, and having seven or eight family servants to take care of you. That is truly the dream life. Hehe."

Fang Yuan laughed lightly, not saying anything.

How could a farmer understand the ambitions of the conqueror!

He turned around, looking outside the window.

House after house, the bamboo roofs had remnant snow, bathing under the bright and beautiful light of spring. Faraway was a willow tree, the branches of yellow-green soft leaves rolling down, gently swishing in the soft spring breeze.

Fang Yuan's gaze was slightly blank as he thought about his current predicament.

After solving the problem of Fang Zheng, the family asset could be said to be in the bag.

The White Jade Gu and Moonglow Gu were successfully refined, he now covered attack and defense. What came next was the Liquor worm.But the Liquor worm was troublesome. To refine the Four Flavour Liquor worm, he needed a second Liquor worm, as well as sweet, sour, bitter and spicy—four types of wine. These things, he had no idea where to get.

"I definitely have to refine the Liquor worm. Without it, my progress will be slower by at least half. But to refine the Four Flavour Liquor worm, I will need to wait for the caravan and borrow that chance to showcase my White Jade Gu. That way, I can show off my true fighting strength and stop hiding my abilities."

Fang Yuan had the Moonglow Gu and the White Jade Gu. Together with his five hundred years of combat experience, he was stronger than most Rank two Gu Masters.

Slightly famous group leaders like sickly snake Jiao San, if fighting one on one with Fang Yuan, might not be his match.

But against Chi Shan, Mo Yan and Qing Shu, Fang Yuan was still weaker.

One was insufficient cultivation level, Fang Yuan was only a Rank two initial stage, but they were upper or even peak stage. Next was the lack of strong Gu worms. Fang Yuan only had two battle Gu worms, but they all had at least three and even hidden trump cards.

Among the same age group, Fang Zheng, Mo Bei and Chi Cheng were already showing their dominance, no doubt.

Especially Fang Zheng, now that he had obtained the Rank two Moon Raiment, he already has the ability to fight with Fang Yuan. As time passes, his cultivation level will get higher and eventually he will leave Fang Yuan in the dust.

Unless Fang Yuan can fuse the Four Flavour Liquor worm and maintain the same cultivating speed as Fang Zheng.

As for the higher ranks, those Rank three or Rank four Gu Masters.

To Fang Yuan, battle results aside, even keeping his life is a difficult thing, not to mention challenging a higher rank.

Transcending rank was very difficult, one was that Fang Yuan did not have trump cards, and two he does not have talent. Even with his rich fighting experience, a woman cannot cook without rice, without a strong Gu worm, his experience cannot display their worth.

"If I can successfully fuse the Four Flavour Liquor worm, my cultivating speed will be satisfactory. But I also have to replenish my Gu worms. Defense I have White Jade Gu, offense I have Moonglow Gu, healing I have nine leaf vitality grass, but I need a movement-type and recon-type Gu, these two although are support types, they can cover up my weakness and at least triplefold my fighting strength!" Fang Yuan pondered.

He did not need to learn step by step, with his rich life experience, he already knew the direction to take.

Beside him, Jiang Ya's voice came, "I heard, recently someone is finding trouble with you, lord? Purposely finding trouble at your bamboo building and wine tavern?"

Fang Yuan frowned, his train of thoughts were broken.

But Jiang Ya was right.

Fang Yuan had investigated, this was his uncle Gu Yue Dong Tu's act.

After Gu Yue Qing Shu warned his uncle, he did not dare to use Fang Zheng to instigate trouble anymore. But after waiting for a while, the indignance and anger in his heart rose, and using his relationships, he got a few Gu Masters to find trouble at Fang Yuan's places.

People who do business hate these kinds of problems.

Thus, recently, he had been finding time to look after the locations.

"Owner, someone is finding trouble again." At this time, a clerk carried a scared expression and walked towards Fang Yuan.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's brows raised, not expecting to encounter this immediately.

Not waiting for Fang Yuan to react, Jiang Ya stood up abruptly, eagerly saying, "Wait a moment lord, let me go see."

He walked out of the partition and came back almost immediately.

"It is Gu Yue Man Shi!" Jiang Ya's expression was pale, suppressing his voice. His gaze revealed shock and worry.

Gu Yue Man Shi?

Fang Yuan did things carefully and knew the importance of information. During this period, he had gotten the information of all the Rank two Gu Masters in the clan, and memorised most of them.

Gu Yue Man Shi is a slightly famous Gu Master, specializing in defense and having a great strength, being the Man Shi group's leader. In terms of fame, he was higher than Jiao San by a little.

Bam!

Smashing sound came from outside.

Thereafter, a coarse and arrogant voice resounded, "Blah, what sort of wine is this? Tastes like horseshit, you dare sell this to me?"

"Hmph!" Fang Yuan's gaze shone with cold light as he stood up.

Chapter 108: That pair of eyes!

Jiang Ya saw that Fang Yuan intended to go out, and hurriedly stopped him —"Lord Fang Yuan, a wise man does not fight when the odds are against him. This Man Shi is very strong, one of the few people who managed to escape for their lives from Bai Ning Bing, he cannot be underestimated."

"Using his loss as a glorious fame, what fear is there for these kinds of people?" Fang Yuan laughed lightly, stretching his hand to put it on Jiang Ya's shoulder, "Just sit here and drink away."

"Lord..." Jiang Ya was about to urge again, but he met with Fang Yuan's icy gaze.

The chilliness in Fang Yuan's eyes caused his heart to stop.

He was tongue-tied, helplessly sitting on the chair again while Fang Yuan took a few strides and left the partitioned room, walking towards the main hall.

He saw that at the center on a square table, a Rank two Gu Master had one foot stepping on a stool while another stepping on the table.

His body was slightly short, but his arms and waist were thick. With a thick black beard, extending downwards from his cheeks to meet at his chin, his body emitted a strong aura of ferociousness.

The ground near him had broken wine pot fragments, and most of the liquor had seeped into the ground along the concrete cracks on the floor.

Only two or three puddles of wine accumulated on the surface, or in the broken pots.

The shopkeeper old man bowed his head low as he apologised in trepidation, "Lord please be appeased, if this wine is not to your satisfaction, the shop will give you another brew free of charge!"

"Hmph, I don't want wine! Your wine tastes like shit, why are you opening a shop. Compensation, I must be compensated! My good mood was ruined by you guys, you have to compensate me at least five hundred primeval stones!" Man Shi demanded a ridiculous amount.

"This is the third time already, it seems this wine tavern has offended some people."

"Sigh, let's not drink here anymore."

"Quick, go, when Gu Masters fight, we mortals suffer."

The surrounding people frantically left their seats, only a few Gu Masters remained and continued their chat.

"I heard this tavern is opened by Fang Yuan, who is it that is finding fault with him?"

"Oh! The one whose parents died and inherited their fortune, the lad who got rich overnight?"

"No wonder people are doing this, even if it is me, I'd be jealous. Just think, we fight for our lives out there for these fortunes to live a stable life. But he Fang Yuan is merely a newbie, what rights does he have to obtain these things!"

"That's right, even if his ancestors are taking care of their future generations, times have changed. The clan's resources are limited. Everyone can only get a small piece of the pie. How can he, a C grade talent, enjoy such fortune at this age? Preposterous!"

"Is Man Shi trying to anger him into a duel? If they had a Gu fight, he might be able to get a piece of the pie."

Someone shook his head, "Heh, you think those clan elders are fools?"

Someone nodded, "Could be true. The clan policies are there, haven't you guys understood from all these years? To a degree, they allow us to compete, the strong should get more resources, isn't that right? If the weak cannot protect their assets, they would have to give it up. It is all for the clan's prosperity!"

"Mm, makes sense. Let's see first. There's something going on here. I heard that Man Shi has a retired elder behind him," someone suppressed his voice and said.

"Who dares to leave, all of you stand there, no one is to leave!" On the table, Man Shi suddenly shouted.

Those mortal drinkers were already at the doorstep, but did not dare to disobey, they all stood at the spot in horror. Some of the pedestrians found that there was drama going on and they went to the doorstep, stopping to watch the show.

"Purely here to find trouble!" Fang Yuan upon seeing this scene, his face was emotionless, but his eyes glinted with cold light.

Man Shi saw him.

"Oh? You are that Fang Yuan right. Junior, your wine tavern is cheating my money with your horrible wine. However, since you are a newbie, I'll give you a chance to repent and apologise in public. If not others will say that I, Man Shi is bullying a junior with my status. Hahaha!"

Man Shi laughed loudly, "As long as you apologise and bow to me, this matter will be over. I walk my talk, I will do as I promised!"

He patted his chest in thunderous volume, showing an air of magnanimity, but his intention could not lie to the surrounding Gu Masters.

"What a bastard move."

"That's right, If Fang Yuan apologised, he would no longer be able to raise his head, and anyone would come over and step on him and bully his weakness. But if he does not apologise, that is disrespecting a senior, and with such an attitude, the entire community will keep him away."

"Yeah, he's stuck with two difficult decisions... oh my, what the fuck!!!"

The Gu Masters whispered, but suddenly someone's mouth went wide open, able to swallow a duck's egg.

The remaining Gu Masters were in a similar state.

Some stared until their eyeballs almost fell out.

Some choked and spilled out the wine in their mouths.

Some stared in utter disbelief, like statues.

They were here to watch a show, an enjoyable show.

In the end, Fang Yuan not only satisfied their wish, but also gave them a great "surprise". The young man instantly flicked his wrist and shot a moonblade out.

Pew!

The moonblade of the Moonglow Gu!

The eerie blue crescent fang flew in the air, as large as a face. Trailing along a square desk, it was quickly cut like tofu into two halves.

"Eh?!" Man Shi's laughter stood, his pupils dilated as the moonblade became increasingly larger in his eyes.

In the blink of an eye, the eerie blue moonblade was already near his face, showing every single strand of his moustache with its glow.

Facing strong feelings of death, at the very last moment, Man Shi screamed out in panic, "Monolith Gu!"

Immediately, his entire body had a deep grey light. His skin turned and became rock skin.

But before it had fully grown, the moonblade had already hit his chest.

With a light sound, the rock skin tore open and Man Shi's chest became a large diagonal injury. Blood spilled and poured out of his large wound.

"Ah—!" Intense pain rushed through his nerves as Man Shi shouted out in horror, his voice full of disbelief and shock.

He had never expected Fang Yuan to attack immediately without a single word.

He dared to attack!

In the village, directly using a Gu worm and attacking a clansman?!

Not to say Man Shi, even the onlookers showed utter disbelief, and were lost for words.

"What situation is this, is this lad crazy?!"

"Not saying a word and immediately going for a fatal attack! Isn't he afraid of killing Man Shi and being arrested by the punishment hall, paying for his crimes?"

"Young men are way too rash."

"Did you guys see that moonblade? It is definitely not the Moonlight Gu but the Moonglow Gu, to think Fang Yuan succeeded in his fusion already."

"Fang Yuan, what are you doing?!" Man Shi stood on the square table, tearing his throat and screaming in a thunderous volume with a face full of ruthlessness.

His entire body's muscles bulged, growing into rock skin at a deeper intensity. The injury was also covered by the rock skin, but large amount of blood still poured out, although less of a fountain.

Fang Yuan's face was calm as he continued his walk. He did not talk, or rather, he did not have the intention to talk.

He made another move to reply to Man Shi.

Another moonblade!

Pew.

The moonblade flew across the short distance and shot out.

"You!" Man Shi had no time to talk, but raised his arms and protected his brain and chest.

His limbs were covered with a thick deep grey coloured rock, as if arms made from a statue, sturdy and thick.

The moonblade hit his arms, cutting a deep wound, numerous small rock fragments flying out.

The moonblade's strength caused Man Shi's body to fly backwards.

His entire body was made of rocks, causing his weight to rise drastically. Finally, the table under him could not bear the weight, and with a crack, it collapsed completely.

Man Shi lost his footing and fell on the ground, his defenses revealing a weakness.

Fang Yuan walked slowly, his eyes shining in cold light as he captured the weakness, and fired another moonblade at it.

The moonblade tore through the air and emitted a swooshing sound of the wind.

Man Shi hurriedly raised his hands, but he underestimated Fang Yuan's intense battle experience. Although the moonblade was moving straight, it tunneled for an angle not parallel to the ground.

Man Shi's arm could block half of the moonblade, but the other half hit his chest.

Injury on top of injury, Man Shi's chest had even greater blood loss now.

"Is, is he going to kill him?" The Gu Masters who were originally sitting on the seat could not stand it any longer, and they all got up.

The mortals did not dare to make any noise. They watched in fear and anticipation.

Gu Masters killing each other, it triggered something that had been repressed in their hearts all along.

Man Shi breathed heavily, wanting to climb up. But due to his injuries, the intense pain caused his hard work to be wasted as he crashed on the ground once again with a thump.

Fang Yuan walked over slowly.

Man Shi lost a lot of blood, and his face was pale. He stared at Fang Yuan in horror. Fang Yuan was walking slowly with a cold expression, getting closer, bringing him greater pressure by the second.

"Fang Yuan, you cannot kill me! Killing me, you will be arrested by the punishment hall!" Man Shi pushed against the floor, trying to move backwards.

He was still bleeding, and along with his body, carved a bright red line on the concrete.

The gallery was silent.

Everyone was stunned by Fang Yuan's cold aura and held their breaths as they wanted. Nobody felt that Man Shi was a worthless piece of shit. Without any composure, they would not have fared any better if they were in his shoes.

Fang Yuan walked to Man Shi, raised a leg and harshly stepped on his chest injury.

The pain caused Man Shi to draw in a cold breath.

Fang Yuan continued to stomp, and Man Shi began to feel immense pain; like a wild boar charging around was trampling him repeatedly.

He could not endure it any longer, screaming loudly. Even with the thick rock skin's protection, his chest was still enduring great pressure from Fang Yuan, and the injury area was still overflowing with blood.

More importantly, Fang Yuan's right hand was covered in an eerie blue moonlight, held in place but not fired yet.

This was the symptom before a moonblade attack. Man Shi thought this worriedly as he did not dare to move a muscle.

"You, you cannot kill me!" He stared with his eyes wide open, growling in difficulty.

"I won't kill you." Fang Yuan said the first sentence since he arrived.

His tone was flat, and in the dead silent wine tavern, it reverbed into everyone's ears.

"But I can cripple you, breaking one of your arms, or a leg. According to the clan rules, I have to compensate you a number of primeval stones and be imprisoned for some time. But what about you? Your remaining life would be spent in bed, your injury would reduce your battle capability greatly, and you shall no longer be able to execute missions. Do you think this result is acceptable for you?" Fang Yuan stared down at the sprawling Man Shi, slowly reasoning.

The emotionless voice travelled into Man Shi's ears, causing his heart to stop and his body to shudder.

He opened his mouth, breathing heavily, his brain becoming more chaotic. Fang Yuan's leg exerted strength that made him feel like he was being crushed by a rock, making him feel harder to breathe.

"Damn it, damn it! If I was on guard, if I was not caught off guard and were injured at the start, how could he... Urgh!"

Man Shi's voice came to an abrupt stop as his gaze met with Fang Yuan's eyes.

He lay on the ground, staring upwards.

Fang Yuan's half-narrowed eyes, dark and eerily looking down on him.

Just what sort of pair of eyes was that?

If it was full of killing intent, Man Shi would not be afraid. However, this pair of eyes was filled with indifference.

This indifference was like arrogance towards reality, the disdain towards people of the world, the trampling of life and the abandonment of rules!

"This pair of eyes, this pair of eyes..." Man Shi's eyes shrunk into pin-size as the deepest memory in his heart played.

The nightmare of his life!

Two years ago, at night in the bamboo forest.

A young man in white clothing, similarly trampling him under his feet.

"Damn it, god damn it! If I had refined the Monolith Gu, how could you break my defense?" Death was impending. He screamed with his life, full of indignance.

"Oh, in that case, I shall not kill you." The white-clothed young man's lips curled, revealing a smile full of interest, "Go back to the village and cultivate harder. Refine the Monolith Gu and let's have a match again. Hehehe, I hope that in the future, you can bring a tint of excitement to my life." Saying so, the young man lifted his feet, sparing him.

Man Shi breathed roughly, lying on the ground, not expecting this turn of events.

He stared at this white-clothed young man in shock.

The young man looked at him like an ant, saying indifferently, "Why aren't you scramming?"

Man Shi's body shook as he hurriedly got up and made his escape.

This white-clothed young man was none other than Bai village's number one genius, Bai Ning Bing. Back then, he was only Rank two, but could already kill Rank three clan elders!

Man Shi escaping from him and preserving his life caused his fame to shoot up.

Through the two years, Bai Ning Bing's facial expression had become a blur in his memories, and he could only remember those eyes.

Eyes that looked at the common life, the world with indifference. The high and mighty iris, hiding an unbelievable pride that mortals cannot comprehend.

To think...

To think!

To think that in his own village, he could see these eyes!

At this moment, Man Shi's heart was filled with terror, the indignance and anger in his heart dissipating without a drop of fighting spirit left.

Fang Yuan closely observed Man Shi's facial expression.

The young man was slightly shocked, not expecting Man Shi to be so cowardly.

But, nevermind... just a cowardly mouse.

Fang Yuan's objective was achieved, and he let go of his leg, "You can scram now."

Man Shi felt like he had heard a divine mantra as he rolled and climbed out of the tavern with a pale face.

The audience were stunned.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot, his gaze sweeping the area.

The surrounding Gu Masters, Rank one and some Rank two, avoided his gaze subconsciously.

The shopkeeper and clerks were all terrified and excitedly worshipped him. Who did not want a strong backer?

Behind him, Jiang Ya was staring dumbfounded.

He heard a commotion and ran out, but saw Fang Yuan chasing away Man Shi.

That is Gu Yue Man Shi...

His heart was shocked to the limit, and his gaze towards Fang Yuan changed.

Jealousy had vanished.

At this point, Jiang Ya understood why Fang Yuan had such an achievement.

"Because he was never the same kind of person as myself!"

Chapter 109: Treehouse hides the Liquor worm

Gu Yue Man Shi was defeated by the newbie Fang Yuan!

The news spread quickly and caused small waves of gossip among Rank two Gu Masters.

Everyone was familiar with the two main characters of this event.

Man Shi was a slightly famous Rank two Gu Master who had managed to escape with his life under Bai Ningbing's hands; he was not to be sniffed at.

And Fang Yuan was the year's champion, many had witnessed him defeating Fang Zheng at the yearly assessment. He also obtained his family inheritance and became rich overnight, causing many to become green with envy.

The gap between the two was clear, but against all expectations, the weaker Fang Yuan had defeated the stronger Man Shi. Such a discrepancy really caught the people by surprise.

As more and more people continued to discuss the event, Fang Yuan's fame also rose.

Rank two Gu Masters began to take this young junior seriously.

"He directly attacked without saying a word. Young people are too impulsive."

"He has wealth and has also refined Moonglow Gu, he has some ability."

"He is a lunatic, he is too hard-handed. Reportedly, Gu Yue Man Shi had to lie in bed for at least three days to recover from his injuries!"

People commented on Fang Yuan.

He had made a sudden attack on Man Shi, initiating a head start; inflicting serious injuries on the very first attack and establishing great dominance. It felt like he did not win honestly.

However, victory was victory and loss was loss.

The result was everything.

Maybe on Earth, most would emphasize the process instead of the results, but in this world where survival was arduous, surroundings full of deadly dangers, victory often meant survival and defeat meant death, losing everything.

Winners gained everything, losers lost everything; almost everyone approved this notion.

Fang Yuan had won; it was the fact, no matter how he did it.

A newbie had sprung up by stepping on Man Shi, entering into everyone's eyes.

Man Shi had become a stepping stone, his reputation was destroyed. Once he recovered, he would resign from the group leader position.

This was the outcome of a failure.

Close relatives would sympathize with the losers, but they respected and acknowledged the winners even more. Winners represented strength and strength meant better security to the people.

After this event, Gu Yue Dong Tu sensibly stopped his dirty tricks.

Gu Yue Man Shi stepping down had finally made the astute uncle aware of the reality. Fang Yuan's growth made him feel helpless, resentment and indignation.

He knew he now had no chance of seizing the inheritance. Continuing was meaningless.

He had used his connections and employed other people to find trouble for Fang Yuan; this consumed his primeval stones. Yet Fang Yuan had profits coming from all sides.

In case the stalemate continued, even if he had a large amount of primeval stones, the final loser would definitely be he, himself.

Because he lost the bamboo houses, wine tavern and Nine Leaves Vitality Grass, he was now without any source of income; the used primeval stones would be difficult to replenish. By contrast, Fang Yuan lacked primeval stones but it was increasing day by day.

The main point was that Gu Yue Dong Tu dispiritedly realized that the stalemate would not have any benefits.

Thus, when he heard Man Shi running away in defeat, he immediately stopped these meaningless actions.

In fact, when Fang Zheng had not been able to create trouble for Fang Yuan, it already signified Gu Yue Dong Tu's defeat.

With this, Fang Yuan's wine tavern's business returned to normal, which was a joyous thing.

There was another joyous matter—the caravan would be coming early.

March.

In the bright and beautiful spring sunshine, the light song of the days of spring treaded a lively and cheerful beat as it arrived.

With the warmth of spring, flowers bloomed and grasses grew wildly.

Qing Mao Mountain was a scene of green as far as the eye could see. Wild flowers blossomed on the sunny side of the hills, forming a colorful and gorgeous sea of flowers. The gurgling and burbling river surged up like a flame and entangled with the sunshine.

Newborn dragonpill crickets came out of their eggs and formed a batch of new swarms, enlivening the nighttime.

At daytime, a large flock of colorful peacock parrots hovered in the air, chirping and twittering.

The warm spring spread its favor and kindness, letting all living things grow in brilliance.

In such a scenery, a caravan was slowly making its way to Qing Mao Mountain.

Fat black beetles were slowly moving forward, their backs filled with people and goods.

Proud ostriches with brightly colored feathers were pulling handcarts. Hairy mountain spiders disregarded the terrains, winged snakes twisted and snaked forward, occasionally opening its wings and flying forward.

A Treasure Brass Toad was leading the caravan. It was two and half meters tall, its entire body orange-yellow in color. On its back was the Rank four Gu Master, Jia Fu.

After the caravan stationed in the village, Fang Yuan sighed inwardly, "It changed again. In my previous memories, this caravan should have arrived in summer. According to the previous precedents too, the caravan should have only come in summer. Now, however, it has come in spring, two-three months earlier. And its scale is also much bigger."

Fang Yuan's rebirth changed his current situation and similarly also influenced his surroundings, creating changes in the future.

The root cause should be due to him killing Jia Jin Sheng.

Fang Yuan had deceived everyone, so Jia Fu mistakenly believed Jia Jin Sheng's death was a conspiracy by his rival, Jia Gui.

After Jia Fu returned to the clan, he had taken radical steps which made the competition between them more intense.

To strive for exceptional achievements, the Jia brothers rushed out even before the year's snow had completely melted, leading the caravans to peddle their goods everywhere.

The clan leader Gu Yue Bo received Jia Fu.

The two Rank four Gu Masters were the leaders of the both sides.

"Brother Gu Yue, I trust you have been well?" Jia Fu was full of smiles and warmth, but his face had a long scar now.

"Hahaha, brother Jia Fu, you are quite early this year." Gu Yue Bo looked at the scar on Jia Fu's face. His heart jolted but he didn't ask about it.

"The early bird gets the worm. This time, I have brought many precious goods and I believe the noble Gu Yue clan will have lots of needs." Jia Fu had made a big effort this time to fight for better achievements.

"Yes, this is good news." Gu Yue Bo's eyes flashed. Continuing on, "It just so happens that the day after tomorrow is our clan's Awakening Ceremony, and I would like to invite brother Jia to attend it."

"Haha, it is my honor to be able to witness the prosperity of Gu Yue clan," Jia Fu immediately cupped his hands and sincerely replied.

Inviting others to watch the clan's awakening ceremony was treating them as honoured guests. Jia Fu could feel Gu Yue clan's sincerity from this invitation.

"In fact, there is also another matter." Jia Fu hesitated.

"You have come from afar, so if you have any requests, please say it. Our clan will definitely do our best to fulfil it." Gu Yue Bo said.

Jia Fu sighed, "Ah, it is regarding Jia Jin Sheng's matter. I have especially brought over a few investigation experts from the clan, and I hope that in the course of our investigation, you can allow us some convenience."

Gu Yue Bo immediately revealed a look of understanding.

Apparently, Jia Jin Sheng's death had caused Jia Fu to fall into an awkward and passive situation in the competition for family assets. It was said that after returning to the clan, Jia Fu had squabbled with Jia Gui in public and the situation had erupted into an intense fight. The scar on his face could very well be a trace from that fight.

It was no wonder he had come running over at the start of spring; he had a lot of pressure on his shoulders.

Fang Yuan was strolling around tents and street stalls.

The scale of this year's caravan was much bigger than any of the previous years. Not only were there more tents, there was also a Gu house.

Gu house was something only large-scale caravans had. A large-scale caravan usually had two to three Gu houses. Jia Fu's caravan was at most a middle-scale, but it had a Gu house.

This Gu house was a large tree.

It was eighteen meters tall and it really seemed to reach to the sky. Its roots and branches were twisted like the tangling of dragons and snakes.

The diameter of the trunk at the base was ten meters; it decreased as it went up but the decrease wasn't that visible. The brown trunk was not actually a single entity, and had three layers of space inside.

There were also windows on the trunk. Sunlight and fresh air passed through the window and entered the three layers of space inside.

The branches and leaves seemed to be scarce on the trunk. Only at the treetop was it verdant and lush. The spring wind blew, and the tree leaves shook and created soft rustling sounds.

This was the most common type of Gu house.

The Rank three plant Gu named 'three star cave'.

It could instantly grow once primeval essence was poured into it. There were three rooms arranged in these three layers of space. The defensive power of these rooms were incomparable to that of the tents.

In the continuous stretch of tents, an enormous tree was standing aloft in the middle like a tower; it was like a crane among a flock of chicken.

At the base of the enormous tree, there were two wide doors used as entrance.

Fang Yuan followed the stream of people and walked into the enormous tree.

The tree had three layers of space which were transformed into the layout of stores. There were rows of counters inside and on them were displayed all kinds of Gu worms.

These counters were made of wood and were a part of the enormous tree. On top of growing green leaves and branches, the three star cave tree Gu could grow different designs according to the Gu Master's will.

Apart from these counters, there were stools and benches for the customers to rest upon.

A Rank three support Gu Master was constantly operating and monitoring the situation from somewhere in this enormous tree.

In case someone snatched the Gu worms in the counters, the monitoring Gu Master could operate the enormous tree to immediately close the doors and create a momentary prison cell. Countless branches would be madly grown and perform group attacks. At the same time, the security Gu Masters in the tree would also make their moves.

The treehouse was much more secure than the tents and so the goods sold inside were more precious.

Fang Yuan had just entered the first layer when he saw a lone counter in the middle and on it was a Liquor worm.

Many Gu Masters were surrounding this Liquor worm, assessing it. Some clicked their tongues in admiration.

Fang Yuan swept his eyes over the place, where the other counters also displayed many precious Gu worms.

There were Jade Skin Gu, Whirlwind Gu, Scar Stone Gu and so on.

All these Gu worms were compatible with the Moonlight gu and could fuse into higher Rank Gu worms.

Jia Fu wasn't completely clear on these fusion recipes, but with his many years of business experience, he knew which Gu worms the Gu Yue clan might need more.

"Naturally, Jia Fu's caravan isn't just targeting the Gu Yue village, he is really making an all-out effort this time. It seems he was thoroughly provoked when he returned to the clan." Fang Yuan's heart moved when he saw this.

Chapter 110: Old woman, you’re too tender!

"Liquor worm…" Fang Yuan lightly muttered, walking to the side of the center reception desk.

He only needed this Liquor worm, along with the sweet, spicy, sour, bitter—four types of wine, to refine the Four Flavours Liquor worm. Of course, such a fusion also entailed a chance of failure.

But if Fang Yuan did not have a second Liquor worm, he does not even have a chance to try.

This is life after all, hard work does not mean results, nor success. But if one does not work hard, they are destined to fail.

The Demonic path was the same, the demonic cultivators are good at clearing obstacles in their way, bravely advancing in their paths. To most people in the world, they were seen as extremists and adventurous.

"I was still worried earlier as to where to find a second Liquor worm. To think that fate sent this Liquor worm right to my doorstep. The chance is in front of me, how can I give up? I must get this Liquor worm!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone with determination.

"If my cultivation reaches Rank four or five, with a strong fighting capability, I would snatch it away without a thought, killing gods and slaying buddhas in my way! If I was Rank three or four, with my ample experience, I can steal it without anyone finding out. Sadly I am just a Rank two now, in fact I'm just initial stage…"

Fang Yuan sighed in his heart, "I can only purchase it fair and square like this."

He looked at the price on the counter.

"Liquor worm—Five hundred primeval stones."

The Liquor worm's normal price is five hundred and eighty primeval stones. The price here was actually eighty pieces cheaper than the market.

But if Fang Yuan really thinks he can spend five hundred primeval stones to buy this Liquor worm, then his five hundred years of living would have been in vain.

The low price was just to attract customers and trigger people's mentality and greed into buying it.

This treehouse was obviously Jia Fu's asset.

"Grandma, this Liquor worm is only five hundred primeval stones!" A young girl walked in, screaming in shock.

The young girl's eyes were glowing, shaking her grandmother's hand, "Grandma, tomorrow is the awakening ceremony. Didn't you promise to give me a present? Why don't you give this Liquor worm to me."

The young girl's grandma had a white waist belt, and the belt had a square silver piece with the number "3" on it.

Once a Gu Master reaches Rank three cultivation, they automatically ascend to clan elder position.

Only that among clan elders, there were differences. There were elders in power who held great political power. While others were not, they would only be controlling the departments with little profits.

But this Rank three elder was not those weak clan elders.

"Gu Yue Yao Ji…" Fang Yuan recognised her immediately, this was the medicine hall's clan elder. The medicine hall is the clan's support faction, it can be said to be the most lucrative department. Gu Yue Yao Ji had very great influence due to her seniority, even towards the clan leader, she could do away with paying respects and reply while sitting. She was the number one healing Gu Master in the clan and had saved many lives of the clan elders, thus having very strong network in the clan.

"Alright, alright. If my obedient granddaughter wants it, grandma will buy for you." The old woman's face was full of wrinkles. She was a hunchback and had a walking cane in one hand, helplessly sighing and saying with a benevolent face.

"Grandma is the best, I knew grandma dotes on me the most," The young girl happily grabbed Gu Yue Yao Ji, joyfully planting her lips on her grandma's cheek.

"Then grandma, let's call the shop assistant and buy this Liquor worm immediately!"

Gu Yue Yao Ji shook her head, "My lovely granddaughter, the Gu worm here isn't bought like that. Let granny teach you, you see that stack of paper and pen over at the counter?"

The young girl nodded, "I see it."

Gu Yue Yao Ji said, "Go get a piece of paper and use the pen to write down the price of the Liquor worm. After that, stuff it into the hole. If among all the bidders, your price is the highest, this Liquor worm will belong to you."

"So that's it, very interesting." The young girl took a bamboo paper and held the pen, but hesitated when writing down.

Her lovely eyebrows frowned as she thought hard for a moment, then finally pouting her lips, she said, "Grandma, what price would be appropriate? If I set it too low, other people will get the Liquor worm, but if I set it too high, I would be making a loss."

Gu Yue Yao Ji laughed, teasing her, "How can it be so easy to buy the Liquor worm? Let's see your luck…"

"Grandma!" The young girl said coquettishly, hogging Gu yue Yao Ji's limp and shaking arm.

"Alright, alright, stop swinging, my body is going to collapse." The old woman sighed, "Grandma will fill it for you."

The young girl quickly jumped, saying, "I knew grandma is the best!"

Gu Yue Yao Ji wrote a price before putting her own name as the young girl watched in anticipation.

After she had finished, she folded the paper and signalled to the girl, "Go, put the paper in."

The young girl obediently took the paper and found the hole in the counter and stuffed the paper in.

She returned beside Gu Yue Yao Ji, feeling uncertain, "Grandma, will this do?"

The old woman nodded, "That's about it. But life is hard to predict, someone might put a higher price. But that price would be too high. If they really bidded so much, the person who bought this Liquor worm is a fool. Don't worry, the Liquor worm is in the bag."

"Oh." The young girl nodded with a cute expression.

"Let's go. Come accompany grandma upstairs and look around."

"Okay, grandma."

Seeing them leave, Fang Yuan's eyes shone with severity.

This Gu Yue Yao Ji, to him, was a tough competitor, not to be underestimated.

But this situation, Fang Yuan had prepared and anticipated it.

The Liquor worm was precious. Although it was only usable for Rank one Gu Masters, the Liquor worm could refine primeval essence and that was very useful. Refining primeval essence and raising it by one small stage—this meant that the primeval essence storage increased and this had a great driving force towards Gu Master cultivation.

The only flaw is that the Liquor worm did not have a good prospect in the future.

According to the popular recipes, Liquor worm was only used as a fusion ingredient, and the new Gu worm created does not have the primeval essence refining ability.

This was too much of a waste. In fact, it was not worth it.

Thus, most clans have the Liquor worm and did not use it to undergo fusion, but is used by the academy to allow students to take turns using it.

If Fang Yuan exposed his advancement recipe, the Liquor worm's market value would rise drastically.

"Sigh, it is not easy to get this Liquor worm. This grandma and granddaughter is just one competitor. I wonder how many others are there who have placed the paper into this hole?"

Liquor worm was a good thing, and people naturally want good things.

Just that among these competitors, some were sincere about buying it, while others were just trying their luck. Some are affluent, like Gu Yue Yao Ji, while some were poor, like Fang Yuan.

"Luckily, I got back the family assets, and these few days I've sold some Rank one vitality leaves, plus the wine tavern and bamboo buildings are all rented out. Thus I could accumulate some savings. If not, I would not even be able to compete."

But he had too little time to save up. On the one hand he had a lot of Gu worms to feed, and in terms of fortune he could not compete with an old woman like Gu Yue Yao Ji.

"Sigh, let's go. Lord Yao Ji just tossed in a paper."

"I saw it too, it seems I'm not fated to have this Liquor worm."

The Gu Masters surrounding this counter all left dejected.

Only Fang Yuan still stood there.

His eyes were like the abyss river, shining with cold light.

The Gu Masters who left were all scared off by Gu Yue Yao Ji's aura and backed out of their own accord. But how could Fang Yuan be scared away?

"Some chances are just in front of you, only that people choose to give it up. I still have a chance!" Fang Yuan's brain worked intensely as he fell into deep thought.

To compete with fortune, Fang Yuan was not her match.

Even then...

That did not mean that Gu Yue Yao Ji's bidding amount was definitely higher than Fang Yuan!

Even though the Liquor worm was precious, it was still a Rank one Gu worm. The price of any commodity would fluctuate, but it would definitely not rise or fall beyond a certain limit. Thus, all price deviations have a range.

The crucial point now is, what price did Gu Yue Yao Ji give!?

She did not lack money, and for the granddaughter she doted, how much was she willing to pay?

As long as Fang Yuan's price, if even a single point, is higher, he wins.

This is a different kind of battle! The strong might not necessarily win, the weak might not necessarily lose. Guessing and gambling made the fight much more exciting.

"If it were others, they might not be able to guess it. Gu Yue Yao Ji, you purposely said some things earlier to scare away competitors? But in front of me, you are still too tender!" Fang Yuan's lips curled into an angle as he smiled confidently.

In this world, transactions were very interesting.

If it was on Earth, the seller would definitely adopt an auction style when selling rare Gu worms like the Liquor worm.

But in this world, auction did not work well.

An important reason was that kinship is the greatest value here, it is the clan's cohesiveness.

If an auction was held, the clan's members would have a subconscious animosity towards outsiders like Jia Fu.

Once the auction items are priced too highly, they would step out of the competition and even try to appease the seller, making some leeways to exchange and compensate.

This world's people had one viewpoint—Losing to the family is okay, but for an outsider to earn from it, that is an insult to the entire clan!

Unless, a few clans joined in an auction together. In that case, there is competition, and it would be full of rivalry.

But these auctions were hard to conduct.

Because transportation was inconvenient.

Transport is the basis of trade, and if the transport system is not developed, the business and trade would dwindle. Because in trade, it was the movement of commodities that matter.

Each village occupied a mountain and stayed far from each other. The roads that connected them are hard to travel, constantly having wild beasts, cliffs, coupled with dangerous terrain and weather, and even dangerous wild Gu worms—it was truly full of difficulties.

Such an inconvenient transport system made it difficult for different clans to come together for an auction.

Even at Qing Mao Mountain with its three clans, Jia Fu did not dare to organise an auction.

Firstly, where would it be held? It isn't safe in the wilds, and if it is held in the Gu Yue Village, the other two clans would not feel safe.

He was only Rank four, and the head of the other three villages were also Rank four. He could not suppress the situation. Compared to Earth, trade here was not developed and had its own rules.

Using his knowledge of business and enterprise from Earth, Fang Yuan managed to earn and also lose money. After some painful experiences, he finally learnt from experience.

Combining the complete business knowledge from Earth, along with his personal experience, without bragging, Fang Yuan had the top tier knowledge in the business industry in this entire world.

Just an old woman who had lived in the Qing Mao Mountain's village her whole life, she dares to obstruct me in getting the Liquor worm?

Old woman, you're far too tender!

Chapter 111: Primeval stones are but material goods

"Grandma, what Gu is this?" The young girl curiously pointed at the central counter in the third floor.

There were three floors in this treehouse; the first floor sold Rank one Gu worms, the second floor sold Rank two Gu worms and the third floor sold Rank three Gu worms.

The higher you went, the lesser the Gu worms and the more expensive the price.

Naturally, the Gu worms that were put for sale in the treehouse were all rare and precious.

Gu Yue Yao Ji followed her granddaughter's gaze and saw a round bucket-shaped, tall and thin tree stump. The stump had five branches like five fingers of a human and were intertwined in the middle.

A sphere-shaped Gu worm that was thumb-sized was wrapped around by the fine branches and covered by green leaves, emitting a white silvery glow.

"This is a white silver Relic Gu, it can only be used once and can instantly raise a Rank three Gu Master's cultivation by a small realm," Gu Yue Yao Ji slowly explained.

Relic Gu was a series Gu worm.

Rank one had green copper Relic Gu which was specially targeted towards Rank one Gu Masters. Rank two had red steel Relic Gu which was effective only on Rank two Gu Masters, and Rank three was this Silver Relic Gu.

Rank four had yellow golden Relic Gu.

"The price is thirty thousand primeval stones, it's so expensive!" The young girl was so shocked, she stuck out her tongue.

Gu Yue Yao Ji nodded, "Its final price should reach at least fifty thousand primeval stones. Alright, we have strolled long enough here, let's go to the first floor reception desk, the results to the Liquor worm's bidding should have come out."

In the treehouse, a Rank one Gu worm would only be displayed for half a day once there was a bid on it. For Gu worms that people had little interest in, it would be kept on display till someone made a bid.

Rank two Gu worms would be displayed for a day and Rank three ones for two days.

At first glance, this practice looked odd but when put in practice, this was the most suitable way of doing business.

At the reception desk.

"What, the Liquor worm has been bought by someone else?" Gu Yue Yao Ji immediately frowned upon seeing the results. She had put a high price and was confident in obtaining the Liquor worm, but to think she had actually miscalculated.

"Hmph! Who is it to be so bad as to snatch my dear Liquor worm?" The young girl angrily asked.

"Yao Le," Gu Yue Yao Ji reminded her granddaughter.

The young girl pouted and obediently shut her mouth.

The sales clerk behind the counter was a Rank two female Gu Master. She slightly bowed and answered the young girl, "I am sorry, we can't divulge our customers' information. Each business has special rules, please forgive me."

It was this confidentiality that dispelled many customers' apprehensions and allowed them to freely take part in the bid.

Sometimes, people would have some things they clearly wanted, but they would yield to others because of feelings and courtesy. After all, they would frequently see each other in the clan.

But such a method of doing transactions secretly allowed one to go around the problem of sentiments.

Why would such a good thing need to go to you? Because you are my senior, relative or friend?

Never underestimate the dark side in everyone.

Such secret transactions allowed this dark side to come out.

Gu Yue Yao Ji ruminated for a while and said, "I know the rules. You don't need to worry little girl, I won't ask the name of that person who bought the Liquor worm, I only want to know what the final price was."

The female Gu Master bowed again, "I am really sorry, the price is also confidential. But please don't worry, the final price was definitely the highest among all the bids. Jia family's business has always centered around honesty."

"Hmph, little girl, do you know who I am?" Gu Yue Yao Ji's face sank and coldly snorted.

"What is going on?" At this moment, a Rank three middle-aged Gu Master hurried over.

This treehouse was constantly being monitored; they would naturally know if anything occurred.

"Lord supervisor." The female Gu Master immediately greeted this middle-aged man.

The man waved his hand at the girl, "You can leave now, I will handle it here."

He turned towards Gu Yue Yao Ji and smiled, "So it was lord Yao Ji. She should be your granddaughter, right? She looks smart and sweet."

Gu Yue Yao Ji's expression softened upon seeing that this man was also a Rank three Gu Master, but she still asked to know the final price.

The male supervisor felt that the situation was rather tricky.

He was an elder at the caravan and also a trusted aide of Jia Fu. After doing business for many years, he had a deep understanding of the Gu Yue village's situation and knew the influence this old woman had.

To them, even if they offended Gu Yue Chi Lian or Gu Yue Mo Chen, they wouldn't want to offend Gu Yue Yao Ji. The latter's influence was second only to clan leader Gu Yue Bo.

The male supervisor pondered and said, "How about this, since lord Yao Ji wants to purchase the Liquor worm, I could call the shots and secretly transfer one over. To be honest, the warehouse has three Liquor worms and Lord Jia Fu personally decides where to sell them. You should know how precious the Liquor worm is. As for the price, let's decide your bidding price as it."

However, Gu Yue Yao Ji slightly shook her head and knocked the cane on her hand on the ground.

She said, "I am not looking for a bargain. The price... will be the same as the selling price of the previous Liquor worm."

"This....." The supervisor hesitated, he naturally saw Gu Yue Yao Ji's aim.

Gu Yue Yao Ji pretended to be annoyed and continued to pressure the male supervisor, "What? Is the price so high that you are afraid I won't be able to afford it?"

"Of course, I didn't mean that. Sigh, alright, we will do like you say." The supervisor sighed and said a price.

Upon hearing the price, the young girl first heaved a sigh of relief, but soon after that she felt somewhat indignant, "What, it was only twenty primeval stones more than ours?"

Gu Yue Yao Ji narrowed her eyes, but didn't speak.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan had already exited the treehouse and arrived at the wine tavern.

The second Liquor worm was already in his possession, and now the only things he needed were the four types of wines—sour, sweet, bitter and spicy wines.

"I already have the sweet wine; there is still quite a lot of the golden honey wine remaining from the family inheritance mission. Spicy and sour wines should not be a problem. My only concern is the bitter wine." Fang Yuan was a bit worried when he thought of this.

If he had bitter wine, he could begin refining the Four Flavours Liquor worm tonight.

Many things in life were like this, whatever you fear, it will come true.

Fang Yuan's worry became reality. He spent several hours rushing through countless tents; he found spicy and sour wines, but he didn't find bitter wine.

"Not everything in this world follows our wishes." Fang Yuan was very helpless. He could only set aside the fusion plan for the Liquor worm.

Without the Four Flavours Liquor worm, his cultivating speed would be ordinary.

In the afternoon, he went to the treehouse again.

There were new Gu worms in many counters on the first floor.

The central counter—where the Liquor worm had been displayed—was now occupied by a Cleansing Water Gu.

The Cleansing Water Gu resembled the leech on Earth, except it was much cuter than the leech; its whole body had a light-blue luster like that of the glimmering water.

"Cleansing Water Gu can remove the mixed aura in the aperture. To Chi Cheng, it is a Gu worm that he must have." Fang Yuan thought of Chi Cheng when he saw this Cleansing Water Gu.

He knew Chi Cheng only had a C grade aptitude and had forcefully raised his cultivation with the help of his grandfather Gu Yue Chi Lian's primeval essence, thus Chi Lian's aura was mixed inside Chi Cheng's aperture. If Chi Cheng didn't clean it off, then his future prospects would be jeopardized.

"Chi Lian will definitely buy this Gu worm for Chi Cheng. Hmm, let me think.....his quote should be between six hundred thirty to six hundred forty."

This price was much more than the Liquor worm's market value. The main reason was that Chi Cheng especially required this Gu worm.

"If I quote six hundred fifty, it should get me this Cleansing Water Gu. Just by adding ten primeval stones, this Cleansing Water Gu is bound to fall in my hands! As for the Liquor worm I bought this morning, my quote should have been about twenty primeval stones higher than Gu Yue Yao Ji's." Fang Yuan coldly smiled inwardly.

He had this self-confidence.

His five hundred years of experience and the advanced business knowledge from Earth had combined to form this self-confidence. It was beyond ordinary.

With his previous life's experience, when he just put ten more primeval stones, he had an eighty percent guarantee of getting the goods. When he bought the Liquor worm, the reason why he had put ten more primeval stones was because of his cautious nature.

Fang Yuan didn't make a quote, he didn't need the Cleansing Water Gu. And if he obtained it, then it would be investigated by Chi Lian. Of course, the main reason Fang Yuan did not bid was because he needed to hold onto the remaining money to see if there were any good Gu worms in the coming days.

"I lack two types of Gu worms; a scouting-type and a movement-type. The wolf tide will come in the coming year, and the caravan won't come again. Although there is the Flower Wine Monk's hidden inheritance, that was hastily left behind by Flower Wine Monk after he was injured. Who is to say if it is complete or not and what Gu worm would be next?"

In his memories, the wolf tide next year will be very dangerous. Fang Yuan didn't want to be powerless just because he lacked Gu worms, being injured or even perishing in the wolf tide.

It would be a disaster for the current him if he were to be surrounded by wolf packs.

Before that happens, he needed to make sufficient preparations; both his cultivation and Gu worms shouldn't be lacking.

After this, he repeatedly went to the treehouse for three days.

On the third day, in the first floor of the treehouse, he discovered something to be happy about—a Black Boar Gu!

Black and White Boar Gu were Gu worms that could increase the fundamental strength of Gu Masters. Fang Yuan had already used the White Boar Gu and received a power equal to that of a boar. If he used another White Boar Gu again, he wouldn't receive any increase in strength. But the Black Boar Gu was different, its ability could overlay with the White Boar Gu's.

Hence, at noon, there was one more Gu worm in his possession.

After that, there was nothing.

Some scouting and movement-type Gu worms appeared on the counters but they couldn't satisfy Fang Yuan.

These Gu worms were displayed on ordinary counters and the price wasn't good, so there weren't many who would purchase them. Fang Yuan heard the caravan would be staying for eight days, so he patiently waited without becoming anxious.

It was the seventh day.

In the second floor of the treehouse, Fang Yuan discovered a red steel Relic Gu.

It could instantly raise a Rank two Gu Master's primeval essence by a small realm!

Its price was marked at three thousand primeval stones, attracting many Rank two Gu Masters to bid over it, dropping papers in the counters; it was a very lively scene.

"If I obtain this red steel Relic Gu, I could push my cultivation to middle stage instantly. With the middle stage scarlet primeval essence, I would be able to use the Moonglow Gu and White Jade Gu many more times."

Cultivation was the foundation of a Gu Master, an increase in cultivation meant an increase in fighting power. In terms of its effects, it was far better than getting the scouting and movement Gu worms.

Moreover, these two types of Gu worms in the treehouse were all ordinary to Fang Yuan, with none catching his eyes.

"I have purchased the Liquor worm and Black Boar Gu, I also bought some wine. This red steel Relic Gu's final price will definitely cross five thousand primeval stones and could even reach eight thousand. After all, everyone knows about the wolf tide, so raising one's cultivation by a small realm will be a lot of help. My primeval stones won't be enough if I want to get this Relic Gu!"

Fang Yuan instantly realized that an obstacle had appeared in front of him.

Chapter 112: Truly a great resolve

Even though he inherited his parents' assets, to Fang Yuan, the time he had to accumulate wealth was still too little.

Activating the vitality leaf, he could not do it daily as it consumed a lot of time. Every time he grew out nine vitality leaves, half a day would be expended.

Fang Yuan considered for a moment. The sale time of this red steel Relic Gu is only one day. In such a short time, to come up with these large amount of primeval stones, the only way was to mortgage his wine tavern or the bamboo buildings.

This was nothing to feel pity over.

A year later, it would be the wolf tide. Under the wolves' attack, Gu Yue Village would desperately hold on several times, and during the most severe attack, even the front gate was broken through. The clan leader and the clan elders restrained the lightning crown head wolf, and Gu Yue Qing Shu sacrificed his own life to block the gate and stabilized the situation.

The wolf tide caused Qing Mao mountain's three clans to suffer a great reduction in clan members. Although not as much as 90% was gone, but at least half the population was wiped out.

By then, there would be more property than people, what talk would there be about renting out the bamboo building? The wine tavern was facing the eastern gates, who would dare to drink there? Even if they wanted to drink, the tavern would've gotten used by the clan and turned into a defensive tower.

Right now, the clan and many people were underestimating the severity of the wolf tide. At this point, if he could get rid of the tavern and bamboo buildings, he would be able to sell it at the best price.

"Money and fortune are just material goods, only one's cultivation is the root. But, selling it to the clan is too cheap. If I sell it to an individual, the price would be higher. But who would have the financial ability right now to buy my bamboo building and tavern? Such a huge transaction, it is not something that can be settled at one go. Both sides have to observe and haggle for the best prices, that would take too much time. I only have one day. Wait, maybe someone can..."

Fang Yuan's inspiration struck as he thought of someone.

This person was none other than his uncle Gu Yue Dong Tu.

Uncle and Aunt were both cunning and miserly. These decades of operating the tavern, bamboo buildings and selling the vitality leaves, they must have a huge stash of primeval stones.

Moreover, these assets were originally operated by them. All and all, it can save a lot of observation time.

The most important part was, they desperately needed this family asset to continue operating. No matter how much assets they had, without any income, this was like a river without a source; their primeval stones would get lesser and lesser, anyone would also be anxious over it.

It could be said, Uncle and Aunt were the best transaction targets.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan hesitated no longer, leaving the treehouse and walking towards Gu Yue Dong Tu's estate.

The one who opened the door was Shen Cui, his former servant.

"Ah, it- it's you!" Seeing Fang Yuan, she was very shocked.

Soon, she realized her slip of the tongue, and her face turned white from horror. Fang Yuan was now a Rank two Gu Master, but she was a mere mortal, the difference between them was like heaven and earth.

More importantly, Fang Yuan was the ruthless person who dared to kill the Mo family servant, later mincing the corpse and sending it to the Mo family.

"This servant pays her respects to Young Master Fang Yuan, welcome home, Young Master." Shen Cui shivered from her fear and her knees went soft, kneeling on the ground.

"Home?" Fang Yuan took a step into the courtyard. Seeing the familiar settings, his face showed a hint of mockery; there was no sense of belonging or attachment.

A year later, he had returned here once again.

Compared to his mental impression, this place was much more vacant. Just as Fang Zheng had said, some family servants were already sold away or retrenched.

Fang Yuan's sudden appearance had alarmed Uncle and Aunt.

As the housekeeper, Matron Shen arrived at the first moment, kneeling and bowing to invite Fang Yuan into the living room, and served him tea by hand.

Fang Yuan sat on the chair, observing the living room.

Many of the furniture was missing, and the decor was much more simple and plain.

But this did not mean that Uncle and Aunt had no savings.

"Gu Yue Dong Tu is still very cunning, this is an act of self-preservation. He had already stepped into the background, and his battle strength had drastically slipped. Most importantly, he had lost the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, meaning that he had lost the trump card in maintaining his personal relationships, no longer able to exert influence outside."

A man's wealth is his own ruin by causing another's greed.

After Fang Yuan inherited the assets, many clansmen were jealous and eyed his fortune.

As for Uncle and Aunt, they faced the same problem. The huge amount of savings they had was both a blessing and a problem.

Not showing off one's wealth, to them, this was the correct method of living.

At this time, footsteps could be heard.

The footsteps got closer, and soon, Aunt appeared at the doorstep.

"Fang Yuan, you actually still dared to come back here!" Seeing Fang Yuan, the rage in her heart appeared out of nowhere, screaming shrilly, "You traitorous scoundrel, how did we raise you. And to think you treat us like this, do you have a conscience, has your conscience been eaten by a dog!"

"You still have the cheeks to come here, and have the cheeks to drink tea here? Are you here to see our sorry states, now that you've seen it, are you happy?!"

Her finger pointed at Fang Yuan, her other hand at her waist as she screamed like a shrew.

If not for Fang Yuan wearing a glaring Rank two Gu Master battle attire, reminding her, she would have pounced on him and strangled him.

Fang Yuan paid no heed nor showed any expressions to Aunt's finger or her angry accusations.

A year of not meeting, Aunt's yellow face, although full of rage and hatred, could not hide her haggardness.

Her clothes had already changed to a simple hemp garment, and the accessories on her head had reduced. WIthout any make up, her mouth looked sharp and her face small, like a monkey.

Fang Yuan getting back the assets had caused a great influence and impact on her daily life.

To her furious bantering, Fang Yuan paid no heed to them, he held up his cup and drank some tea before saying slowly, "My trip here today is to sell the tavern and bamboo buildings, does Uncle and Aunt have any interest?"

"Pah, you traitorous wolf, what good can you have, wanting to sell the tavern and bamboo..." Aunt's tone stalled as she finally reacted, her face showing disbelief, "What, you want to sell the tavern and bamboo buildings?"

Fang Yuan put down his teacup, leaning back on the chair, closing his eyes to rest, "Better to get Uncle here to discuss with me."

Aunt gritted her teeth, not believing it, her eyes like erupting flames as she stared angrily at Fang Yuan, saying, "I know you're trying to toy with me, that's why you said that! Once I agree, I will get harshly mocked and ridiculed. You think I'm a fool, and would be played by you?"

This was purely a way of thinking from a person of low social status.

Fang Yuan sighed in his heart, before saying one sentence to change his aunt's attitude—

"Say any more bullshit and I'm leaving. I believe others would be interested in these assets. By then, I would have sold it to other people, so don't you both regret it."

Aunt paused for a moment, "Do you really want to sell these assets?"

"I am only waiting for five minutes." Fang Yuan opened a slit of his eyes to talk, before shutting them again.

He heard Aunt stomping her foot before a series of quick and softer footsteps.

Not long after, uncle Gu Yue Dong Tu appeared in front of Fang Yuan, but Aunt did not accompany him.

Fang Yuan looked at him.

Uncle was already aging extensively, his originally well-maintained face had shrunk, and there was much more white hair on his head now.

He had been worrying for the past few days.

Losing the family assets, he lost his financial sources all of a sudden. Without the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, he also lost his outside influence.

His "hidden elder" title, was already falsifying.

Although he had a huge amount of fortune in his hands, without his influence, these primeval stones had gotten troublesome.

The clan's politics was to encourage the clansmen to compete for resources, especially the rules on Gu fighting, it was inhumane and non-friendly. But this could exterminate parasites and the appearance of a good-for-nothing second generation, allowing the clan's people to maintain a sense of alertness. This also allowed the clan's fighting force to maintain at a strong position.

In this world, only strong fighting force could ensure survival. Tornadoes, floods and beasts do not speak sense with you.

These years, Gu Yue Dong Tu had lived a life of peace, and his fighting ability had diminished. In order to reduce his burden, the Gu worms that he used to fight with, he had sold them away already.

If someone sent him a challenge now, he would definitely lose more than winning.

Towards his uncle, Fang Yuan spoke openly about his purpose in coming.

"Fang Yuan, I shall not beat about the bush. I don't understand something, why do you need to sell the wine tavern and bamboo buildings? If you keep them, you will have a steady source of income." Uncle could not believe it, but his tone was much more acceptable than aunt's.

"Because I want to buy a red steel Relic Gu." Fang Yuan said honestly, there was no need to hide such things.

"So that's it." Uncle's gaze shone, "Then, you are selling the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass too?"

"That is impossible." Fang Yuan shook his head without any hesitation, "I am only selling the wine tavern, the bamboo buildings, the land and the eight servants."

Nine Leaf Vitality Grass was the most valuable thing in the asset, Fang Yuan needed its healing ability as well as selling them to earn primeval stones. It could sustain his cultivation and also feed the Gu worms.

Furthermore, next year the wolf tide was coming, and the vitality leaves' price would soar. With this Nine Leaf Vitality Grass in hand, Fang Yuan would have no problems with primeval stones for his Rank two cultivation journey.

But if uncle obtains the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, his "hidden elder" influence would instantly recover. Fang Yuan did not want to see this happen.

Seeing Fang Yuan's determined attitude, Gu Yue Dong Tu's heart was very disappointed. At the same time, he felt helpless.

The two had a secret talk for two hours, then they signed an extremely secure transfer agreement.

Gu Yue Dong Tu regained the tavern, bamboo buildings, family servants and land, while Fang Yuan led three family servants who were holding a box full of primeval stones each, towards the treehouse.

They each got what they wanted.

Hearing the news, Aunt rushed over. Seeing Gu Yue Dong Tu's contracts and deeds in his hands, she stared with round eyes and showed overwhelming joy, "Hubby, that lad got stupid from cultivating, he actually sold away such a profitable business! So stupid, wanting the eggs and not keeping the hen that lays eggs."

"Will you die if you stop talking, shut up." Gu Yue Dong Tu sounded very irritated.

"Husband..." Aunt pouted, "I'm just happy about it."

"Do not get complacent! With this tavern and the bamboo buildings, we have to be even more cautious now and keep a low profile. A huge tree attracts the wind. Although Fang Zheng is our adopted son, we cannot misuse this relationship. After all, Fang Zheng has not fully developed himself yet, who knows what the future entails?" Gu Yue Dong Tu sighed deeply.

"Got it, husband!" Aunt listened while staring at the stack of deeds, laughing uncontrollably.

Gu Yue Dong Tu's face was solemn throughout.

The transaction went well, and he now had income. The primeval stones he spent would be replenished with two or three years of operation. But he was not happy at all.

His mind was full of Fang Yuan's silhouette.

For a Relic Gu, Fang Yuan unhesitantly sold the assets, this was akin to giving up the comfortable life ahead.

Gu Yue Dong Tu placed himself in Fang Yuan's shoes and thought, Would I be able to do this?

I can't.

Even if he did not like Fang Yuan, filled with hatred and disgust, at this moment he could not help but exclaim in his heart, Able to give up and abandon his future comforts just like that, what great resolve he has!

Chapter 113: Keeping quiet and earning a fortune

"The competition is really fierce, who knows who the final winner will be."

"I have been standing here for just fifteen minutes and have already seen over ten Gu Masters putting quotes in the counter."

"Ah, this is a game for the rich. People like us don't even qualify to compete."

In the second floor of the treehouse, Gu Masters were surrounding the central counter; discussing and sighing.

As night approached, the competition for the red steel Relic Gu had reached its peak. Many Rank two Gu Masters who were observing in the dark started putting their quotes in this final hour.

Some Gu Masters even made several bids.

"The final winner for this struggle should be either Mo Yan or Chi Shan," someone guessed.

"That's possible. Mo Yan and Chi Shan are both at Rank two upper stage. With this Relic Gu, they can advance to peak stage and be at the same level as Qing Shu."

"In recent years, Gu Yue Qing Shu has been hanging over their heads. I don't believe these two don't have any thoughts about it."

"We can't say for sure. It is not only us Rank two Gu Masters, there are even some Rank three elders who have made bids. Just this morning, someone saw Lord Yao Ji casting her bid."

"Right, I also heard that. Lord Yao Ji's granddaughter Gu Yue Yao Le is taking part in the coming Awakening Ceremony; Lord Yao Ji should be preparing ahead and paving the way for her granddaughter."

"Ah, how good would it be if I had such a doting senior!"

Fang Yuan was among the crowd, his gaze tranquil as he listened to the discussions.

No one had mentioned his name. In the people's eyes, Fang Yuan was only a lucky kid who had just inherited the family assets. In their minds, Fang Yuan was still not at the level of people like Chi Shan, Mo Yan and Qing Shu.

"Great. The less attention on me, the more smoothly can I get this red steel Relic Gu. But with these repeated purchases, I should have attracted his attention."

Fang Yuan was ninety-nine percent sure of getting this Relic Gu; he began to think of another problem.

If the following events develop according to his expectations, then there would be a perfect ending to his several days of effort.

It was time.

The leaves and branches on the counter suddenly grew and wrapped firmly around the Relic Gu. The green leaves blocked the people's sight and when these leaves again unfolded, the red steel Relic Gu was not there anymore and was replaced by a Revert Gu.

The Revert Gu looked like a flat, oval, palm-sized stone. Its surface was slightly bulging and smooth, forming an eye pattern. The base of the stone was flat and felt rough to the touch.

The stone was black whereas the eye's pattern was covered with white lines.

About every two seconds, the eye would blink once and the white lines that portrayed the eyeball would swivel, giving the feeling that this stone was rolling its eyes.

Revert Gu had a special function.

It decomposed Rank two Gu worm to Rank one.

For example, if the Revert Gu was used on Fang Yuan's White Jade Gu, the White Jade Gu would again change back to White Boar Gu and Jade Skin Gu.

This process was called reverse-refining.

Fang Yuan glanced at it and immediately lost his interest. He didn't need the Revert Gu.

The surrounding Gu Masters began arguing. Revert Gu couldn't become everyone's focal point like the red steel Relic Gu.

Everyone was very curious on who the red steel Relic Gu went to.

Some people looked for the floor's caravan Gu Master and some people waited at the main desk.

The crowd slowly thinned out, but Fang Yuan didn't move away.

"Young Master Fang Yuan, please come to the third floor. Our lord Jia Fu would like to have a chat with you." A voice suddenly entered Fang Yuan's ears.

Fang Yuan wasn't surprised; there were many types of secret sound-transmission Gu worms in this world.

He followed the directions given by the voice and walked to a wall in the third floor.

Branches and leaves stacked together and covered the wooden wall.

Swoosh.....

The branches and leaves automatically parted to the sides and revealed a concealed door.

Fang Yuan pushed open the door and saw an exquisite whirling staircase that moved up.

He walked along the stairs and came to a small study room.

In the study room, Jia Fu was handling some accounts, his hand writing away speedily.

He raised his head when he heard Fang Yuan's footsteps, revealing the scar on his face. He gave a gentle smile, "We meet again, little brother Fang Yuan."

"Respects to Lord Jia Fu." Fang Yuan clasped his hands and saluted.

"Come, sit here." Jia Fu pointed at a nearest desk.

After Fang Yuan sat, his left hand pushed a bamboo paper on the desk towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan took a glance and immediately recognized that this bamboo paper held all his quotes that he had made in the recent days. Under every quote was his signature.

He was inwardly happy, it had gone according to his expectations. But on the surface, he wore a doubtful expression as he asked, "I am not sure what Lord Jia Fu wants to show me?"

Jia Fu's smile slightly decreased, his eyes flashing as he looked at Fang Yuan, "These are your quotes you made along with the quote you gave for the red steel Relic Gu. I will be honest, I am amazed at your business talent. Do you know, every one of your bids was very close to the final sale price."

"Although you only succeeded in buying a Black Boar Gu, a Liquor worm and the red steel Relic Gu, your quotes for other Gu worms only lacked by ten or so primeval stones. Brother, do you have any interest in working for me?" Jia Fu tried to recruit Fang Yuan.

"Here it comes!" Fang Yuan laughed inwardly. He had repeatedly made bids these days and had intentionally lost on most of them; his bids differing from the final price by only ten or so primeval stones. He had only successfully won Black Boar Gu, Liquor worm and red steel Relic Gu.

And just like he wished, Jia Fu was interested in the business talent he showed and took the initiative to recruit him.

However, in fact if Fang Yuan wished so, he had almost full guarantee of being able to purchase all the Gu worms.

"This...." Fang Yuan hesitated, then shook his head, "I am greatly honored to receive Lord Jia Fu's kindness, but I don't want to leave the clan."

"Oh, so it's like that." Jia Fu's gaze flashed, "Brother might have some misunderstandings towards me. A year ago, I indeed doubted you, but after using the Bamboo Gentleman, the suspicions on you have already been removed. Jia Jin Sheng was my brother, I hope you understand what my mood was like then. There is another piece of good news, I have already invited divine investigator Tie Xue Leng. There isn't any case which he cannot solve. I believe he will definitely be able to investigate the truth and give justice to you."

"Divine investigator Tie Xue Leng....this is a problem." Fang Yuan thought over this name. This was not good news to him.

In this world, there were many magical places and also many amazing methods that could be used to investigate.

When Fang Yuan killed Jia Jin Sheng, he had only been at Rank one. Even if he knew a lot of methods, he couldn't use them.

In his memories, Tie Xue Leng had a profound cultivation and wouldn't even tolerate a bit of sand in his eyes. He followed the thought of punishing evil and rewarding the right throughout his whole life. He had an extremely rich sense of justice and his thoughts were meticulous. He was very good at finding subtle traces from any clues.

"Divine investigator has a high reputation, I have also heard of him. But when will this lord divine investigator arrive at Qing Mao Mountain?" Fang Yuan put on an anticipating look and directly asked.

"That....." Jia Fu awkwardly smiled, "Divine investigator is very busy. From his reply, it might only be the year after the next."

Fang Yuan immediately felt relieved, he had a lot of time to prepare.

"Brother, I think highly of you. I hope you can carefully consider my proposal." Jia Fu made attractive offers.

Fang Yuan tactfully refused; now was not the best time to leave Qing Mao Mountain.

If he went to a strange environment without enough strength, he was bound to be bullied and pushed aside. The caravan was also full of unwritten rules on bullying and pushing aside.

"That is really a pity for your talent. How about this, I will give you this token. If there comes a day where you want my help, this token will be the proof that I will always welcome you." Jia Fu had failed in recruiting Fang Yuan, but he didn't feel surprised. He had a deep understanding towards this type of clan's cohesiveness.

If he was to know now that Fang Yuan was Jia Jin Sheng's murderer, who knows what his expression would be.

Fang Yuan apologised in shame as he received the token handed by Jia Fu along with the red steel Relic Gu.

He kept the two items close to him and backtracked his way out.

A young female Gu Master was caressing the leaves on the wall, when suddenly she cried out in shock. The branches and leaves suddenly parted and revealed a door.

The door was pushed open from inside and Fang Yuan walked out expressionlessly.

"You, you, you!" The young girl widened her eyes and blankly looked at Fang Yuan brushing past her.

Among the surrounding Gu Masters who saw this scene; some were familiar with this, some gave a knowing smile and some threw amazed looks.

Fang Yuan paid no heed to these gazes and walked down to the second floor. Some Gu Masters were still waiting there, excitedly discussing who the red steel Relic Gu went to.

Some people brazenly made guesses whereas some people gave some little news- "Mo Yan had a mysterious smile when she walked out of the treehouse,"—"Chi Shan's face was ashen,"—and so on.

And to top it all, some people pledged that so and so had bought the Relic Gu, even making an oath.

Fang Yuan went past this bored group of people. No one knew that at this moment, the red steel Relic Gu was so close to them.

When Fang Yuan walked out of the treehouse, he bumped into Chi Shan.

His face indeed looked unsightly, and at his side, Chi Cheng was asking about the whereabouts of the red steel Relic Gu.

After seeing Fang Yuan, Chi Cheng snorted and turned his head, intentionally not looking at him. Chi Shan silently nodded his head towards Fang Yuan as a greeting.

Fang Yuan also nodded his head as a reply, his face carrying a wisp of smile.

The last of the sunshine shone on this young boy's face; he was indeed happy.

With the red steel Relic Gu, his cultivation would instantly advance by a level.

And there was also the token.

A year ago, Fang Yuan wanted to build a friendship with Jia Jin Sheng and rely on him to take part in the future large-scale Gu fighting competition, reaping benefits in that period of upheaval.

Unfortunately, life was unpredictable, the final outcome made Fang Yuan not know whether to laugh or cry—unexpectedly, he ended up killing Jia Jin Sheng with his own hands.

No matter. Without Jia Jin Sheng, relying on Jia Fu also worked. This token was equivalent to the admission ticket to the future large-scale Gu fighting competition.

Chapter 114: Monkey King in the cave

Three days after the caravan left the village.

In the rock forest inside the mountain, filled with dark red light.

Huge stone pillars extended down from the ceiling, resembling long and gigantic tree trunks, forming into a majestic grey coloured stone forest.

Fang Yuan was retreating from battle in the rock forest.

Chirpchirpchirp...

A bunch of stone monkeys stared with their green circular monkey eyes, chasing after Fang Yuan relentlessly.

"Moonglow Gu!" Fang Yuan called in his mind, his right arm chopping towards the direction of the monkey gang.

Pew.

An eerie blue moonblade as large as a face formed into a crescent and pierced through the air, cutting into the monkey gang.

A jade eye stone monkey was jumping in the air. With no foothold to escape on, it was hit directly by the moonblade.

Before it could scream, in the next moment, its entire body was split into two from head to toe.

It had lost all its remaining life force and was enveloped in a deep aura of death.

In a split second, its lively eyes became a pair of jade pearls. As its body descended, it turned into a rock statue.

Bam.

With a crisp sound, the statue fell onto the ground, smashing into pieces.

The moonblade only dimmed a little, and after killing this stone monkey, its force remained as it rushed for the monkeys behind.

Kachakkk...

After a few cries, five or six stone monkeys were killed on the spot.

Chirpchirpchirp!

Their companions' death fueled the monkey gang's rage as they screamed furiously, their influence doubling, imposingly leaping at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was unfazed by the danger, his heart remaining as calm as ice. He fought and retreated appropriately. As the stone monkeys neared, he attacked with the moonblade.

The Moonlight Gu in the past, even with the boost from Little Light Gu, each moonblade could only kill one or two monkeys. But now, with one attack the Moonglow Gu could kill five or six stone monkeys.

But there were positive and negative impacts. The Moonglow Gu, to the current Fang Yuan, had a huge cost.

Each moonblade used 10% of his red steel primeval essence. Fang Yuan only had 44% Primeval Sea in his aperture.

This meant that he could only use four moonblades in one go.

"If I can successfully fuse the Four Flavors Liquor worm and refine my primeval essence, I would be able to shoot eight moonblades. What a pity. Even though I have the second Liquor worm and three out of the four flavours of wine, I am lacking the final one, I'm stuck at the final step," Fang Yuan sighed deeply.

Three moonblades later, his aperture only had 14% light red primeval essence left.

To play safe, he no longer used the moonblade, but activated the White Jade Gu.

The stone monkeys encircled him, the closest monkey jumping to Fang Yuan's leg and going into a frenzy. From down to up, it used its monkey head to hit Fang Yuan's chin.

Fang Yuan snorted, he wanted to use his fist to crush this overconfident monkey.

But suddenly he had a thought and stopped his hand, using his chin to receive the blow instead.

A moment before the point of impact, his chin shone with white jade cold light.

A loud bam sound resounded.

The force of the attack caused Fang Yuan's head to tilt back. But that monkey laid on the ground, hugging its head and rolling around the ground screaming in agony.

Without the White Jade Gu, Fang Yuan's chin would've been smashed. But now, Fang Yuan only felt slightly dizziness with no injuries.

But, even with the White Jade Gu's defense, he still had to withstand the impact of the attack.

Fang Yuan took a few steps back before recovering and seeing the scenery clearly before his eyes again.

He had intentionally withstood the monkey's headbutt earlier, it was to have this body get used to such attacks and get used to the slight dizziness.

This way, in the future when he falls into a life-and-death crisis, encountering such an attack, he would be able to recover much more quickly and fight for a survival chance.

Fang Yuan was always ruthless with his methods. This ruthlessness was not only towards enemies, but also himself!

He came here to kill stone monkeys almost every three days.

His motive was not just the Flower Wine Monk's strength inheritance, but also another motive—to utilize the stone monkeys to train his own fighting ability.

A Gu Master's physical stats, physical combat proficiency, aperture primeval essence, battle experience and every Gu worm, they were all elements that affected the overall battle strength.

Only by gathering all these elements tightly together can one exert the greatest fighting strength.

The stone monkey group was like a hammer, and Fang Yuan was the ingot that had just came out of the cauldron. With every hit of the hammer, he would become more sturdy, more refined, and more compact.

Fifteen minutes later, this battle ended.

On the ground, there were rock fragments all over the ground, and within those were dozens of jade pearls.

"I killed fourty-one jade eyes stone monkeys this time," Fang Yuan counted in his heart, and every time he would collate the battle results. From each battle, he'd reflect upon himself and improve upon what he did not do properly. At the same time, he would feel his own improvement speed.

"In the earlier battle, the Moonglow Gu was the most contributing factor, with three moonblades killing at least seventeen or eighteen stone monkeys. That is about half of the entire battle results, the remaining monkeys were all killed by my close combat.

Moonlight Gu's effect on the stone monkeys was not very obvious. But after advancing to Moonglow Gu, it jumped to being Fang Yuan's most powerful attacking method.

Not only was its attack power strong, but more crucially, its efficiency was very high.

Fang Yuan utilized three moonblades only in the span of a few breath's time, but when he used his fists and kicks to smash the stone monkeys, that took over ten minutes.

These stone monkeys were very agile and had swift movements.

When the stone monkeys were on the ground, there was no point thinking of hitting them physically. With a jump, they could easily leap away and avoid Fang Yuan's attack.

The only weakness was that when they jumped in mid-air, they couldn't change their moving direction. Fang Yuan being able to kill them, was due to this weakness.

But this was owing to his rich fighting experience. If it was any other Rank two Gu master, even Chi Shan, Mo Yan or Qing Shu, they would not be able to catch the weakness every time like Fang Yuan.

His previous life's memories could allow Fang Yuan to sensitively catch the opportunities in battle and seize them. He could meticulously use every ounce of his strength. Even though he was Rank two, he could already utilize his fighting strength to the limit of his abilities.

He was definitely not like Fang Zheng, having the Jade Skin Gu, but on the arena after being overwhelmed by Fang Yuan's aura, could not even display his supposed strength.

Of course, Fang Yuan's cultivation was still very low, and against the monkey group, he could not overwhelm them by brute force.

Every time, he had to fight while retreating.

Luckily, the monkeys did not have high intelligence. They could not adjust their attack patterns, and even after seeing Fang Yuan crushing them in mid-air many times, they still leapt towards Fang Yuan while attacking.

At the same time, every time they chased Fang Yuan, if it was too far from their homes, their longingness to their homes would overwhelm their anger. Many monkeys gave up on the chase due to this.

Gu are the essence of heaven and earth, humans are the spirit of all living things.

Fang Yuan is relying on the intelligence of humans to understand the stone monkeys' habits and using the correct fighting methods to get deeper into the rock forest, at this point he was already near the central area of the rock forest.

After many attempts, Fang Yuan finally exterminated the monkey group on this rock pillar.

Right now, in front of him, was the final pillar.

It was the largest and thickest rock pillar in this rock forest.

The pillar extended downwards from the ceiling, almost touching the ground. It emitted a majestic aura amidst the silence.

Fang Yuan counted the number of rock caves on the pillar, getting an estimation of at least five hundred stone monkeys. This was the largest monkey group he had encountered up till now.

But no matter how many jade eye stone monkeys there were, to Fang Yuan, it was just a small bit of trouble, at most he'd have to exert more effort and waste a few more trips.

What caused his gaze to become serious, was the rock cave at the most upper level.

The entrance of this cave was larger than any of the surrounding caves, at least twice as large if not more.

And below it, the caves were tightly cluttered together, forming and resembling a position where they were worshipping and revering.

"It seems that there is a monkey king in this rock cave." Fang Yuan frowned.

This was where the problem lay.

As long as a beast group is large, there would be a beast king created. There was a wild boar king in the wild boar group. Obviously there would also be a monkey king in the monkey group.

The threat of a beast king was multiple times higher than a normal wild beast.

The reason was that their bodies had one or two Gu worms inside. These Gu had a mutual partnership with the beast kings, and once the beast king is attacked, they would come out and assist.

"This jade eye stone monkey king should not be very strong, at least weaker than the wild boar king. Otherwise, the surrounding monkey groups would've been under his control already." Fang Yuan using his experiences, gauged the monkey king's strength.

Normally, the bigger the beast group, the stronger the beast king; weaker beast kings did not have the ability to rule over a large number of its kind.

According to the beast group's size and classifying of the beast kings, from low to high, they could be classified as hundred beast king, thousand beast king, and myriad beast king.

The wild boar king that sickly snake's group hunted was a thousand beast king, it ruled over a thousand wild boars.

The stone monkey king before Fang Yuan was a hundred beast king, it only had several hundred stone monkeys under its rule.

The culprit behind the wolf tide, the lightning crown wolf was a myriad beast king, every single lightning crown wolf ruled over at least ten thousand lightning wolves.

The difference in ability between the three beast kings, were huge.

Thousand beast kings needed three teams to cooperate together to be able to barely kill it. The sickly snake group was able to deal with the wild boar king, mostly due to it being injured beforehand.

A myriad beast king required the clan elders and clan leader to work together to be able to go against it head on.

As for hundred beast king, a regular five man group would be able to handle it.

But for Fang Yuan who wanted to deal with this monkey king, he could not borrow outside strength, and could only rely on his own power.

"Rank two initial stage primeval essence is ineffective here, it seems it is time to use the red steel Relic Gu." Fang Yuan eyed the rock cave deeply, then left the second secret room and closed the rock door.

If what stands in his way is a thousand beast king like the wild boar king, Fang Yuan would retreat without thinking.

But if it is only a hundred beast king, if Fang Yuan had Rank two middle stage cultivation, he could give it a shot.

Of course, the results could go either way. Even with middle stage cultivation, he still had roughly 75% chance of failure, his chances of success not even hitting 30%.

Chapter 115: Advancing to middle stage

The translucent light membrane, faint red Primeval Sea and the surging waves.

On the sea surface, two fat white Liquor worms were absorbing the water. In the air above the sea, a black ladybug-like Black Boar Gu was shaking its wings and hovering around the red steel Relic Gu.

The pebble like White Jade Gu had sunk to the depths of the sea and was motionless.

Spring Autumn Cicada had concealed itself; it was in a deep slumber to recuperate.

"It is time." Fang Yuan willed; the sea waves paused, and a portion of primeval essence surged up and poured towards the red steel Relic Gu.

The red steel Relic Gu immediately shook and flew up, giving off bursts of red rays of light.

It was like the slowly rising sun, its rays of light shining upon the aperture wall.

The rays of light were as hot as fire and as dazzling as a sword.

The Black Boar Gu was soon unable to bear it and fell down to the Primeval Sea.

The two Liquor worms also sunk down to the depths of the Primeval Sea.

White Jade Gu was flashing inside the sea.

For Fang Yuan to advance to rank two middle stage with normal methods, he could only use the method of grinding; using his light red primeval essence to cleanse the light membrane aperture wall.

But now, red steel Relic Gu gave off majestic red light which replaced the light red primeval essence and poured directly into the aperture wall, giving astonishing results.

Fang Yuan could see the whole light membrane thickening at an astonishing pace.

The light on the light membrane condensed into streams of light, gradually changing to a water membrane. The white shimmering rays flowed continuously; becoming clear one moment and dark in the next.

Right now, Fang Yuan had advanced to middle stage!

However, the Relic Gu was still bursting with red rays of light.

The rays of light filled the whole aperture; it replaced the primeval essence and continuously injected its essence and foundation into Fang Yuan's aperture.

The water membrane accepted it all and the shimmering rays of light on it was like water as it flowed freely.

This continued on for about fifteen minutes.

Red steel Relic Gu had thoroughly exhausted all its energy; its body turned transparent and disappeared in the red light.

The penetrating red rays of light also suddenly dissipated with its disappearance.

The aperture recovered its tranquility once again.

However the water membrane had become much thicker. Using the red steel Relic Gu had saved Fang Yuan from wasting a lot of time and effort.

A thread of scarlet red primeval essence appeared in the Primeval Sea.

This was the rank two middle stage primeval essence. It was more condensed than the light red initial stage primeval essence. It sank to the depths of the Primeval Sea and lingered around the White Jade Gu.

A red steel Relic Gu could directly strengthen the foundation of the aperture. To a Gu Master, this meant advancing by a small realm.

This type of Gu worm was naturally better if used early.

To a Gu Master, higher cultivation meant stronger fighting force, better survival rate, more mission completions and also more primeval stones earnings. It had a great influence on every aspect.

After reaching the middle stage, Fang Yuan took several primeval stones and started recovering his primeval essence. He stopped only after the 44% percent Primeval Sea in his aperture had completely filled with middle stage scarlet primeval essence.

Half an hour later, he once again stepped into the stone forest, heading towards the central area.

He stepped into the warning zones of the monkey groups; immediately, furious jade eye stone monkeys came out of the stone pillars.

They screeched and pounced upon Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's expression didn't change, most of his attention was on that cave at the highest layer of the stone pillar.

When encountering a common jade eye stone monkey, there was no need to be nervous as long as you weren't surrounded by them. The main problem was the stone monkey king.

What Gu worms resided on it? Fang Yuan didn't know.

Fang Yuan slowly retreated while cautiously observing, but the stone monkey king didn't appear.

Fang Yuan was baffled, "Is there no monkey king in this monkey group? If there was a monkey king, then it would no doubt be the first to come out if someone infringed on its territory. Hold it, maybe it has already come out!"

Just as he thought of this, the sleeping Spring Autumn Cicada in his aperture suddenly floated into appearance. Its body was trembling as it gave a weak startled cry that resonated only within Fang Yuan's mind.

The vital Gu's warning!

This appeared only when the vital Gu felt there was an intense threat against the Gu Master's life.

In that split second, Fang Yuan's hairs stood up. Without thinking twice, he directly used the White Jade Gu.

A layer of bright white jade light covered his whole body.

In the next instant, the stone monkey king—who was three times bigger than a normal stone monkey—suddenly appeared on the left side of Fang Yuan and fiercely struck out with its sharp claws at Fang Yuan's left shoulder.

Bang.

The stone monkey king's attack was blocked by the White Jade Gu's defense; its attack failed.

In the instant Fang Yuan received this attack, the White Jade Gu in his aperture suddenly lit up and consumed five percent of the scarlet primeval essence.

If it was when Fang Yuan was at the initial stage, ten percent of light red primeval essence would have been used up.

From this, one could see how sinister and vicious the stone monkey king's sneak attack was.

Despite Fang Yuan having a calm character, he couldn't help breaking out in cold sweat at this moment. If it were not for him sharpening himself these days and polishing his condition to a peak combat state, he might have really been hit by the stone monkey king's attack.

Had his reaction been just a bit late, his left shoulder would have become crippled and unusable. Fang Yuan would then end up miserable just like Gu Yue Man Shi not long ago.

"There is actually a wild concealing-type Gu worm residing in this stone monkey king!" Fang Yuan hurriedly retreated, he had no way to detect a concealing Gu worm and ended up in disadvantage all of a sudden.

The stone monkey king seemed to be more cunning than normal stone monkeys. After its attack missed, it again hid itself away.

This undoubtedly was a huge mental pressure on Fang Yuan.

He used the White Jade Gu to form a defense around his whole body. Such a method used primeval essence every moment and it was impossible for him to maintain this defense.

Even when he had fought with the stone monkey troops before, he would only use the White Jade Gu at the crucial moment.

If he continued to maintain this state, then his primeval essence would completely dissipate not long after.

Over five hundred stone monkeys encircled Fang Yuan aggressively.

Fang Yuan used his greatest speed to retreat and pull some distance.

Some stone monkey's momentum became weaker, whereas some stomped on the ground and began to head back to their homes.

"Chirp!" Right at this moment, the jade eye stone monkey king appeared and commanded in a loud voice.

"Chirp chirp!!" The stone monkey groups immediately responded; their confusion and hesitation disappeared and again started their chase after Fang Yuan.

Over five hundred jade eye stone monkeys were persistently chasing after him, but Fang Yuan didn't panic; his lips revealing a cold smile on the contrary.

This accident was already in his expectations.

He had chosen the easiest route towards the central area of the stone forest, opening up a passage. In the surroundings of the passage were large numbers of stone monkey groups.

Fang Yuan was very familiar with this passage.

However, with the low intelligence of these stone monkeys, how could they know? Under the supervision of the stone monkey king, they stormed through the stone forest, infringing on other monkey groups' warning zones and resulting in counterattacks from the other monkey groups.

The stone forest was in a great chaos!

Countless jade eye stone monkeys stood at their place, starting a massacre to defend their homes.

In ten or more years, the stone monkey king might even advance to become a thousand beast king and completely unify this stone forest. But now, it was only a hundred beast king and didn't have the ability to control so many stone monkeys.

The different groups of stone monkeys fell into a chaotic battle with each other.

For a moment, all Fang Yuan could hear was the screeching and screaming sounds of the stone monkeys.

Those five hundred stone monkeys that were chasing him were quickly entangled with the other stone monkey groups. But the stone monkey king still persisted on chasing after Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was attacking and retreating. In this period of time, he suffered many sneak attacks from the stone monkey king and every attack would consume great amounts of his primeval essence. Luckily, he had advanced to middle stage before this. Otherwise, with the initial stage primeval essence, he wouldn't have been to handle this consumption.

Fang Yuan landed in absolute disadvantage; he had not found any weakness in the stone monkey king.

The only chance to attack lay in the moment the stone monkey king was about to attack. But even if Fang Yuan was able to react, he had no time to even make an attacking movement.

The stone monkey king possessed a concealment-type gu worm and firmly held the initiative. It could attack Fang Yuan whenever it wanted to attack. Even if Fang Yuan injured it, it could use the concealment-type gu worm to safely escape; it was in an invincible position.

"Without a stealth-removal Gu worm, the probability to win this battle is extremely low! If I had a wide area attacking method, maybe I could give it a try. But Moonglow Gu... I will only be able to hit this stone monkey king if I am lucky, but the probability is too low."

Fang Yuan clearly understood the battle situation and immediately retreated.

However, the stone monkey king seemed to be determined to kill him.

Fang Yuan retreated to about a hundred meters from the rock door when he suddenly stopped.

"I only have a bit over 10% of my primeval essence remaining. It won't be enough to cover this hundred meters of distance. And even if I am able to enter the second secret room and close the rock door, this stone monkey king might just break the door!"

Fang Yuan had thought that the stone monkey king would give up after chasing him for such a long period of time. Yet who could have thought that it still persisted on chasing him.

He was already out of the stone forest now and around him was a patch of empty ground.

Countless stone monkeys were fighting chaotically in the stone forest, causing an uproar. Their noisy sounds kept on echoing within this empty space.

Fang Yuan didn't budge; his battle intuition told him that the stone monkey king was hiding somewhere, waiting for him to show a gap before making a fatal attack.

Fang Yuan knew he had already fallen into an impasse.

Normal Rank two Gu Masters would have already fallen apart from this fear, unable to endure this formless pressure.

But Fang Yuan was still calm.

This situation was also within his expectations, though its probability was very low. According to logic, the stone monkey king should also possess the stone monkey's habits and be reluctant to leave its home. But for some reason, this stone monkey king was hell bent on chasing and killing Fang Yuan.

"If you choose to take a risk, you need to be willing to risk your life!" Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with a cold light; he then took off his upper garment.

Chapter 116: Killing the Monkey King and getting new Gu

"11% primeval essence, this means two moonblades or sustain the monkey king's sneak attack twice. Relying solely on the Moonglow Gu or White Jade Gu will not do. My only chance is the instant where the monkey king attacks me, I have to grasp the opportunity and shoot the moonblade, instantly killing it!" Fang Yuan's thoughts sparked like flint, thinking of the most optimum strategy.

Stone monkeys did not have outstanding defense, and since the monkey king chose a sneak attack approach, it revealed that defense was its weakness.

One moonblade could slaughter five or six jade eye stone monkeys. Even if it couldn't kill the monkey king, it can still heavily injure it.

But do not think that this is easy; getting to this point is difficult, even if a group of Gu Masters came, without a stealth removal type Gu they would still lose their lives.

"This monkey is cunning, choosing not to attack, is it waiting for my primeval essence to be used up? Nevermind, I shall trust the Spring Autumn Cicada once and bet on this chance!" Fang Yuan instantly decided, his eyes shining with a cold and ruthless light.

He stood on the spot, both hands hanging beside him, holding the collar of his shirt. At the same time, he closed his eyes, only leaving a slit of visibility. What is more shocking is that he removed the defense of the White Jade Gu.

The expenditure of the primeval essence in his aperture, finally stopped. At the same time, he was no longer under the protection of the white jade light.

The rock forest continued to reverb with the cries and anguish of the monkeys, but Fang Yuan could feel that these noises were getting closer and closer to himself.

A type of calmness enveloped his heart and mind.

He was silently waiting for the stone monkey king's attack.

When it attacks, that is when the match is decided!

Waiting...

Waiting...

Suddenly, the Spring Autumn Cicada vibrated in the aperture.

Pew!

The very next moment, Fang Yuan heard an explosion and the stone monkey king appeared on his left!!

"White Jade Gu!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance as the white jade light covered his entire body.

Bam.

The stone monkey king hit Fang Yuan's body with a strong force, almost causing him to topple, his primeval essence dropping by 5%, only left with the other half!

Seeing that his attack did not finish Fang Yuan off, the stone monkey king tried to escape!

Fang Yuan had no time to counterattack, but it was enough for him to flick his upper shirt.

Suddenly, he felt that there was someone on his upper shirt, tugging towards the outside direction.

The shirt was not made of steel, and to prevent it from tearing, Fang Yuan let go of both hands, seeing the floating shirt fly around the place at a shocking speed.

"Now!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone with cold light as the battle's outcome would be decided with this moonblade, his heart cold and calm as ice.

The monkey king was afterall a wild beast, and after having its face covered by a shirt, it flew into a panic.

It emitted a shrill scream, calling its stone monkeys to help. At the same time the shirt continued to move around, changing directions and going all over the place.

An eerie blue moonblade flew out and hit the stone monkey king.

The monkey king cried in pain as its camouflage was exposed.

Its appearance was the same as a normal stone monkey, but its body size was three times bigger, and at the same time its eyes shone with a bloody red light.

A long and deep wound stretched from its chest to its left leg, blood continuing to pour from it.

Although not dead, it had already suffered a heavy injury, and the aura of death permeated its entire body. It covered its wound in shock, going invisible again.

Fang Yuan's upper shirt was cut open by his moonblade, falling onto the ground. But the blood traces exposed the monkey king, and it hurriedly retreated, no longer having the idea of killing Fang Yuan. With such a grave injury, if it did not deal with it, it would lose its life.

At this time, Fang Yuan also retreated to the rock door. After activating the moonblade, his aperture only had a little bit of primeval essence left, and his battle strength dropped drastically.

Although it looked like a draw, Fang Yuan had won.

The monkey king's injury could not be recovered shortly. The more blood it lost, the weaker it felt.

But Fang Yuan could use the primeval stones to recover his primeval essence and recover his battle strength.

Even without a stealth removal type Gu, nor a wide area attack method, with his rich fighting experience and the will of steel in the face of danger, Fang Yuan could beat the strong in a weaker state.

"Monkey, fox, bei(1), these wild beasts have extraordinary intelligence compared to ordinary wild beasts, and are more cunning. Because of this, they lack the wild courage and often retreat while injured. If it were a wild boar or bull, they would go into a frenzy while injured. This monkey king seems to only have one Gu worm. Although the Gu worm could grant stealth, it cannot hide blood traces, and if my guess is correct, it should be the Rank one stealth rock Gu."

Fang Yuan pondered in his heart, and relying on his memories, the monkey king had no more secrets in front of him.

"The results has been decided." Fang Yuan returned to the rock room, closing the door and replenishing his primeval essence.

A moment later, his primeval essence went back to its peak state, and Fang Yuan opened the rock door, being in the rock forest once again.

The rock forest was still a mess, but better than before.

"After this chaos, the entire rock forest's forces will be reset. The stone monkeys will relocate and regroup, and the roaming and isolated stone monkeys form into new monkey gangs. The path that I painstakingly created would thus vanish."

Fang Yuan's heart sank, he needed to kill the stone monkey king before this path is completely gone.

If not, opening this path would expend much of his time again, and by the time he got to the center again, the monkey king would've completely healed.

He shall chase after and annihilate lingering enemies with bravery, rather than be easily contented with fame and compliments like Xiang Yu(2).

Fang Yuan trailed along the opened path, invading the rock forest. The stone monkeys who appeared in his way were all exterminated.

Fifteen minutes later, he appeared at the central pillar once again.

The stone monkey king laid on the ground; it had turned into a statue and was already dead.

A jade eye stone monkey was stepping on its corpse, screaming about.

Replacing the title of king, with the death of the former king, a new king takes its place. Regardless of the beast group or human society, this was the cruel elimination system.

"Saved some effort of mine." Fang Yuan slowly got closer.

At this moment, a Gu worm slowly floated from the corpse of the stone monkey king, flying towards the new king.

Moonglow Gu!

Fang Yuan shot out a moonblade just in time, chasing away the new stone monkey king, then walking up and grabbing the Gu worm.

This Gu looked ordinary like a grey rock, with an uneven surface that was not even squarish nor spherical. If this Gu was thrown on the road, no one would notice it based on appearance.

But in reality, it was the essence of a rock, a natural Gu nurtured by Mother Nature.

It seemed like an inanimate object, a rock. But in fact, it was the real deal, a living being with its own consciousness and thought.

As Fang Yuan predicted, it was the Stealth Rock Gu.

Grabbed by Fang Yuan, it desperately struggled, trying to be free of his demonic grasp.

Spring Autumn Cicada.

Fang Yuan called in his mind, and the Spring Autumn Cicada appeared in his aperture, leaking a trace of its aura.

The Stealth Rock Gu instantly went dead, not daring to struggle, like a mouse meeting a cat.

Fang Yuan's red primeval essence activated and instantly refined it.

Another Gu in the bag!

The Stealth Rock Gu was kept in the aperture and sunk to the bottom of the Primeval Sea, side by side with the White Jade Gu.

The stone monkey watched helplessly at the side, and on seeing Fang Yuan keep the Stealth Rock Gu into his body, it frantically jumped about, screaming incoherently.

It had just gotten the new position, so not many monkeys obeyed it.

With another moonblade, Fang Yuan took a few more monkey lives. Those that gathered around their new king instantly dispersed.

The new stone monkey king gnawed its teeth at Fang Yuan.

"Scram." Fang Yuan stared at it, saying a word, with his expression cold as ice.

The monkey king shuddered, feeling the intense killing intent from Fang Yuan. It stared at Fang Yuan blankly before gulping and turning around to escape, showing its superior intelligence compared to wild beasts.

Fang Yuan chased these stone monkeys away and ignored them, getting to the bottom of the rock pillar as soon as he could.

As he got close, he found a cave below the rock pillar.

The cave was not big, and some rock stairs extended downwards into the darkness.

Fang Yuan had no investigative Gu worm, so he could not tell what was down there.

With the situation unclear, Fang Yuan did not enter the cavern and walk down the stairs. He had barged his way in earlier, and his body condition was not at its prime. Furthermore, the chaos in the rock forest was disappearing and was stabilizing.

He had spent much effort and time to open the path, but many stone monkeys were starting to reside in the pillars along the way.

"Haste brings no success. Now that I have found the inheritance clue, I have achieved my goal. It is time to return." Fang Yuan controlled the urge to investigate, and returned via the same route.

On the way, the pressure intensified but eventually, he endured the pressure as he was chased by hundreds of monkeys, tragically rushing out of the rock forest.

TIme passed quickly, and summer replaced spring.

Unknowingly it was the scorching summer again already.

Fang Yuan spent every second of his time cultivating diligently. Using the red steel Relic Gu, he instantly caught up to Fang Zheng's cultivating speed.

He did not have a special Gu that could hide his middle stage aura. After killing the monkey king and obtaining the Stealth Rock Gu, a day later, his cultivation level was exposed.

The clansmen only knew then that he was the one who obtained the red steel Relic Gu; it was actually Fang Yuan!

At the same time, he intentionally revealed the Black Boar Gu.

Fang Yuan sold such a huge amount of assets to get the Black Boar Gu and red steel Relic Gu. Many people could not understand his thoughts, calling him a 'fool', 'dumbass', 'maniac' and 'short-sighted', as they became his new nicknames.

With a rise in attention, Fang Yuan had to reduce the number of times he ventured into the Flower Wine Monk's inheritance.

He continued to nurture his aperture as he steadily moved towards Rank two upper stage, while collecting the ingredients to fuse the Liquor worm as well as the Stealth Rock Gu. At the same time, he used the vitality leaf to earn primeval stones, sustaining his cultivation.

July, the start of autumn.

At the foot of the mountain near the village, a wild Rank five Gu suddenly appeared, causing a huge tremor at Gu Yue Village!

(1) Bei—A legendary wolf in chinese mythology

(2) Xiang Yu—Qing Dynasty conqueror

Chapter 117: Bitter shell wine and River Swallowing Toad

A solemn and serious atmosphere filled the conference hall.

A group of elders silently sat on their seats; their faces were either indifferent, gloomy or serious.

Clan head Gu Yue Bo was sitting on the main seat, his gaze also filled with unconcealed worry, "Three days ago, a River Swallowing Toad appeared near the village by the foot of the mountain. This toad flowed along with the Huang Long River(1) and accidentally reached here. Right now, it is blocking up a river channel and sleeping there. If we ignore it, the village will constantly be in danger. So I would like to ask the elders if you have any good ideas to drive this toad away?"

The elders looked at each other; for a moment, no one spoke.

River Swallowing Toad was a Rank five Gu; it had an enormous might and could spit out a river. If this was not handled properly and it was provoked, over half of the Qing Mao mountain could be submerged with water and the whole village would be destroyed.

After a long silence, Gu Yue Chi Lian spoke, "The situation is grave, and we need to resolve this as quickly as possible. If this news gets leaked, we can't say for sure if those with evil intentions might not secretly go and intentionally provoke this River Swallowing Toad to entrap our Gu Yue clan."

"Elder Chi Lian is right." Gu Yue Mo Chen nodded in agreement. Although he and Gu Yue Chi Lian were political enemies, but at such a critical time for the village, he let go of his past prejudices.

He continued speaking after a moment, "There is another more serious problem. If the River Swallowing Toad floods the Qing Mao mountain, the wolf lairs will be submerged and for their survival, the wolf hordes will move up the mountain. At that time, the wolf tide will break out before its time. And we will have to fight with countless wild beasts to fight for the space at the top."

The elders' complexion turned pale when they heard this.

Gu Yue Bo spoke with heavy tone, "Everyone, don't forget the foundation of our village. The first generation ancestor set up the village in this place because of the underground spirit spring. If Qing Mao mountain gets flooded, this spirit spring might also be destroyed."

"What should we do?"

"Sigh....even if we withstand the beast tides and survive at the mountaintop. After the flood subsides, the spirit spring will have disappeared, many beasts will have died, our surroundings will turn to a wasteland and we will be lacking cultivation resources."

"If we are to die, then why not ask help from Xiong and Bai villages? We are three boats tied with one rope, I don't believe they won't help!"

The elders whispered to one another with panic hidden inside. Some had already started thinking of asking for reinforcements.

"It is too premature to ask for help now," Gu Yue Bo shook his head and denied this idea immediately. "It is not the most challenging period now. When the first generation ancestor had just established the village, a Rank five Blood River Python attacked the village, but the first generation clan head killed it. Compared to the Blood River Python, the River Swallowing Toad is just so much more adorable."

"It has a warm temperament and is harmless to ordinary people. Only if it senses the aura of other Gu will it be alert. If it receives serious injuries, it will be angered and spit out a river. By chance, I heard the previous clan head talk of a rumor about the River Swallowing Toad...."

Gu Yue Bo's composed and calm voice resounded within the conference hall.

The group of elders listened attentively; their nervous and panicked expressions eased up.

"He is really worthy of being the clan head. He calmed their hearts with just his words." Gu Yue Yao Ji sensed the change in the atmosphere. She gave a profound look at Gu Yue Bo and praised him inwardly.

"If we follow what clan head said just now, chasing away the River Swallowing Toad wouldn't be a difficult thing," An elder spoke.

"We can't say that." Gu Yue Bo shook his head, "These are only rumors, I haven't personally seen it or even put it to use. The important thing is that we can't be careless. I suggest we first send a group of Gu Masters to test it."

All the elders agreed.

Gu Yue Chi Lian spoke, "Then how about I send a member of my Chi family. If he can't do it, then no one among our clan might be able to do it."

Everyone knew who Chi Lian was speaking of, and they approved of it one after another.

Clan head Gu Yue Bo smiled, "Since it is so, then we shall just assign it to the Chi Shan group."

It was early autumn, the weather was gradually turning cool.

On a table by the window of the tavern, Fang Yuan was sitting alone, calmly tasting some wine.

The tavern shopkeeper was standing beside him, bowing his head.

"Shopkeeper, is there progress on the matter regarding bitter shell wine that I asked you to look into a few days ago?" Fang Yuan asked.

Fang Yuan was lacking a bitter wine for the liquor worm fusion.

However, bitter wines were difficult to find and because of the matter regarding the red steel Relic Gu, people had been focusing on him. Wherever he went, people would point him out. Thus, it was not easy to make inquiries of bitter wines.

The disturbance had settled down only recently, and maybe because extreme sorrow turns into joy, Fang Yuan had accidentally found a clue regarding the bitter wine.

The old shopkeeper promptly replied, "Young Master, the bitter shell wine you wanted me to look into, someone had drunk it in Bai village. The raw material of this wine is a type of conch found in deep ponds.This type of conch is completely black, with circles of white lines on its shell resembling a tree's growth rings. We call it a bitter shell. Normal conches can form pearls. The bitter shell swallows the sands and stones in the water, dissolving them and forming bitter water instead. Someone pried open its shell and obtained this bitter water, using it to brew wine, making the bitter shell wine. Its taste is very unique; bitter and fragrant."

Fang Yuan slightly raised his brows upon hearing this, "Does that mean Bai village has this bitter shell wine?"

The shopkeeper hurriedly bent down, "I don't dare to guarantee it, I have only heard people talking about it occasionally. However, the truth is Bai village is famous for its white grain liquid. This wine along with our clan's green bamboo wine and Xiong village's bear gall wine are called the three wines of Qing Mao. Bitter Shell wine.... I think even if the Bai village possesses it, there wouldn't be much."

"Even if there is little, I have to find it," Fang Yuan said in his mind.

But this matter was troublesome; Bai village had been gradually showing signs of coming to emergence these years, starting to shake the Gu Yue village's position as the overlord.

If Fang Yuan wanted to enter the Bai village without permission, the patrolling Bai village's Gu Masters might kill him before he even sees the village gate.

Even if it was so, Fang Yuan still wanted to attempt it. After all, getting this bitter shell wine was more reasonable that the green Ai wine that was immeasurably far away.

As he broke away from his contemplations, Fang Yuan found that the old shopkeeper was still standing beside him. He waved his hand, "Alright, you can leave, there is nothing for you here."

The old man didn't leave, his face revealed hesitation, not speaking out what he was about to say.

He finally summoned his courage, "Young Master, could you please take back this tavern again? All the waiters and I want to work for you. You don't know that when the old landlord came back, he deducted most of our wages. With such little primeval stones each month, it is really difficult for us to support our families."

Fang Yuan shook his head, his face without any expression, "I have already sold this tavern to him. I can't take it back according to the contract. Moreover, I don't want to engage in this tavern business. You can leave now."

"But, young landlord....." The old man still didn't move.

Fang Yuan frowned in annoyance, "Remember, I am no longer your landlord!"

He had previously increased their salaries, only to arouse their passion for their work. It was all for himself. However, these people mistook it for his tolerance and wanted to push their luck.

Right now, by selling the vitality leaves, he could only fulfill his own needs. On top of that, he was feeling vexed due to the bitter wine. So why would he take back the tavern for these people?

"But young landlord, we really can't keep on living like this! Please show mercy and have pity on us." The shopkeeper knelt on the ground and implored.

The sound immediately attracted the surrounding guests.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly. He picked up a wine jar from the table and smashed it on the shopkeeper's head.

Kachak.

The jar shattered; the wine splashed all around and blood flowed from the old man's head.

"Did you think I won't dare to kill you? You tactless fool, get lost." Cold light flashed out from Fang Yuan's eyes.

The old shopkeeper's whole body trembled from this killing intent; he was startled and hurriedly left.

No matter which world, there will always be a group of weak people who will brazenly and indiscreetly ask charity from the strong. As if helping them was the manner of the strong and not helping them was wrong.

The weak should have the manners of the weak; they should either resign to their fate and act like slaves or try hard while keeping a low profile.

The strong helped the weak only as a charity when they were in a good mood.

The weak refuse to work hard, shamelessly begging from the strong, and even demanding definite results, acting like a leech; they deserve getting rejected.

People who were content with being weak, who don't put their own effort and only think of begging from the strong, simply aren't deserving of sympathy.

"Shopkeeper..."

"Quick, bandage the wounds."

The waiters hurriedly surrounded the old man whose face was covered with blood.

The old shopkeeper was only a mortal, it wouldn't be a problem even if he was killed on the spot.

Such an ending took away the interest of the surrounding guests; they turned back and continued with their discussions.

"Do you know? Something big happened recently!"

"Are you talking about that River Swallowing Toad? Right now, who wouldn't know of this?"

"This is a Rank five Gu, if it isn't dealt properly, the village might fall into crisis!"

"It is said that this River Swallowing Toad's food is water. When it is hungry, it opens up its large mouth and directly sucks a river in!"

"If it is angered, it can release the water into the Qing Mao mountain, its power is extremely horrifying. We might die!"

"Then what should we do?"

"Sigh, we just have to see how the clan's higher-ups will deal with it. After all, we can't escape, where can we escape to?"

Bewilderment and confusion pervaded the air in the tavern.

"River Swallowing Toad...." Fang Yuan inwardly smiled when he heard this.

Fear was infectious, it increased the more it is spread.

Actually, the River Swallowing Toad was very gentle and was not dreadful. Its natural disposition was to sleep and people would often see it flowing with the river. The toad would lie down on the water surface with their white bellies facing up, and sleep soundly.

When it wakes up, it would swallow the river water up to its fill and return back to sleep. They had no interest towards fighting and killing; if they meet an enemy, their first reaction would be to flee. Only if they fall into an impasse and couldn't escape will they make fierce counterattacks.

They were very powerful and could release torrential river from their mouths, engulfing the lands instantly and turning them to marsh.

"This River Swallowing Toad probably fell asleep, then drifted along the Huang Long river and accidentally entered a tributary, reaching the foot of the Qing Mao mountain." Fang Yuan guessed the truth.

(1) Huang Long River—The name means Yellow Dragon River.

Chapter 118: Legend of the River Swallowing Toad

It is said that every single River Swallowing Toad's stomach carries a river.

Fang Yuan did not use the River Swallowing Toad in his previous life, but he has a strong impression of this Gu, because of one person.

A normal person, a family servant.

Around two hundred years later in his previous life, a very special Gu Master will appear— Jiang Fan.

His existence shocked numerous Gu Masters, and his story would be spread around by the mortals.

Once he appeared, he became a legend.

His entire success was attributed to a River Swallowing Toad.

Jiang Fan was a mere family servant, single-handedly taking care of a fishery for his master. One day, a River Swallowing Toad arrived at the coast with its belly side up, lying in the water, asleep the entire time.

Jiang Fan was initially scared and shocked, but slowly, he felt that this toad was dead, why was it not moving at all?

The "toad corpse" blocked the upflow of the river water, and this caused many problems for Jiang Fan who was taking care of the fishery.

Jiang Fan tried many different methods and ways to move this "toad corpse" away. But he was just a mere mortal, how could he move something as heavy as the River Swallowing Toad?

His master was stingy and cruel, and if he could not meet the monthly quota, his head will be decapitated. Jiang Fan did not dare to report it, as someone not too long ago did not manage to fulfill his quota and reported it with a proper reason, but ended up getting killed on the spot.

Seeing that the due date was getting closer, and the corpse still remained there blocking the water, it greatly affected his revenue. Gradually, Jiang Fan became more frightened, and his temper became more abusive and frustrated.

Although he knew that he could not move this corpse away, he would still go to it everyday, to punch and kick the "toad corpse", crying and making a din. Letting go of all the fear and anger he had in the face of death.

But one day, the River Swallowing Toad woke up, and with its half-opened eyes, stared at Jiang Fan.

Jiang Fan's legs went soft from the shock.

The River Swallowing Toad was half asleep and half awake, but it still laid there like it was a "corpse". After some time, Jiang Fan regained his composure.

He was not afraid, he was going to die anyway, what is there to be afraid of?

He climbed to the top of the River Swallowing Toad's belly, and lied down face up. Staring at the sky, "Toad, oh toad. You are the same as me, with only one last breath left in you, you're about to die too huh?"

He did not know about the characteristics of the River Swallowing Toad. Looking at its half dead state, he thought that it was going to die. After saying so, Jiang Fan's face flooded with tears.

The River Swallowing Toad squinted its eyes, listening to Jiang Fan's words while staring at the sky.

For the next few days, he continued to lie on the River Swallowing Toad's white and soft belly, crying while talking, complaining about the pain and the repressed feelings of a mortal.

Finally, the deadline was here. The person-in-charge came down from the village to the fishery to collect the fish.

Where could Jiang Fan find fish to meet the quota? Left with no choice, he could only give an excuse that he needed to do some packing, and ran to the River Swallowing Toad to bid farewell.

He patted the River Swallowing Toad's belly, "Old toad, to think that I'm going to die first. It must be affinity that led to me knowing you. I hope that in your remaining days, you will have a better life."

At this moment, the River Swallowing Toad started move.

Jiang Fan was taken aback. Seeing that the River Swallowing Toad's actions were becoming larger, he quickly jumped off.

Plop!

The River Swallowing Toad turned around, with its belly side down and back facing upwards. It had fully woken up.

Jiang Fan's body was drenched, and on having seen this scene he became angry and stomped his foot, "Old toad, oh old toad, so you can still move? Ahhhh, you have caused my death, if you had moved a few days ago, I would not have to die!"

The River Swallowing Toad ignored his words, it had just woken up and felt hungry.

Half of its body was submerged into the water as it opened its mouth, starting to suck in the river water in order to sate its hunger.

Seeing this, Jiang Fan was dumbfounded. He shockingly saw that the water level was receding, dropping at an observable pace, rapidly falling.

Large amounts of river water were swallowed into the toad's belly, but its belly did not even expand a bit, it was almost like a bottomless hole.

A moment later, the River Swallowing Toad stopped its meal. The river water had already dropped to an extreme level, and the bedrock was exposed. If a person stood in the river, the water would only reach their knees.

Jiang Fan stood at the coast, at a lost for words.

The River Swallowing Toad glanced at him and suddenly burped. Its stomach expanded and contracted, its mouth opening wide as it and it vomited out a large amount of seafood.

Fish, prawn, turtle, crab, snails, eels, everything!

The River Swallowing Toad only ate water as its food, but did not consume these seafood, hence it vomited all of them out.

At this point, it seems like it was raining seafood.

In the blink of an eye, the seafood gathered into a mountain, and Jiang Fan upon seeing this, was overwhelming exhilarated. He screamed loudly, "I'm saved, I'm saved! These seafood is enough for me to hand up for three months. Old toad, oh old toad, it is all thanks to you!"

He packaged those seafood, and quickly handed them to the person-in-charge.

The person-in-charge was both shocked and suspicious, how could there be so much? He quickly reported it, and the Gu Masters in the village also found out that the water level had changed drastically.

After investigating, they found out about the River Swallowing Toad's existence.

It was a Rank five Gu!

The village fell into a panic and they formed into large groups, trying to expel the River Swallowing Toad.

Jiang Fan did not want the River Swallowing Toad to be harmed; these days he had treated the River Swallowing Toad as his only friend.

He kneeled in front of the Gu Masters and pleaded hysterically. But why would Gu Masters care about a mere mortal? They kicked him aside and were about to murder him.

But at this moment, the River Swallowing Toad arrived.

Nobody knew if it had treated Jiang Fan as its friend, or felt that being with Jiang Fan was interesting and could cure boredom.

The point is, it struck.

It carried Jiang Fan and vomited out a stream of river water that engulfed the whole village and drowned half the hill.

This battle startled the entire southern continent!

Thereafter, Jiang Fan's name spread throughout the one hundred thousand mountains. With the River Swallowing Toad staying by his side, it meant that he owned a Rank five Gu worm!

After all, even a Rank five Gu Master, might not have a Rank five Gu worm.

Rank five Gu Masters were rare, even in the Gu Yue clan's history, there were only two people—the first generation clan leader and the fourth generation clan leader.

But he Jiang Fan did not have an awakened aperture, yet as a mere mortal he had a River Swallowing Toad.

His existence stunned the entire Gu Master world.

After that, Jiang Fan built a hamlet at the village's location. He was endearing to people and sympathized with mortals, aspiring to reach equality among all people. It was a village without oppression.

He became a flag, and the mortals in the surrounding villages came to him and wanted to depend on him.

But eventually, he was still assassinated.

With just a River Swallowing Toad, it could not make him truly powerful. He was not a Gu Master after all, and after his death, the River Swallowing Toad left.

Gu Masters razed his hamlet to the grounds, and slaughtered the mortals who dared to oppose them.

With his mortal self, Jiang Fan challenged the entire system of society, and that brought forth the rage of the Gu Masters.

"I wonder if Jiang Fan will still appear this time after my influence." After his recollection, Fang Yuan laughed.

But Chi Shan could not laugh.

His face was grim as he returned.

The villagers at the mountain foot were waiting for the Gu Masters to deal with this problem.

But the great Gu Yue Chi Shan arrived and still could not solve the issue. This caused the villagers to panic, and the panic spread and reached a high point.

They dragged their families, brought big and small bags, and rushed up to the village. They naturally did not dare to step inside, thus more and more villagers kneeled outside the village's doors, begging the Gu Masters to have mercy and let them in.

In the hall.

"What? These lowly commoners dare to surround the main gate. Atrocious, they are getting more and more daring, kill, kill them all!" The punishment hall clan elder screamed.

Medicine hall's Gu Yue Yao Ji's face was also grim, "Although these lowly commoners deserve death, killing a few is enough to threaten the rest and chase the group away, but it would be like a joke for the other villages to observe."

Gu Yue Chi Lian said, "The important thing now is not this. If even Chi Shan cannot wake this River Swallowing Toad, who else in our clan can? It seems we have to get reinforcements, the Xiong clan specializes in strength." He sighed and continued, "for the safety of the clan, we should get them to do it. Even if we have to pay a price, it is worth it."

These words got the consent of the other clan elders, and even clan leader Gu Yue Bo was moved.

"Clan leader and the other clan elders, this junior has something to report." Gu Yue Chi Shan had been standing in the hall, listening to the clan elders, but suddenly he bowed and said spoke.

Gu Yue Bo nodded, he had an appreciative attitude towards Gu Yue Chi Shan, "Chi Shan, if you have any ideas, you might as well say it."

Chi Shan asked instead, "Elders, to push this River Swallowing Toad awake, does it really need one person's strength?"

Gu Yue Bo said, "According to the previous clan leader's words, the River Swallowing Toad has a mild temper and loves to sleep. Even if it is awakened by someone pushing it, it would not rage. Thus, we asked you who has the greatest strength in the village to wake it. But it ended in failure."

Chi Shan said, "Then can clan leader grant me a Brute Force Longhorn Beetle Gu? With one bull's strength and my inborn strength, I would be able to push this River Swallowing Toad awake."

"You definitely cannot use a Gu worm's strength." Just as Chi Shan finished speaking, a clan elder denied his request, "A Gu worm's aura will invite the vigilance of the River Swallowing Toad. If this causes it to feel threatened and rampage about, who would face the consequences?"

"That's right." Gu Yue Bo nodded, "By using a Gu worm, even if we wake up the toad, we cannot get its approval. It has to be a single person, using his own strength to wake it and get its approval."

Gu is the spirit of heaven and earth, but it behaved more like wild beasts. Wild beasts have their territories, and roaming wild beasts when encountering the king of a territory, would have a battle. The victorious takes the territory and the loser roams.

The formation of a beast tide is also based on this wild beast instinct. Strong beast groups will invade and conquer neighbouring land. Weaker groups would be exiled and this forms the beast tide.

To chase the River Swallowing Toad away, they have to abide to its habits.

River Swallowing Toad has a mild temperament, not enjoying conflict, and as long as the territory's "beast king" can be recognised, it would leave.

Thus, using Gu worms is a no-no, the Gu worm's aura will be sensed and cause the River Swallowing Toad to take unpredictable actions. Using everyone's strength was not possible too. Once there are many people, even if it is moved, the toad would not leave.

That is because everyone acting together was not fair, and would not be recognised by it.

Thus, the clan leader got Chi Shan to go ahead, as he had the greatest strength in the village.

"So that's it, I understand." Chi Shan finally understood the situation, he cupped his fists, "In that case, I will recommend someone to the clan elders, he has greater strength than me."

"Oh, who?"

"There's such a person, why did we not know?"

"Chi Shan, don't keep us waiting, quickly say it!"

"This person, is Gu Yue Fang Yuan." Chi Shan said a name.

Chapter 119: This lad is stubborn, he needs more polishing

"Gu Yue Fang Yuan?" The elders couldn't help but look at each other upon hearing this name.

They clearly recognized this name. In fact, from the beginning, Gu Yue Fang Yuan's name would occasionally reach their ears.

Especially after the Awakening Ceremony, when his Gu Master cultivation started, this lad had been getting restless; he frequently caused some disturbances that attracted attention.

"Ah, I remember him. Isn't this kid the one who sold his family assets and bought a red steel Relic Gu?" An elder came to realization.

Gu Yue Chi Lian and Gu Yue Mo Chen's faces turned ugly.

If Chi Shan or Mo Yan had used the red steel Relic Gu, they could ascend to rank two peak stage and be equal to Gu Yue Qing Shu.

This would reflect towards the higher-ups—whether it was the Mo faction or Chi faction who got the relic gu, it would be a political victory. But to think that this prodigal kid had ruined it all!

"Returning to the main topic, this kid is truly strong. At the arena previously, he used his bare fists to shatter Jade Skin Gu's defence and pummeled Fang Zheng down, achieving the championship," an elder recalled.

This time, it was the clan head Gu Yue Bo's turn to be embarrassed.

He had especially nurtured Gu Yue Fang Zheng, thus Fang Zheng's defeat—in some sense—was his, the clan head faction's, defeat.

As long as one entered the system, anyone would be labelled with factions. There were neutral political factions, but absolutely not a person without any faction.

"But in terms of power, his strength shouldn't be comparable to yours, right?" Chi Lian doubtfully asked Chi Shan.

Chi San respectfully answered, "Elders, perhaps you might not know, Fang Yuan not only bought red steel Relic Gu, he also purchased a Black Boar Gu. These few months, he has been buying pork to nurture the Black Boar Gu and increase his strength. Once, I even saw him moving a huge rock in the mountain to measure his strength. I am not sure how much strength he has, but from what I have seen, his strength absolutely doesn't lose to mine."

"So it was like that. To think this kid, Fang Yuan has grown to this stage." Gu Yue Bo nodded his head. "Then let's assign Fang Yuan's group to give it a try."

Hearing this, the internal affairs hall elder awkwardly stood up from his seat, "Lord clan head, this Fang Yuan is a loner and hasn't joined a group."

"What is that supposed to mean?" Gu Yue Bo frowned.

"The thing is—after the first beast tide, his group was completely annihilated and the only survivor was him, alone," the internal affairs hall elder replied.

"Even if it is so, why was he not considered during the group reorganizing?" An elder curiously asked.

"Sigh!" The internal affairs hall elder gave a heavy sigh, "I also urged him about this, but he didn't have any intention to join any groups. Honestly speaking, I don't approve of this kid. He is very good at goofing around, it might be that he has lost the will to fight after inheriting that inheritance."

"Goofing around? How can that be, he hasn't joined any groups so how could he complete the monthly clan missions?" An elder doubted.

The internal affairs hall elder's face sank, "Every month, he receives the compulsory mission but the results are all failure. I haven't seen records worse than his; almost all the missions are recorded as failures. I have already tried talking with him several times, but he still wants to continue in his way, without any repenting. However, he hasn't violated the clan rules, so I can only give light punishments to this unruly and crafty kid!"

The elders looked at each other; they had never seen such a younger generation who didn't want to advance forward.

Mission failures represented a narrower career progression within the clan.

"This kid has become muddled.....""Hmph, he is too unruly!""He is destroying his own future!""If I had such an indolent child, I would directly slap him to death!"

"Enough." Gu Yue Bo raised his hand, putting a stop to the elders' private chats; one couldn't tell if he was happy or angry.

Gu Yue Bo's gaze moved around and finally stopped on the internal affairs hall elder, "Send a compulsory command, let Gu Yue Fang Yuan try his strength on River Swallowing Toad. This kid is stubborn, rebellious and unruly, he needs to be polished. If he fails, we can use this pretext to give some punishments."

"It will be as lord clan head says." The internal affairs hall elder promptly agreed.

There was a racket in the tavern.

"Do you guys know, the clan sent the Chi Shan group to the foot of the mountain but they ended up returning in defeat.""The villagers living at the foot of the mountain are all kneeling in front of the clan's entrance, blocking the gate.""Hmph, these lowly commoners don't even have a bit of knowledge. River Swallowing Toad is a Rank five Gu, do they really think they will be safe in the village?"

Although this was said, the air was dense with panic. These Gu Masters were all forcefully calming themselves.

Fang Yuan listened for a short moment before no longer paying attention; this was no longer fresh news. He stood up and was about to leave when a person entered the tavern.

This person was tall with a thickly built body. The upper half of his body was naked and his muscles were the color of bright red, seemingly wanting to erupt.

It was Gu Yue Chi Shan.The chatters within the tavern immediately stopped. Countless gazes landed on Chi Shan.

Chi Shan ignored these gazes; he glanced around and found Fang Yuan.

"You were here." Under the numerous gazes, he walked in front of Fang Yuan, "Let's go, the clan has already given a compulsory order. Let's head to the foot of the mountain, I will tell you the details on the way."

Fang Yuan's gaze flashed, he couldn't refuse a compulsory order. Moreover, there was not much danger when facing the River Swallowing Toad, thus he agreed.

Only after Fang Yuan and Chi Shan left the tavern did the racket start again in the tavern.

"Shopkeeper, the heavens have eyes. Look at this, such a quick karmic retribution! That is a Rank five Gu, even other lord Gu Masters are helpless facing it, whereas he is so young, isn't this just losing his life in vain?!"

"We thought Young Master Fang Yuan was different from other Gu Masters and would empathize with us mortals' pain and sufferings. Hmph, to think he would also be of the same mould. Screw him, we wouldn't have any regrets even if he dies."

"Shopkeeper, you didn't suffer this wound in vain, getting a Gu Master's life for it is absolutely a profit."

The old shopkeeper's head was bound with circles of white bandages. Right now, he continued to groan, leaning weakly against the corner.

Several waiters were by his side, consoling him.

The old man's eyes flashed with resentment, but his mood slightly eased up upon hearing these words.

However, after a while of listening, he hypocritically berated them in a low voice, "Shut your mouths, is this something we can talk of? Aren't you afraid of losing your lives if the other Gu Masters hear it?!"

The waiters giggled, "Shopkeeper, you are too worried. It is so noisy in the tavern, who could have heard our whisperings?"

They had just said this, when a Gu Master sitting nearest to them spoke, "I heard it."

The shopkeeper and the waiters' complexion changed greatly; they were extremely terrified.

"Lord..." The old shopkeeper ignored the dizzy feeling in his head and hurriedly walked towards the Gu Master to ask for forgiveness.

This Gu Master raised his hand and stopped him.

"You all spoke very well, I liked what you said. Fang Yuan, this bastard, even if he dies, it shouldn't be regretted! Speak more, I will give you great rewards if I like what you say!" The Gu Master took out a primeval stone and slammed it on the table with a bang.

If Fang Yuan was here, he would recognize this person. This person was that healing Gu Master of the previous small beast tide. Fang Yuan had used the girl this Gu Master sought after as a shield to cover his body. Thus, this Gu Master had a deep hatred towards Fang Yuan and it was irreconcilable.

The waiters looked at each other. One of them with more guts started staring at the primeval stone on the table with wide-eyes.

The Gu Master's three companions frowned, but didn't stop him. They could only listen to the waiters scolding Fang Yuan as if they were in a competition.

It was early autumn and the scenery was good.

In the forests, some leaves were of dark shade and some were of light. Green leaves had started changing to yellow and yellow leaves faintly showed red.

In the paddy field, fields of yellow-orange rice crops waved along with the autumn wind.

In some lush vegetable fields, the vegetable leaves were fat, tender and pleasing.

Fang Yuan sped all the way from the middle of the mountain, following the Chi Shan group down to the foot of the mountain where he saw the Rank five River Swallowing Toad.

It was huge and resembled a small hill. It lay belly side up in the riverbed and blocked the river channel. The upstream of the river was already filled with so much water that it was almost spilling to the riverside. And there was almost no flow of the river downstream; only a shallow moist riverbed could be seen.

The River Swallowing Toad's belly was exquisite snow-white and was covered with a layer of luster. Its back was clear sky blue color and also had a glossy shine to it, with no warts like the ones found in common frogs and toads.

It was sound asleep at this moment. But there were no sounds of snoring; it was sleeping very quietly.

Sensing its aura, the two Liquor worms in Fang Yuan's aperture curled up into a ball. The Black Boar Gu's lively appearance seemed to have been wiped out as it flew down. The Moonglow Gu that resided in his right palm hid its glow.

Only the Spring Autumn Cicada was still sleeping peacefully.

Fang Yuan withdrew the Moonglow Gu into his aperture. As long as he didn't take the initiative to use these Gu, their aura wouldn't leak out. Putting them in the aperture was very safe and reliable.

"Fang Yuan, it's your turn next," Chi Shan spoke from the side.

He had already explained most of the details on the way.

Fang Yuan also approved of this method. Of course, the simplest way was to use Spring Autumn Cicada; once a Rank six Gu worm's aura leaked out, this River Swallowing Toad would be frightened and immediately flee.

This was also because the River Swallowing Toad didn't like fighting. If it was a vicious Gu like the Blood River Python, Spring Autumn Cicada's aura would instead cause it to go berserk and retaliate madly.

Fang Yuan stood at the riverside, trying out to push at first. The River Swallowing Toad's skin was slippery, making one feel that his strength has been nullified.

In addition, it was extremely heavy, one simply couldn't even budge it.

"Can you do it?" Chi Cheng sneered from the side.

Fang Yuan ignored him and said to Chi Shan, "Although I have the increased strength from Black Boar Gu, my strength is probably only a little more than yours. As for pushing this River Swallowing Toad, it is not hopeless, but I need your help."

"What help?" Chi Shan immediately asked.

Fang Yuan slowly explained it. Chi Shan was doubtful, "If we do this, wouldn't it be teaming up? Even if the River Swallowing Toad wakes up, will it still acknowledge you and then willingly leave?"

Fang Yuan smiled, "You don't have to worry about it. As long as you guys keep a distance and not let it detect you, it will be possible. After all, it is a Gu, don't think it as too intelligent."

Chapter 120: Literally effortless

At the height of autumn, the air was refreshing, and the breeze moderately flowed under the beautiful sun.

The blue dome of heaven was clean and clear like a crystal.

The wind blew gently, brushing Fang Yuan's appearance into motion.

Looking from afar, the nearby villages had little people. Nearby, the hill-like River Swallowing Toad was slumbering, blocking the river bed. Fang Yuan who was standing at the river edge looked like a tiny monkey beside a large elephant in comparison to this Rank five Gu.

Fang Yuan's heart was calm as water, without a trace of nervousness, thinking internally, "I used the White Boar Gu and the Black Boar Gu to enhance my body and raise my strength, having the strength of two boars. Together with my own strength, I have around the strength of five or six adults. But to push this River Swallowing Toad, I need to have around two bull's strength. With just my current strength, it will not do. But, if I borrow the power of the tides... it's here."

Swish swish swish...

Fang Yuan turned his body around and saw that waves were crashing and approaching, causing a huge movement in the peaceful river water.

The tides got bigger and continually crashed against the River Swallowing Toad, causing the waves to fly high into the sky.

Fang Yuan only stood for a while before he got drenched.

He did not mind it, and began to push the River Swallowing Toad with vigor.

The River Swallowing Toad was still dead asleep. It was originally a Gu worm that lived in the rivers and sea, and to it, the force of the waves was normal and could not awaken it.

With the force of endless waves, Fang Yuan tried for some time and finally managed to push the River Swallowing Toad away from its original location.

The riverbed was wider as the river got downstream. Along with the flow of water, it made Fang Yuan's pushing easier.

After about three hundred meters, the River Swallowing Toad opened its sleepy eyes.

A pair of deep green eyes, in its sleepy state, gradually contracted and stared at Fang Yuan who was beside it.

Fang Yuan was fearless as he matched its gaze.

From its dark eerie eyes, Fang Yuan could see his own reflection.

"Jiangaaaang!" River Swallowing Toad raised its head, suddenly opening its mouth and emitting a strange croak.

The cry spread out and reverbed throughout Qing Mao mountain.

At once, Fang Yuan could feel his ears going deaf from the ringing noise.

River Swallowing Toad lowered its head, its mouth sucking at the river water that was approaching.

Swish swish swish!

The river water flowed at ten times the original speed as it was all sucked into its stomach, and the water level could be seen decreasing at an observable pace.

Fang Yuan stood beside the River Swallowing Toad, clearly seeing a large amount of seafood also being sent into the River Swallowing Toad's stomach along with the river water.

Sensing the river water's change, the Chi Shan group also hurried over, and as the three observed the River Swallowing Toad who was ingesting water, they were stunned.

"What a spectacular sight!" Chi Cheng observed, unable to hide his shock.

"You succeeded?" Chi Shan looked at Fang Yuan.

"Seems so," Fang Yuan nodded lightly.

The water level decreased until the water stopped flowing, and the River Swallowing Toad raised its head once again, its stomach expanding and contracting, vomiting out numerous fish, prawns, turtles etc.

At once, a large amount of seafood fell onto the ground, emitting a crisp sound.

A fish splashed on the ground, a turtle fell on its back confused, the crabs walked away horizontally, and then they were smashed by the falling seafood.

Fang Yuan did not mind it and only looked casually, but suddenly he smelt some wine fragrance.

"Strange, why is there a wine smell?" Chi Cheng sniffed, a face of surprise.

"It should be the Hundred year bitter shell," the female Gu Master in the group said and pointed at a disc-sized broken black shell.

This shell was black as ink with white round markings on it, like the rings in a tree trunk.

"That's right, bitter shell can turn the sand and rocks into bitter water juice. Hundred year bitter shell's bitter water, after the accumulation through time, can turn into wine. Bai clan's current clan leader loves to drink this bitter shell wine," Chi Shan added on.

He needn't go into detail; Fang Yuan had already long taken up this seashell, starting to collect his bitter shell wine.

Not too long ago, he was still worried about how to get this bitter shell wine, but to think it appeared in front of him like this.

Truly the phrase 'spending lots of effort looking for something fruitlessly, but it appears in front of you when least expected'!

The River Swallowing Toad had pretty much swallowed all the water in this river. Deep in the river bed, there had been some Hundred year bitter shells buried in the soil, and because of the River Swallowing Toad, the shells were exposed.

Fang Yuan quickly collected six little Hundred year bitter shells. Two of the shells were broken, but the other four were intact.

"I've finally collected the bitter wine, this way, I can start refining the Four Flavor Liquor worm!" This moment, Fang Yuan was overjoyed, but had no one to share the joy with.

"Jiangang!"

After the River Swallowing Toad vomited the seafood, it croaked again, and then looked at Fang Yuan once before moving its large body to swim downstream along the river.

"He really succeeded!" Chi Shan muttered, his heart feeling relief. He observed the River Swallowing Toad leaving until its shadow was completely gone, away from his vision.

"What, he scared it away so easily. If I knew this earlier on, we could've done it ourselves, but now we let Fang Yuan become a hero so easily!" Chi Cheng pouted, his tone full of jealousy and indignance.

"Fang Yuan, no matter what, this time you have done a good deed, you are the Gu Yue Clan's hero!" Chi Shan stared at Fang Yuan with a complicated expression.

"Oh," Fang Yuan replied absent-mindedly, giving a half-hearted feeling. At the same time, his gaze shone as he continued to rummage and search for Hundred year bitter shells among the seafood.

What hero, it was merely a title.

Between praise and slander, they were all views and expressions of others onto oneself.

What opinions others had of him, Fang Yuan did not give a damn.

You can think all you want, I live my own life.

Hero? Zero? Hehe, I rather have a bitter shell.

News of chasing away the River Swallowing Toad reached the village at once.

Gu Yue Bo said "Good" three times continuously, and the solemnness in the hall was swept away at once.

Only the internal affairs elder's face was complicated, he did not think well of Fang Yuan. Not too long ago, he even criticized Fang Yuan, but now that the village was in danger, Fang Yuan was the one who resolved the issue. With these two issues coming together, wasn't it a slap in his face?

"Gu Yue Fang Yuan has the credit of chasing away the River Swallowing Toad, we'll make an exception to promote him to team leader and reward him five hundred primeval stones."Gu Yue Bo thought, before giving the order filled with a special meaning.

In the wine tavern.

"What, Fang Yuan actually succeeded?!"

"Strange, he's just a newbie, how can he chase away a Rank five Gu worm?"

"Even Chi Shan failed miserably, but he did it..."

The news spread, and everyone was filled with shock.

"Fang Yuan became the savior of our clan? This..." The male Gu Master who had animosity with Fang Yuan was lost for action after hearing this news.

His group leader suddenly shouted, pointing at the clerks in the tavern, "You mere mortals, you dare to slander our clan's hero, you deserve execution!"

Even before finishing his words, he shot a moonblade.

The elderly shopkeeper did not expect that such a life-threatening situation would occur, and after being hit by this moonblade on his neck, he was beheaded.

"Lord, spare us!" The clerks upon seeing this were first stunned but quickly kneeled on the ground, begging for mercy loudly.

"Group leader, what are you doing?" The Male Gu Master stood up.

"What am I doing huh?" His group leader moved his brows, sighing solemnly, "Times have changed, Ah Hai. Fang Yuan has turned into a hero suddenly, the higher-ups will pay attention to him. If words of our slander towards him spread, what do you think will happen? There are lots of detection-type Gu Masters around, and if someone wants to harm us and said several bad things to the clan elders, our future would be ruined!"

The male Gu Master broke out in cold sweat from fear.

It was indeed like this, clan relationships ruled above all. Fang Yuan had gone and dealt with a Rank five Gu worm, risking his life to defend his clan. At the same time he was slandered and insulted by them. What mindset was this? This was ungratefulness, coldness, emotionless and utter disregard for relationships!

Like history on Earth, Yue Fei fought in the battlefields, defending his country, but Qin Hui framed him as a spy in court.

Although these Gu Masters did not go as severe as framing, but if this matter was spread out, would the higher-ups feel safe with these people around?

If it was Mo Yan or Chi Cheng, people with tough backgrounds, that would still be alright. But these few were people without backing.

Trying to climb up the system's ladder, it was push and shove, stepping on each other. If others used this incident and attacked them, to their future, it had a destructive influence!

"It is still not too late to salvage the situation, we just have to express our attitudes, and outsiders won't say much. These mortals have cheap lives, so be it if they die. But they can be sacrifices for us, and this is their honor. You guys should immediately strike, each one of you must kill one each. After killing you should praise Fang Yuan and express our stand!" the group leader shouted.

"Dammit!" The male Gu Master cursed; between hatred and his future, he unhesitantly chose the latter.

With a moonblade, a clerk died on the spot.

"Lord, please spare us." At once, all the other clerks were paralyzed on the ground, scared until they peed their pants.

The male Gu Master did not care about them, and under everyone's watchful gaze, he pointed at these pitiful clerks righteously, shouting, "You lot deserve death. Gu Yue Fang Yuan is a hero, and with his own strength, he defended the clan, what gave you the courage to slander him!"

The male Gu Master said this while frowning.

This was his true emotion. Fang Yuan was someone he deeply hated, but he had to praise him in public; he felt a strong sense of disgust and irk for himself.

"Lord, didn't you ask us.... Urgh!" A clerk felt feelings of injustice deeply, shouting out loudly.

But he could not finish his sentence before he stopped.

A moonblade went flying, splitting him in half.

"A bunch of lowly slaves, not only slandering Fang Yuan, but also wanting to implicate us!" A female Gu Master struck, her expression cold as she shouted fiercely.

Other Gu Masters seeing this, felt like they were watching a soap opera.

Some smirked, some were indifferent and some continued chatting, but nobody stopped them.

So what if a few mortals died?

Just compensating a few family servants would do.

Everyone was part of the clan, they were family. No one would interfere or pursue the matter for these outsiders, causing conflict for themselves.

Chapter 121: Four Flavours Liquor worm

"Gu Yue Clan...." Xiong Li stood at the mountainside and gazed at the distant Gu Yue village; a complicated expression on his face.

Cool autumn wind was breezing gently.

The color of autumn dyed the mountain.

Tree leaves were a mix of yellow and red, with wild fruits growing all over the place. Only the Qing Mao bamboo remained green and erect.

"Not long ago, Gu Yue Clan was like these Qing Mao bamboo, evergreen all the year, the overlord of Qing Mao mountain. Now, they are actually falling behind," Xiong Li's lips curved with a cold mocking smile.

But quickly, he thought of the Bai village and the curve of his lips smoothed out; his mood turned serious.

Bai village's uprising had already broken the old balance of Qing Mao mountain. The traditional hedgemon, the Gu Yue clan had weakened; Xiong village's operations were not running properly; all these were pushing the situation in the Qing Mao mountain towards an upheaval.

Xiong Li knew this upheaval hadn't erupted yet because of the pressure from the wolf tide. The three villages needed to collaborate if they wanted to overcome this wolf tide, thus they tacitly maintained peace and threw away grievances for the time being.

"Once the wolf tide is gone, Qing Mao mountain's old structure will be shattered. Bai Ning Bing has already reached Rank three in only a couple of years. It's really terrifying....." Xiong Li recalled the figure of a white-clothed youth, and he felt stifled as if he was pressed down by a huge rock.

He, Xiong Li, was the top amongst the Xiong village's Rank two Gu Masters. He had fought all sorts of battles and won most of them, establishing his name. He held the Grand Bear Gu and could erupt with a bear's strength. He was also known as the strongest person in Qing Mao mountain.

He had already made his debut and had personally seen the rocket-like emergence of Bai Ning Bing, so he was clearer than others regarding the terror of this youth.

"Group leader, that is Gu Yue village! It's still far away, why are we stopping here?" From the side, Xiong Lin raised his two hands and clasped them behind his head as he curiously asked.

In this five-person group, Xiong Lin was the youngest and was a newbie who just made his debut. He was the same age as Fang Yuan and was this year's top genius of Xiong village.

His stature was short and he had shaved his head which seemed to shine under the sunlight.

Xiong Li looked at this new talent of the clan, his heavy mood eased up a little. He answered in a deep voice, "We are here on a diplomatic mission and not on a scouting mission. This area is already the warning area of the Gu Yue clan, and we will probably be treated as enemies if we boldly enter."

"Oh, so it was like that." Xiong Lin realized.

"We have two objectives this time. One is to hand the clan head's personal letter to Gu Yue's clan head. Another is to investigate the matter regarding the River Swallowing Toad. Gu Yue village is not our area, so make sure to keep your temper in check when we get there. However, you absolutely can't degrade the prestige of our Xiong village, understood?" Xiong Li's gaze swept all around and shouted.

The rest of the Gu Master's expressions all turned serious and silently nodded.

"Group leader, someone's here," the scouting Gu Master in the group suddenly spoke.

"We have revealed our movements for so long, they should be here by now. But who would it be... hmm? So it was Chi Shan." Soon after, Xiong Li also discovered Chi Shan group; his eyes flashed.

"Wow! That person is so tall, is he Chi Shan? He is even taller than the group leader. Such muscles, piece by piece... group leader, isn't he the guy born with super strength who has been trying to seize the title of the strongest person of the Qing Mao mountain?" Xiong Lin immediately looked straight at Chi Shan.

"Hmph, it had to be him....." Xiong Jiang spoke gloomily and twisted her lips in disdain.

"Xiong Li!"

"Chi Shan."

The two groups were fifty steps apart from each other. The two group leaders came face to face, their gazes clashed in the air and seemed to form sparks."Looks like you are Xiong village's special envoy this time," Chi Shan snorted coldly; he had fought many times with Xiong Li.

"That's right. Has the special envoy from the Bai village arrived?" Xiong Li's expression steeled up.

"Why ask so much? Follow me," Chi Shan cautiously turned and invited.

Meanwhile.In the second secret room, four wine jars were in front of Fang Yuan.

Sour, sweet, bitter and spicy, four flavors of wine. Sweet belonged to golden honey wine; spicy was white grains liquid; sour came from redberry wine; bitter was from bitter shell wine.

Fang Yuan sat cross-legged on the ground. He then willed the two Liquor worms to fly out of his aperture.

The fusion process of Four Flavours Liquor worm was slightly different from normal fusion.

The two Liquor worms followed Fang Yuan's will and entered the redberry wine jar.

They started the fusion within the redberry wine. A white ball of light formed in the wine jar, its majestic light pierced out of the wine jar and shone on the wall.

Fang Yuan threw primeval stones in the wine jar; one piece, ten pieces, fifty pieces.....

When it reached the hundredth piece, the light ball shrunk to a fist's size and floated in the wine jar.

The redberry wine was completely used up. Fang Yuan picked the second wine jar—golden honey wine—and poured it into the jar.

The white ball of light was immersed in the honey wine, suddenly swelling up to its original size.

Fang Yuan's head was soaked with sweat; he was constantly maintaining the fusion of the two Liquor worms' consciousness, and such multitasking was extremely taxing on the mind.

He continued to throw primeval stones towards the wine jar.

Every piece of primeval stones caused the ball of light to shrink by a bit, until it condensed to a fist's size again, reaching its limit.

Fang Yuan followed the pattern and successively poured the bitter shell wine, then the white grains liquid.

When the four types of wine were completely used up, the light in the wine jar suddenly flourished before disappearing completely.

"Success." Fang Yuan knew he had succeeded without even looking in the wine jar.

He willed and a Gu shakingly flew out of the wine jar.

It was the Four Flavours Liquor worm.

Comparing it with the Liquor worm, there wasn't much change in its external form, except that it was slightly bigger.

It also resembled a silkworm and had a tiny pair of shiny black eyes.

The difference was that the Liquor worm's body was completely white, but this Four Flavours Liquor worm's body continuously flickered with four colors; red representing spicy, blue representing bitter, green representing sour and yellow representing sweet. Fang Yuan couldn't help but associate it with the neon lights on Earth.

"Huff..." Fang Yuan let out a big sigh of relief. His luck was good this time and didn't encounter failure, succeeding the first time.

If it failed, the Liquor worms could suffer serious damage and one of them could even die, or the bitter shell wine might be used up. Either of these outcomes would be troublesome.

Fortunately, this situation didn't occur.

A Gu Master needs to use, nurture and refine Gu; none of them were easy. And in the aspect of fusing Gu worms, many Gu Masters would go through a lot to look for recipes and collect materials.

There were various recipes and they might not necessarily be suitable. As for collecting materials, Gu Masters might even spend over ten years of efforts on it. Even if they find the recipe and collect all the materials, if the fusion failed, the materials would be used up, and all their previous efforts and preparations would go down the drain.

"Gu Master's cultivation is difficult....." Fang Yuan sighed.

Fusing Gu worms were easy at the beginning stage of the cultivation. But the success rate for Rank four and Rank five fusion would often not reach even one in ten times.

Rank six fusion success rate was even as low as one percent. Every failure when fusing high rank Gu worms meant a loss of a great sum of resources.

However, once succeeded, the benefits would be extremely high.

Taking Fang Yuan's newly refined Four Flavours Liquor worm into account, it could refine Rank two primeval essence and increase it by a small realm.

Fang Yuan used a red steel Relic Gu to advance to middle stage. Now, with the Four Flavours Liquor worm, he would have upper stage primeval essence.

His fighting strength was now doubled. At the same time, the Four Flavours Liquor worm would nourish his aperture which meant faster cultivation speed.

However, with advantages comes disadvantages.

Using the Four Flavours Liquor worm to refine his primeval essence would definitely lead to an increased consumption of primeval stones. Just by relying on the income from selling vitality leaves was already not enough to maintain his cultivation expenditure.

"Next, I need to fuse the Stealth Rock Gu into Stealth Scales Gu. This will add on to another expenditure."

Fusion, whether success or failure, used up primeval stones every time. Fang Yuan had used up over four hundred primeval stones earlier for refining the Four Flavours Liquor worm.

The clan had awarded him with five hundred primeval stones for chasing away the River Swallowing Toad. Five hundred primeval stones was enough for other Gu Masters to spend for a long while, but Fang Yuan had almost used it completely.

Fortunately, from the reselling of the assets, after using up most of it to purchase the red steel Relic Gu, some of it still remained. There was no need to worry for a short period of time.

But it was necessary to refine the Scales Stealth Gu.

Fang Yuan had obtained the Stealth Rock Gu after he killed the stone monkey king. However, it had no practical use.

It could only conceal the body. That meant, once Fang Yuan used it, his body would be concealed and be invisible to people.

But the clothes on his body—his wrist guards, leg wrappings and bamboo shoes would still be visible to the naked eyes.

The stone monkey king had no worries about this; it was a wild beast and didn't need clothes.

But Fang Yuan would be in an awkward situation. To use the Stealth Rock Gu to the best of its ability and be invisible, he would need to take of all the clothes on his body. Otherwise, even if he concealed his body, others would see a set of 'walking' Rank two Gu Master's uniform.

Stealth Rock Gu was a Rank one Gu worm. Once it advanced to Rank two Stealth Scales Gu, this problem would be resolved.

Stealth Scales Gu could conceal even the clothes. If the stone monkey king had Stealth Scales Gu, then even if Fang Yuan's shirt covered its body, the shirt would also become invisible.

Supposing that the stone monkey king had Stealth Scales Gu, then the matter of whether Fang Yuan could defeat it was rather suspenseful.

Refining a Stealth Scales Gu naturally required other materials other than the Stealth Rock Gu. These materials were quite common and Fang Yuan had already requested Jiang Ya's help to gather them.

"If I could refine Stealth Scales Gu, it will become very convenient for me to enter the secret cave. Moreover, during the wolf tide, I could easily attack and retreat with this method," Fang Yuan pondered.

It was getting late, he retrieved the Four Flavours Liquor worm into his aperture and exited the cave, walking towards the village.

He had instantly attracted a lot of attention after successfully chasing away the River Swallowing Toad. It was not easy moving about these days, so he was slightly worried that if he stayed for long in the secret cave, people would harbor suspicions.

At the village gate, a bout of strength contest had concluded.

Xiong Li's group was proudly standing whereas Chi Shan's group along with the Gu Masters guarding the gate had heavy faces.

Xiong Li wasn't as tall as Chi Shan but his gaze seemed to be overlooking everything at this moment. He slowly spoke, "Chi Shan, you are indeed blessed with super strength. But I have Brown Bear Innate Strength Gu and I possess the strength of a bear. You saw from the battle just now that you are still not my match."

"Hmph, wanting to get the title of the strongest in Qing Mao mountain, dream on," Xiong Jiang sneered from the side.

Chi Shen's face was ashen, he knew the other party had intentionally challenged him and their conduct was filled with political intentions. His loss now was no longer just his personal affair; rather, it was tarnishing Gu Yue clan's name.

"What are you being proud over defeating me? You don't know that I am no longer the strongest person in the clan. If you have skills, then speak after defeating Fang Yuan," Chi Shan had no choice but to mention Fang Yuan.

"Oh, Fang Yuan? I heard an A grade genius emerged in Gu Yue clan and his name was Fang Zheng. But who is this Fang Yuan?" Xiong Li asked, doubtfully.

Chi Shan sneered, "Fang Yuan is Fang Zheng's older brother, he is also blessed with innate super strength and similarly possesses a strength-increasing Gu worm. Previously, he alone pushed the Rank five River Swallowing Toad over a hundred meters, finally driving it away. If you don't believe me, you can ask anyone in the village."Xiong Li group's expressions couldn't help but change.Rank five River Swallowing Toad!Fang Yuan!

This name was instantly engraved in their minds.

Chapter 122: There are many blizzards in life

Whizzzz!

Three face-sized moonblades slashed through the air, carrying an eerie blue light.

Screeeech!

Instantly, sixteen to seventeen jade eye stone monkeys were killed on the spot.

The stone monkey groups chasing after Fang Yu were instantly cut down by a small half.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot and didn't retreat. Instead, he lifted his right hand and slashed the air three times.

Three moonblades ran through the stone monkey group, beheading any stone monkey in its way.

The corpses of the stone monkeys fell on the ground, shattering into countless pieces. Their eyes turned into jade pearls and rolled on the blood-filled ground.

Fang Yuan inspected his aperture; he still had greater half of dark red primeval essence remaining.

The Moonglow Gu required ten percent of light red primeval essence to use a moonblade. Fang Yuan could only use four moonblades repeatedly at Rank two initial stage. The number increased to eight when he reached the middle stage. And at the upper stage, the number doubled once more, reaching sixteen.

Fang Yuan wasn't really at Rank two upper stage, but with the Four Flavours Liquor worm's refining of upper stage primeval essence, he could be considered to be at false upper stage; his fighting strength was rising sharply.

Before, he would have needed to fight while retreating when chased by these seventy or eighty stone monkeys. Now, he just attacked with the moonblades, rapidly killing most of them. The remaining stone monkeys had escaped.

"I cleared up three stone pillars within just two days. This speed is many times faster than before! If this goes on, I will be able to re-open a path to the central area in about half a month," Fang Yuan pondered.

"From the Flower Wine Monk's style, the underground cave in the central pillar should be the next barrier. It is very likely that there will be another Earth Treasure Flower Gu at the barrier. I reckon the Flower Wine Monk's strength inheritance is almost over. After all, he was seriously injured and his state was far from good, thus he hurriedly set up this inheritance. At most, there will probably be two more obstacles remaining."

Fang Yuan recalled the scene on the image wall; the blood-soaked Flower Wine Monk on his last breath. With his previous life's deep experience, he reached this conclusion.

Flower Wine Monk had too little time to set up this legacy, there was no way for him to do more. However, this was a special case.

Gu Masters normally used years to set up their legacies. There were some large scaled legacies that would only open once every ten or more years. Some legacies were even divided and scattered across different areas and could even be at the different ends of the world.

The latter generations would need ten or more years or even decades of time to go through all the tests of such legacies.

Some legacies might not even be explored completely throughout a Gu Master's life; the Gu Master would often leave this incomplete task for their descendants.

"Flower Wine Monk's inheritance can be classified as a micro-scale legacy; its shortcoming being the small amount of inheritance items. But this also has its advantage—the first barrier is arranged according to the local conditions and is thus simple. I have successively obtained White Boar Gu, Jade Skin Gu and Liquor worm from this inheritance. Stealth Stone Gu can be barely considered as the inheritance. Next, there are probably only two more earth treasure flowers remaining. I hope that the Gu worms in them will be related to scouting or movement-type!"

Time passed quickly, autumn went and winter arrived.

Early winter, the first snowfall had come.

The sky was grey, snowflakes floated and fell on Qing Mao mountain.

Fang Yuan was moving alone through the snow. He had just come out from the secret cave in the stone crack and was hurrying towards the village.

"Over two months have passed, but my progress in clearing the stone pillars has not been good." Fang Yuan's countenance carried a dark scowl.

It was not because he hadn't put in effort, but rather the prelude to the wolf tide had already shown its signs.

Food was scarce during the winter; the growing wolf packs started to increase their hunting scale to gather enough foods to eat their fill.

The wild beast groups in the surroundings were purged due to this. Small beast tides frequently started to occur due to the disorder; similarly, there were also the crippled wolf packs.

These crippled wolves were expelled from the nest. These wolves gathered together and formed a group; they had started making frequent movements near the village.

It hadn't reached the wild stage of attacks on the village yet, but the hunter families no longer went up the mountain to hunt. Similarly, there were occasionally some villagers who lost their lives to the wolves.

Gu Yue village mobilized many Gu Masters to carry out a clean-up operation. Due to this, there were many people moving about, along with lot of scouting Gu Masters among them. Thus, Fang Yuan sensibly decreased the amount of times he went to the secret cave inside the stone crack.

No doubt, this caused the speed of his progress in the stone forest to fall steeply.

The cold wind was getting stronger; snow was also falling heavily.

Houuuuu...

A deep beastly howl suddenly spread through the wind and snow.

Fang Yuan swiftly stopped and looked around, alert.

A small scale wolf pack with about twenty or more lightning wolves quickly appeared in range of his sight.

"Here we go again....." Fang Yuan muttered, this was already the eighth beast group he had encountered this month.

However, this time was somewhat different.

"The wolf packs are starting to make their moves so near to the village. Next, the clan's Gu Masters will make their moves more often. The stone crack's secret cave is not far away; looks like I can't go there for some time." Fang Yuan's heart sank upon this thought.

The journey was difficult, there would always be some obstacles preventing people from progressing.

The wolf pack closed in on Fang Yuan.

Houuu! Houuu! Houuu!

They howled before charging at Fang Yuan, coming at him one after another.

"Moonglow Gu," Fang Yuan willed; a moonblade flew out from his hand.

The eerie blue moonblade slashed through the wind and snow, going through the sickly wolves. It instantly beheaded three wolves, but when it reached the fourth wolf, the wolf suddenly rolled and cleverly dodged the moonblade.

Although most of these crippled wolves were handicapped, blind or missing their tails, they had plenty of battle experience and were very cunning.

A normal Rank two middle stage Gu Master would be in intense danger if they ran into such a group of crippled wolves and especially if they were surrounded by these wolves.

But Fang Yuan was calm.

His plentiful battle experience and the refined upper stage dark red primeval essence were the source of his confidence.

Kill, kill, kill!

He nimbly moved under the joint attacks from the crippled wolves, calmly dodging and decisively attacking.

The wolves continued to die by his hands.

After a short while, the number of the lightning wolves in the pack had sharply decreased by half.

Houuu—!

A wolf gave a mournful howl; the wolf pack immediately stopped their offensive attacks and began retreating.

This was the cunningness of these wolves.

When they discovered that Fang Yuan was a tough bone, they decisively retreated, giving up their plan to hunt Fang Yuan.

These old, sickly and injured wolves weren't in a perfect state but being able to live till now showed their survival wisdom.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot, calmly looking at these crippled wolves disappearing into the wind and snow. If he could hide his strength, then he didn't feel it necessary to reveal it.

After confirming that the wolf pack had completely escaped, he promptly collected the items on the wolf corpses.

Wolf skin, teeth and so on were all valuable.

Although their market price was on the low end, it could be made up by the quantity.

In these two months, Fang Yuan had made some earnings from the spoils of war from eradicating these crippled wolves.

The blood flowing from the wolf corpses were still warm. There were some crippled wolves who still had some breath left, their eyes showing a trace of vigor.

"In this world, not only humans but all living things are struggling to survive. This world is using life and death to unfold a brilliant stage!" Fang Yuan sighed before ruthlessly killing off these dying wolves.

A crippled wolf's fighting strength was higher than two jade eye stone monkeys. Under the coordination with the pack, their fighting strength would double.

"I can still deal with these small-scale crippled wolf packs. But it would be troublesome to handle large scale crippled wolf packs or a small scale healthy wolf pack."

Fang Yuan could feel a faint pressure.

"The wolf tide will break out soon and the whole clan will be mobilized. I won't be able to act aloof. If I want to hunt the lightning wolves by myself, I must have a scouting or movement-type gu. Otherwise, I will fall to the wolf tide."

Fang Yuan clearly recognized his shortcomings due to his ample experience.

His fighting strength had increased sharply after getting the Four Flavours Liquor worm. With the Moonglow Gu and Jade Skin Gu, he had both offense and defense. With his previous life's deep accumulation, he could totally be ranked along with Qing Shu, Chi Shan and Mo Yan.

One could say, he was barely, but already able to stand in the top ranks among the Rank two Gu Masters of the clan.

Why it was barely, was because he was not truly at the upper stage, and at the same time his aptitude was also only C grade and was thus very limited.

Being able to accomplish this much with his fighting strength was already the best result, but fighting strength was only one aspect in surviving the wolf tide.

"I must have a scouting method. If I have a scouting Gu worm, I will be able to sense the movements of the wolf pack and quickly retreat or move through another route. Or use movement-type Gu worms to quickly run and escape from the wolf pack's besiegement," Fang Yuan pondered.

His survival rate would greatly increase if he had just one of these two Gu worms. If he had both, then he would be able to move about easily.

"I hope Flower Wine Monk's legacy contains such Gu worms. It's not a problem even if it doesn't. From my memories, the three clans would jointly establish contributions list during the wolf tides and put their stored Gu worms out for exchange. There were many precious Gu in the list. At that time, I can use my contributions and exchange them for Bai or Xiong village's Gu worms."

Fang Yuan planned in his mind and stood up.

He had swiftly arranged the spoils of war in a short period and packed them in a bag which he then carried on his back.

The snow continued to fall and soon froze the wolf blood, covering their corpses.

"Look, Fang Yuan is back.""He is carrying a bag, did he go out to hunt the crippled wolves again?""It was him that saved our village?"

"Hey, it was only by a stroke of luck. We both know how it went, if I had such great strength, I could also do that. It's no big deal."

As Fang Yuan walked through the village, the people made way for him; there were praises, curiosity and also envy.

"Fang Yuan!" Chi Shan suddenly appeared from a corner and shouted.

Note: The 'blizzards' in the chapter title "There are many blizzards in life" is a metaphor for 'obstacles'.

Chapter 123: I travel alone through heaven and earth

"What's the matter?" Fang Yuan looked at Chi Shan.

Even if it was winter, he continued to be topless, his red skin emitting a warmth that made people feel like they were near a heater.

The white snow that landed on his body instantly melted.

This is because his aperture had a Double Orifice Stove Gu.

The Stove Gu was a Rank two Gu worm. It could store internal heat that could be used for attacking. Subduing the cold was just a side effect.

Chi Shan's expression was complicated, he stared at Fang Yuan and said gravely, "Do you know that these days, Xiong Li from the Xiong clan has been finding you for a contest of strength?"

"I know," Fang Yuan nodded.

Chi Shan sighed, "Xiong Li finding you for a contest of strength is not a mere competition, but it involves the interest allocation of the three clans' alliance. Under the wolf tide, non-alliance means destruction. But after forming an alliance, the biggest problem is how to distribute the interests and profits. These days, the three clans have been at a stalemate due to that."

Fang Yuan looked at Chi Shan, instantly understanding why he had looked for himself.

Negotiation was the hardest thing to do. For their own interests, the three clans would not give way automatically, and they would have to fight for their best interests. The negotiation table was long filled with gunpowder and smoke, battling wits.

In this world's system of values, first was strength, second was kinship.

Qing Mao Mountain's three clans were individual clans, having great conflict towards each other since a long time ago, each bearing old and deep grudges. Of course kinship cannot be used to alleviate their tensions. So to break the tension, they had to rely on strength.

On earth, there are military exercises to display one's strength. In this world, it worked similarly in that there are Gu contests to display the strength of one faction and achieve greater benefits for themselves.

Xiong Li finding Fang Yuan for a contest to compete strength, was due to this.

As expected, Chi Shan said next, "I have competed with Xiong Li, he has the Brown Bear Innate Strength Gu and already possesses the strength of one bear. He also has the Grand Bear Gu, and can increase his strength by another bear. Together he has two bear's strength. I am far beyond his match, as much as I want to deny it. But as Qing Mao Mountain's number one strongest person, the title belongs to him no doubt."

He paused for a while, then continue, "Let's talk business. Your strength is around mine, so you are not his match either. But you cannot lose, as you were the one who woke up the River Swallowing Toad, the hero that saved Qing Mao Mountain. Once you lose, our Gu Yue Clan's interests will be compromised. So for the clan's interests, discard your personal honor and avoid battle!"

Fang Yuan stared silently at Chi Shan.

Chi Shan looked down, "I know that this matter towards you is very difficult. After all, avoiding the competition has a disastrous damage towards one's own reputation. But it is for the interests of the clan; if you lose, the clan would have to give up much more. The clan has nurtured us, we naturally have to contribute to the clan right? The clan needs you. Sacrificing your own reputation for the clan is only natural! But this matter started due to me, so in my personal name, I will compensate you for it, as part of my goodwill."

Saying so, Chi Shan handed Fang Yuan a large money bag.

Fang Yuan weighed it, and chuckled, "So my reputation is only worth two hundred primeval stones?"

Chi Shan could hear the sarcasm in his words, his gaze sharpened as he said solemnly, "Fang Yuan, please do not have any indignant feelings! Earlier, I tried to console you with kind words, but the truth is I'm here with a mission. Avoiding the competition is the clan higher-up's orders. Regardless of what you think, this is an order. I hope you understand your position."

Saying so, he turned around and left, leaving deep footprints in the snow.

Fang Yuan looked at Chi Shan's back as his eyes revealed a sign of understanding.

"In order to get the greatest benefits, the clan has already used the event of me chasing away the River Swallowing Toad as a chip in the negotiation. After all, the River Swallowing Toad was a danger to the entire Qing Mao Mountain. In order to get rid of this chip, the Xiong clan sent Xiong Li to challenge me."

"To the clan, I am but a chess piece. Xiong Li is the same, and Chi Shan is also a chess piece. What is sad is that these people are willingly being pawn pieces, even basking in its glory and finding it natural; this is truly a successful brainwash by the clan."

"But I originally did not want to compete with Xiong Li anyway, the so-called reputation is merely praises from others. This chain that binds people has captured many heroes and geniuses in the past. But to me, what loss is there? Hehe, I have to thank Chi Shan for sending me two hundred primeval stones."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan smirked.

Why did he attract Xiong Li's challenge? Merely because he had the glory of saving the village. Why did Chi Shan challenge Xiong Li? It was merely for the reputation of Qing Mao Mountain's number one strongman.

The so-called reputation is merely a superficial carrot. It has tempted many people and trampled many others, manipulating countless people.

Sad, how sad!

Snow continued to descend slowly.

The entire Gu Yue village was silently erected in the snow. The people beside him rushed through the streets.

"What's laughable is that these people have had their bodies trapped by this fictitious glory!" Fang Yuan's eyes drooped down as his eerie dark iris was half-covered by hair.

The light reflecting from the snow shone on his face. The young man's face was pale and had a sort of coldness.

Suddenly laughing, Fang Yuan recited a poem, "White snow blankets the land as I travel alone through heaven and earth. Alone without any attachments, my solitary shadow travels freely."

He took a large step and continued travelling.

While others rushed, Fang Yuan walked alone.

Whether it was clansmen, snow or the village, they were merely a blurry background.

A moment later, he reached his rental apartment.

The bamboo buildings and the wine tavern, he had already sold them all away. He continued to stay in the rented flat, and although it was very simple, Fang Yuan did not ask for more, he just needed a shelter over his head.

Sitting on the bed, Fang Yuan began to cultivate.

Gu Masters in cultivating to breakthrough a large realm, needed ability and talent. But to break through a small realm, it was merely the accumulation of time. With enough time, the aperture would be continuously nurtured, and it can continue to elevate.

According to agreement, when it reached evening, Jiang Ya came to Fang Yuan's residence.

"Lord Fang Yuan, these are the primeval stones this time, please inspect it." He walked into the room, handing over five money bags respectfully, filled with primeval stones.

There was more than four hundred primeval stones inside, and as the wolf tide approached, Gu Masters had an increased reliance on the vitality leaves. This caused Fang Yuan's sale price to continuously go up.

Fang Yuan handed Jiang Ya nine vitality leaves, asking, "The thing I asked you to purchase, have you done it?"

Jiang Ya showed a look of disappointment, shaking his head, "Lord Fang Yuan, this is bad timing. The wolf tide is coming, and the clan has increased its control on resources. Other things aside, that Fish Scale Gu is only slightly less valuable than the Jade Skin Gu. I have already tried my best, but it is difficult to have results immediately."

Fang Yuan frowned.

Fish Scale Gu was used with Stealth Rock Gu to create the Stealth Scale Gu. Without the Fish Scale Gu, he couldn't refine the Stealth Scale Gu.

"Even with resource control, it does not mean we cannot find a Fish Scale Gu. The root of the problem is Jiang Ya's ability being too small. It seems that fusing the Stealth Scale Gu would have to drag on." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

But he was not discouraged.

Nine out of ten things in this world will not go according to plan.

This is life, and the phrase "smooth-sailing" is only a beautiful greeting.

"Bai clan produces the Fish Scale Gu, and our clan also has them, although less in number. It seems this matter has to wait after the formal alliance."

Fang Yuan was not in a rush, he knew that once the three clans form an alliance, they would create the battle merit board. This would encourage Gu Masters to proactively hunt wolves. By then, he would be able to use his merit points to exchange for the three clan's resources.

Of course, Gu Yue Clan's Moonlight Gu, Xiong clan's Bear Strength Gu and Bai clan's Stream Gu were the clan's signature, and would not be exchangeable.

But the Fish Scale Gu was definitely inside.

Danger is accompanied by opportunity.

To Gu Masters, the wolf tide was a strict examination, but also an opportunity to rise up.

Under the attack of the wolf tide, numerous famous Gu Masters died while many Gu Masters gained fame due to it. The older factions in the clan would weaken due to this, but new factions would rise up into the political stage.

At night, unexpected guests arrived.

Gu Yue Qing Shu and Gu Yue Fang Zheng.

Qing Shu got to the main point, mentioning his previous objective, wanting to buy the Liquor worm from Fang Yuan.

At the same time, he also wanted to buy the Black Boar Gu, and even the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass.

Nine Leaf Vitality Grass was a no brainer; Liquor worm had long become the Four Flavor Liquor worm, even if Fang Yuan wanted to, he couldn't even produce it now, thus he rejected them.

But the Black Boar Gu...

"I have already gained the strength of a boar, so the Black Boar Gu has little value to me anymore. Black Boar Gu's best advancement path is the Steel Mane Gu. Although it is a Gu with both offense and defense, to me who already has the White Jade Gu, it has little use. I might as well exchange it into a Fish Scale Gu."

Fang Yuan thought of this, and mentioned it.

"Fish Scale Gu?" Qing Shu frowned, then nodded, "I know, you lack a defensive Gu worm. The Fish Scale Gu can be fused into the Rank two Scale Armor Gu. It can provide good defense."

Using the Fish Scale Gu and Stealth Rock Gu to create the Stealth Scale Gu, the recipe would only be discovered two hundred years later, so it was natural that Qing Shu had no clue.

Fang Yuan did not expose himself, "The Black Boar Gu is more valuable than the Fish Scale Gu, so if we exchange it, you have to compensate me the difference in price."

"Naturally." Qing Shu nodded then asked, "Nevermind about the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, are you really not selling the Liquor worm? It is useless to you already, raising it for nothing is just a waste of your primeval stones."

Fang Yuan shook his head, "Don't mention the Liquor worm, it is not for sale."

Qing Shu rubbed his nose, laughing bitterly, "Fang Yuan, this matter is more complicated than you think. Do you know Gu Yue Yao Le? She is the granddaughter of medicine hall elder Gu Yue Yao Ji, a new student this year, and has B grade aptitude. Gu Yue Yao Ji loves her granddaughter and once tried to buy a Liquor worm in the treehouse, but did not succeed."

"You've used the Liquor worm before, I'm sure you know the benefits it has. I won't say anymore, but Lord Yao Ji really wants this Gu worm for her granddaughter. An elderly's affection for her grandchildren is completely understandable. Thus, she has come to you, she is serious about buying it and has offered a high price. She even promises that if you got injured in the wolf tide, you'd get special attention from the medicine hall. I hope you consider it thoroughly."

Chapter 124: I don’t need your understanding

"So that's it," Fang Yuan rubbed his chin, then shook his head, "This Liquor worm is not for sale. Since Yao Ji is insistent, why isn't she finding that Gu Master who bought the Liquor worm?"

Hearing this, Qing Shu looked like a dark cloud was looming over him as he sighed deeply, "Sigh, we do not know which clansman has it. After buying this Liquor worm, there has been absolutely no news. We cannot find anything, and we cannot simply inspect apertures right? That is a taboo, the biggest taboo among Gu Masters. For a small matter like the Liquor worm, causing public rage is not good. But it is understandable that this clansman is keeping a low profile on his treasure, this is also human nature."

Qing Shu did not know that the real person who bought the Liquor worm was sitting in front of him.

But Qing Shu never suspected Fang Yuan, since in his perspective, Fang Yuan had the Liquor worm already, he wouldn't need to buy a second one. What's the use of it?

If he knew about the Four Flavor Liquor worm's recipe, he would definitely suspect Fang Yuan. But now, this recipe was solely Fang Yuan's secret to keep.

The only one who knew that Fang Yuan was the buyer, is Jia Fu. But to Jia Fu, Fang Yuan could be helping another person to buy it. Whether it be a relative or a lover, something like this is natural. Yao Ji is the same right, buying the Liquor worm for her granddaughter?

"No matter what, I am not giving way for this Liquor worm matter." Fang Yuan's attitude was firm without any loosening, as he smirked in his heart.

This was the system.

The system made one strong, but it was also a restraint.

Gu Yue Yao Ji was a Rank three Gu Master. She was much stronger than Fang Yuan, but due to the system she could not snatch it from him. Due to the rules of the system and minding her own reputation, she cannot forcefully purchase it either.

Fang Zheng who was at one side suddenly urged, "Brother, the Liquor worm is useless to you, why cling on to it. Granny Yao Ji is very kind. I've met sister Yao Le many times too, she is a good person, I am sure she will take good care of the Liquor worm. And the Liquor worm is very helpful to her. Kindness begets kindness, brother, you saved the village and I am happy for you. This brings honor to our family as well. But why are you being so stubborn now, isn't this too petty?"

Fang Yuan's expression stiffened as he said coldly, " My good little brother, are you lecturing me? The Liquor worm is my business. Even if it rots in my hands, you have no rights to dictate what I do."

He was not really angry, but attitude is the mask of the heart, and by expressing his attitude, it would allow Qing Shu to see his determination to reject.

"It seems Fang Yuan is bent on rejecting. Bringing Fang Zheng here on purpose was a bad move. These brothers have a poor relationship and are always at odds, I've shot myself in the foot," Gu Yue Qing Shu's gaze shone.

"Fang Zheng, go out and shop around." Fang Zheng wanted to say more, but he was stopped by Qing Shu.

Fang Zheng gritted his teeth, but still obeyed Qing Shu's command.

"Either way, I cannot understand you in this matter, brother." He opened the door, leaving his last sentence.

"What I do, does not require your understanding, Fang Zheng." Fang Yuan was expressionless.

Fang Zheng's movement of opening the door stopped for a moment, but he quickly walked out of the room without turning around, closing the room door with a bam.

This movement caused the room's atmosphere to become even more awkward.

"If there is nothing else, brother Qing Shu can take your leave." Fang Yuan instantly evicted his guest.

"Hehehe," Qing Shu laughed dryly, trying to alleviate the tension, but Fang Yuan's face was cold as ice, showing no signs of change.

But his temper was mild, and he did not get frustrated.

Touching his nose, Qing Shu laughed awkwardly, "There is another matter, regarding the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass."

"The Nine Leaf Vitality Grass is not for sale." Fang Yuan rolled his eyes.

"I know, I know," Qing Shu nodded, "It is regarding the vitality leaf, this is the personal business of my group. I hope you can supply the produced vitality grass to us. Of course, we will pay you an appropriate compensation."

Seeing business approaching, Fang Yuan naturally did not reject, "Then, sixty-five primeval stones per leaf."

Qing Shu on hearing the price, was tongue-tied.

According to market rates, the clan's original sale price is fifty-five primeval stones. Although the vitality leaf is an expenditure type Rank one Gu, gone after one use, this was something to save lives, and nobody would mind more of it.

Especially with the wolf tide nearing, the clan is also raising prices, and each leaf is sold at sixty primeval stones. Actually, not just the vitality leaf, but also resources are also getting pricier. This is the volatility of the situation, and Gu Masters have to live with it.

But what Qing Shu did not expect was, Fang Yuan's price was even higher than the clan's.

"Finding it expensive? You don't have to buy it. But as far as I know, after the wolf tide, the clan will tightly control resources, and the vitality leaf would have excess demand. By then, the prices will soar again, there might not even be stock, what do you think?" Fang Yuan's tone was calm as he safely evaluated his pricing.

Qing Shu was stumped, his tone turning helpless, "You sure are clear of it. But your price raising is slightly overbearing. Aren't you afraid of offending people? If you reduce the prices, you can use the opportunity to build relationships. But if you raise prices like this, the clansmen will keep a grudge on you for earning profits this way."

Fang Yuan raised his head and laughed, "The wolf tide is nearing, I am but a small fry, I can die anyday. How can I bother with these trivialities?"

"You have long gone past the stage of a small fry, and human relationships are not trivial either." Qing Shu stared at Fang Yuan deeply, then lightly shook his head, "But everyone has their own thoughts and choices, I will not force you. However do be more careful, Lord Yao Ji will not let go so easily... Goodbye."

Qing Shu no longer mentioned the matter of purchasing vitality leaves, Fang Yuan's prices had scared him.

He was a smart person, and when a smart person buys things, they do not act on impulse, but only after intelligent consideration. A smart person would have an evaluation in their heart, and once the prices exceed their worth, they would calmly pull out.

Fang Yuan seemed to have only increased the price by five primeval stones, but Qing Shu was not just buying one vitality leaf, and the wolf tide would be going on for at least a year, he would be expending a lot of vitality leaves. If this accumulated, it would be a heavy cost.

"Thanks for your advice, take care, I shall not send you off," Fang Yuan said, watching Qing Shu leave. His heart was clear as he knew that Qing Shu would definitely be back.

That is because he had underestimated the wolf tide's severity too much.

Under such a wolf tide, death might instantly befall anyone, and the vitality leaf had no lack of customers. In his memory, the price rocketed to over a hundred primeval stones!

Of course, this price was also during the period when the wolf tide was at its strongest. Right now, what Fang Yuan wanted to do was to accommodate to the time period, gradually raising prices.

As time flowed, the winter wind grew more cold and harsh.

This year's winter winds were evidently colder than previous years for Qing Mao Mountain's three villages.

Taking the Gu Yue village for example.

More and more crippled wolves appeared near the village surroundings.

The clan sent out large amounts of missions, and almost all of them were about exterminating the crippled wolves.

During December, when the crippled wolves' amount reached its peak, this caused the situation to worsen quickly, reaching an atrocious level. In fact, there was even a situation where a hamlet at the mountain foot was slaughtered by a large group of wolves.

Good thing was, the dozen Gu Masters in the village retreated in time. The clan higher-ups breathed a sigh of relief secretly, as the death of a Gu Master would cause them to feel pity for over half a day, but for mortals, they were all slaves anyway, so be it if they die.

In this world, there are no human rights.

A Gu Master's life is more valuable than a hundred mortals, this is the viewpoint of everybody.

However death and injury would definitely not be little, thus, the village had sounds of crying and sniffing from morning to night.

The village emanated a sense of grief and suppression throughout.

The crippled wolves were only the prelude; the true wolf tide was even more horrifying.

More and more people started to realize that the wolf tide this year, is exceptional.

Under such pressure, the negotiation that had been under a stalemate obtained quick progress, and the three-clan-alliance was formed.

A month later, at the end of winter.

Alliance Slope, Three Clan Alliance Meeting.

Little snowflakes that were like soft white fur slowly drifted down.

Hundreds and thousands of Gu Masters gathered here, forming a grand scale.

The alliance slope was originally an ordinary mountain slope, but throughout history, the Gu Yue clan's second generation clan head managed to create the first three clan alliances at the slope. Thus forth, all future alliances were held there.

After many years of refinement, the current alliance slope had already expanded tens of times, becoming a giant town square.

The town square was along the mountain wall, and there was a huge rock erected there.

On the huge rock, there were rock carvings of buildings, and in the buildings there was rock furniture properly assembled. The three clan higher-ups were sitting inside, closely discussing.

Below the giant rock building, the three clan's Gu Masters had their respective standings, forming three large groups.

Gu Masters wore similar battle clothing, and along with a belt, their respective cultivation levels were apparent. Fang Yuan was within them.

He secretly observed the situation.

The Gu Masters below the stage were all Rank two Gu Masters. Most Rank one Gu Masters were allocated to support, and only Rank two Gu Masters were the true mobile troops. As for Rank three Gu Masters, they were clan elders, and for a mid-size clan like the Gu Yue clan, even after each generation's effort they only had a little more than twenty clan elders.

Fang Yuan was observing, and the other Gu Masters were also watching. Countless gazes intersected with hatred, curiosity, and alertness.

Gu Yue clan's Gu Masters were on the skinny side. Xiong clan's Gu Masters were strong and robust, and from appearance their strength could be shown. Bai clan's Gu Masters, maybe due to living by the waterfall behind the mountain, had whitish skin and had a Yin aura(1) around them.

"That long hair guy is Gu Yue Qing Shu, Rank two peak stage, and is the Gu Yue clan's number one Rank two Gu Master," some pointed out.

"Mo Yan! Hmph, this wrench caused me to lose an arm. After the wolf tide, I must get revenge!!" Someone snorted in their heart.

"Woah, that girl riding on the giant bear, she should be the Xiong clan's Xiong Jiao Man. Don't be deceived by her appearance, she goes battle-crazy when fighting."

"Do you see that white fat girl? She's Bai clan's Bai Zhong Shui, a Rank two upper stage fighter, who has the Water Boar Gu. She is very promiscuous and very lustful towards men. You newbies be careful, don't get fucked by her."

The three clan's animosity and grudges had long been deep-seated.

Alliance slope's discussion noises became louder as it turned into an uproar. Many Gu Master seniors were pointing around, introducing the strong people from the other two clans to their juniors, reminding them to be careful of them.

(1) Yin aura, this is a bit hard to explain? Yin is associated with females, dark energy, water energy...

Reminder:

Xiong clan—Bear clan.

Bai clan—White clan.

Chapter 125: Oh, then I admit defeat

"The traditional overlord Gu Yue clan, the newly rising Bai clan, and the never-underestimated Xiong clan..." Fang Yuan's gaze flew across the people as he stood in the crowd, observing the entire situation.

Gu Yue clan has Qing Shu, Chi Shan, Mo Yan; Xiong and Bai clan also had their outstanding Rank two elite Gu Masters.

Together with the different clan's heads and elders in the rock building, the alliance slope can be said to be filled with elites.

"I wonder which one is Bai Ning Bing? The man who symbolizes the Bai clan's rise!"

"Bai Ning Bing is already Rank three, he is definitely not among the Rank two Gu Masters."

"It seems he isn't in the rock building either."

Gradually, the discussions gathered on Bai Ning Bing.

Although Bai Ning Bing did not appear, his brilliance had already suppressed all the Gu Masters below the rock building.

"I remember that three years ago on the alliance slope, it was Bai Ning Bing who was the first to step out and start the Gu battle. In just three years, he became a Rank three clan elder, thinking about it makes me shudder."

"He rose to heaven in one step. When he was Rank two, he could defeat a clan elder in the Xiong clan, this guy has a bright future ahead."

"The point is that right now he has already grown up, and at this rate, he can become a Rank four expert and even rank five. As for Rank six..."

"Rank five is mortal, while Rank six is immortal. Rank five is already amazing. Rank six? Hmph, you are all overestimating him...."

"That might not be, who can predict the future?"

Under such discussions, the three clan heads in the rock building stood up, staring down at the thousands of Gu Masters.

Gu Yue clan head was in the center, Bai clan head and Xiong clan head at his left and right respectively.

The alliance slope gradually quietened down.

Gu Yue Bo held the railings, sweeping a glance at the crowd, before saying, "The three-clan-alliance will pull together in times of trouble. For the Gu battle tournament, in the spirit of competition, competitors shall stop before fatality occurs. Start."

The alliance slope was dead silent. The crowd looked at each other.

The three-clan-alliance, would always hold a Gu battle tournament. Not only was it to show off the clan's individual strength, it was also to promote conversation and temporarily alleviate their grudges, to achieve the aims of working together.

But who will stand out first?

If the first Gu Master to stand up failed in public, it would be shameful on their own reputation, and it even shames the clan elders up in the rock building.

Last time, Bai Ning Bing stood up. But this time...

The crowd continued to hesitate. Suddenly at the Xiong clan's side, a group of Gu Masters stood first, it was Xiong Li's group.

Immediately, the group of five invited numerous people's attention and gaze.

The Xiong Li group walked past the Gu Yue clan's area, and under everyone's watchful eye, he stood at the Bai clan's territory.

"It's Xiong Li."

"Qing Mao Mountain's strongest man?"

"That's right. It seems that not too long ago, the Gu Yue clan's Chi Shan lost to him in public. His title is unmovable, not even Bai Ning Bing can take it away."

"Damn it, the Gu Yue clan isn't going over, are they trying to bully our Bai clan?"

At the Bai clan territory, there was a mild disturbance. Many people knew Xiong Li's strength, and felt a sense of pressure.

But Xiong Li looked around, and did not move from his spot; instead, Xiong Jiang who was beside him stood out.

Xiong Jiang had a thin body, and at the Xiong clan's area with lots of burly men, he was very striking.

He took a few steps forward, facing the Bai clan's Gu Masters, cupping his fist, "Xiong clan Xiong Jiang, challenges brother Bai Bing Yi."

Once he spoke, astonished noises could be heard below the rock building.

Bai Bing Yi's status was around the same as Chi Shan and Xiong Li etc. Among the Bai clan's young Gu Masters, he is only inferior to Bai Ning Bing. For Xiong Jiang to challenge him, he was evidently trying to overcome the stronger foe.

But could he?

Bai Bing Yi stood up with a grim face. His body was small and his face was pale; he was like a patient who had just recovered from a serious illness, giving off a feeling of being weak and sickly. But no one dared to underestimate him.

"You, Xiong Jiang dare to challenge me, you have some courage. How do you want to compete? Say it, I'll accept it," He said to Xiong Jiang.

Xiong Jiang laughed darkly, "I specialize in defense, and you specialize in attack. How about this, I defend and you attack. I'll give you three attacking opportunities, and we'll compare the results.

This was not a life and death match, it was only sparring.

But Xiong Jiang had such confidence, he was obviously prepared, and this caused many people to mutter among themselves.

Bai Bing Yi raised his brows, "Xiong Jiang, no matter what Gu worm, you are still a Rank two Gu Master, your cultivation is like that. Do you really think you can block my Water Drill Gu? If I injure you, don't complain."

Xiong Jiang snickered, "We wouldn't know unless we try right? Come."

Saying so, he activated the Gu in his body and his body changed colour, becoming dry and green like a dead block of wood.

At the same time his teeth turned sharp and long, and four fangs were exposed out of his lips.

His iris also turned green.

This was the Rank two Gu, Roaming Zombie Gu.

Once activated, it could turn one into a zombie.

Compared to living people, zombies are better at resisting punches and kicks and have greater regeneration, but is afraid of fire, lightning and light, although it has greater resistance towards water, wind and poison.

At the same time, zombies when fighting under the sunlight are not as strong as in the night, and thus are weakened by the time of the day.

"Even so, I am not afraid," Bai Bing Yi laughed coldly, raising his right arm.

Under everyone's watchful gaze, he gathered his five fingers at one point and contracted his fist.

First, a droplet of water formed on his five fingers, then in the blink of an eye, the droplet expanded, turning into a fast flowing current, and from his fingertips, the water coiled around his palm in a spiral manner.

In two breath's time, Bai Bing Yi's fist was already covered by a light-blue coloured spiral drill that rotated non-stop.

Rank two Water drill Gu!

Able to drill through rocks and steel with very strong attack power, barely any Gu worm could defend against it.

"Receive my blow," Bai Bing Yi coughed, throwing out his fist.

Xiong Jiang raised both arms, forming an arm shield.

The water drill hit his arm, and a large amount of water splattered. The two were at a deadlock for a few breaths when suddenly the water drill's rotation intensified, and Xiong Jiang flew five to six steps back.

Xiong Jiang laid on the ground, but quickly did a belly-flip, standing again.

One could see that the muscles on both his arms were torn by the water drill, showing his pale white bones.

Bai clan's Gu Masters upon seeing this scene uncontrollably cheered, but a small number frowned.

"Hehehe..." Xiong Jiang laughed slyly, not minding his injury as a zombie; his pain sensors had been reduced to zero.

Bai Bing Yi stood on the spot, but suddenly his pale face changed, and he vomited a mouthful of blood.

Bai clan Gu Master's cheers ended.

"What happened?!" someone exclaimed.

"It's the Shadow Bond Gu!" Bai Bing Yi stared deeply at the ground, where Xiong Jiang's shadow was distorted at a creepy angle, pasted on top of the snow. It connected both Xiong Jiang and Bai Bing Yi together.

"It seems I win, brother Bai. With this Shadow Bond Gu, no matter how much injury I suffer, you will take 10% of it. I specialize in defense, but you are a pure attacker, and you have poor health, so even 10% of the damage is deadly to you," Xiong Jiang said plainly.

Bai Bing Yi wiped the blood traces off his lips, staring deeply at Xiong Jiang for a while before saying, "Good. Very good. You planned well with such great tactics. I lost."

He admitted defeat on the spot.

"Too unscrupulous."

"Absolutely cunning and shameless!"

"To think he had a Shadow Bond Gu, senior Bai Bing Yi was completely outplayed."

Bai clan's Gu Masters exploded into a series of discussions.

Xiong Jiang cupped his fist, "I'm flattered. If we really fought, the final winner would still be brother Bai. The Shadow Bond Gu's range is limited, it can only bully close-ranged Gu Masters, I hope brother Bai can take good care of me in this upcoming wolf tide!"

"Of course." Bai Bing Yi's expression softened a little, and nodded.

Bai clan's Gu Masters also started to quieten down.

Standing on the rock building, the three clan's higher-ups who had been observing, nodded discreetly at this scene.

The Gu fighting competition was only for sparring and not ruthless assault. Xiong Jiang exposing a trump card also increased each other's trust and understanding.

Whether it was Xiong Jiang or Bai Bing Yi's attitude, they were good.

Resolving it like this, the Bai clan's Gu Masters, even if they did not admit it, felt admiration towards Xiong Jiang.

After all, the strong were respected.

"Xiong Li's group had a good start," Gu Yue Bo lightly praised.

"Hehehe." Xiong clan head beside him laughed lightly, Xiong Jiang had given him face.

Bai clan head at the other end had a tough expression.

But Xiong Li's group did not quit while they were ahead, the five left the Bai clan's area, and came to the Gu Yue clan.

"After challenging the Bai clan, they are challenging the Gu Yue clan now?"

"Oh no, Xiong Li himself is stepping up now!"

Gu Yue clansmen were slightly nervous, many of their gazes were gathered on Chi Shan, Mo Yan and Qing Shu.

But who knew Xiong Li shouted loudly, "Who is Fang Yuan, please stand up. I heard you could chase away the River Swallowing Toad alone, why don't we have a contest of strength!"

Instantly, the crowd exploded.

Xiong Li stood up, yet he did not challenge Qing Shu, Chi Shan or Mo Yan, but instead pointed out a newbie junior.

"Fang Yuan, who is Fang Yuan?" Some of the other village's Gu Masters had never heard this name before.

"Chasing away the River Swallowing Toad alone, oh my god, that's a Rank five Gu, is he so absurd?" Some shot glances of shock and curiosity.

Gu Yue clan's Gu Masters took the initiative and opened up a path, and Fang Yuan who was among them was exposed.

Without anything hindering their vision, Xiong Li and Fang Yuan stared at each other.

Xiong Li's lips curled to an angle, saying with a very manly elegance, "I hope Fang Yuan would generously teach me."

"This Fang Yuan, who in the world is he, he doesn't have three heads or six limbs anyway."

"Chasing away the River Swallowing Toad is also by coincidence and luck, it is nothing hard. Heh, being targeted by this muscled man Xiong Li, he is in big trouble now."

"Fang Yuan, you can't avoid it anymore. Sigh, in that case, just hope for the best and go ahead and battle!" Chi Shan sighed in his heart.

"Oh, is that so..." Fang Yuan shrugged with a plain expression, "Then I admit defeat."

The moment he said so, the crowd all went dumbfounded.

Chapter 126: Demise of the wood charm

Admit defeat.....

Fang Yuan's words were still lingering in the crowd's ears.

Instantly, almost all the Rank two Gu Masters below the rock building looked at Fang Yuan with surprise.Fang Yuan ignored them; he held his arms and stood on the spot with an indifferent expression."Admit defeat? He directly admitted defeat, did I hear that wrongly?""He is Fang Yuan? He doesn't even have the guts to come out, haha.""We recognize Xiong Li's power, he is indeed strong. But even if you want to admit defeat, at least do that after the formalities. By directly admitting defeat, he is not only showing that he is a coward, he is even tarnishing the clan."

The whispers were like ripples in a calm lake.

The Gu Masters' gazes turned from surprise to despise, scorn and gloating.Many Gu Yue clan Gu Masters felt unease; the gazes from the Xiong and Bai clan's Gu Masters were like invisible needles, piercing their self-esteem.

Fang Yuan was a member of the Gu Yue clan, with him directly admitting defeat, this made them feel absolutely humiliated.

"How could you admit defeat? Fang Yuan, you are a man of Gu Yue village, stand up and fight bravely with Xiong Li!""Even if you lost, it wouldn't be anything serious."

"If you don't even have the guts to go out, then that would really be throwing away our dignity!"

Some Gu Yue clan Gu Masters shouted and urged Fang Yuan to take the challenge.Fang Yuan was indifferent; to him, these words were like dogs barking.The so-called name, face and honor was only a pie painted on a paper; shackles used by the higher-ups to bind the organization members.These Gu Masters were also dogs on a leash.Xiong Li gazed at Fang Yuan and suddenly laughed, "I am truly disappointed. Is this how a Gu Yue village's bravery looks like?"

Gu Yue clan Gu Masters looked unsightly when they heard this.Hoots of laughter came from Xiong village's side, and even Bai village's Gu Masters looked at Gu Yue clan with mockery.The people around Fang Yuan started moving away. Everyone made some distance from him; their faces were filled with embarrassment.Soon, there was no one within five steps from Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan stood alone. My way or the highway(1), his expression was calm as opposed to the surroundings.Others fancied a courageous reputation, but Fang Yuan scoffed at it. This made others loathe him.Because Fang Yuan loathed fame, he was rejecting the society's values. Denying this system of values was rejecting the people who lived their lives following these values.Others naturally wouldn't deny their own values, otherwise they would feel that they were living in a wrong way. Thus, they had subconsciously started to reject and boycott Fang Yuan.A weak-hearted person would be defeated by such rejection and they would change themselves to suit the public.However, Fang Yuan needed such rejection. He had too many secrets on him and so he needed to be solitary. At the same time, these people weren't worth being friends with. In his memories, Qing Mao Mountain's three villages barely survived the wolf tide, but the accident two years later would totally destroy them and turn the entire Qing Mao Mountain into a desolate area.What Fang Yuan needed was to use this time to improve himself as much as possible, then leave the clan and avoid the fatal disaster.Gu Yue Qing Shu—the number one Rank two Gu Master in the Gu Yue Clan—couldn't help but stand up seeing this situation.

"Xiong Li, how about sparring with me?"

"Hehe, what will we compete on?" Xiong Li was smiling, but his expression was serious.Gu Yue Qing Shu didn't look at Xiong Li; he slightly raised his palm and silently moved his primeval essence, his eye watchfully looked at the green vine that was slowly growing out from his palm.

He calmly said, "Let's compete on your strength. If you can break away from my green vine's binding, I will admit defeat. Is that okay?""Hehe, good suggestion, let's do it that way." Xiong Li grinned, his eyes revealing a bright light.

He inwardly thought, I already have the strength of a bear and combining it with the strength-increase from Grand Bear Gu, I possess the strength of two bears. Although green vine is tough, I have absolute guarantee of breaking it away with the strength of two bears. Xiong Jiang won against Bai Bing Yi and if I defeat Qing Shu, it would give us great reputation!Qing Shu gently smiled. Without speaking, he extended his two hands; two green vines grew out from his palms. Like two nimble green pythons, the two vines climbed up Xiong Li and twisted around his body.

Xiong Li's hands were at his waist; the green vines coiled around both his arms and instantly made a dozen circles around them, tightly binding his hands with his back.The Gu Masters on the scene couldn't take their eyes off this contest.

"Please." Qing Shu said to Xiong Li.Xiong Li opened his eyes. He tightly clenched his fists and started putting strength.Every muscle on his body seemed to stand out like lumps on a huge rock.

Strength of a bear!Boom.

The green vines started to snap under his enormous strength."Hahaha, brother Qing Shu, it seems the winner of this contest belongs to me!" Xiong Li was using his strength to break free, but he still had enough energy to make a conversation.

"Senior Qing Shu...." Fang Zheng was nervous and his hands were sweatingThe other Gu Yue clan's Gu Masters were also the same. Gu Yue Qing Shu was the number one among them and if he lost the contest, the Gu Yue Clan would have thoroughly lost their face this time!

"Not necessarily." Gu Yue Qing Shu smiled, his eyes showing confidence.When he finished speaking, the green vines on his hands started changing. The originally green-like jade color suddenly changed to a dark green color. At the same time, the vines also became thicker and green wide leaves started growing on it.Xiong Li's face changed, he sensed the green vine's coiling strength had increased by more than ten times.

What made him more apprehensive was that those green vines which he had broken away from started growing and reconnected with the broken areas.Grand Bear Gu!

He sensed the situation going bad and immediately used the Grand Bear Gu in his aperture.Immediately, his hair started stiffening up like steel needles. The muscles on his whole body enlarged and he seemed to have become much taller and bulkier.Strength of two bears!

The green vines gave creaking noises but it was still able to resist this terrifying strength, firmly confining Xiong Li.

Xiong Li's face became very red, and he brought out all his strength to break the green vines. But finally, he was only able to snap one green vine and couldn't continue anymore.

"I lost." He released the supporting strength of Grand Bear Gu and said while gasping."You let me win." Qing Shu cupped his hands and retrieved the green vines."Senior Qing Shu, you are the best." Gu Yue Clan's Gu Masters were jubilant."Senior Qing Shu really deserves his name. Brother can't compare to him at all." Fang Zheng stood beside Qing Shu and looked at the latter with reverence.

Xiong Li's gaze was complicated as he looked at Gu Yue Qing Shu. He had progressed and obtained Brown Bear Innate Strength Gu, but Qing Shu had also progressed. Although he didn't know what the latter used, but this was his true rival. As for that Fang Yuan, he was only a newbie and was nothing to worry about."It really is the Wood Charm Gu," Fang Yuan thought as he observed Qing Shu from afar.

Xiong Li hadn't discovered anything when facing Gu Yue Qing Shu. Two emerald-green leaves had grown on Gu Yue Qing Shu's hair.

This was the sign of using the Wood Charm Gu.The so-called Wood Charm was a tree spirit.

Using the Wood Charm Gu could let one battle as a tree spirit.The tree spirit was an unusual creature. It could directly absorb the natural essence in the air and use it.Gu Masters couldn't do this, they could only use the primeval essence in their aperture.

When one used the Wood Charm gu, they could become an embodiment of a Wood Charm tree spirit and would be able to directly absorb the natural essence in the air and replenish their primeval essence. It was the same as absorbing the primeval essence from primeval stones.

When normal Gu Masters battle, they are unable to divide their mind and absorb primeval essence from primeval stones while fighting.

But as an embodiment of the tree spirit, the absorption of natural essence is an instinct and does not need one to divide their minds. This meant that the Gu Masters who used Wood Charm Gu were experts in war of attrition. Although one couldn't say that they could use the natural essence endlessly, they could fight for as much as three times longer because of the continuous replenishment.

And once one became an embodiment of the tree spirit, Gu worms like Green Vine Gu and Pine Needle Gu would also have their strength amplified.

Fang Yuan instantly connected the dots, "Wood Charm Gu's fusion advancement can be said to be one of the most extravagant advancement routes. It is a Rank three Gu and needs to fuse with a hundred-years Lifespan Gu to advance to a Rank four hundred-years Wood Charm gu. The hundred-years Wood Charm Gu needs to fuse with a thousand years Lifespan Gu to advance into a Rank five thousand-years Wood Charm gu. Everyone knows this fusion route, but Gu Masters rarely use this recipe. The reason is due to the preciousness of the Lifespan Gu. When the Gu Masters finds Lifespan Gu, they will usually use it directly to increase their own lifespan."In this world, a human could live for at most a hundred years if they didn't encounter any accidents or illnesses. A hundred years was the lifespan limit of the humans.

But a Lifespan Gu can increase lifespan.A hundred years Lifespan Gu can increase the lifespan of a person by a hundred years and a thousand years Lifespan Gu could increase it by a thousand.

Lifespan Gu were extremely rare and everyone sought after them.

Fang Yuan had lived for five hundred years in his previous life because he used five hundred-year Lifespan Gu in his previous life, thus adding five hundred years to his lifespan—his one hundred years lifespan had turned to six hundred years. But in the end halfway through, he was attacked by the righteous factions and had no choice but to self-detonate and die.

Lifespan Gu represented 'long life' and could let people live for long, but it didn't mean 'undying'.

"The Wood Charm Gu is powerful but has its weakness; Gu Masters can't use it for a long period. If they use it for too long, the Wood Charm Gu's strength will affect their body and will transform their body to that of wood, finally changing the body into a wooden corpse. In my previous life, Gu Yue Qing Shu had died in this way."Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's eyes flashed.Ordinarily, powerful Gu worms had huge side effects and needed to be used with other Gu worms. Otherwise, there would be harmful influences on the Gu Masters' body.Xiong Jiang's Roaming Zombie Gu was best used with the Bloodline gu. If not, the blood in his body would decrease when used for too long and he would change into a true zombie.The Xiong Li group returned to their camp. They first won against Bai Bing Yi, then met defeat against Qing Shu. Even so, the group still received a lot of applause and praises."Mo Yan, I challenge you."

"Come, Xiong Jiao Man, I will fight you!"

After the Xiong Li group, the whole scene suddenly became noisy. Many Gu Masters continuously came out and challenged the powerful opponents in their minds, demonstrating their bravery.

The Alliance slope turned chaotic, and all kinds of brilliant and varied Gu battles were occurring.

The true Gu battle had started.

(1) Not entirely sure how to fit this into the passage, it is an idiom, but it just means he does whatever he wants/to persist in whatever he is doing no matter what others say.

Chapter 127: So-called morals and relationships (Long chapter)

Only until evening did the Gu tournament come to an end.

On the alliance slope, the Gu Masters from all three clans were no longer as divided as earlier. Gu Masters plastered the slope and only three densely packed groups could be vaguely seen remaining.

Gu battle sparring was both a form of venting and also compromise.

In this world where the greatest value is strength, only with strength comes respect, and that forms the basis for cooperation.

After Xiong Li challenged Fang Yuan, no one else came to look for him.

Fang Yuan was only a newbie and did not have much interaction with the other two clan's Gu Masters, not to mention any animosity. As for his own clansmen, they would not challenge someone from their own clan in this situation.

Especially after Fang Yuan admitting defeat, it caused other Gu Masters to lose interest in him. Towards this 'lazy', 'cowardly' opponent, what value is there in winning?

Not wanting to be trampled on, there are two ways. One is to become strong, strong until no one dares to step on you. Another is to turn into dog shit, something no one would want to step on.

Fang Yuan did not care about dog shit, or the reputation of the strong. He always acted unscrupulous, and only cared about the results. Without anyone challenging him, it made his life easier.

The surrounding people's contempt and disdain , he treated it like air. If he could not endure even these gazes, what right did he have to pursue the demonic way?

The alliance gathering ended successfully, and Gu Yue clan, Bai clan, and Xiong clan all reached an agreement.

First, declaring the rules. The three clans will temporarily put aside their grudges and resist the wolf tide together. In times of danger, they will assist each other. At the same time, internal killing is prohibited, and an investigating battle group will be set up. Once they find any murders, the murderer will first be chased out of the clan, then the three clans will bring judgement together, making them pay with their lives. If the murderer escapes outside, their families' lives will be forfeited.

Even if the Gu Master dies, Gu worms retrieved from their corpses have to be given to the clan, and if it is used secretly, they will be charged with murder. After the Gu worm is submitted, they can exchange it for merit points.

Secondly, setting up the battle merit board. With a small group as a unit, every moment will be showing the battle achievements of the groups from all three clans and their rankings. A lightning wolf's eyeball is exchanged for ten merit points. Merit points can be used to exchange for Gu worms, primeval stones, and other resources.

The appearance of the battle merit board naturally inspired the hot bloodedness of the Gu Masters.

The result of the Gu battle sparring could not explain the true strength of both parties in actual combat. For example in the case of Xiong Jiang and Bai Bing Yi, other than the Water Drill Gu, Bai Bing Yi naturally had other attacking methods, but Xiong Jiang's Shadow Bond Gu only had an effective range of ten meters.

Furthermore, the results of any battle are swayed by many external factors.

Gu battle sparring lacked a convincing element, which the battle merit board can provide as a fairer method of competition.

The Gu Masters from the three clans wasted no time in hunting lightning wolves, fighting for a better ranking on the battle merit board.

This was not just for one's own glory, but also for the reputation of the clan.

Especially the top three positions in the merit board, it showed intense competition. Almost every day, the top three would have some sort of change.

Very quickly, a month passed.

Winter left and spring came, causing all living beings to grow once more.

After a battle.

Fang Yuan stepped on the remaining snow, regulating his breathing as well as observing the battlefield around him.

On the battlefield, there were over ten lightning wolves, all dead. Wolf blood and minced corpse could be seen everywhere, and the air emanated a smell of thick blood.

Howl...

At this point, wolf cries could be heard from a distance not too far away.

Fang Yuan's expression changed slightly. With his experience, he knew that a pack of wolves were heading this way rapidly.

If it was any other Gu Master, after an intense battle, without enough primeval essence in their aperture, they might have thoughts of retreating. But Fang Yuan did not care about this; he squatted down and began to gather the eyeballs from the wolf corpses.

His movements were fluid and highly efficient, but even so, after he was done extracting, he was already half-surrounded by the wolf pack.

This was a mid-sized wolf pack with around one hundred crippled wolves, their greenish wolf eyes showing a ruthless expression as they stared at Fang Yuan firmly.

Fang Yuan kept the wolf eyes well before standing up with a smile. Next, his body flickered like water ripples, and he vanished on the spot.

The wolf pack that had come to assault him were instantly riled up, and some of the crippled wolves stood in their tracks, showing their hesitance.

After all they were wild beasts. Seeing such a magical scene was incomprehensible.

"But, this is also because the lightning wolf king uses its wolf eyes to observe, and not its nose. Lightning wolves are fantastical creatures of this world; their vision is sharp like an eagle, but their sense of smell is no better from humans. My Stealth Scales Gu counters these lightning wolves perfectly, but it cannot hide from a dog's nose." Fang Yuan was clear in his heart.

Stealth Scales Gu was successfully refined by him before the Gu battle tournament. It was like a fossilised carp, grey throughout, lying in Fang Yuan's Primeval Sea, letting the liquid essence flow around its very realistic fish scales.

The Fish Scale Gu that Fang Yuan lacked was naturally obtained by trading the Black Boar Gu with Qing Shu.

With this Stealth Scales Gu, Fang Yuan could retreat from under the lightning wolves' nose.

In these few days, this situation had already occurred many times.

Normally, wolves or hounds had very sensitive noses. But lightning wolves were different—they were very fast, but without a clear vision, they would knock into a tree or the mountain rocks.

But nature is fair, as when it bestowed the lightning wolves with its sharp vision, it also took away their sense of smell.

However, the lightning crown wolf was different.

Even with the Stealth Scales Gu, Fang Yuan could travel freely among the normal wolf tide, but in front of a myriad beast king like the lightning crown wolf, he had nowhere to hide.

That is because the lightning crown wolf's eyes had the Lightning Eye Gu residing in it—this Gu allowed the ability to see through all sorts of cloaking.

Other than the Lightning Eye Gu, there are actually also many other Gu worms that can detect the stealthed Fang Yuan.

For example, the Snake Communication Gu, it can detect heat. The Beast Language Gu can allow a Gu Master and wild beasts to converse and obtain information. The clairaudience Gu can allow a Gu Master's hearing to be extremely sensitive.

Thus, even with the Stealth Scales Gu, it did not mean Fang Yuan was completely safe, but it was at most a good life-saving trump card.

When he returned to the village, it was still afternoon.

The day in spring was bright and beautiful, and there were many people passing in and out of the village door. What was different from previous years was that people on the road were mostly Gu Masters, while there were very little mortals.

Under the influence of the wolf tide, the wilderness was not safe. Hunters did not dare to hunt in the mountains, and farms were almost abandoned.

On the streets, Gu Masters were high in morale, each returning with blood traces all over, or enthusiastically leaving.

They were either talking about the battle merit board's ranking, or discussing their experiences in killing the lightning wolves. Some were talking about the well-performing Gu Masters from the other villages.

Fang Yuan was among the crowd that walked into the village, and he went to the village square in front of the family head pavillion.

The square already had a stage; the merit points were exchanged here.

A large amount of Gu Masters gathered here, and Rank one Gu Masters were doing administrative work. Some Rank two Gu Masters squeezed around, using the bloodstained wolf eyes to exchange for merit points.

There was also a portion of them that were using their merit points to exchange for primeval stones, Gu worms or food ingredients, etc.

In the middle of the village square, a large banner was erected, and on it there was the written language of this world; it was constantly changing.

This is the battle merit board, and on it there are over a dozen Swimword Gu.

Rank one Swimword Gu, after being manipulated by Rank one support Gu Masters, can freely convert the contents of the writings on the banner.

"Hmph, why is the #1 still the Bai clan's Bai Bing Yi's group?" Some stared at the battle merit board, frowning.

"Let me see, Bai Bing Yi is #1, our clan's Qing Shu group is #2, and Xiong Li group is #3, my group is the 137th." A Gu Master counted.

This time, someone suddenly said, "It changed, it changed! Qing Shu group is now #1. They pushed Bai clan's Bai Bing Yi to #2!"

On the battle merit board, the symbol showing the second ranking Qing Shu group suddenly moved, crawling its way upwards and pulling the Bai Bing Yi group down with its "hands", ascending the position of number one itself, even using its "leg" to trample around.

Such a human reaction, it was naturally due to the Gu Master manipulating the Swimword Gu.

Seeing this interesting change, the Gu Masters in the village square laughed heartily, pointing a thumbs up towards Qing Shu's group, praising nonstop. The Rank one Gu Master controlling the Swimword Gu had a red face as he showed an expression of excitement.

"Lord Qing Shu, you are indeed our number one Rank two Gu Master!"

"Good job, Lord Qing Shu."

Gu Yue Qing Shu walked among the crowd, smiling faintly. Gu Yue Fang Zheng who was behind him clenched both fists, following closely with an excited expression on his face.

The praises from all over the square filled the young man's strong materialistic desire. This made Fang Zheng feel like he was walking on a bright path, unknowingly increasing his recognition towards the clan.

"Brother..." He saw Fang Yuan standing among the crowd, observing with his arms folded.

"Brother, you are still alone, all by yourself. No wonder you have been at the bottom of the ranking every since the start. Only by removing your prejudice and fusing into the masses can you feel the warmth and happiness of the clan," Fang Zheng sighed, feeling that Fang Yuan was somewhat pitiful and pathetic.

People who were like Fang Yuan, always fighting alone without any companions, could not feel any kinship from the clan or friendship forged from fighting together with your teammates.

Facing everything alone is not only dangerous, but mundane.

A person living without friendship, love or kinship, what is the meaning of being alive?

Fang Yuan stood among the crowd, staring at the tall merit board. Without doubt, the last position on the ranking was written in large letters —"Fang Yuan Group".

Other Gu Masters upon seeing this, felt extremely shameful, but Fang Yuan's gaze was calm, not minding it one bit.

After being promoted to group leader, he had never recruited any members. He was a loner group leader, the most special group in the entire Qing Mao mountain's three clans.

With only him alone, of course his daily hunting results could not compare to other groups. Of course, with Fang Yuan's current abilities, if he tried hard he would definitely not be in last place.

But this was pointless to Fang Yuan.

He did not need much merit points, living resources or Gu worm's food, he had stock for everything. He had planned to exchange for a Fish Scales Gu earlier, but now he no longer needed to.

Right now he was hunting lightning wolves daily just to put on a show to fulfil the quota, and secondly accumulate some merit points to exchange for moon orchid petals.

After all, his Moonglow Gu needed this food.

Half a month soon passed, and the spring atmosphere intensified.

Trees started to grow leaves, and wildflowers on the roadside bloomed.

Under the warm spring winds, Gu Masters sang in battle, and the battle situation was getting better and better.

Fang Yuan walked on the pavement, seeing everyone's happy faces, their exchanges of praise like courageous acts and the likes.

Of course, there were also some Gu Masters who were in deep worry, showing an unhappy expression. These Gu Masters were mostly the elderly, as with their rich life experiences, they knew that the real wolf tide was coming in summer and autumn.

Fang Yuan realized in his heart.

"What caused this current situation is due to the three-clan alliance, thus people have reduced their caution of each other, and this enabled Gu Masters to be more invested in resisting the wolf tide. Secondly, the lightning wolves exterminated were only the crippled wolves. Thirdly, with the coming of spring, many wolves are busy mating. When summer comes, the truly energetic and healthy wolves would attack from all directions, causing great damage and deaths to the three clans."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's eyes shone with cold light.

In this year's wolf tide, the intensity was like never before, it reached a danger level that was unforeseen. Even the clan higher-ups greatly underestimated the severity of this wolf tide.

In his memory, most of the Gu Masters died, and the trump cards of the three clans were nearly fully expended.

Fang Yuan had never thought of warning the higher-ups. One is that even if he did, they might not listen to his suggestion, and even emphasize on where he got the information, which he is unable to explain. Secondly, there was no point in telling them, it is a fundamental difference in strength. Thirdly, and the most crucial reason, warning the clan did not fit his biggest interest!

I would rather let the world down, than be let down by the world!!!

What kinship, friendship, love—these were but an ornament in life, how could they compare to a man's great ambition?

On Earth, Xiang Yu wanted to cook Liu Bang's father, and the Han dynasty ancestor Liu Bang even laughed and said, "Go ahead, don't forget to give me a piece of meat."

Tang Dynasty Li Shi Ming killing his brothers, Cao Cao's army having no rations and cooking people to turn them into dried meat as food. Liu Bei borrowing Jing Zhou but never returning.

The higher-ups praised the values and morals, but those are just tools to maintain their rule.

If one is restrained by these, how can they achieve anything?

Amongst those who stepped into high society, who didn't have bloodstained hands as they stepped on corpses along the way? In a capitalist's initial startup funding, the process was always bloody. Any politician's hands were stained dirty, and so-called philanthropists were merely using money to gain recognition in society.

It was just that the successful were apt in hiding their past acts, and those who believed the stories of the successors were truly fools.

"These fools are everywhere, restrained by emotions and morals, they deserve to be stupidly manipulated by rules. What's sadder is that when they see others not being restrained, they would jump out and criticise, trying to impart these morals to the people, not allowing others to have more freedom than them. In this process, they would even enjoy this ridiculous moral superiority and bliss."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan looked at the Gu Masters walking past him.

These people, they had a body full of abilities, and some even had higher cultivation than him, but for what?

They were just pawns, merely restrained dogs.

What truly stalled a person's success was not talent, but mindset.

Any organisation, once a person is born, would impart their morals and rules, constantly brainwashing. Those that want to surpass humanity's achievements have to break this restraint on their mindset. Sadly, most people are trapped by this their entire lives, using this to move forward with motivation and even use their chained collar as a symbol of pride.

Thinking so, Fang Yuan laughed coldly.

Walking out of the village door, he retracted his thoughts.

There was something important today, he was preparing to enter the rock crack's secret cave again!

Chapter 128: If not for the harshness of the winter, how could we look forward to spring!

A faint red glow pervaded the stone forest, the petrified growths sprouting out from the ceiling towards the ground like upside-down trees. It was a sight to see.

"It has been over a month since I last came here." Fang Yuan thought helplessly.

After the three clans united, they had commenced a crusade to continuously eliminate the surrounding wolf packs. Because the of the constant traffic for the war effort, Gu Masters made up an almost ever-present flow moving nearby the stone crack cave. In such a situation, even if Fang Yuan possessed Stealth Scales Gu, there was a danger of exposing himself.

Despite the risk, Fang Yuan was very careful in the way he did things. Five hundred years worth of life experience had nurtured enough patience in him; he kept reign over his desires and made sure not to make movements around the stone cave during this period.

When spring came, the crippled wolves had been successfully rooted out and there were few Gu Masters left roaming around. Only then was he willing and Fang Yuan circled around the village before using the Stealth Scales Gu to come back.

A month had passed by, allowing some stone monkey groups to repopulate and they had moved to the stone pillars he had cleared before.

Fortunately, the number were quite few.

Fang Yuan spent some time killing the monkey groups and advancing towards the central area of the stone forest.

Under the shadow of the huge stone pillar, an obvious artificial cave entrance appeared before his eyes.

Some crude rock stairs extended downwards from the cave mouth into the darkness.

Fang Yuan used the White Jade Gu to cover his whole body with a layer of faint jade light and carefully descended down the stairs.

His left hand held a fire torch, whereas bright moonlight shone on his right palm—The Moonglow Gu was already activated.

It was completely dark underground and even the fire torch could only illuminate five steps ahead.An illumination-type Gu would be a lot helpful in such situations. Unfortunately Fang Yuan was not so affluent.

Step by step, he walked on for a long while before reaching the end of the stairs.

A crude artificial stone door was in front of him.

"Golden Centipede's cave is precarious, Earth Communication is the way to avoid the disaster." Fang Yuan lifted his fire torch which illuminated some characters carved on the stone door.

Earth communication... Golden Centipede.....

Fang Yuan's eyes gleamed, comprehending the meaning.

"If this is what I think it is..." He crouched down and touched the ground; the soil was wet."There's something." He was happy. He began to dig the soil and indeed, he found an Earth Treasury Flower.

He carefully uncovered the petals and took out a Gu worm from the heart of the flower.

This was a special Gu.

It resembled a human ear, but much smaller. It was yellowish-brown, and looked shrivelled and dull.He felt it in his palm; it was shrivelled like marinated radish and carried some warmth. Dozens of roots like the ginseng roots grew out from its sides.

This was a Rank two grass Gu—Earth Communication Ear Grass.

Looking at the Earth Communication Ear Grass, Fang Yuan's gaze flashed.

This Earth Communication Ear Grass's usage was to scout. It had appeared in a great time and was perfect for Fang Yuan.

Earth Communication Ear Grass had a great advantage; it could scout up to three hundred paces. This range was among the best of Rank two investigative Gu worms.

It was easy to feed too. Its food was the ginseng roots.

There were many forested mountains in the Southern Border. There were far more ginsengs here than in Earth. Hunter families would occasionally pick some when they went to hunt in the mountains.

Especially when ginseng is easy to store; as long as it is completely dried and sealed up properly, it could be kept for a long time under room temperature.

Moon orchid petals wilted in a few days, but ginseng could be stored for a long time.

"Gu worms need to be nurtured, used and refined. These three aspects are broad and has many mysteries within them. Earth Communication Ear Grass is easy to nurture, but using it is rather troublesome," Fang Yuan pondered. He held the Earth Communication Ear Grass and poured primeval essence, instantly refining it.

Earth Communication Ear Grass was very outstanding and could compare with many Rank three investigative Gu worms. However, heaven was fair, and using the Earth Communication Ear Grass didn't end with just refining, it still needed a certain price.

Just like the Zombie Gu and Wood Charm Gu which needed to be used with other Gu worms,, there was a consequence. If used for a long time, the Gu Master's body would slowly corrode and turn into a true zombie or tree man.

"Many Gu worms can't be used by merely refining them, they still need some special prerequisites. This Earth Communication Flesh Ear Gu is also the same. By using it to ascertain the situation, I can truly move about freely in the wolf tide and even achieve some of my goals during this wolf tide....."

Fang Yuan pondered for a while and decided to use this Earth Communication Flesh Ear Gu.

As the gains would be greater than losses, even if he had to pay the price, it was nothing for the sake of his future.

"No matter which world, how could one gain anything without paying a price?" Fang Yuan coldly smiled and put the Earth Communication Ear Grass in his aperture.

He gazed at the stone door deeply then turned around and left.

If he didn't guess wrong, there would be a great danger in the other side of the stone door. Only by using the Earth Communication Ear Grass, could he be able to avoid it.

Fang Yuan exited the secret cave and leisurely circled the village; after making several rounds, hunting several lone wolves and taking their eyeballs, he returned.

He was still the last in the battle merit board. As he walked through the street, the Gu Masters who recognized him laughed at him or threw a contemptuous look.

Fang Yuan didn't care and still went his own way.

After several days, he used small battle merits to exchange for ginseng roots, properly feeding the Earth Communication Ear Grass and recovering its vitality.

Most of the clan's attention was on the wolf tide, no one paid attention to Fang Yuan. If it was before, Uncle and Aunt might have brought him some troubles, but they had made no more movements ever since Fang Yuan sold the family assets to them.

Difficult to do openly, easy to do secretly.

Soon, Fang Yuan smoothly completed some preparations in the dark.

Tonight, the moon was bright and stars were few.

The moon hung high above like a jade plate and the gentle darkness of the night was like a yarn, covering Qing Mao mountain.

From time to time, wolf howls could be faintly heard from afar.

Fang Yuan securely closed the door and windows. He stood inside his rented room, his whole body naked. There was a table in front of him and a basin filled with warm water was laid on it. Beside the washbasin was a white towel and a sharp dagger on top.

Even the floor he was standing on was covered with a layer of thick cloth.

Strands of moonlight passed through the cracks in the windows and shone upon the table.

Fang Yuan's expression was indifferent as he grabbed the dagger. The dagger was sharp and had a cold shine to it. It could even be used as a mirror.

Under the faint light, the young man's indifferent face was reflected on the dagger.

Right now, Fang Yuan couldn't help but think of a martial arts skill book from Earth called the <Sacred Sunflower Scroll>.

The first sentence in the first page of <Sacred Sunflower Scroll> was 'Castrate yourself to train this skill."

One needed to give up or pay something if they wanted to receive quick strength!

So what if you needed to castrate yourself?

If you don't have such ruthless decisiveness and aren't willing to let go, how could you accomplish your ambitions and become a lord ruling over everything?

Wanting to receive without paying anything was only fairytales to deceive children.

Back to Fang Yuan's current state, to use this Earth Communication Ear Grass, the price he needed to pay couldn't amount to anything.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan coldly smiled.

He used his fingers to lightly caress the cold blade and softly hummed—

Moon like the frost-filled night, the dagger shines with a cold light.

If not for the harshness of the winter, how could we look forward to spring!

He quickly moved his hand.

The hand rose and the dagger fell; blood burst out.

A piece of flesh fell on the table—

Fang Yuan had cut apart his whole right ear and blood was spurting out of it.

He first felt a little cool before an intense burst of pain suddenly attacked him.

He gritted his teeth and sucked in breath through his teeth. He resisted the pain and called out Earth Communication Ear Grass from his aperture.

He had nurtured this Earth Communication Ear Grass back to its full vitality. It was now completely different from how it looked back when he just got it.

Back when he had taken it out of the Earth Treasury Flower, it was shrivelled and dull. Now, it was plump and warm; fat and big and had grown up to an adult palm size.

It was highly elastic and resembled the Buddha's drooping ear of Earth.

Fang Yuan pressed the Earth Communication Flesh Ear Gu on his wound at the right side of his head and immediately poured red steel primeval essence towards it.

The Earth Communication Flesh Ear Gu's roots immediately came to life and rapidly began to grow, taking root in Fang Yuan's wound.

Another burst of pain came!

Fang Yuan felt like dozens of earthworms were drilling towards his brain from his wound.

This feeling was painful and also nauseating.

Generally speaking, Gu Masters would use some Gu worms to numb their nerves in this stage. But Fang Yuan wasn't in that situation and could only rely on his iron willpower to forcefully endure it.

In the end, his body was that of a youth's, and Fang Yuan who endured this pain couldn't help but feel his body starting to sway.

More and more roots extended, entered his wound. Slowly, the Earth Communication Ear Grass glued together with the bloody wound, becoming Fang Yuan's new right ear.

Finally, there was no more blood flowing out of the wound, there wasn't even a scar.

However, Fang Yuan's face was pale; the pain had only slightly decreased, it was still tormenting him.

Veins bulged out from his head and his heart thumped rapidly.

At this stage, Fang Yuan was already finished for the most part, but some time was still necessary for his body to adapt to the Earth Communication Ear Grass.

He picked up a mirror and looked at it under the faint moonlight.

He saw his pale face and frowning brows in the mirror. His right ear was bigger than his left by over two times and looked like a deformity.

Fang Yuan didn't mind it; after looking at the mirror for a moment and seeing no problems, he felt satisfied.

He put the mirror down and picked up the towel. He dipped the towel in the warm water in the basin and wiped the bloodstains on his body.

He had no clothes on, so it was very easy to clean the bloodstains. Some blood had flowed down his foot but were absorbed by the cotton cloth spread on the floor.

Fang Yuan cleaned the bloodstains, then picked up his right ear from the table.

He coldly snorted, then used the Moonglow Gu, slicing his own right ear into meat paste and completely destroying it.

Fang Yuan held the basin filled with the watery blood and put it under the bed before throwing a piece of coal in it.

Only after doing all this did Fang Yuan lay down on the bed.

The pain had weakened for the most part but was still tormenting him.

Fang Yuan felt the pain in his head along with his heartbeat.

He did not know how much time had passed, but he finally fell into a deep sleep.

Chapter 129: Chainsaw Golden Centipede

When Fang Yuan woke up, it was already noon of the second day.

His headache was gone, and the intense pain had vanished completely.

He touched his ear subconsciously, the sense of touch no different from before. It was as if the cutting of his ear never happened last night.

He climbed down from his bed, finding a mirror to look at himself.

In the mirror, a young man's face was shown; he was not handsome, but his dark abyss-like iris, made him stand out from mortals, showing a special unique coolness and charisma.

The young man's ears were the same as any others.

Last night, when he planted the Earth Communication Ear Grass, Fang Yuan's right ear was plump and big, his ear drooping till it nearly reached his chin. But now it was completely normal from appearance, there was nothing different.

This is because his body and the Earth Communication Ear Grass had gotten used to each other.

Fang Yuan's thought moved, and from his aperture a little red steel primeval essence flowed along his body, moving up towards his right ear.

At once, his hearing improved multiple times, and numerous footsteps could be heard.

Although he was on the second floor, he had a feeling of stepping on earth.

Fang Yuan paid attention and listened as his primeval essence continued to be used, and his hearing improved as well. In the mirror, roots started to grow out of his ear.

These roots were like the roots of a thousand year ginseng, extending from his ear towards the outside, constantly growing longer and moving towards the ground.

At the same time, his right ear had the notion of becoming fatter.

Fang Yuan stopped using the Earth Communication Ear Grass, and a second later, the roots growing out of his ears retracted, and his right ear became normal again.

Of course, his hearing also went back to its initial state.

"This way, I have a recon-type Gu." Fang Yuan wore his upper shirt, taking out a water basin from under his bed.

Last night, the bloody water had turned into blackish dirty water due to the charcoal tossed in. The bloody towel submerged within was the same as well. There was still some white in the red colour initially, but now it was all covered by the black soot. It was easy to make people assume that it was a cloth for wiping grease in the kitchen.

This basin when brought out, even if it was poured in front of someone, nobody would notice.

Summer was coming, and many clansmen were trying to clean the stove that they used in winter. Often they would end up with a basin of dirty water just like this.

While the iron was still hot, Fang Yuan entered the rock crack secret cave again.

This time, he did not enter empty-handed, but caught a deerling outside and tied its four limbs together. He used a steel contraption to bind its mouth, and then used the Stealth Scales Gu to hide his presence and brought it to the rock door.

He did not open the door in a hurry, but activated the Earth Communication Ear Grass.

The roots extended from his ear, and his hearing ability amplified.

Dongdongdong...

Firstly, he heard a light sound, the sound of slow heartbeat.

As the roots grew longer, the heartbeat became louder, and the sources of sound also increased.

Fang Yuan did not need to think to realize that these heartbeats were coming from the jade eye stone monkeys in the rock forest.

His shut his eye and he could imagine in his head, the owners of these sounds hiding in their caves, curling into a ball and sleeping.

But this was not what he wanted to find out.

He continued listening, his right ear already becoming slightly fat, the ginseng limbs growing out of his ear almost half a metre long, the roots having sentience. They extended to the rock door, and stabbed in rather shallowly.

At this moment, Fang Yuan felt that his hearing had a gigantic boost.

With him as center, he could hear the numerous noises of a three hundred step radius!

This was the Earth Communication Ear Grass' true usage; what he did in the village was merely a test.

If the Earth Communication Ear Grass' roots did not touch the ground, for a Rank two recon Gu, it was at a very average level. But once the roots are in the ground, its range would drastically improve.

This was understandable.

On earth, the theory was that sound travels at a speed related to its intermediary. Sound in the earth or in water, the speed of transmission was far greater than through air.

In ancient China, some soldiers in war when sleeping, would use a wooden quiver as their pillow. Once any cavalry attacks, the soldiers would hear the noise from the earth and be awakened in time. If they waited for sound to travel by air, they would not have time to react.

The roots grew into the rock door, and Fang Yuan could instantly hear the commotion behind it.

It was a very scrambled and confusing noise, but very frequent. Compared to this noise, the stone monkeys' heartbeat was like the sound of drums.

If a newbie was using this Earth Communication Ear Grass for the first time, upon hearing this they would be thinking of all the possible guesses. But to Fang Yuan, this noise was expected, and he only listened for a while before frowning.

He pushed open the rock door.

The rock door was heavy, but with his strength of two boars now, it was easy.

The rock door opened, and a dark long tunnel appeared in front of him, stretching on at a straight line, towards the unknown.

Fang Yuan untied the deer he had caught, and tossed it into the tunnel.

The deerling was very smart. Sensing the dangers of the dark path ahead, it did not dare to move forward. Its huge eyes stared at Fang Yuan, showing fear and a begging intention.

Fang Yuan snorted and threw a moonblade.

This moonblade was controlled to be small, slicing vertically and inflicting a light wound on the deerling's body.

The blood gushed out from its wound, and under the pain, the deerling's fear towards Fang Yuan won and it rushed into the dark tunnel.

Darkness soon engulfed it.

Fang Yuan activated the Earth Communication Ear Grass again, this time the roots grew into the walls.

His hearing amplified, and first he heard the deerling's footsteps, its heartbeat, and some other noise.

Golden Centipede's cave is precarious, Earth Communication is the way to avoid the disaster...

Fang Yuan knew in his heart that these noises were the movement sound of a centipede.

In his ear, he could hear the deerling's cries.

Evidently, it had gone into the cave and met the centipede.

Fang Yuan could see the image in his mind, the flustered deerling attacked by a centipede swarm, completely engulfing it. The deerling turns around in fright, and as it kicks its young hooves it felt the sense of death approaching and gave cries for help.

Uncountable number of centipedes climbed onto its body, and the deer laid on the ground, rolling and struggling.

Only after a while later, its heartbeat stopped.

The centipede army started to consume the deerling meat on its body.

Fang Yuan's gaze shone as he heard a special sound.

This sound was like a buzzing, like the turning on of a chainsaw; it was full of arrogance, dominance, and wildness.

If a newbie heard this, they would be confused. But with Fang Yuan's experience, he could guess the identity of this sound at once.

Rank three wild Gu worm—Chainsaw Golden Centipede!

This was the worm king in the centipedes, the true killer in the centipede cave.

Fang Yuan could completely imagine: A metre over in length, the breadth of two fists, coiling and slithering around the cave.

On the two sides of its body, there is a row of sharp saw-like teeth. As it moved, the chainsaws also moved around rapidly, just like an electric chainsaw.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede's arrival caused the centipede army to quieten.

It came ferociously, and wherever it went, the centipedes gave way, showing the half-body remains of the deerling.

It climbed to the deerling's body, opening its mouth and consuming the deer blood and deer meat, and when it got to the bones, it coiled its body up and used the chainsaws to lightly grind against the bones, turning it into powder easily.

"Even the White Jade Gu's defense cannot endure this Chainsaw Golden Centipede's attack. It seems that the Flower Wine Monk's intention is to make me use this Earth Communication Ear Grass and avoid the centipede. But I have the Spring Autumn Cicada, so to subdue this Chainsaw Golden Centipede, it is not impossible!" Fang Yuan had a thought in his head.

He was overjoyed at this prey.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede was an outstanding Gu worm. If it was his to use, it would be another strong method of attack.

Only that, in order to subdue this Chainsaw Golden Centipede, even a Rank four Gu Master would have to expend a lot of effort.

Catching and killing are two things, the former is way harder than the latter.

Wild Gu worms were all crafty, and if the Chainsaw Golden Centipede saw something amiss, it would burrow into the ground and escape. If a Gu Master did not have a burrowing method, how can he give chase?

But Fang Yuan had the Spring Autumn Cicada, thus as long as he caught this Chainsaw Golden Centipede and released a hint of the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura, he would make the Gu worm cower and not dare to move.

Spring Autumn Cicada was a Rank six, its aura was extremely powerful against Rank one to Rank four Gu worms. But against Rank five, it had less effect, and towards other Rank six, there was no deterrence force in it.

This phenomenon is very interesting, but actually human society is just the same.

Towards someone outstanding, people would envy, worship and admire. But to someone who is only slightly better performing, they would dare to offend, and was mostly competition and jealousy.

"I am only at Rank two middle stage now, hence to subdue this Rank three Chainsaw Golden Centipede, it is possible but still too early." Fang Yuan assessed.

Rank two Gu Masters should use Rank two Gu worms which is the most appropriate, and most useful. Of course, Rank two Gu Masters can also own Rank three or even Rank four Gu worms.

But this was not common.

Firstly, the higher rank the Gu worm, the more expensive it is to feed it. Secondly, they become harder to use and require more cost when activating. Like a baby trying to wield a large hammer, if it forcefully tried to, it might pull a muscle due to the hammer's weight and smash its own leg.

"The deerling has already alerted the entire colony, it would take ten days to half a month for these centipedes to calm down. After my testing, the thought in my heart has been affirmed, but I have no chance to strike yet. Why don't I slow down and give it some time, this matter cannot be rushed."

Fang Yuan left his thoughts here and closed the rock door again. He then left using the Stealth Scales Gu.

Chapter 130: Clansmen are still more reliable

Dark clouds covered the sky, casting shadows over the entire Qing Mao mountain, seemingly signifying the coming of a storm.

On a remote mountain side, a dozen robust lightning wolves drew back the corners of their mouth and made low roars. They had surrounded Fang Yuan.

These wolves had a healthy body and were not like the crippled wolves.

Any other Rank two Gu Master would be desperate if they were caught in such besiegement, alone. However, the situation was quite opposite right now.

Fang Yuan was standing on the spot, his expression calm. Instead, these lightning wolves that were surrounding him were slightly nervous and afraid.

The battle had already continued for a while and the ground was soaked with blood. Several lightning wolves had collapsed on the ground, and the silence showed Fang Yuan's battle accomplishments.

Kill!

Fang Yuan shouted inwardly, he took the initiative to attack even though he was the one surrounded. His foot pushed the ground as he pounced towards a lightning wolf on his left side.

This lightning wolf immediately shrunk back a small step in fear, but then its vicious personality was stimulated; it made a powerful jump and attacked Fang Yuan.

It opened its mouth in the air, revealing the many sharp wolf teeth that filled its mouth.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly; he didn't evade but just swung his right arm.Whoosh.An eerie-blue moonblade flew horizontally through the air and struck the lightning wolf's open mouth.

There was only a ripping noise, this unfortunate lightning wolf was instantly cut apart into two—from its mouth to tail—by this moonblade.

Boiling blood spurted out and poured like a rain of blood.

Fang Yuan's whole body flashed with white jade light as he charged through the blood rain and rampaged within the wolf pack.

The lightning wolves reacted, they attacked him from all sides. They opened their mouths and tore at him but were blocked by the White Jade Gu's defense, causing their own teeth to be broken.

Their claws were also of no use.

Fang Yuan punched and kicked, and the lightning wolves were sent flying under his enormous strength of two boars. Some lightning wolves had their skulls directly smashed and died on the spot. Fang Yuan grasped the upper hand in this battle.

But good things don't last forever, for his primeval essence was being used quickly.

Fang Yuan's aptitude was only C grade and his cultivation was at Rank two middle stage currently. The primeval essence in his aperture was not even fifty percent.

He looked at his declining primeval essence, but there were still several lightning wolves remaining. He had no choice but to use—Stealth Scales Gu!

His body gradually disappeared like the ripples in the water. In a blink of an eye, there was no more trace of him.

The lightning wolves were at their wits' end, and they gave off furious howls and started searing the area but didn't find anything.

Fang Yuan had not gone far. He gazed at the lightning wolves' movements while absorbing primeval stones to recover his primeval essence and also maintaining the concealment of the Stealth Scales Gu at the same time.

Lightning wolves had extraordinary eyesight but their sense of smell were not sharp. The Stealth Scales Gu just so happened to be their bane.

When Fang Yuan's primeval essence recovered to thirty percent, the lightning wolf pack finally retreated unwillingly.

Fang Yuan didn't have a movement Gu worm, so if the lightning wolves really retreated, he would definitely not be able to catch up to them with his speed. Thus, he removed the concealment of the Stealth Scales Gu and became visible.Hooooowl!

The lightning wolves saw Fang Yuan and as if he had killed their fathers, they rushed at him.

Fang Yuan sneered. He waited till the lightning wolves were in front of him, then he suddenly struck with his right hand.

His right fist was covered with a layer of faint white jade light which was extremely hard. The punch ferociously struck a lightning wolf's lower back.

Crack. A crisp sound was heard immediately and this unlucky lightning wolf was sent flying by Fang Yuan, its lower back fractured.

It fell on the ground and crazily struggled while letting out miserable howls, but it could no longer get up.

Fang Yuan had recovered sufficient primeval essence and with his formidable fighting strength, he killed four more lightning wolves in a few moments.

The remaining several lightning wolves lost their fighting spirit and looked at Fang Yuan with fear. They whimpered and then tucked their tails and escaped.

Fang Yuan didn't chase after them.

He couldn't compare to these lightning wolves in speed; chasing was pointless.

The ground was filled with wolf corpses and they were all Fang Yuan's spoils of war. But Fang Yuan was cautious, he didn't hurry to take out the lightning wolves' eyeballs.

Earth Communication Ear Grass!

He got down on his hands, his right ear close to the earth. Roots grew out from the ear and pierced the soil.

His hearing strength amplified instantly; he could scout anything within a three hundred step radius.

Many sounds entered his ear, but there were no sounds of wolf packs or the sounds of other Gu Masters moving about.

"It is safe for the moment." Fang Yuan let out a breath of relief. He took out a dagger and began to dig out the eyeballs of the lightning wolves.

He only handed over a small part of these eyeballs and hid the rest.

If he handed all of them, it would no doubt attract suspicions and even result to secret investigations. Fang Yuan wanted to prevent such inconveniences as much as possible.

Fang Yuan immediately left after digging out all the eyeballs of these lightning wolves.

When he had killed two more wolf packs like this, the sky was already covered with thick dark clouds. Strong wind blew, blowing through the pine forests, creating a green wave in the mountain along with the rustling of the leaves.

Hoooowllll...

Faint howls of large numbers of lightning wolves echoed within the wind.

Fang Yuan's expression slightly paled; according to his previous life's memories, today was the day the wolf tide truly broke out.

He used the Earth Communication Ear Grass again but didn't hear the rapid advancement of the lightning wolves.

He wasn't surprised, but instead became calm.

This meant that there was at least over a three hundred step gap away between him and the lightning wolves. This distance along with his own speed and the knowledge of the topography, sufficed to let him reach the village safely.

"These lightning wolves are cunning, choosing to attack in such weather. The noise from the strong wind and the sounds from the pine forest will mask their movements to a great degree," Fang Yuan sighed inwardly, then ran towards the village with his greatest speed.

After running for hundreds of meters, he bumped into a five person Gu Master group.

"Hey, you are Gu Yue Fang Yuan!" A young Gu Master in the group raised his eyebrows when he saw Fang Yuan and greeted him in an odd way.

This Gu Master was Gu Yue Peng, Fang Yuan's classmate. During the academy period, he had suffered from Fang Yuan's bullying and extortion.Fang Yuan indifferently glanced at him before brushing past him without pausing, not giving him a chance to speak again.

"Bastard!" Gu Yue Peng was stunned, then a stifled feeling rose up in his heart and his speed slowed down.

He didn't get the chance to ridicule Fang Yuan.

"Little Peng. Don't slow down. We need to hunt at least fifty lightning wolves today to preserve our rank in the battle merit board!" The group leader spoke.

Gu Yue Peng immediately restrained his furious expression and quickly followed the group members.

"My group is ranked seventy-five in the battle merit board. That Fang Yuan is ranked at beyond two hundred. This difference is like that of heaven and earth! I am also quite fortunate to have such a caring senior as the group leader. From the start of the wolf tide till now, I have exchanged part of the battle merits to get a Gu worm. My future is bright, how could Fang Yuan compare to me?"

Gu Yue Peng calmed down a lot when he thought of this, even feeling blessed at that.

"In this world, what can one accomplish by fighting alone? Many hands make light work, unity is the greater power. It is still the clansmen that are reliable! Borrowing the clan's strength, we newbies can safely grow up. That Fang Yuan is an idiot, he really thinks he is a hero. He resolved the problem of the Rank Five River Swallowing Toad only by luck and he is putting on airs. Although he has become a group leader, he hasn't recruited any group members, serves him right to be ranked last! Haha. Anyway, with his eccentric personality, how will he recruit any group members?"

Gu Yue Peng's movement became more relaxed.

Strangely, all along the way, they hadn't run into any wolf packs.

Gu Yue Peng raised his head to look at the sky, it was afternoon but the sky was already dusky as if it was evening.

The wind blew, and the dark clouds densely covered the sky and moved rapidly, brewing thunder and rainstorm.

However, Gu Yue Peng was not afraid, a mocking smile appearing on his mouth as he thought, "Hahaha, so Fang Yuan was hurriedly rushing back because he was worried of this rainstorm? What a coward, what is there to be afraid of a rainstorm?"

Right at this time, the group leader's face suddenly paled, he opened his mouth and sucked in a deep breath.

"Sir group leader, what happened?" Other four members naturally noticed this.

In this Gu Master group, the group leader was in charge of scouting. Although he was also a Rank two Gu Master, his scouting Gu worm didn't have as great a radius as Fang Yuan's Earth Communication Ear Grass.

His face was deathly white right now and he had no wish to give detailed explanation.

"Run, quick!" He shouted with terror and amidst other group members' astonished gazes, he turned around and ran.

"Follow the group leader!!" Other group members were not foolish, they quickly reacted and broke into a run.

Hoooowllll——!

Wolf howls came from behind them continuously. From these noises, they knew there was more than a thousand lightning wolves!

Everyone in the group was pale, they breathed heavily and used all their strength to run.

"Wait for me!" Gu Yue Peng sprinted with all he had but was still the last; he lost his composure and started screaming for help.

He felt the breathing sounds of the lightning wolves behind his back.

But what made him despair was the group leader who normally showed great consideration to him, didn't even turn his head back. The teammates who used to pat their chests and speak of brotherhood and sentiments ignored his shouts.

Houuu!

Gu Yue Peng suddenly heard a wolf howl right next to him.

In the next moment, he felt an enormous force pressed on his back and knocking him down.

He tumbled on the ground; the fall had made him dizzy.He subconsciously turned around to try to resist.

Boom!

A lightning snake flashed through the air.In the darkness, a bold lightning wolf's figure immediately became visible.

Its body was twice the size of a normal lightning wolf, the hair in its body erect. It opened its mouth and revealed its silver white sharp fangs.

Gu Yue Peng's pupils shrank to a needle size, a thought echoing within his mind—"Hundred beast king!"

The wolf pack's scale in the wolf nest was enormous; not only were there three myriad beast king level thunder crown wolves, there were also hundred beast king level bold lightning wolves and thousand beast king level frenzy lightning wolves.

In the very next second, the bold lightning wolf opened its mouth and with a crack sound, Gu Yue Peng's whole head was gnawed off.

Fresh blood and brain matter splashed. The bold lightning wolf lowered its head and began to swallow the blood from Gu Yue Peng's neck and gnawed at his fatty meat.

Countless lightning wolves came from behind it and rushed ahead.

Rumbling sounds continued incessantly.Pitter-patter, heavy rain also started pouring.

The true wolf tide had begun!

Chapter 131: Loneliness is the deepest darkness

The rain poured heavily from above, and snake-like lightning danced in the sky randomly. This sustained for the entire night.

Fang Yuan lay on his bed, hearing the shouting of Gu Masters outside his house and the sound of their footsteps in the rain.

He squinted his eyes, visions of his past life flashing in his head again.

In his previous life when the wolf tide attacked, he was still a Rank one Gu Master, and being part of the support group, he hid within the village and managed to escape the disastrous fate.

But this time, he was already a Rank two middle stage, and he had the Four Flavor Liquor worm, currently moving towards upper stage. Thus, he had to be like other Gu Masters, resisting the wolf tide in such a dark night.

The rain is pouring outside, and they still have to fight the large amount of lightning wolves in this poor vision, this is truly torture. Fang Yuan snorted in his heart.

He did not sleep in the rented apartment, but instead he was at the inn.

If Fang Yuan was at the rented house, he would definitely be forced to participate.

"The clan higher-ups have definitely underestimated this wolf tide's severity, the correct method would be to hide in the village and defend to the end. Unfortunately, they are blinded by past experiences..." Fang Yuan flipped around in his bed while thinking about this.

Outside the window, the rain splattered all over the place, it was definitely a storm.

Sounds of thunder constantly entered his ears.

On the streets, Gu Masters hurriedly moved about, the sounds of their footsteps and furious bellows never having a pause.

At once, the cries of the wolves reached the village.

This was destined to be a sleepless night.

Whether it was the Gu Masters who were risking their lives fighting, or the mortals hiding in the village shivering, or even Fang Yuan. After sleeping until the midnight hour, they naturally awoke.

He did not get up, but opened his eyes in the darkness while lying on his bed.

The sounds outside the window entered his ears. People's life and death battles, he could imagine, along with the thunderstorm outside the village. Gu Masters and wolf packs formed an extraordinarily lively stage. No matter which character, they were displaying the essence of life.

Life was like a show, this was a good show. But Fang Yuan had no intentions of joining the act.

On the contrary, he felt a sense of unexplainable loneliness.

A loneliness with boundary.

This was not because he was a transmigrator, reincarnator, or the fact that he carried an unspeakable secret.

But because everyone was born lonely!

Humans are like isolated islands, floating in the sea of fate.

Human encounters are like the collision of these lonely islands, and once they touch, there would be an effect.

Sometimes, the islands would stick together, in the name of 'interest', 'kinship', 'friendship', 'love' and 'hate'.

But eventually, they would separate, walking towards the path of destruction.

This is the truth behind life.

Unfortunately people are always afraid of being alone, they craved the liveliness of human crowd, and they refused to do nothing with their time.

Because once they face loneliness, it meant facing pain and hardship.

But once they can face this pain, people would obtain talent and courage. Thus, there is a saying—High achievers are definitely lonely.

"This is the feeling of being lonely. Every time I savour this, it strengthens my resolve to pursue the demonic way!" Fang Yuan's gaze shone, thinking of the story of Ren Zu.

Legend says, Ren Zu had obtained the Attitude Gu. Attitude Gu was like a mask, and without a heart Ren Zu couldn't wear it.

Because before this, Ren Zu had given his heart to the Hope Gu, and from then on he never feared difficulty.

But if Ren Zu wanted to use the Attitude Gu, he needed to have a heart.

Ren Zu was troubled, thus he asked Attitude Gu; he said, "Oh Gu, sometimes attitude says its all. Now that I have encountered a problem, you know it, thus I'm here to seek advice."

Attitude Gu said, "This is not hard. Ren Zu, you lack a heart, thus you just have to find a new one."

Ren Zu was confused, asking again, "Then how can I find a new heart?"

Attitude Gu sighed, "Heart, is nowhere and everywhere. Finding a heart, it is both easy and difficult. With your situation, you can obtain a heart now."

Ren Zu was overjoyed, "Quick, tell me, how?"

Attitude Gu warned him, "This heart, is called loneliness. Human, are you sure you want it? Once you obtain it, you will face endless pain, loneliness and even fear!"

Ren Zu did not listen to his warning, he continued asking.

Attitude Gu could not defy Ren Zu's orders, thus he said, "You only have to stare at the sky on a starry night, and say nothing. Once you reach daylight, you will obtain the heart of loneliness."

That night, it was a star-filled sky.

According to Attitude Gu's instructions, Ren Zu sat alone at the mountain peak, staring at the night sky.

Before this, his life was very difficult, constantly struggling for survival, he had no time to admire this beautiful yet mysterious sky.

But now, as he stared at the starry sky, his thoughts began floating. Constantly thinking about himself, such a meagre and weak being like himself, living a life of constant fear and insecurity.

"Sigh, although I have Hope Gu, Strength Gu, Rules and Regulation Gu, and Attitude Gu, to survive in this land, it is still difficult as ever. Even if I die tomorrow, it is not shocking. If I die, will the world remember me? Will anyone rejoice over my existence, and grieve over my death?"

Thinking of this, Ren Zu shook his head.

In this world, he was the only human, how can there be others?

Even with Gu accompanying him, he still felt a strong sense of —

Loneliness.

Heart of loneliness!

At this moment, when Ren Zu felt lonely, his body suddenly had a brand new heart.

The sun rose from the horizon, and shone on his face. But Ren Zu felt no happiness, and instead felt an endless pain, despair, confusion and even fear.

He could not endure this loneliness and fear, for all he felt was the advent of darkness and apocalypse!

Thus, he painfully cried, stretching out his fingers and digging out his eyes.

His left eye fell onto the ground and transformed into a young man. He had golden hair and a strong body. Once he appeared, he kneeled at Ren Zu's feet, saying: "Oh Ren Zu, my father, I am your eldest son, Verdant Great Sun."

At the same time, his right eye turned into a young girl, and she held Ren Zu's hand, saying, "Oh Ren Zu, my father, I am your second daughter, Desolate Ancient Moon."

Ren Zu laughed loudly, tears flowing out of his empty sockets. He said 'good' three times and continued, "I have children now, I can finally endure the pain of the heart of loneliness. From now one, there will be people celebrating my existence, and grieving for my death, even if I die now, you will remember me."

"Only that..." Finally, he sighed. "I lost both my eyes, and can no longer see the light. From now on, you two shall observe this world for me."

It rained the entire night, only at dawn did the rain stop.

Fang Yuan left the inn. Along the streets the passersbies carried heavy and sad expressions.

This night, the clan suffered great losses.

The truth was, for the three clans on Qing Mao mountain, none of them escaped this fate; all had suffered heavy losses.

Fang Yuan could tell from seeing the merit board.

After a night, the battle merit board lost twenty-five small groups, all sacrificed in the wolf tide. Even if there were one or two survivors, they were either injured or crippled.

The group Gu Yue Peng was in, was among this.

The dozen over days after this, the situation worsened by the day.

First, the hundred beast king bold lightning wolf had appeared, and then soon after, reports came in that there was the thousand beast king frenzy lightning wolf!

Information like this, caused the Rank two Gu Masters battling to be frightened.

If they met the frenzy lightning wolf, they would need at least three groups to cooperate to deal with it. This is not including the normal wolf groups together with the frenzy lightning wolf.

The three clans had to send out their Rank three elders to deal with the situation.

In this situation, the Gu Masters' daily lives became very dangerous and long.

Even with the Stealth Scales Gu, Fang Yuan had to be careful and meticulous. After all, he might encounter a beast king class lightning wolf with a Lightning Eye Gu.

The good news was that he had previously paid a price to be able to use the Earth Communication Ear Grass.

This investigative Gu's range was very large, allowing him to avoid the large-sized wolf packs.

Eventually, the weather got warmer as July was at its end. Even though the situation was not optimistic, under the cooperation of the three clans, the situation was under control.

Somewhere near the mountainside.

Three Gu Masters who had already experienced an intense battle were facing against a bold lightning wolf that had just arrived.

The aura of death was impending.

"Damn it, insufficient primeval essence, if I had 60%, no just 30%, we would not have to be chased like this!" Group leader Xiong Zhan stared at the slowly approaching bold lightning wolf, like a cat chasing a mouse, he vomited a mouthful of bloody water.

"The mountain cliff is ahead, there is no path left, what do we do?" A group member asked with a pale expression.

"What can we do? We can only put our hopes on the reinforcements. I heard lord Bai Ning Bing from my clan has come out of his closed door cultivation and is rushing into battle."

The two original groups, from both the Xiong clan and Bai clan, faced the wolf tide together and cooperated, but now only three people were left.

"Rather than relying on the Bai Ning Bing who is nowhere to be found, I'd rather fight for a chance to survive!" Xiong Zhan gritted his teeth, "The reason why a beast king is so dangerous, is because of the Gu on its body. I have a Plunder Gu, it can forcefully steal a Gu worm from my enemy. But it needs to be sustained when activated and I cannot move. During this period, you have to protect me."

"Okay!" The other two looked at each other and stood in front of Xiong Zhan, helping him block the bold lightning wolf.

Even though they knew that there was little hope, no one was willing to resign themselves to death.

"If the plunder is successful, we have a chance to live! Heaven bless us!" Xiong Zhan's face was determined as he raised his right arm.

Life and death depends on this!

The three humans and one wolf did not know that, high up on the cliff, a white haired young man wearing a white shirt was staring at this scene.

"Life is so boring..." He sat on the ground, one hand propping himself up, while the other was pouring liquid from his wine bottle.

What he poured out was not wine, but sweet mountain springwater.

He did not drink wine, but only liked water.

As this young man drank, he stared at the show before him.

"Fight, and die. Such a mundane life is too boring. Only with an intense battle like this, can your lives have a hint of excitement and colour. This way, your life has some meaning."

He laughed lightly in his heart, not showing any inclination to help.

Even if he had the ability, even if his Bai clan member was there.

So what?

To him, loneliness is the deepest darkness, and the light of kinship is just a facade.

He Bai Ning Bing would not do something as boring as saving someone!

Chapter 132: Three Step Fragrant Grass

On the cliff, Bai Ning Bing watched with interest.

As he sat at the cliff, a life and death battle was on full display.

The bold lightning wolf took its move, slowly approaching.

Two Gu Masters blocked its path with a grim expression.

Behind them, Xiong Zhan was half-kneeling on the ground, his left hand grabbing his right wrist, his right hand in the shape of a claw, aiming at the bold lightning wolf.

"Plunder Gu!" Suddenly, he shouted loudly, all the primeval essence in his body gushing towards the Plunder Gu.

An invisible grabbing force exploded from within.

Xiong Zhan's right hand grabbed the air, and a sense of illusion made him feel that he had grabbed onto a Gu worm.

But this Gu worm continued to struggle, contesting with him.

This force was very large; his center of gravity had already been very low, but he still felt a very strong force dragging him forward.

"Plunder Gu's success rate is very low, but I have to succeed this time, otherwise we're doomed!" He gritted his teeth, veins popping up on his forehead as his expression turned ferocious, contesting with all his ability.

Xiong Zhan had no other way.

Failure means death!

Under the pressure of death, he infused the Plunder Gu with all the primeval essence he could muster. With the infusion of the primeval essence, the Plunder Gu residing in his right palm also increased its sucking force. The bold lightning wolf felt something amiss, and started howling, attacking in a frenzy.

The two Gu Masters could hardly block it.

Just when Xiong Zhan felt that his plunder was going to succeed, his expression changed.

"Damn it, not enough primeval essence!" He suddenly vomited a mouthful of blood, his state of health being at the worst. Once a plunder fails, he would face some backlash. This was a flaw of the Plunder Gu.

Howl!

Without the Plunder Gu's restriction, the bold lightning wolf opened its mouth, and started to howl.

The Gu worm that lived within it used its ability, and made its teeth shine with lightning.

Eerie blue lightning discharged and finally shot out from its mouth.

The lightning shot through the middle of both Gu Masters, aiming for the half kneeling Xiong Zhan.

Xiong Zhan did not even have time to cry before he got hit by the lightning, turning into a piece of charred black cooked meat, instantly dead.

"Run!" The remaining two Gu Masters no longer had any fighting spirit as they ran in two directions.

The bold lightning wolf chased up to one of them, pouncing on him and biting the throat.

The final Bai clan Gu Master was blocked by the bold lightning wolf, and could only retreat towards the cliff.

"Ahhhhh. I'm going to die!" With his back against the cliff, he roared in despair, venting out the fear in his heart.

But suddenly his voice came to a stop—He saw Bai Ning Bing on top of the cliff.

"Lord Bai Ning Bing! Lord Bai Ning Bing, is that really you?" He was stunned but then started shouting, overjoyed.

"Oops, you found me," Bai Ning Bing laughed, and raised his right hand.

His right index finger pointed downwards and an icicle instantly formed, shooting downwards.

The icicle hit the Gu Master crying for help, penetrating his skull, all the way to his chin.

"Ah!" His face was still fixed with intense joy after finding hope, but then fell to the ground with a plop.

The bold lightning wolf was shocked by the event.

It stared at Bai Ning Bing, its mouth opening. Within, lightning coiled around its teeth.

"Ignorant beast." Bai Ning Bing stared plainly, jumping down lightly from the five metre cliff.

In the air, he clapped his palms together, and icy mist instantly formed.

Next his palms splitted, and an ice blade appeared.

This ice blade was around 1.7m, like the katana on Earth, with a transparent icy body. The handle was grabbed by Bai Ning Bing.

Bold lightning wolf shot out electric light from bottom to up, and Bai Ning Bing laughed while two lines of white water vapour poured out of his nose.

The water vapour swirled around, wrapping around his body into a layer of water barrier.

The water ball continued to rotate on its own, and the bold lightning wolf's lightning dissipated upon hitting this barrier.

The water ball burst open, and the white clothed young man appeared from within.

"Die." The young man's iris turned from black to pure blue, like two pieces of blue crystal, devoid of feelings and emotion.

The light of the blade shone.

Bai Ning Bing landed lightly, and from his half-transparent white ice blade, a drop of blood fell.

Meanwhile, the bold lightning wolf stayed still like a statue.

A breath later, fresh blood poured from its neck as the large wolf head fell on the ground, rolling several times. As for the body, it collapsed on the ground.

The Lightning Current Gu that resided in its body shot out like lightning towards Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing flicked his wrist, and a light shot out from his blade.

The Lightning Current Gu, under his sword, exploded into a ball of eerie blue lightning current with a bang, perishing instantly.

Bai Ning Bing slowly walked towards Xiong Zhan's corpse.

"The other Gu worms, they are all ordinary. But this Plunder Gu is slightly interesting." From Xiong Zhan's corpse, he extracted the Plunder Gu and held it near his chest.

Even though the three clans have an agreement—after a Gu Master dies, if anyone after that obtains a Gu worm that has lost its Gu Master, they need to hand it over.

But Bai Ning Bing did not care about this rule.

Even if they found out, so what?

He was the symbol of the Bai clan's rise, and the clan would definitely protect him.

This, he was very sure of.

"Only... this wolf tide is really boring." He used his hand to caress his ice blade, feeling the intense freezing sensation.

"Come to think about it, it is more fun competing with someone." He yawned, suddenly smiling, "I wonder how Qing Shu, Xiong Li and the others are doing, how much have they grown? After cultivating behind closed doors for so long, maybe they can give me a surprise, maybe."

Days later.

At the square where it was overflowing with people, Fang Yuan stared at a giant flag.

On the flag, words were formed by the Swimword Gu. The content was about the resources co-supplied by the three clans.

These resources were very broadly categorized, from food used to feed Gu worms, rice and condiments for humans, oil and other living necessities, to Gu worms themselves and primeval stones.

But behind these resources, there was a number attached to them, corresponding to the amount of merit points needed to exchange for them.

A wolf's eye was ten merit points, and five merit points was for a bag of 500g of rice. Using twenty-five merit points could let a Gu Master exchange for one primeval stone.

Undoubtedly, the arrival of the wolf tide brought about an opportunity never seen before during peaceful times.

The battle merit board and this resource board urged on many Gu Masters, making them willingly bath in warm blood, hunting lightning wolves day and night.

Especially recently, as the wolf tide intensified, the three clans brought out the savings they had and spurred on the Gu Masters' battle spirit, also raising their battle capability to help the village survive this ordeal.

Thus, the resource board had many things that were not commonly seen.

Like now, Fang Yuan's attention was on this Gu.

"Three Step Fragrant Grass Gu," he muttered, staring at the description on the large flag.

Three Step Fragrant Grass Gu was a Gu worm Fang Yuan needed, as it could assist with movement, raising Fang Yuan's running speed.

Honestly speaking, these days, the resource board had many new Gu worms. But only this Three Step Fragrant Grass Gu was what Fang Yuan wanted.

Except that this grass Gu was not easy to get. It was not only the only one of its kind on the resource board, but the merit points required to exchange for it is also very high.

"If I use my true ability, I can definitely gather enough merit points to exchange for this Three Step Fragrant Grass Gu. But if I do that, it would invite the suspicion of the clan, and that is not desirable."

Fang Yuan thought silently.

"There is another way, and that is to produce a large amount of vitality leaves and sell these Rank one Gu to the clan, exchanging it for merit points. But this method is slow, by the time I get enough points, someone might have exchanged it already."

Fang Yuan shook his head internally, this method had a flaw that would lead to failure.

Then what should he do?

He stared at the resource board and the merit board, falling into deep thought.

Towards the merit points, he had a clearer and deeper understanding of it compared to all the surrounding people.

Merit points are basically a kind of emergency currency.

During peacetime, primeval stones are the common medium of exchange. They were hard currency and had high commercial value in themselves, thus would never devalue.

But with the wolf tide, the need for primeval stones surged, and it could no longer be used as a currency. Thus, an emergency currency was needed to take over.

Thus, merit points were born.

"With an alternate currency like the merit point, it can prevent the economy from collapsing temporarily. Like on Earth, when there's a war, the government would print large amounts of paper money. Of course, that causes inflation and rising price levels. The merit points are the same; the more it drags on, the more it devalues. But during the time of the village's life and death situation, without merit points and using only primeval stones is not sustainable. Thus, they can only pick the lesser poison. Hence after the wolf tide, the economy always has signs of depression."

"Sigh, this rough form of an economy is nothing worth mentioning. If I am a Rank three, I can easily play around. But unfortunately, I do not have enough strength, so I'm unable to handle the risks. If I push on, it is equivalent to playing with fire."

Fang Yuan sighed internally.

The point was that his cultivation was not high, and his strength was not sufficient.

Without strength, only having wisdom, it is useless.

Thus, in Ren Zu's story, Ren Zu chose to deal with the Strength Gu, obtaining strength and giving up on wisdom.

That is because, strength is the foundation.

Fang Yuan was still thinking deeply when he heard the discussions of the people around him.

"Do you guys know? Bai Ning Bing struck again!"

"What, what, which unlucky Gu Master is it this time?"

"It's Xiong clan's Xiong Li, that dejected-looking one."

"Sigh, what is this Bai Ning Bing doing? Last time, injuring Chi Shan, and now attacking Xiong Li. With the wolf tide coming, he is still fooling around!"

"He's always does what he wants, he is already a Rank three Gu Master and is still finding problem with Rank two Gu Masters. For fairness, he even used a Gu worm to suppress his own cultivation to Rank two, he is really bored and hard to understand!"

"Bai Ning Bing huh... hmph, a person halfway into the coffin. But that reminded me of something." Fang Yuan upon hearing this felt something in his heart stir.

He knew how to get a large amount of merit points quickly.

Chapter 133: Thanks for letting me kill you

Sprinting rapidly!

The trees before Fang Yuan looked like they were crashing into him, and he quickly avoided them nimbly, pushing off with his legs.

His right ear had roots swaying around, and behind him was a bold lightning wolf angered by him on purpose and several hundred healthy ordinary lightning wolves.

The lightning wolves' speed was faster than him. Especially the bold lightning wolf, its streamlined body jolted around in the complicated terrain, having an extremely fast speed.

Seeing Fang Yuan who was about to be caught up, suddenly, his body had ripples of light around him, and he vanished.

The bold lightning wolf had to halt its steps and observe the surroundings with bewilderment.

Fang Yuan sprinted to a faraway place, before reappearing again.

Bold lightning wolf's eyesight was sharp, immediately finding him. It growled angrily and chased after Fang Yuan again.

As for those ordinary lightning wolves, they followed closely behind.

Fang Yuan laughed internally and continued sprinting.

Rinse and repeat, he had finally reached his destination. This time, he activated his stealth completely.

The wolf pack who came chasing sniffed around the area where Fang Yuan disappeared, and soon after, the bold lightning wolf found its new target.

Not far away, on the mountain valley, there were five Gu Masters fighting with a pack of wolves.

Howl!

The bold lightning wolf had limited IQ, immediately forgetting Fang Yuan. It turned its head and growled, and the lightning wolves behind it entered the valley's battlefield like tidal waves.

"How can this be?" The Gu Master in battle saw this scene and despaired.

"Didn't they say that each pack of wolves have their own mobility range?"

"We took so much effort to kill a bold lightning wolf, and here comes a second one! We're screwed."

"Quickly send the distress signal to the clan!"

This new pack of wolves joined in and the Gu Master's pressure intensified, their tone showing a panicky and flustered emotion.

The investigative Gu Master shot out a Gu worm from his hand.

This Gu worm was like a golden round ball, but had a pair of colourful feathered wings. It flew into midair and exploded, turning into a rainbow flame, observable from a 50km range.

This was the signal Gu, a Rank one expendable Gu worm, often used to send signals.

"The signal has been sent, everyone hang in there, wait for reinforcements!" The group leader shouted at an appropriate timing, slightly raising the morale and stabilizing their fighting spirits.

"It's useless." Fang Yuan appeared at a high point on the cliff, staring downwards, his heart smirking.

This Gu Master group's situation was already well investigated by him. The nearest group in the vicinity was also deep in the wolf pack's encirclement.

That pack of wolves was also lured over by Fang Yuan, to restrict them.

"Killing lightning wolves, each eyeball is ten merit points. But on the battlefield, reclaiming Gu worms and bringing them to the clan higher-ups is worth at least a thousand points! This kind of thing, after doing it two or three times, I will be able to exchange the Three Step Fragrant Grass Gu," Fang Yuan thought in his heart.

Under his scheme, the Gu Master group's fate was sealed.

"Next, I will wait for them to be exterminated. Then I shall lure the lightning wolf pack away and come back here to collect the Gu worms." Fang Yuan walked to a nearby tree and sat down leisurely.

No one was willing to die, so these Gu Masters put up a strong resistance.

Fang Yuan did not risk it to lure a thousand beast king frenzy lightning wolf, but instead chose the bold lightning wolf, so this gave them the opportunity to struggle for a longer time.

Especially when among them, there was a defeated opponent of Fang Yuan's.

Gu Yue Man Shi.

He had the Monolith Gu and had strong defense, thus he alone could block many lightning wolves' attack.

But, this was also why Fang Yuan chose their group.

The more precious the Gu worm, after returning them, the more merit points are awarded. After bringing back the Monolith Gu, Fang Yuan can get around 3900 merit points, and that can let his position on the battle merit board rise by at least twenty positions.

Of course, Chi Shan, Mo Yan and Qing Shu's Gu worms, were more precious than the Monolith Gu.

But Chi Shan's group had Gu Yue Chi She, who possessed the Snake Communication Gu, able to rely on heat to detect living beings. Fang Yuan's stealth had no use against him.

As for Mo Yan, she had an even stronger investigative Gu Master than Chi She, with even more methods. She had single-handedly completed wolf den investigation missions given by the clan many times.

Qing Shu group does not have a strong investigative Gu Master, but because of Gu Yue Fang Zheng's existence, the clan has definitely sent a clan elder to follow and protect him, thus if Fang Yuan lures them, it is courting death.

For the Gu Masters in the other two clans, Fang Yuan was not familiar with them.

Setting up others was not easy to do. After choosing left and right, he finally decided on a few groups, and after following them for a long while, he managed to find an appropriate chance.

Bai Ning Bing was sleeping when sounds of battles entered his ear.

His opened his eyes slightly, the slit of his eye shining with cold light.

"Another boring scene." He was sleeping on the edge of the cliff, and just turning around allowed him to have a clear view of the valley. He was about to go back to sleep, but suddenly saw a figure.

"Oh?" His eyes shone with shock as he saw Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was leaning against the tree, eating a wild fruit he picked, staring coldly at the battlefield with no intention to help.

Bai Ning Bing instantly grew interested, he had never met someone like this. From young, the people around him were all loyal to the clan, and indulged in kinship.

But from Fang Yuan, he felt a sense of familiarity, loneliness and aloofness.

"Who is he?" Bai Ning Bing's heart developed confusion and interest.

The wild fruit was picked on the spot, but with his experience, Fang Yuan could tell it was harmless.

The fruit was juicy, sour and sweet. As he ate, his right ear twitched; he heard something, and it was nearby!

Bai Ning Bing was sleeping on a higher terrain of the cliff earlier, but without making any movements, the Earth Communication Ear Grass could not sense him. However, now that he moved, he was instantly discovered.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with lightning as he turned his body to see a white haired and white clothed young man, stabbing his ice blade into the cliff and sliding down along it, landing not too far away.

Bai Ning Bing!

Fang Yuan's eyes squinted, recognising him instantly.

Qing Mao Mountain's number one genius, the symbol of Bai clan's rise. Killing a Rank three clan elder at Rank two, and at this young age he already reached Rank three, a crucial person capable of changing the entire power distribution of Qing Mao mountain!

If it was other Gu Masters facing Bai Ning Bing alone, their expression would be rapidly changing, either nervous or wary.

But Fang Yuan's gaze only stayed on him for a second before looking back at the valley. His expression was calm, almost uncaring. This is because Fang Yuan knew all about Bai Ning Bing's trump cards and secrets. Very clearly.

"Oh..." Bai Ning Bing walked over, staring at Fang Yuan blankly. His mouth opened, dragging his word.

He curiously stared at Fang Yuan like he was looking at an object he had never seen before.

He got closer and closer. The more he looked at Fang Yuan, the more his eyes shone, and the greater interest he had in his heart.

"On this person, why do I sense a familiar smell? It feels like I've seen him before. Like long ago, we are already friends, this feeling!" Bai Ning Bing's heart was turbulent.

Friend—This word, he was always sceptical, despising, and even felt disdain towards it.

He never thought he would have a friend. Those commoners around him, they only had the right to admire him, they had no right to become his friend.

Bai Ning Bing always thought, he would never have a friend in his life.

But now—he suddenly had this feeling!

This was a mystical feeling, but he was very sure of it. When he looked at Fang Yuan, it felt like he was looking at himself!

Bai Ning Bing got slightly too close, and Fang Yuan turned around, staring at him plainly with his deep dark iris.

Without a reason, Bai Ning Bing understood the meaning of his gaze.

It was a warning.

He halted his steps, slightly stunned, very impolitely staring at Fang Yuan while saying, "Eh, you really are interesting."

If the Bai clan Gu Masters who were familiar with him heard this, they would go crazy.

That is because, since his birth, Bai Ning Bing had never praised someone like this.

Fang Yuan ignored him, biting his wild fruit and staring at the valley's intense fight.

Bai Ning Bing circled around Fang Yuan, observing him closely. As if he was looking at the strangest food on earth. He looked from every angle, even squatting down on the ground and looking up at him from the floor.

His silky white hair which was impeccably clean like a crystal, instantly laid on the muddy ground, but he did not care.

His white robe dragged across the ground and he paid no heed either.

This moment, he was like a pure child, seeing his playmate, curiously staring at Fang Yuan with a longing expression, many times wanting to speak but couldn't.

Bai Ning Bing felt that he had many things to say to Fang Yuan, but when he was about to speak, he felt no need anymore, because he felt that Fang Yuan understood.

After being silent for a while, he asked, "The valley's battle is not interesting at all, what's there to look at."

Halfway through, his eyebrows raised, showing an expression of realization, "I see. You lured this wolf pack, you want to kill these Gu Masters, but why did you not do it yourself. Oh, afraid of leaving evidence. You are too vigilant, from your aura, you already have Rank two cultivation. If I were you, I'll just go ahead and do it myself!"

Suddenly, he chuckled like he had seen the most fun toy in this world as a kid. His eyebrows darted around, "You are really interesting, even the things you do are interesting. Hehehe, I am starting to like you!"

Fang Yuan retracted his gaze, turning around and looking at Bai Ning Bing.

He knew this person.

That is because this person is also a natural demon.

What is a demon?

Abandoning the worldly customs, treating the people of this world with indifference. Engulfed by loneliness, and despising relationships!

This person was like Fang Yuan's shadow, except that Fang Yuan was deeper down the path, and Bai Ning Bing was more pure.

In simple words, they were kindred spirits!

In his previous life's memory, after the three clans barely survived the wolf tide, this man murdered the three clans and caused the lustrous green Qing Mao Mountain to turn into a hellish ice mountain!

"Bai Ning Bing, Bai Ning Bing..." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart, saying slowly, "You're very lonely, huh."

Bai Ning Bing's eyes widened, squatting on the floor, nodding continuously, empathising and sighing, "Yes, these days, life has been super boring. Some time ago, I killed a Xiong clan Gu Master and that was somewhat fun. Getting this Gu, look."

Fang Yuan looked at the Plunder Gu in his hand, starting to laugh, "So, you want to kill me?"

Bai Ning Bing's eyes turned from black to blue crystal colour as he jumped up and straightened his body.

"Hahaha!" He raised his head and laughed thrice, staring at Fang Yuan with an excited expression, "You do know! That's right, I want to kill you, come kill me too. Life and death battles are the most fun, meeting someone as interesting as you, I swear I've never done anything so interesting!"

He got more and more excited as he suddenly opened both arms, arching his head and sighing, "Ahhhh! I can feel that my life had never been so colourful! Thank you, thank you, although I don't know your name, thank you for letting me kill you!!! Hehehe..."

Chapter 134: Hunting down

"Do not worry, you are only a Rank two, I will not lower myself and take advantage of you. I shall restrict my cultivation to the same rank for your sake; so come, let's have a fair fight!" Bai Ning Bing roared with savage laughter.

Facing the crazy Bai Ning Bing, Fang Yuan easily maintained a languid expression. He met the heated glare in an equal manner, responding coolly.

"Wanna kill me, then come."

Nothing left to say, Fang Yuan took the first step, his body drifting away like a falling petal.

Bai Ning Bing's laugh came to an abrupt stop at this, his voice easily tainted with anguish.

"Don't you run from me!"

He instantly ran after, engaging Fang Yuan in a relentless chase.

Fang Yuan ridiculed the disheveled master soundlessly, sprinting towards the mountain valley.

Disturbed by the two barging into the valley's inner battlefield, the wolf pack reacted with fury, wasting no time in attacking Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing.

The Gu Masters who had already been forced into the valley and lost one man noticed the spectacle, the remaining four revealing a relieved expression when they saw saw the wolves become distracted.

"Hang in there guys, reinforcements are here!" One even shouted loudly, blatantly trying to encourage the wolves against the newcomers.

"Why is there only two?" Another asked, clueless while they saw the muffled figures of Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing.

But as they got closer, Gu Yue Man Shi's face turned weird with realization.

"It's him!"

It was impossible for him to not remember Fang Yuan, along with a sharp feeling of fear mixed with shame; it was this man that had defeated and publicly humiliated him. Those cold, merciless eyes, dug out the deepest nightmare in his heart. He would never forget that terrifying event and the fiendish man who accompanied the memory.

He had once sworn to himself that he would buck up and reclaim his pride.

But now, faced with Fang Yuan who was here to 'save' him, Gu Yue Man Shi felt very complicated internally.

"Wait, the second person is..."

They all were able to recognise Bai Ning Bing, and showed collective signs of shock at his appearance.

"Bai Ning Bing ... Bai Ning Bing!" Gu Yue Man Shi's eyes widened, he did not expect in the least to suddenly see Bai Ning Bing appear under such a situation.

"Scumbag, stop right there!" Behind him, Bai Ning Bing was continuing to shout vehemently.

Fang Yuan paid no attention, however, and transversed among the wolf pack.

His body was glowing with a white jade light, protecting him from the rabid lightning wolves' bites and scratches. But because each assault made contact, his aperture's primeval essence dropped quickly in turn.

Not far away, Bai Ning Bing's nose had flared and was blowing out water vapour, forming into a round shield of condensed moisture, enveloping his body.

As each of the numerous lightning wolves hit this seemingly water shield, though, all of their kinetic force build up by their charge was simply dispersed by the water flow, and they were quickly sent flying away after with the resounding ripples of water.

Logically speaking, Bai Ning Bing's performance now wasn't that impressive though. He was already a Rank three, even though according to him, he had already seemed to have suppressed his cultivation personally, using only Rank two strength to deal with Fang Yuan.

Even with Rank two strength, Bai Ning Bing's speed was slightly faster than Fang Yuan's, and he had more primeval essence, but with the interference of the wolf pack, his distance with Fang Yuan started to increase.

The crucial deciding factor was the difference in physical strength between the two.

Fang Yuan had the strength of two boars, while Bai Ning Bing's strength was of a slightly lower quality. Fang Yuan could also endure the wolf pack's attacks and continue moving forward. Bai Ning Bing's water shield, although it is able to mitigate some of attacks, could not open a path forward for him, unlike Fang Yuan.

"Howl!"

One especially bold lightning wolf began to pay attention and was drawn to Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing.

It howled, commanding the ordinary lightning wolves around it to give way, opening a path for it instantly.

The lightning wolf wasted no time and spread its limbs, charging towards Fang Yuan.

Seeing this scene, the four trapped Gu Masters all showed expressions of worry.

As for Bai Ning Bing, still behind Fang Yuan, upon seeing this new development, laughed loudly.

But the next moment, Fang Yuan's body disappeared right before Bai Ning Bing's eyes, vanishing from his vision like a fleeting ripple of water.

His laughter cut off abruptly at the sight, the other Gu Masters in the valley being left similarly speechless.

The bold lightning wolf howled angrily after having lost track of Fang Yuan, but did not reduce its speed while charging towards Bai Ning Bing to take it's fury out on him instead.

This prompted a smile from Bai Ning Bing, his lips curving once more in amusement.

"Hehehe, this is really interesting- you really are interesting! Hahaha, then I shall start my meal with this appetizer!"

As he finished speaking, his eyes transitioned, changing from black to a shade of blue the same color as that of the sky.

Taking a stance, he propped one leg up like a flamingo, holding out the ice blade, and started to rotate. Quickly picking up speed, the ice blade carved out many waves of sword traces, maneuvering and slashing the air to form a scene similar to a tornado.

The bright sword waves congealed into a blizzard storm and quickly engulfed the wolf pack.

Numerous lightning wolves were torn to shreds by the act, becoming pieces of minced meat flung about by the storm. But not much blood ended up splattering against the surroundings, as it had almost all been completely flash frozen by the icy blizzard storm already.

The bold lightning wolf howled, showing its ferocity against the storm. The Gu worm in its body started to work as well, causing golden sparks of electricity to flicker throughout its rugged coat.

The hair on its body stood on ends, golden electricity flowed like chains, coiling around its body and limbs. Altogether it formed what looked to be a modest chainmail.

Its four paws sprinted and it streaked like a golden shooting star, rushing into the ice blade storm.

"Bam!"

A thunderous explosion sounded through the valley as the ice blade storm came to a stop, a broken piece of the ice blade flying in the air and with a swoosh, stabbed into a mountain rock above.

The white mist dispersed around the area.

The bold lightning wolf laid on the revealed ground, its heart pierced through by an ice blade. Such a fatal attack ended its life almost instantly.

Bai Ning Bing laughed as he retracted the ice blade in his hands, gloating in his victory.

The ice blade itself was broken from the middle down, the blade that managed to survive full of cracks, seemingly in a sorry state in his grip. But Bai Ning Bing did not care as he stretched out his left hand and wiped the blade.

The icy mist from before emanated from his left hand at the touch, spreading across the blade starting from the handle before covering it completely.

Everywhere it reached, the ice blade was regenerated, the edge being sharpened once again. Soon a new tip was fully grown in place of the broken end.

The death of the bold lightning wolf had dispersed the wolf pack, but Fang Yuan was nowhere to be seen.

"We will definitely remember Lord Bai Ning Bong's act of saving us!" The few Gu Masters that survived went up and gratefully paid their respects to Bai Ning Bing.

Only Gu Yue Man Shi stayed on the spot, his expression being uncertain.

Back then, he lost to Bai Ning Bing, and was very indignant, but was let off by the latter. Now, though he had already successfully refined the Monolith Gu, upon seeing Bai Ning Bing again, he did not have any confidence to challenge him anymore.

Bai Ning Bing snorted. Suddenly his arm moved, and the ice blade drew a few shining traces in the air.

"This..."

"Ah!"

The three Gu Masters were caught off guard, not expecting their savior just moments ago to attack. They carried a look of disbelief as they laid on the ground, forever.

"Bai Ning Bing, what are you doing?!" Gu Yue Man Shi screamed, shocked and angry at the sudden manslaughter.

"Murdering of course. Is something wrong in your head, isn't this obvious?" Bai Ning Bing shrugged and laughed coldly.

"Accursed bastard!" Gu Yu Man Shi tightly clenched his fists out of rage while he gritted his teeth and scolded the other master. "Our three clans have formed an alliance, yet you attack our Gu Yue clansman; this is a violation of our alliance treaty! If you have any problems, come at me, I'm here. Nevermind, it is time we settle our grudge from back then!"

Saying so, Gu Yue Man Shi shouted and took a few steps, charging towards Bai Ning Bing.

He activated the Monolith Gu with all his strength, and all the muscles on his body bulked up while a thick rock skin formed. His entire appearance had turned into a rock man.

"Courting death." Bai Ning Bing laughed coldly, raising his blade.

The sharp ice blade came down relentlessly, first hacking Gu Yue Man Shi's head, moving down past his brows before carving through his nose, lips and throat. The blade quickly came to a rest after it bisected the Gu Master down past his chest in an instant.

Rock fragments flew out as the ice blade hit the abdomen, and the blade snapped. But the icy mist had already frozen all the remaining life force left in Man Shi's body.

"Plop."

He fell to the ground with a splatter, as dead as can be.

The rock skin on his body slowly vanished, revealing his true form.

"Looks familiar..." Bai Ning Bing shook the wrist that was hurt by the vibration of the rock; he had pretty much forgotten the incident where he spared Man Shi.

He shook his head, turning around and facing the wide valley to shout.

"Come out. The Gu Masters you want dead, I've done it for you. Come come come, let's have a life and death match!"

Just as Bai Ning Bing's words had finished, Fang Yuan appeared not far away.

The white hair young man's gaze became excited, as he raised his ice blade, slashing towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed soundlessly at the act, turning around and leaving.

Bai Ning Bing shouted in anger that he was still fleeing, once again chasing Fang Yuan relentlessly.

On the way, Fang Yuan lured Bai Ning Bing to the battlefield that was the closest, where the Xiong Li group was fighting against another group of wolves led by a bold lightning wolf.

This pack was obviously lured by Fang Yuan as well.

"Everyone put in more effort, the wolf pack is at its limit! The south-east direction sent a distress signal, it's been a while, they need our help!" Xiong Li urged on his group, but halfway through, he could no longer speak when he saw Fang Yuan, and the Bai Ning Bing persistantly behind him.

Ever since Fang Yuan surrendered, Xiong Li no longer cared about him. Thus, his gaze quickly shifted from Fang Yuan to Bai Ning Bing.

"Bai Ning Bing!" Xiong Li's eyes spewed fire upon seeing the white clothed, white haired young man, his heart uncontrollably growing with rage.

Not long ago, Bai Ning Bing had appeared in front of him and attacked without a word, the event still fresh in his mind.

And had been purposely suppressing his cultivation to Rank two.

Xiong Li was caught off guard, and lost the battle. His personal honor, and the clan's glory, was all trampled by Bai Ning Bing ruthlessly! This to him, was a big disgrace, how could he not be furious?

"Wait, Bai Ning Bing seems to be chasing Fang Yuan." Xiong Lin suddenly noticed.

His body was short in stature, his round bald head glowing with light. Xiong Lin is the same age as Fang Yuan, but having B grade talent instead, he is the number one talent among Xiong clan's new Gu Masters of age.

He was a Rank two cultivator as well now, and after getting some experience, had grown up.

Xiong Li suppressed the urge to attack.

Fang Yuan was from the Gu Yue clan, not from his Xiong clan. Even though there was the three clan alliance, they are still not close. Since it is an outsider fighting, it is best if one does not get involved.

The Xiong Li group was about to watch on the sidelines, but how could Fang Yuan not expect that? One sentence from him changed their perspective in an instant.

Fang Yuan quickly got close to the Xiong Li group, shouting in a frightened voice.

"I saw the Plunder Gu on him, protect me! Bai Ning Bing is trying to eliminate all witnesses!"

Chapter 135: Northern Dark Ice Soul, Ten Extreme Talents

"What?!" Xiong Lin was stunned.

"Plunder Gu? There is only one person that has this Gu worm in Qing Mao mountain and that is my cousin Xiong Zhan!!" Xiong Jiang's face turned gloomy.

Xiong Li closed his eyes, fierce light flickering in them. Others might be afraid of Bai Ning Bing and even he was afraid, but this fear didn't represent his weakness and cowardice. In his heart, long was there already thoughts of sacrificing himself for the clan; he had the resolution to fight to the death with Bai Ning Bing!

"Bai Ning Bing, is the Plunder Gu in your possession?" He stepped forward and faced Bai Ning Bing, letting Fang Yuan brush past him.

Bai Ning Bing laughed coldly, "So what if it is?"

Xiong Jiang's face was as gloomy as water and asked, "Tell me how did my cousin die? Why is his Gu worm in your hands?"

Xiong Lin also asked, "Bai Ning Bing, I respect you as my senior but you secretly seized our Xiong clan's Gu worm and didn't hand it over. This is an open violation of the alliance treaty!"

After he spoke, he raised a Signal Gu in his hand.With a bang, bright fireworks burst in the sky.

The colorful light from the fireworks shone upon Bai Ning Bing's face. He laughed, "I have never cared about the dogshit alliance treaty. I only saw someone using the Plunder Gu and thought it was interesting, so I collected it."

Xiong Jiang was unable to hold back his anger when he heard this. He gave a furious shout and charged towards Bai Ning Bing, "Bai Ning Bing, you looked while my cousin fought to death and didn't help. You bastard!"

The five person group was an integral whole. For personal or private reasons, the Xiong Li group were irreconcilable with Bai Ning Bing.

The fight was hard to avoid; the scene immediately turning chaotic.

On one side was Bai Ning Bing facing the Xiong Li group's attack; on the other side, they were surrounded by wolf pack and still had to face their attacks.

Fang Yuan left the battlefield and calmly spectated from far away.

The wolf pack moved together like a large millstone, and the six Gu Masters fought with their lives; the slightest carelessness could land them into the wolves' mouths.

Xiong Jiang used Roaming Zombie Gu, his two irises turning gloomy green; Xiong Li's two eyes were red whereas Bai Ning Bing's pair of pupils were azure like crystals. The fight between these three was the most intense in the battlefield.

Under the Roaming Zombie Gu's ability, Xiong Jiang turned into a zombie; his defense was amplified against water and ice, withstanding Bai Ning Bing's attacks. Xiong Li used Grand Bear Gu; with the strength of two bears, his bowl-sized fists were without rival and even Bai Ning Bing's water barrier was destroyed under their attacks.

It wasn't easy for the remaining three group members to meddle in this fight, they could only do their utmost to fight against the lightning wolves. That bold lightning wolf lured in by Fang Yuan could have been easily dealt with, but it had turned into a huge threat now.

"Bai Ning Bing, you will pay for what you have done!" Xiong Jiang shouted and charged at Bai Ning Bing.

"Hmph, just with you?" Bai Ning Bing coldly smiled. He nimbly jumped back, pulling apart some distance and flung out his left hand, throwing out five finger-sized icicles.

The icicles struck Xiong Jiang's body but Xiong Jiang didn't feel any pain whatsoever. When he turned into a zombie, even if his hands and legs were broken, he wouldn't feel any pain.

The cold aura in the icicles could freeze and slow down ordinary people's movements, but it only felt cool and refreshing to Xiong Jiang. Zombie physique belonged to yin physiques; it had low resistance to fire, lightning and sunlight, but was very powerful against this type of cold aura.

"Bai Ning Bing, you are still playing in this situation? Unleash your true strength!" Xiong Li furiously shouted.

Bai Ning Bing had been suppressing his cultivation base to Rank two from the very beginning and was also mostly using Rank two Gu.

Xiong Li felt like he was being held in contempt, he felt humiliated which caused his anger to burn even more.

"Hahaha, how can you minor characters have the qualifications to make me use my full strength?" Bai Ning Bing coldly laughed; his attacks were becoming more powerful but he was still suppressing his strength and didn't use a Rank three Gu worm.

Fang Yuan who was spectating from afar with his hands crossed, clearly understood the reason.

"It is not that he doesn't want to unleash his true strength, but he cannot use it. Bai Ning Bing, heh, he has Northern Dark Ice Soul physique....."

In the oldest legends of this world, all humans are descendants of Ren Zu.

But as the saying goes, the dragon has nine unique sons. There are no two absolutely same people, and even twins have differences.

In this world, the difference that is of the biggest concern is aptitude.

Those that have the aptitude to cultivate could become Gu Masters, going beyond ordinary. Those with no cultivation aptitude were just mortals, the lowest level in the society, who could be trampled upon and played with.

Cultivation aptitudes were divided into four grades; A grade, B grade, C grade and D grade. Everyone knew this.

But actually, there were still more outstanding aptitudes above A grade.

This was a secret. Clans would never carelessly spread this, and only after reaching a certain status in society, could one know this secret.

Xiong Li and the rest naturally didn't know, even elders and clan leaders might not know. But Fang Yuan, who had reached Rank six in his previous life, shedding his mortal body and becoming a Gu immortal, naturally was aware of this.

There were ten types of aptitudes above A grade and they were collectively called Ten Extreme physiques.

"Before Ren Zu died, he gave birth to ten children. The eldest son Verdant Great Sun, second daughter Desolate Ancient Moon..... Among the ten, there was one named Northern Dark Ice Soul. Ren Zu's legends whether real or false, alluded to many secrets in Gu Master's cultivation. Ren Zu's ten kids individually represented ten types of ultimate aptitudes." Fang Yuan recalled.

"Any one of the ten extreme physiques is superior to A grade aptitude. The most excellent A grade aptitude can only store ninety nine percent primeval essence in their aperture. But any one of the ten extreme physiques holds full hundred percent primeval essence in their aperture!"

"However, everything exists in balance; the ten extreme physiques which holds hundred percent primeval essence is too perfect and heavens won't easily allow their existence. For instance, in Ren Zu's story, his ten kids didn't have a long life. In reality, it is difficult for the Gu Masters who hold ten extreme physiques to grow and mature, almost all dying an untimely death. Of course, if they can really grow to become a Rank six, they will be able to sweep through same stage opponents and even perform miracles such as fighting a higher rank!"

"Bai Ning Bing who possesses Northern Dark Ice Soul is the same. With hundred percent primeval essence, his aperture is too stressed out and has the risk of collapsing any moment. To decrease this risk, Bai Ning Bing must cultivate and use primeval essence to nurture his aperture walls and increase its strength to be able to support the hundred percent primeval essence. Thus, his cultivation speed is outstanding and shocking."

"However, high cultivation means higher quality primeval essence which subsequently increases the pressure on the aperture, instead increasing the risk. Bai Ning Bing is like a victim in a lone boat in the sea; he doesn't have fresh water and can only drink the sea water to relieve his thirst, but the seawater is salty and will absorb the original moisture content of the body instead, making him even more thirsty."

"The higher his cultivation is, the nearer he is to destruction. Yet he cannot choose not to cultivate, since being from Bai village and the one upon whom the clan's expectations lies, he will also face assassination from Xiong and Gu Yue village. This forces him to continue to grow stronger. Being the possessor of the Northern Dark Ice Soul, he clearly understands his situation. Knowing he doesn't have much time left and his death being certain, he has thus formed this temperament."

Fang Yuan sighed when he thought of this.

This was clearly an irony.

Excessively excellent aptitude didn't lead a Gu Master to have a meteoric rise, but would be the main culprit behind their deaths.

Too much is as bad as too little; people need to drink water and eat food, but if they eat and drink excessively, they could die.

From another angle, no matter which world, there is no true perfection. There is no perfect love, no perfect work.

Excessively perfect will just lead to destruction.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, three years after the wolf tide, Bai Ning Bing's cultivation inevitably reached Rank four realm. His aperture couldn't support the burden from the primeval essence and ultimately, it exploded.

Ten extreme physiques wasn't tolerated by the heavens and earth, and the self-detonation of such a heaven-defying thing was like the most perfect song, its power outstanding; directly annihilating everyone in the three villages and turning the whole Qing Mao Mountain into an absolute death ice domain.

Fortunately by that time, because of Fang Zheng who had been making things difficult for Fang Yuan who only had an average cultivation, Fang Yuan could only join a caravan to go away, thus luckily avoiding this disaster.

To delay his death, Bai Ning Bing used Gu worms to dilute his Rank three silver primeval essence into Rank two red steel primeval essence, of his own accord. He also rarely used Rank three Gu worms at the same time.

This was simply because Rank three Gu worms consumed great amounts of red steel primeval essence every time, resulting in the strength waning if it continued. Instead, it was better to continue using Rank two Gu worms which would be of much more help to Bai Ning Bing in battles.This was the real reason Bai Ning Bing suppressed his cultivation.If not, having strength but choosing to bind one's own hands and feet, landing in a dangerous state, was something only a brainless retard would do.

Bai Ning Bing was smart and intelligent, he had received great training and education, so how could he do such a foolish thing?

Except, such a temperament at his young age was indeed unusual. But as someone who was about to die, why would he have misgivings in his behavior?

Such disregard and fearlessness prevented him from being assimilated into the system, and nurtured a heart of the demonic path in him.

Otherwise, with his living environment—countless expectations, great trainings, holding honor, fighting enemies, bright future—he would have already been assimilated into the organization system and nurtured a leader's temperament.

Bai Ning Bing was actually a pitiful child, and Fang Yuan had no wish to deal with him before. But since he wanted to kill Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan also didn't mind making use of him first before removing this misfortune early.

The battle was still continuing.

In this while, the situation had already changed.

Bold lightning wolf was killed by Bai Ning Bing and the wolf pack had ran away in defeat. Xiong Li group's healing Gu Master fell under Bai Ning Bing's blade but he had paid a heavy price for this; his right arm was viciously punched by Xiong Li and it seemed to have fractured as it was hanging limply throughout the battle.

However, all of these couldn't hinder him from occupying the upper hand.

Xiong Li was a top elite amongst Rank two Gu Masters, his strength equal to Qing Shu and Chi Shan. Xiong Jiang was a newly rising defense expert. Xiong Lin was the genius newbie and now had Rank two battle power. There was also another Gu Master, but even after combining their strength, these four were still suppressed by Bai Ning Bing.

One should know Bai Ning Bing had already fought a battle before which had consumed a lot of his red steel primeval essence. He also killed bold lightning wolf and the healing Gu Master, resulting in his right arm losing its ability to move; he could only abandon using his ice blade with his habitual right hand and switch to his left. By doing this, he had to temporarily abandon using his icicles; his offensive power almost reducing by half.

He was still occupying the upper hand in such situation and his dominance was even becoming more solid.

"It is after all the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique. Although he used Gu worm to dilute his primeval essence and sealed the true advantage of the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique, the primeval essence recovery speed is still maintained. His advantage will continue to increase the longer the battle lasts." Fang Yuan looked at the situation and inwardly sighed.

"My current battle strength is not enough to defeat him," Fang Yuan calmly admitted this point.

Fang Yuan only had C grade aptitude with 44% primeval essence. Even the combined strength of B grade aptitudes' Xiong Li, Xiong Lin and Xiong Jiang were being suppressed by Bai Ning Bing. It was obvious that if Fang Yuan faced Bai Ning Bing by himself, his situation would only become more difficult than Xiong Li and the rest.

"However, not being able to defeat you doesn't mean I can't kill you." Fang Yuan coldly smiled.

This was the accumulated wisdom from five hundred years of experience.

Although they had similar reflections, compared to this centuries old devil, Bai Ning Bing was only a little devil forced into it by his cruel fate.

Chapter 136: Clash of brawn and brain

Cold air blew all over the place, accompanying ice blades in flight. Steel fists howled in the wind, and fangs growled their fury.

Xiong Li and the other's fight against Bai Ning Bing had reached its climax.

Not that much time had passed since the battle began, to be honest. But as the pressure from Bai Ning Bing intensified, Xiong Li and the others started to feel that time dragged on longer with the difficulty he posed.

Xiong Jiang's face was dim as water, Xiong Lin's forehead dripping with cold sweat, while Xiong Li maintained a serious gaze.

At this point, even Xiong Li had to suppress his anger and admit Bai Ning Bing's formidable strength. Even though Bai Ning Bing suppressed his Rank three cultivation, and only fought with Rank two Gu worms, he displayed strength that was able to suppress their entire group.

But even then, the truth was that Bai Ning Bing had not even given it his all. This was not intentional to prove a point, rather, it was a precautionary measure against Fang Yuan.

To Xiong Li and the others, their motive was simple, it was to arrest or kill Bai Ning Bing.

But to Bai Ning Bing, the situation was more complicated.

He needed to fight back the Xiong Li group on one end, while simultaneously being on guard to prevent Fang Yuan's sneak attack on the other end.

He had seen Fang Yuan using the Stealth Scales Gu with his own eyes, thus in battle he needed to make sure to divert some of his attention to prevent Fang Yuan's attack.

But till now, Fang Yuan had not made a move.

"Did he leave? Impossible! Although it is our first meeting, he is not the type to retreat! He will definitely act. He is just biding his time." Bai Ning Bing waved his ice blade and suppressed Xiong Li, while his thoughts raced in his mind.

Not only did he have to use his brawn to fight the Xiong Li group, he also had to compete with Fang Yuan using his wit.

Fang Yuan refusing to attack was increasingly putting pressure on himself. A sheathed sword is the most dangerous, because one would not be able to predict where the sword is going to stab.

Although Fang Yuan had not struck, and was secretly watching the battle, he had been able to divert Bai Ning Bing's attention all this time. If not for this diversion, the Xiong Li group would have lost long ago, otherwise they would not be able to hold on for so long.

"This Bai Ning Bing is very meticulous. First he killed the bold lightning wolf decisively, reducing a pawn that I could use. Next he risked getting injured to killing the healing Gu Master in Xiong Li group. All these actions are the most sensible decisions to make in his situation. Although he is engaging in serious combat with Xiong Li group, he is still holding back to prevent my attack, in fact..."

Under the shadow of a nearby tree, Fang Yuan crossed his arm as he watched, his eyes shining with uncertainty.

It was not that he did not want to strike, but he just could not find an opportunity to.

He was not anxious though.

The longer this dragged on, the more battle strength would be drained from Bai Ning Bing. The Ten Extreme bodies had a supreme primeval essence recovery rate, much more than A grade, but it still was spent up over time.

The longer Fang Yuan waited, the more primeval essence used up in Bai Ning Bing's aperture, and the more the scales of victory would shift towards Fang Yuan.

If Bai Ning Bing's aperture had no primeval essence left, so what if he is the Northern Dark Ice Soul Body? One moonblade and he's beheaded!

Fang Yuan knew this, and Bai Ning Bing was aware of this fact as well.

Although he currently had the upper hand, his heart was getting heavier.

"I cannot continue like this!" Bai Ning Bing's blue eyes shone as he took a large step back, pulling some distance from the Xiong Li group.

Next he gulped, his throat expanding like something had risen from his stomach into his mouth.

His jaw was raised high as he opened his mouth in difficulty.

An icy blue colored small bird popped out of his mouth, its head raising above his white teeth. It looked around and soon found a locked onto a specific gaze.

Jumping out of Bai Ning Bing's mouth, the small, icy bird flapped its wings strongly, flying towards Xiong Li.

The the small blue bird was cute like a pigeon, but Xiong Li and the others' faces lost their colour upon seeing it.

"Rank three Blue Bird Ice Coffin Gu?"

"Get away from it, quickly!"

The Xiong Li group frantically tried to dodge around, but this blue ice bird was not like the moonblade; once sent out, it was locked on to the target.

"Boom!"

It smashed into the support Gu Master in Xiong Li group, before promptly exploding.

Frosty air blew all over the place, and the piercing blue light from the explosion lit up the entire battlefield.

The next second, the blue light dispersed, and a partially transparent block of ice was revealed, a cold watery blue in color.

The Gu Master was visibly sealed within the ice block, his face still retaining the fear and anxiety before death, but he had lost all signs of life.

Even though Bai Ning Bing was already a Rank three Gu Master, once a Rank three Gu worm was used, his suppressed Rank two primeval essence in his aperture would be rapidly used up. At the same time, it cannot display the true power of a Rank three Gu worm. Moreover, once used, during the following period, the enemy can make use of this opportunity to attack.

But Xiong Li's group of three were frozen in shock instead, startled by this Blue Bird Ice Coffin Gu.

Bai Ning Bing did not follow up the attack, and instead turned around and left, attempting to leave the battlefield.

This was a wise decision, for if he continued, the situation would become more disadvantageous for him.

"Damn it..."

"Bai Ning Bing, don't run if you have guts!"

"Brother Xiong Xin was killed by him, kill him, take revenge for brother Xiong Xin!!!"

Xiong Li group cursed loudly, but could not catch up.

Originally, the four of them were barely enough to form an encirclement, but now that they had one less person, their blockade was easily broken by Bai Ning Bing.

Seeing that Bai Ning Bing was about to leave the battlefield, at this time, a moonblade flew out from among the bushes, and a person leapt out and quickly following after.

"Bam!"

Bai Ning Bing's ice blade waved, and dispelled the moonblade. But his abdomen was hit by someone, throwing him back by three large steps.

During this period, Xiong Li and the others were sobered from their stupor, getting close and surrounded Bai Ning Bing again.

Bai Ning Bing ignored the three, staring at the newcomer instead, chuckling.

"So you finally appeared ..."

"It's Fang Yuan!" Xiong Lin's eyes shone, seeing a glimmer of hope.

"Fang Yuan, good job!" Xiong Jiang was overjoyed, shouting.

Xiong Li stayed silent; although he seemed rash, his thoughts were more meticulous than anyone else. Fang Yuan did not strike earlier, but suddenly appeared ... was he watching the battle all along? The thought of this possibility brought him unease.

Fang Yuan smiled mildly, showing a victorious appearance, but his heart sank. Bai Ning Bing's act of retreating was to force him to appear. Fang Yuan was clear of his intentions, and saw through it, but so what if he did? He had to show up.

Xiong Li's expression was also taken into account, and he had expected it.

"Rest assured, everyone." He opened his mouth. "I've informed the clan, just hang in there for a little longer, reinforcements are coming!"

Xiong Li was relieved at once.

Xiong Lin, Xiong Jiang's battle spirits were ignited, and Bai Ning Bing suddenly laughed loudly, "Haha, so he's called Fang Yuan, such an interesting guy... I only want to kill you even more now!!!"

"I'm afraid you're not capable enough to achieve that." Fang Yuan's eyes shone with cold light, taking a step forward.

"Bai Ning Bing, the heavens want you dead, you're finished!" Xiong Jiang gritted his teeth, running into Bai Ning Bing.

"Bai Ning Bing, you are too arrogant, you will pay the price today!" Xiong Lin growled, moving towards Bai Ning Bing's back.

"Fang Yuan, stay back a little, back us up and prevent Bai Ning Bing from escaping." Xiong Li said.

If Fang Yuan interfered, it would destroy the chemistry the three of them shared.

Battle continued.

Fang Yuan's expression was tranquil while he continued to constantly attack, treating Xiong Li's words as if they were air.

The Xiong Li group frowned; outsider interference would cause the battle formation to be chaotic, and their cooperation would start to fail. But Fang Yuan's every attack was ruthless and decisive, having a strong grasp of opportunity, instead being of great help to them.

At first, Xiong Li growled threateningly at him, but soon, he shut the fuck up. His frowning face slowly eased, and his brows started to raise instead, revealing his surprise towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not strike much, but each attack he made had great implications on the battle. Once his master level methods were displayed, he instantly grasped the battle in his hands.

Xiong Li's group of five originally were at a disadvantage when fighting Bai Ning Bing, and ended up getting two of their members killed. But once Fang Yuan joined in, along with the three's combined combat prowess, they managed to suppress Bai Ning Bing into a corner.

"Bai Ning Bing, just go and die!"

Xiong Li growled loudly, jumping up and landing heavily. His ten fingers intertwined to form a punch, slamming toward Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing wanted to dodge, but Fang Yuan appeared at that moment, and at the same time shot out a moonblade, blocking the direction where he wanted to leap.

Bai Ning Bing had no choice but to endure Xiong Li's attack.

"Water Shield Gu!"

From his nostrils, two lines of water vapour coiled around his body, forming a spherical barrier of condensed moisture.

With a loud impact and a compressed pop, Xiong Li's heavy punch landed on the barrier, breaking through it instantly.

But this act also caused the punch to lose all its built up velocity and allowed Bai Ning Bing to escape death.

Even so, Xiong Li took a glance at Fang Yuan, showing signs of admiration. If not for his superb cooperation, this hit would've been avoided by Bai Ning Bing. It would not have forced Bai Ning Bing to take the hit head on, expending his primeval essence.

"Water Shield Gu again..."

Fang Yuan did not mind Xiong Li's gaze, but focused on Bai Ning Bing, frowning.

It was this Water Shield Gu that alleviated Bai Ning Bing's predicament. The defensive power of the water shield was superior to even the White Jade Gu.

But it had a weakness—he needed to form a ball shape and rely on the moving water to draw the force away, dispersing the damage in order to display its full defensive capabilities.

If Bai Ning Bing was up against a wall, he cannot form a ball shape and his defense power would be greatly reduced.

There are many forests on Qing Mao Mountain, but even then Bai Ning Bing had been very careful, making sure not to get into a tight spot.

"As long as I beat this Water Shield Gu, I can put Bai Ning Bing in a tight spot. But how?" Fang Yuan was thinking, but suddenly Bai Ning Bing's mouth opened, and a new blue bird flew out.

Xiong Li and the others were fearful of this attack, but Fang Yuan was not flustered in the least.

He snorted coldly, shooting a moonblade.

With a bam, the moonblade hit the ice bird, causing it to explode.

Bai Ning Bing growled in a low voice, he was too close by, and after the ice bird exploded, he was hit by it too.

The impact caused him to fly up and then fall on the the ground. At the same time, half of his left limb was frozen, losing its ability to fight.

"Divine opportunity!" Seeing this, Xiong Li's eyes shone with brilliance, shouting "Go die!" and his arms gathered to form another punch towards Bai Ning Bing.

This hit was too heavy, and as Bai Ning Bing was on the ground, the Water Shield Gu's defensive capabilities were less than half of the usual; if this hit his head, there was no doubt that he, Bai Ning Bing, would instantly die.

Chapter 137: Shadow of death

Seeing that Xiong Li's fist was about to hit Bai Ning Bing, Xiong Lin and Xiong Jiang both showed a joyful expression.

Only Fang Yuan stood far away, his eyes shining with solemnness.

With his understanding of Bai Ning Bing, how could he commit such a beginner's mistake?

As expected, at this moment!

Bai Ning Bing suddenly struck; his right hand and forearm's flesh all turned into a transparent blue frosty ice, from outside his finger bones could be seen.

His fingers gathered straight, forming a palm blade and striking like lightning, puncturing Xiong Li's heart!

"Urgh!" Xiong Li's descending body came to a halt.

He stared with wide-opened eyes, lowering his head and staring at his chest in disbelief.

"How can this be?"

"Lord Xiong Li!"

With the sudden twist of events, Xiong Jiang and Xiong Lin could not believe it.

"You think my right arm was really broken by your punch? Naive! I already used the Rank three ice muscle Gu, and trained a body of ice muscles, this is the ultimate defense! The reason I pretended earlier was to give a certain someone a surprise." Bai Ning Bing slowly got up, showing disdain in his eyes, and at the end of his speech, he looked towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's expression was calm, staring at him too.

Plop.

"Bai... Ning Bing...." Xiong Li opened his mouth, saying his last words with difficulty. Bai Ning Bing's ice hand spread out some cold air and froze his heart, cutting off his life force!

"Scheming scumbag, I will fight it out with you!" Xiong Lin saw Xiong Li's death firsthand, and under the extreme pain and anger, he ignored his own danger and charged towards Bai Ning Bing.

"Xiong Lin, calm down!' Xiong Jiang acted in time, restraining Xiong Lin.

"Group leader is dead, we are no longer his match, quickly leave, I'll block him!" Xiong Jiang controlled his sadness and said.

"Brother Xiong Jiang..." Xiong Lin was dumbfounded, his eyes turning red.

Xiong Jiang shrugged his hand backwards and took a step forwards, blocking Bai Ning Bing.

Shadow Bond Gu!

The shadow below his feet suddenly came alive, distorting creepily, connecting itself to Bai Ning Bing's shadow.

"I have the Shadow Bond Gu! Once I get hurt, Bai Ning Bing takes the same damage. He won't kill me so easily. Xiong Lin, you are still young and have better talent than me or group leader, go away quickly!" Xiong Jiang's gaze was locked onto Bai Ning Bing as he shouted.

"Brother Xiong Jiang!" Xiong Lin's eyes were teary, he knew the weakness of the Shadow Bond Gu.

In the previous battle, Xiong Jiang had used the Gu worm too, but once Bai Ning Bing pulled sufficient distance, the shadow would split. Xiong Jiang saying this was just to console him.

Especially now, Xiong Jiang did not have enough primeval essence; he had already used up too much, and even the Roaming Zombie Gu had stopped working.

Xiong Lin's feet seems to have taken roots, as he refused to move a step. He turned around, staring at Fang Yuan, "Fang Yuan, why are the reinforcements not here yet?!"

Fang Yuan did not speak, only staring firmly at Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing moved his right arm, and after a while, his right arm regained its fleshy state. He used a mocking tone, "Reinforcements? Hehehe, they would've come long ago if it was the case, but this is all a lie. Tsk tsk tsk, you are even more naive than the other one. You really think such a cheap method like Shadow Bond Gu can restrain me?"

He stared at the shadow in disdain, not giving a fuck.

"Fang Yuan, is this true?" Xiong Lin clenched his fist, eyes speaking fire as he asked furiously.

Fang Yuan did not care about him, but stared at Bai Ning Bing, his mouth curling into a smile, "That move earlier, it expended your primeval essence right? By now, how much primeval essence do you still have in your aperture?"

Xiong Li used a defensive Gu worm but it was weaker than Fang Yuan's White Jade Gu. The result was that his defense was penetrated, but such an attack is clearly not owned by a Rank two Gu Master.

According to the earlier situation, Fang Yuan guessed that Bai Ning Bing used the Rank three Frost Demon Gu.

This Gu's ability was strong, renowned among the Rank three Gu, but overuse harmed the user. Joint problems were just a light symptom, but if serious, one's muscles could be frozen and damaged, thus it needed to be used with other Gu worms.

Bai Ning Bing had said earlier that his muscles had become ice muscles, and could take the cold of the frost. Thus, when used together with the Frost Demon Gu, they complemented each other.

This was still Bai Ning Bing using Rank two primeval essence to forcefully activate a Rank three Gu worm, so it had to have high consumption, but he needed to use such a method to break the stalemate.

Bai Ning Bing's expression changed; the move earlier had caused a great consumption of his primeval essence, and Fang Yuan saw through it.

Thus, after killing Xiong Li, he did not strike again, but used the talking time to recover.

He laughed heartily, nodding, and confessed, "Not bad, my primeval essence is running dry, I left my right limb unused to lure you to attack. But you didn't fall for it. Hehehe, the real battle is just starting, isn't it?"

Fang Yuan squinted.

If Bai Ning Bing denied it, he would attack without doubt. But Bai Ning Bing confessed, showing a look of fearlessness...

Either that Bai Ning Bing knew he was going to die, showing no fear towards death, or he probably had other strong trump cards and had great confidence in surviving.

Ordinary Gu Masters only had three to five Gu worms, even Qing Shu and Chi Shan, were as such.

But there are exceptions.

For example Fang Yuan, with the Moonglow Gu, White Jade Gu, Stealth Scales Gu, Four Flavour Liquor worm, Spring Autumn Cicada, Earth Communication Ear Grass and Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, he had seven Gu worms in his possession.

Bai Ning Bing was the Bai clan's hope and had the Northern Dark Ice Soul body, an absolute genius. From the start of his cultivating journey, he had received the full support of his clan, his wealth definitely greater than Fang Yuan.

Up till now, he had displayed over six Gu worms. Fang Yuan was sure that he had others.

And these Gu worms allowed him to be calm despite being in this position of having little primeval essence.

Actually, the most troublesome kind of opponent is like him.

Not only having talent, but not fearing death, and having large amount of Gu worms in hand.

With these three, it greatly affected a Gu Master's battle in terms of victory or loss. Especially Gu worms, with a strong or special one, it can allow a Gu Master to overturn the situation.

Bai Ning Bing's Frost Demon Gu was a Rank three Gu worm, so even with Fang Yuan's White Jade Gu defending, he could be penetrated. This is also why Fang Yuan had not engaged Bai Ning Bing personally.

Fang Yuan had used Gu Yue Man Shi, Xiong Li and others to fish out Bai Ning Bing's secrets. After all, only knowing one's enemy can one be assured of victory.

In comparing talent, Fang Yuan was only a C grade. Compared to Bai Ning Bing, it was a world of difference. Bai Ning Bing started cultivating earlier and had the clan's assistance, and he had more outstanding Gu worms in his possession than Fang Yuan.

In terms of temperament, his fearlessness towards death made him almost invulnerable.

The difference between the two was that Bai Ning Bing was strong, and Fang Yuan was weak. This is the truth, he had to accept it and understand it.

But battles are interesting because the strong might not necessarily win, and the weak might not always fall.

Fang Yuan wanting to win against the odds, it was not impossible, but he had to use all of the methods he had, and make use of all the strength he could gather.

"Gu Yue Man Shi was just the beginning, and Xiong Li group is not the end." Thinking so, Fang Yuan struck.

With a moonblade, a head flew away, and blood spewed!

This moment, Bai Ning Bing's iris shrunk to pin-size, his face changing colour.

Fang Yuan's moonblade did not attack him, but was aimed at Xiong Jiang's head.

Xiong Jiang did not expect Fang Yuan's betrayal; Bai Ning Bing's pressure was too great, and all his attention was gathered on the latter.

He did not have much primeval essence left, so to conserve them, he did not maintain the Roaming Zombie Gu, thus getting one-shotted.

Bam!

Bai Ning Bing's face was pale as he vomited a mouthful of blood, and at the same time, his ears, nose and eyes had blood traces.

Ever since the battle started, this was the most severe injury he had sustained.

Shadow Bond Gu!

With the shared damage effect, when the Shadow Bond Gu Master sustains an injury, the chain-linked Gu Master takes 10% of the damage. Now that Xiong Jiang is dead, his injuries were connected through the shadow and transmitted to Bai Ning Bing.

This injury with a direct effect, even if Bai Ning Bing had the Water Shield Gu, it cannot block against it.

"Fang Yuan, what have you done?!" A second later, Xiong Lin came back from shock and shouted in a furious voice, heartbroken.

Fang Yuan ignored him, his body glowing with white jade light as he charged towards Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing getting such an injury, his body was wavering, and his head was dizzy, his battle strength dropped drastically. Seeing Fang Yuan attacking, he retreated immediately.

"Bai Ning Bing, didn't you want a life and death battle?" Fang Yuan chased relentlessly.

Bai Ning Bing gritted his teeth, escaping silently. His footsteps were messy, but he forced himself to focus, ignoring Fang Yuan's taunting.

Although he knew he was a dying man and did not fear death, he was not stupid, and with such a dangerous situation, his heart grew calmer.

Xiong Lin stood on the spot, not choosing to help Fang Yuan chase Bai Ning Bing.

His heart was filled with pain and anger. He hated Bai Ning Bing, and also detested Fang Yuan.

Bai and Fang moved closely, traversing the valley.

As time passed, Bai Ning Bing's injuries slowly recovered, and his nose and eyes stopped bleeding. Slowly his footsteps became more composed.

He did not simply run away, but during this time, used his Gu worm to heal his body's injuries.

Fang Yuan's pursued and his heart was secretly shocked.

"Previously Bai Ning Bing's primeval essence was almost fully expended, but during this time, the amount he recovered was enough to heal his own injuries. Northern Dark Ice Soul body, Ten Extreme talents, what sort of primeval essence recovery speed is this!"

The more he knew, the more determined he was to kill Bai Ning Bing.

Moonglow Gu!

Fang Yuan sent a moonblade around the size of a face flying; it flew across the sky, emitting a buzzing sound.

Bai Ning Bing heard this sound and tried to dodge, but his arm still got sliced away.

An injury appeared and blood poured out, but the injury was quickly covered by a layer of frost, stopping the blood.

Bai Ning Bing had obtained the ice muscles, and once this is achieved, it was like the Black and White Boar Gu's strength increase—it required no primeval essence to sustain.

But Bai Ning Bing's heart continued to sink. Before his old injuries healed, new injuries would come; evidently, Fang Yuan wanted to slowly grind him to death!

Chapter 138: Someone is actually chasing and trying to kill Bai Ning Bing?

"Hehehe, there has never been anyone who forced me into such a state! Fang Yuan, you... are interesting. Once I recover adequately, I'll definitely kill you!!" Bai Ning Bing screamed in his heart as he ran.

The killing intent from Fang Yuan had him feel suffocated.

This to him, was an unprecedented experience.

The thick aura of death made his body shudder, and it developed a twisted sense of excitement.

Behind him, Fang Yuan was chasing and getting closer.

"Take this!" He suddenly flicked his wrist, and threw a black coloured Gu worm.

Fang Yuan's steps came to a halt as if an enemy had appeared, but once he got closer, he found out that this was the Plunder Gu from Xiong Zhan.

Splat.

With a light sound, Fang Yuan caught this Gu worm in his hands.

The Plunder Gu was a black beetle, and at a normal size, its head had a pair of metal antenna, and its back had white spots.

Once the Spring Autumn Cicada revealed its aura, Fang Yuan easily refined this Plunder Gu and kept it in its aperture with some use of its primeval essence.

He continued chasing.

For Bai Ning Bing to even use such a method, it showed the severity of his injuries and the desperate situation he was in. But with this action, the distance between Fang Yuan and him had been pulled apart again.

"Unfortunately, I lack a movement Gu worm. If I had such a Gu worm, I would have caught up to Bai Ning Bing already." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

"This Fang Yuan, he actually refined the Plunder Gu instantly?" Bai Ning Bing was shocked in his heart.

He obtained this Plunder Gu and had been refining it for the last few days. Although there were improvements, the process was tough and he did not succeed. This is also because Xiong Zhan's death had an indirect relationship with him. The will of this Plunder Gu originated from Xiong Zhan, thus, it had greater hatred towards Bai Ning Bing and raised the difficulty in refining it.

But Fang Yuan instantly refined this Plunder Gu, and Bai Ning Bing who only used his side vision to see this could feel his heart turn shocked and dismayed.

There are a few Gu worms that can achieve this.

But Bai Ning Bing had never owned one, to think that Fang Yuan would instead?

Unknowingly, he had become more wary of Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan's image in his heart had intensified in a dangerous and mysterious way.

However, as time passed, Fang Yuan's heart was the one that sank.

The longer it dragged, the more primeval essence would be recovered by Bai Ning Bing, and the lesser injuries he has. Fang Yuan's advantage over him would become milder and milder.

"I'm afraid I won't be able to kill him this time!" Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

According to this development, it won't be long before Bai Ning Bing's injury and primeval essence recover sufficiently.

Although Fang Yuan had been using the Moonglow Gu to intensify the injuries on him, the Northern Dark Ice Soul body's talent is too outstanding, it can be said to be a gift from heaven. The primeval essence recovery rate was even faster than Fang Yuan using primeval stones.

"Unless... the people in front encountered a wolf pack, and are trapped. Or there will be a Gu Master group appearing, and can temporarily block Bai Ning Bing. But if it is a Bai clan group, I'm in danger."

Fang Yuan's thoughts flowed like a whirlpool as he started to have intentions to retreat.

Their chase was a long road, but in the middle they did not encounter a single pack of wolves or a Gu Master group. This meant to say that Bai Ning Bing who is selecting the escape route also has a recon Gu worm and can avoid danger.

Qing Mao Mountain is so huge, he can escape in all directions, Fang Yuan has no way to force Bai Ning Bing to run in one direction.

"Against the wolf tide, the most important thing is to be united and not be isolated by the wolf tide. Once you are isolated, you are in danger," Qing Shu told Fang Zheng as they were rushing on the road.

"If the opponent is the bold lightning wolf pack, we can defend using terrain, and defeat them head on. But if it is the frenzy lightning wolf pack, the first thing to do is retreat, then use the Signal Gu, and wait for the surrounding Gu Masters to regroup. We need at least three groups to cooperate to have a good chance of defeating the frenzy lightning wolf. Of course, opponents in the wolf tide are not just lightning wolves, but also Gu Masters."

Saying so, Gu Yue Qing Shu paused.

The other four knew who he was talking about.

Evidently, it was Bai Ning Bing.

These days, Bai Ning Bing had been challenging people all over, suppressing his cultivation and only using the Rank two red steel primeval essence, and found trouble with Xiong Li, Chi Shan and the rest.

From what he declared, Gu Yue Qing Shu is his next target.

"If we encounter Bai Ning Bing..." Gu Yue Qing Shu continued, "The best would be to avoid battling."

This sentence entered Fang Zheng's ears and caused his heart to feel disturbed.

In his heart, Gu Yue Qing Shu, although mild on the outside, had a tough personality and stuck close to his principles. From Gu Yue Qing Shu, he could feel a strong sense of kinship. Towards Gu Yue Qing Shu, he respected and loved him, and naturally was not willing to see Bai Ning Bing being superior to Qing Shu.

"Everyone is discussing Bai Ning Bing, what kind of person is he?" Fang Zheng frowned and asked.

The three other people in the group became solemn.

Gu Yue Qing Shu smiled kindly towards Fang Zheng, "He is Qing Mao Mountain's number one genius! Fang Zheng, listen well. You are still young, and have A grade talent, you might be able to surpass him in the future. So before you fully grow up, avoid direct conflicts with him. Remember the story I told you before? Lowering your head and raising it—sometimes, people have to lower their heads."

Fang Zheng looked towards Qing Shu, and when they made eye contact, he could not help but nod and respond, "I understand, Brother Qing Shu. Please be rest assured."

"Good..." Qing Shu was still speaking, when suddenly the recon Gu Master interrupted, "Not too far away ahead, there is a Gu Master rapidly moving."

Everyone's expressions changed.

The healing Gu Master Gu Yue Yao Hong's expression was solemn, "Must be a small group that got scattered by the wolf pack, let's go save them."

Fang Zheng said instead, "Could it be Bai Ning Bing, doesn't he travel alone usually?"

"It could be him, or not. But if it really is a Gu Master that got lost, no matter which village, they are our alliance mate. We have to go save them," Gu Yue Qing Shu said, turning direction and charging towards the Gu Master.

The four around him followed closely.

But quickly, the recon Gu Master spoke, "It is not a Gu Master, behind the first Gu Master, there is another one."

"It's actually two Gu Masters huh. It seems that the situation is just like Sister Yao Hong had said. It should be a group that got separated by the wolf packs," Gu Yue Fang Zheng sighed a breath of relief.

Gu Yue Qing Shu's expression was unchanging, but the other three's expression became more relaxed.

At this point, if one was observing from a higher point of view, they would see Qing Shu's group, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing, getting closer along the mountain road.

"Oh?" Bai Ning Bing's expression changed. He had a recon Gu, and he felt that a group of five Gu Masters were approaching.

He quickly changed his direction.

Although he had a recon-type Gu worm, it could not detect the identities of the people ahead. Every Gu worm had one ability, thus it had pros and cons.

Taking Fang Yuan's Earth Communication Ear Grass for example, it can hear noise and is most sensitive to footsteps, but it cannot discern information like male or female. And if a Gu Master uses the Silent Step Gu, they can conceal their footsteps and he would not be able to detect them.

Not knowing who it was, to play it safe, Bai Ning Bing chose to avoid them.

But this time, the situation was different. Qing Shu's group was full of elites, and their recon Gu Master was a professional as well.

"There's someone!" Soon after, Fang Yuan detected the existence of Qing Shu group.

He was sprinting, and his right ear had roots growing out, but did not go into the ground, thus his detection range was not even half of its peak.

Bai Ning Bing changed his running direction again.

But Qing Shu group followed closely, changing their direction to match.

This way, be it Bai Ning Bing or Fang Yuan, their expressions turned serious.

The two were extremely clever, they knew at once: This unknown group is the biggest uncertainty, it would definitely affect the result of the battle.

"If it is a Bai clan group, I will immediately use the Stealth Scales Gu and retreat. But if it is the other two clans, hehe." Fang Yuan's eyes shone with coldness.

He knew that this decision carried certain risks.

If it was a Bai clan group and the Gu Masters among them had a detection method, he would be chased into a dead end.

But if he lost this prime opportunity, he would probably never have another shot at killing Bai Ning Bing.

Furthermore, whichever clan the Gu Masters are from, Fang Yuan had a 66% chance, while Bai Ning Bing only had one third, so Fang Yuan had reason to gamble.

As they sprinted, the two parties continued to get closer.

"We can almost see them, right behind that turning point," the recon Gu Master pointed at a curve along the mountain path.

They could not help but slow their footsteps, awaiting the meeting further ahead.

A white figure turned around the corner, and appeared in front of them.

"Bai Ning Bing!" Fang Zheng shouted in dismay, he had obviously seen Bai Ning Bing's portrait before.

The other four, even Qing Shu's expression sank.

"Bai Ning Bing is in such a sorry state, he must've encountered a frenzy lightning wolf pack."

"Hmph, he deserves this, travelling alone in the wolf tide, what airs is he trying to put on?"

Everyone at once, did not go up and meet with him.

Bai Ning Bing's movements and expression, showed signs of escaping, this caused Qing Shu group to feel happy internally.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan shouted from over the corner, "Bai Ning Bing, why are you running? I must kill you today!"

Saying this, he was trying to test water.

Using the Earth Communication Ear Grass, he knew that around the corner, there was an unknown group of five.

If it is a Bai clan group, this proclamation would invite their intense rebuttal.

Around the corner, Qing Shu and the others heard this and their eyeballs rolled wide.

"What's going on?"

"There's actually someone chasing and trying to kill Bai Ning Bing?"

"Did I get it wrong, something like this is happening?"

"Getting Bai Ning Bing into such a pathetic state, who in the world is behind him?"

Gu Yue Yao Hong could not help but look at each other, a look of shock all over their faces.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was shocked and suspicious, "This voice, why is it so familiar?"

Before he could remember the owner of the voice, Fang Yuan turned around the corner.

"What?" Gu Yue Qing Shu's serious expression turned into dumbfoundedness.

The other four stared with their eyes wide opened; after seeing Fang Yuan appear, their eyeballs almost dropped.

"This, this, this!" Gu Yue Yao Ji opened her mouth wide, big enough to swallow a duck egg.

"Brother!" Fang Zheng was tongue tied.

"It's him?" Even Gu Yue Qing Shu with outstanding composure, was shocked beyond words.

Chapter 139: Broken Arm

Who was Bai Ning Bing?

The number one genius of Qing Mao mountain—someone who could single-handedly change the structure of the three clans, whose cultivation speed left everyone dumbfounded, dimming the luster of even A grade geniuses. No one doubted his future accomplishments; even his enemies had no choice but to accept the fact his talent was unparalleled.

However, now someone was actually making this genius flee in such a wretched state.

No one among the Qing Shu group expected this.

What was even more astonishing was that the person chasing after Bai Ning Bing was actually from their clan: Fang Yuan.

Regarding their impressions of Fang Yuan, they were mainly based around the arena battles and chasing away River Swallowing Toad. And since the moment Fang Yuan had admitted defeat to Xiong Li, his true strength was widely underestimated.

"When did Fang Yuan become so powerful?"

The Qing Shu group found this difficult to accept.

Fang Yuan turned around the corner.

"Gu Yue Qing Shu!" His mind jolted when he saw the Gu Yue Qing Shu group.

"I won the gamble. Bai Ning Bing, today will be the day you die," Fang Yuan thought. He shouted, "Little brother, you were here! Great! Quickly stop Bai Ning Bing! He is a heinous murderer who killed the Xiong Li group and even our clan's Gu Yue Man Shi group!"

"What?"

"But our clans have signed a treaty!"

"No, nothing is too excessive for Bai Ning Bing."

"So it was like that! No wonder Fang Yuan was able to chase Bai Ning Bing....."

The Qing Shu group was shocked and came to a realization. It seemed that after Bai Ning Bing had fought several intense battles, his fighting power had fallen to its lowest state—allowing Fang Yuan to luckily seize the upper hand.

"Am I really going to die here? No, I have just enough primeval essence to self-detonate the Frost Demon Gu. I still have hope!" Bai Ning Bing thought in his mind. In front of him was the Qing Shu group and behind him was Fang Yuan. The situation was extremely unfavorable.

Actually, there was a rift in Fang Yuan and Fang Zheng's relationship; Fang Zheng naturally wouldn't heed Fang Yuan's words.

However, Bai Ning Bing didn't know of this. As an outsider, he only saw the similarity in appearance between Fang Zheng and Fang Yuan, and firmly made a choice.

He lifted his right arm, pouring all the hard-earned primeval essence that he had recovered into the Frost Demon Gu in his right palm.

The muscles in his right arm transformed into a light blue ice. One could clearly see the white bones of his arm within the ice.

Bang!

With an explosive sound, Bai Ning Bing's whole right arm suddenly self-detonated.

Steam and mist arose, and an intense chill started to crazily pervade the surroundings.

Snap, crack.

Pure, white frost spread onto the narrow mountain path in the blisteringly hot summer, covering the soil and the trees. The temperature abruptly dropped.

"He sacrificed his entire right arm!" Fang Zheng was aghast by Bai Ning Bing's ruthless move.

"Quick, retreat." Gu Yue Qing Shu grabbed Fang Zheng and hurriedly ran away.

Great amounts of frost rushed towards them like the wolf tide.

It would be very troublesome if they actually got frozen.

Fang Yuan retreated to a distance of hundred steps along with the Qing Shu group as the onslaught of frost gradually dwindled.

Originally, the mountain path had been full of lush trees, filled with the fragrance of wild plants. Now, it had become a world of ice. The trees were all frozen and there was a thick layer of snow on the ground.

Fang Yuan stepped onto the snow and approached the middle of the mountain path.

Bai Ning Bing's whole body was frozen in ice like an insect in amber, his expression still showing the malevolent decisiveness and ruthlessness of his personality.

"He.... suicided?" Fang Zheng muttered. The Qing Shu group had quickly followed after Fang Yuan.

"No!" Qing Shu's expression was very heavy. "Bai Ning Bing has already formed ice muscles, this layer of ice crystals won't freeze him to death and will instead act as his armor, giving him time to recover."

Fang Yuan stared closely at Bai Ning Bing and threw a moonblade.

Screech.

The moonblade produced a crisp sound when it struck the ice crystals.

On the three meters high and two meters wide ice crystal, there was only a shallow scar. But in just a moment, the cold aura within the ice crystal filled the injury and the scar disappeared.

"Fang Yuan, is what you said earlier true?" Qing Shu turned his gaze towards Fang Yuan.

"Of course. Only Xiong Lin remains of the Xiong Li group and he can testify for me. We can't stay here for too long; the details will have to wait. We must quickly leave this place." Fang Yuan nodded and answered.

He had made up his mind to leave.

He knew he was unable to destroy this ice crystal. Even if they were to combine their strengths to destroy it, it would waste a lot of time and primeval essence.

If Bai Ning Bing broke out of the ice, their fighting strength would have dropped and his fighting strength would have recovered, making it a bad situation if a battle started.

"Leave? Why should we leave?" Fang Zheng couldn't refrain from asking in a loud voice. "Bai Ning Bing has already destroyed his right arm and with the battles he went through, he is tired both mentally and physically. We can break open this ice crystal and activate the Signal Gu for the clan's reinforcements to eliminate him! This is an extremely rare opportunity."

Everyone's hearts were moved by these words. "Since Fang Yuan could chase Bai Ning Bing and try to kill him, why can't we do the same?" Several Gu Masters looked at each other and they couldn't help but have such thoughts. "If we kill Bai Ning Bing, we will become great heroes of the Gu Yue clan!" "But if we kill him, won't the Bai village start a war in their anger? And now, there is the wolf tide...." "No, it is exactly because there is a wolf tide that even if we kill Bai Ning Bing, Bai village will just have to swallow their bitterness." "Right, a dead genius isn't a genius!" The group members discussed, their minds set on the fame and glory. "Truly stupid, how can you imagine the power of the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique?" Fang Yuan squinted his eyes while sneering inwardly. He was not going to accompany these people if they wanted to look for death. Gu Yue Qing Shu also hesitated. He, no doubt, had a much deeper understanding of Bai Ning Bing than the rest of the group. He didn't know of the secret of the ten extreme physiques, but he didn't have much yearning towards the fame from killing Bai Ning Bing, either.

He was indifferent towards fame and profits; he had once been nurtured by Gu Yue Bo as the next clan head, but he willingly gave up this position to Fang Zheng.

His true concerns lay within the interests of the clan, and his heart was intricately linked with the clan's well-being. "Bai village's emergence is completely due to Bai Ning Bing. If we kill Bai Ning Bing, our Gu Yue Clan will remain the number one clan of Qing Mao mountain! Although Bai Ning Bing is a Rank three Gu Master, I have the Wood Charm Gu and the ability to fight with him. Moreover, he just lost his right arm and he will certainly need some time to get used to the absence of a limb. This can be the greatest disadvantage in a life and death battle!" Qing Shu thought.

Gu Yue Qing Shu's gaze turned resolute. Fang Yuan was observing Qing Shu's expression the entire time; he realized what the latter had chosen to do when he saw Qing Shu's expression. "If Gu Yue Qing Shu uses the Wood Charm Gu without any regards to the consequences, he will be much stronger than the average Rank three Gu Master and even have the power to surpass levels and fight. However, the one he is facing is Bai Ning Bing who possesses the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique. The battle definitely won't be easy. Since Bai Ning Bing can dilute his primeval essence and suppress his cultivation, he can naturally restore his Rank three cultivation. Right now, he has enough time inside the ice crystal to remove this restriction. Once he breaks out, he will very likely be as a Rank three Gu Master." Bai Ning Bing was extremely talented and Fang Yuan had needed external help to fight against him even when Bai Ning Bing's cultivation was suppressed to Rank two. Once Bai Ning Bing enters Rank three, his fighting strength would rise by several times. Fang Yuan was the main cause of the loss of his right arm. When the battle begins, Bai Ning Bing's ruthless temperament will definitely target Fang Yuan. Moreover, Fang Yuan had some concerns and didn't want to reveal his true strength in front of Gu Yue Qing Shu.

Thus, Fang Yuan immediately expressed his intention to leave and left the battlefield, ignoring the urges of others to stay.

"He really left? Such a coward."

"Hmph, him leaving is good. If he were to meddle, it might instead destroy our tacit teamwork."

"Hahaha, it really frightened me when I saw him chasing after Bai Ning Bing. Now, it seems Fang Yuan is indeed Fang Yuan: a coward who admitted defeat in the Gu battle competition!"

"Quit it, everyone has their own ambitions. At least, he gave us intel on Bai Ning Bing before he left. Moreover, he will inform the clan who will send reinforcements." As Qing Shu gazed at the departing figure of Fang Yuan, his brows slightly furrowed.

"Group leader, you are too kind. There is no need to justify for cowards like Fang Yuan."

"Right, although Fang Yuan is Fang Zheng's older brother, the way I see it, one is earth and the other is heaven."

" I, I have already stopped talking with Fang Yuan," Fang Zheng's face grew red, he felt ashamed at Fang Yuan's running away before battle.

"Fang Zheng, you leave too," Gu Yue Qing Shu suddenly spoke.

"What?!" Fang Zheng's eyes were wide open.

"As the clan's only A grade talent, we can't lose you. Bai Ning Bing may have lost an arm, but the following battle will definitely be very dangerous. For the clan, we can die, but you, Fang Zheng, must not die."

The other four members were all moved.

"Well said!" A bright laughter echoed and an old Gu Master appeared. "Lord elder." Fang Zheng promptly paid his respects. He recognized this man as a very senior clan elder.

The elder drew near, looking at Gu Yue Qing Shu with praise, "Gu Yue Bo raised a great adopted son. With such feelings of fighting to the death for the clan, why would we have to worry about our Gu Yue Clan not expanding?" Fang Zheng was still growing up and after the Wang Er's assassination attempt, the clan had sent an elder to always follow Fang Zheng and protect him. "Fang Zheng, you don't need to take part in the fight. But don't leave; you can just observe from a distance. Isn't it just a Bai Ning Bing? I've always heard about how outstanding he is and how he has the strength of an elder. Hmph, now it seems he is only just a kid. How much battle experience can he have? Mutilating himself, he is really amateurish!" The elder snorted in disdain.

Gu Yue Qing Shu still wanted to persist in his own viewpoint, but it wouldn't be good to refute the elder's decision.

As a junior, he needed to respect the old and take care of the young. How could he so easily refute and question his elder?

Chapter 140: Gu Yue Qing Shu vs Bai Ning Bing (Part 1)

The time Bai Ning Bing took to break out of the ice was shorter than anyone had imagined.

With a loud crack, the ice crystal began to fracture, the cracks intensifying until it completely broke from within.

The clan elder, Gu Yue Qing Shu, Gu Yue Yao Hong and the others, totaling up to five altogether, had surrounded him. Gu Yue Fang Zheng was standing far away on the mountain slope, staring at the battle from a higher ground while staying vigilant. Once a Bai clan Gu Master group appears, he has to send out a warning immediately.

"Bai Ning Bing, you dare to kill the Gu Masters in our clan, breaking the three clan alliance openly. Paying a life for a life is natural law! What else do you have to say?" the clan elder said with a haughty snort.

Bai Ning Bing did not pay him any mind, staying quiet and staring at his right arm instead.

His left arm floundered in vain, grasping nothing as it was reaching for something that wasn't even there in the first place.

He started to frown, his face dim like water as lightning started to nurture between his eyes.

"Actually forcing me to lose off my right arm, this guy is called Fang Yuan, right..." Listening to Xiong Li and Qing Shu's words, he had already learned Fang Yuan's name.

Muttering, Bai Ning Bing's pair of crystal blue eyes was filled with extremely callous killing intent.

His body emanated the oppressive aura of a Rank three Gu Master. As Fang Yuan had predicted earlier, with the capabilities to seal his own cultivation, Bai Ning Bing was also able to release the restrictions on it. It was just that in the battle earlier, he did not have sufficient time to unlock it.

Now, the white silver primeval essence of Rank three filled his aperture fully. The dense primeval essence placed great pressure on his surrounding aperture walls; Bai Ning Bing knew that he was moving towards the path of destruction.

A Gu Master's aperture produced primeval essence, and the primeval essence in turn, nurtures the aperture.

The truth being, as long as the primeval essence exists within the aperture, it acts as a form of nurturing towards the aperture. It is just that this effect is not very evident, far less effective than the Gu Master using the primeval essence to do so.

This was similar to how a still sea water would still have a corrosive effect towards surrounding rocks, but this effect is less evident than the waves hitting on the rocks.

But to the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique, after attaining Rank three, even if they do not expend primeval essence, as long as the primeval essence is stored in the aperture, the nurturing effect would be the same as if a Gu Master was actively using the primeval essence to nurture their aperture.

This is the secret behind the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique's ability to raise a Gu Master's cultivation at rocket speed.

Moreover, this nurturing effect would become stronger as the primeval essence is refined. At Rank four, as long as primeval essence exists within the aperture, they would nourish the aperture and the effect would be several times better than a regular Gu Master using primeval essence to nurture their aperture.

With ordinary Gu Masters, the higher their cultivation, the slower the speed of cultivation. However, the ten extreme physiques were the opposite—the higher the cultivation, the stronger their aptitude and the faster their cultivation, until they explode into oblivion.

As an analogy, it is similar to a person in free fall, dependent on the posture and qualities of that person, they would continue to accelerate as they descended, albeit dying a horrible death once they reach the ground.

The ten extreme physiques' cultivation technique is falling from the highest point with the most suited conditions to fall faster than anyone else. As their cultivation gets faster and faster, it only gives them the temporary glory that they attain before they face the threat of death approaching. Like a meteor landing on Earth, moving toward its own destruction; the point where it shines the brightest comes only at the very moment where it burns up completely in the atmosphere.

Earlier, the reason Bai Ning Bing had diluted his white silver primeval essence into red steel primeval essence was for because of this.

Right now, his aperture was completely filled with white silver primeval essence again, and he could feel that every second, his cultivation was steadily rising and improving.

"Actually forcing me to use the white silver primeval essence, and even making me go as far as to sacrifice the Frost Demon Gu! Where is Fang Yuan?" Bai Ning Bing's killing intent intensified as he asked. His blue iris swept across the surroundings, but could not find a trace of Fang Yuan.

The Frost Demon Gu that he sacrificed was a Rank three Gu worm, one that he only managed to refine after three failures and consuming a large amount of resources. Now that it was gone, it is truly a waste.

Although Bai Ning Bing is Rank three, it only happened recently, and even with the clan's support, he could not hog all the resources to himself. Thus, he only had two Rank three Gu worms. Now that the Frost Demon Gu is gone, he only had the Blue Bird Ice Coffin Gu left.

The more he thought about it, the more he felt angered! Since the start of his youth, he had never suffered such a loss!

If Fang Yuan was here, he'd have attacked in a frenzy with no one able to stop him.

Bai Ning Bing's disregard caused the Gu Yue clan elder to feel greatly humiliated.

"Arrogant young lad, eat my moonblade slash!" He shouted, and jumped.

"Hmph!" Bai Ning Bing's left arm swept, and the frost air that gushed out formed into a long ice blade.

The original ice blade he created was only over a meter long, but now it was two meters in length, with an even deadlier edge and greater frost energy.

Ching!

The Clan elder raised both hands shining with moonlight to collide with the ice blade, emitting a metallic noise.

The Clan elder's face was full of shock however as he took a step back, and both his palms clapped together and slashed out.

Golden moon slash!

A curved moonblade, over a meter long with a golden body, emitted a dominating aura as it flew out.

The golden moonlight reflected on Bai Ning Bing's pale face. He laughed as he raised the ice blade in his left hand, attacking head on.

Clank!

Moonblade and ice blade colliding, the golden moon disappeared, and the ice blade broke into small fragments of ice.

"This is a battle between Rank three Gu Masters? Really strong, not only the ice blade, but also that golden moonblade, I cannot block either!" Far away, Fang Zheng watched in fascination, with his lacking knowledge.

"How can this be? A Rank two Ice Blade Gu, managing to block my Rank three Moonhand blade, as well as the golden moon!" Clan elder stared with bulging eyes, disbelief in his tone.

The Northern Dark Ice Soul physique had a strengthening effect towards Ice Gu, a variation of water-type Gu. In addition, this boost grew stronger as the Gu Master's cultivation rose.

Bai Ning Bing, at Rank three in cultivation, can make a Rank two Gu worm display Rank three power. When he is Rank four, if he used a Rank four Gu worm, it would have an effect that can even surpass Rank five.

Firstly, he suppressed his cultivation, thus only the effect of recovering primeval essence remained. Now that his limiter was off and he was back to Rank three, the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique's true ability was starting to show up.

"Hmph, old man, you don't know a lot of things." Bai Ning Bing's feet paused, holding his ice blade horizontally, as he started to rotate.

Huhuhu...

The intense sound of the wind enveloped him as he became faster and faster.

Howl!

The wind seemed to have transformed into a beast howl, a five meter sword storm forming after a matter of minutes.

The tornado-like winds were white in color, whipping out and causing the people nearby to have numbed senses.

"Quickly dodge!" Even a clan elder, upon seeing this, did not dare to challenge it—he quickly avoided.

But the other Rank two Gu Masters could not manage to dodge in time.

The ice blade storm came at once, with a speed three times or even greater than before.

Ah——!

As soon as the two male Gu Masters were caught up in the storm, their cries came to a stop. In a matter of seconds, they were already minced to a paste by the ice blades and lost their lives on the spot.

"Save me!" Gu Yue Yao Hong screamed in fear, seeing that she was about to be swept into the tornado and perish.

Green Vine Gu!

Gu Yue Qing Shu shot out green vines, which quickly coiled around Gu Yue Yao Hong's waist like snakes.

Just as he was about to drag her back, the ice blade storm had already reached her, devouring her in one shot.

Swish swish swish.

The ice blades instantly went to work, cutting this female Gu Master into five or six pieces. The icy air had already frozen her blood before she could bleed.

Soon after, these pieces were further cut into smaller pieces, forming palm-sized frozen corpse fragments.

"Yao Hong!" Seeing this scene, Qing Shu grieved with sorrowful eyes.

"Sister Yao Hong..." On the slope, Fang Zheng could not take such an intense scene, kneeling on the ground with a soulless gaze, tears overflowing from his eyes.

"Damn it, Steel Shirt Gu!" The clan elder took a deep breath as his body glowed with black light, looking as he was covered in a steel armor.

He used both arms to cover his face as his legs sprinted, charging towards the icy blue ice blade storm.

Chink chink chink.

He charged inside bravely.

In a few breaths time, the ice blades hacked on his body numerous times, emitting a crisp sound.

A moment later, the storm ended.

Bai Ning Bing and the clan elder faced each other.

"Old thing, you are asking for death." Bai Ning Bing's blue iris were purer, complementing his white hair and white clothes while standing still in the cold winds.

His left hand's ice blade had already broken into two. But this did not stop it from penetrating the elder's heart.

"Huh..." Clan elder lowered his head, staring at his left chest, his mouth emitting a sound of helplessness and shock.

Bai Ning Bing let go of his right hand, abandoning this ice blade. He walked past the clan elder, steadily approaching.

Behind him, the clan elder's face was covered with a light blue frost, and soon he collapsed onto the ground to never get up again.

Far away, Fang Zheng saw this scene and his irises shrunk to the size of pins, intense fear spreading throughout his body.

This was out of his wildest dreams.

A grand Rank three clan elder actually died like this. This Bai Ning Bing is so strong?!

"Where is Fang Yuan? Tell me, and I can let you die peacefully." Bai Ning Bing walked towards Gu Yue Qing Shu.

"Bai Ning Bing..." Gu Yue Qing Shu sighed deeply, staring at Bai Ning Bing without fear, "You and I have fought over ten times, you are getting stronger, and right now I have to admit that you have surpassed me. But your strength cannot cause me to betray my clansman. Come, fight me!"

"Just you? Hehe." Bai Ning Bing snorted in disdain, turning around to look at Fang Zheng, raising a brow. "That is Fang Yuan's brother?"

Gu Yue Qing Shu's expression changed, taking a big step out and blocking Bai Ning Bing. "Don't think of finding trouble with him!"

Bai Ning Bing's face sank. "You are quite an interesting opponent, keeping you alive can add some colour to my life. But my mood is very bad now, don't take my patience for granted. Tell me nicely, which direction Fang Yuan went."

Gu Yue Qing Shu replied him in the most direct way with action.

He closed his eyes, and opened them again.

Wood Charm Gu!

Chapter 141: Gu Yue Qing Shu vs Bai Ning Bing (Part 2)

Under the power of the Rank three Gu worm, Qing Shu's eyes turned into a jade green colour.

At this moment, his aura changed. From a vibrant human, it turned into a deep serene forest feeling.

"Oh?" Bai Ning Bing showed slight shock unknowingly. He pouted in dissatisfaction, "It seems that after a long time, you've gained some interesting new skills."

Icicle Gu.

He willed the Gu, and five sharp icicles appeared out of nowhere.

"Go." Bai Ning Bing's ice hand pointed, and the icicle shot out.

Pow pow pow.

From Qing Shu's palms, two vines grew out. The vines danced in the air like two snakes, dancing agilely, easily deflecting the icicles.

The icicle changed directions, only scraping Qing Shu's shoulder, and stabbed deeply into the ground, the hard mountain rock, and the forest that stood like a statue.

Qing Shu easily broke through the attack, causing Bai Ning Bing's attack to be futile.

Bai Ning Bing laughed coldly, "Your whipping skills got better, but I want to see, how many icicles can you block?"

Saying so, Bai Ning Bing's eyes shone with a mild blue light.

Ten icicles appeared immediately, floating in front of him before shooting towards Qing Shu.

After that, ten more were created...

Like this, over several times, it turned into an icicle rain.

Swoosh...

The icicle tore through the air, emitting a sound that shocked people's hearts.

Qing Shu dodged while manipulating his green vine with both hands, dancing like a shadow.

His whipping technique after countless practices, had gotten to a level where he could command them like his fingers, fully in sync.

But there was too many icicles; Qing Shu was bound to miss some, and his shoulder was hit by an icicle.

The icicle penetrated his right shoulder, and the tip appeared from behind him.

Pin Needle Gu.

Qing Shu controlled the pain, sweeping his long hair. From the tips of his hair, numerous jade coloured pin needles shot out.

The pin needles engulfed Bai Ning Bing, but he managed to activate the Water Shield Gu in time—it had gotten stronger too, and was much thicker than before, being no weaker than a Rank three Gu worm's defense.

The pin needles entered the water shield and slowed to a halt, before being purged by the water currents.

But this also forced Bai Ning Bing to stop his icicle attack.

Seeing this opportunity, Qing Shu ignored the pain and pulled out the icicle from his shoulder by force.

There was no blood dripping out, one was due to the icicle's cold air, and the other was because his body was gradually turning into wood.

Bai Ning Bing kept the Water Shield Gu, his gaze attracted to Gu Yue Qing Shu's injury.

From the opening on his torn shirt, he could see Qing Shu's injury, revealing the rings of the tree trunk, and his flesh could be seen recovering at an observable speed, and on the newly grown muscles, the tree's ring lines were formed.

At the same time, both his ears started to become longer, and his hair turned jade green, with green leaves growing within. Both his hands, from the fleshy colour of a normal person, turned darker and more reserved. His skin became harder, and turned into the brown tree bark.

This was the first time he had used the Wood Charm Gu without considering the consequences!

The Wood Charm Gu was causing him to turn into a tree spirit, and at the same time, Gu Yue Qing Shu could feel the rich natural essence in the air.

These essence could not be felt by ordinary Gu Masters. Only special lifeforms like tree spirits could feel, absorb and use them.

Gu Yue Qing Shu felt that he was soaking in his mother's liquid, thick essence enveloping him, giving him a strong sense of fulfillment.

On his body, the Moonwhirl Gu did not change, but the Green Vine Gu, Pin Needle Gu and the vitality grass all showed signs of growth. With Qing Shu's identity as a tree spirit, when he uses these wood attribute Gu worms, their power is amplified!

Gu Yue Qing Shu breathed deeply, he had never felt so strong before! The rich natural essence gave him an almost infinite source of primeval essence to use. This was the power of the Wood Charm Gu.

But in his heart, a deep sense of fear also rose.

He knew that if he was greedy over this strong and comfortable feeling, and used the Wood Charm Gu without restraint, he would eventually turn into a dead treeman.

Any thing had its price.

Gu Yue Qing Shu soon suppressed this fear. He stared at Bai Ning Bing and said two words —"Let's fight."

Thus, the intense battle started.

Green vine vs Ice blade, Icicle vs Pin needles!

One was the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique, with insane primeval essence recovery rate, and the other was the wood charm tree spirit, using all the natural essence as his own.

This battle, had far surpassed the realm of ordinary Rank three Gu Masters.

Fang Zheng stood on the slope, watching dumbstruck. He had never seen such an all-out intense fight!

Normally speaking, Gu Masters have limited primeval essence, and they always have to keep 10% of it as reserves. Carefully using them, like thin ice.

But now, be it Qing Shu or Bai Ning Bing, both were using it without constraints as if they had an unlimited supply of primeval essence.

The entire path was wrecked by their battle. Huge trees fell and were destroyed, mountain rocks smashed to bits.

After a long time...

Blue bird ice coffin Gu!

Bai Ning Bing grabbed an opportunity and opened his mouth, and from within, an ice blue bird flew out.

The flying bird chirped, its body like a pigeon, but under the boost of the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique, it gradually turned into the size of an eagle while flying, and after circling for a while, flew towards Gu Yue Qing Shu.

Gu Yue Qing Shu could not dodge in time, so he faced it head on.

Bam.

A sound explosion later, Gu Yue Qing Shu was frozen in an ice crystal as large as a room.

"It's over..." Bai Ning Bing sighed as he had not fully enjoyed himself.

He saw the immobile Gu Yue Qing Shu within the ice crystal, and muttered, "Thanks for providing me such an interesting experience, this battle is the most exciting one I've had thus far. Qing Shu, your death has meaning, I will remember it clearly."

"Lord Qing Shu!" On the slope, Fang Zheng shouted loudly.

"Why are you shouting, you mere ant, the next one will be you." Bai Ning Bing snorted, walking towards Fang Zheng.

At this point, the sound of the ice crystal breaking entered his ears.

"How can this be?" He turned around and saw that within the ice crystal, Qing Shu had undergone a massive transformation.

His body became bigger, and his Rank two Gu Master outfit was almost ripped.

His hair turned into green vines, and palm-sized leaves grew on it endlessly, turning into a thick greenery.

His fingers had turned into sturdy wood, his limbs turning into thick tree branches, only having a rough form for his arms and legs.

With a sound, the ice crystal broke completely.

Gu Yue Qing Shu stood up; he had already changed in appearance completely, the original delicate and handsome human face turned into a sharp-nosed, huge eye tree spirit face.

He was three meters tall with a strong body, wearing tree barks as his armor, and on them were large amounts of leaves and vines.

Bai Ning Bing stared at his transformation in shock; compared to this Qing Shu, he was like a child beside an adult.

"This appearance, did you refine the Wood Charm Gu? This Gu is way harder to refine than my Frost Demon Gu!" Bai Ning Bing found the answer.

"Tree spirit wood charm can use the essence in the air, no wonder Gu Yue Qing Shu had such ample primeval essence." He realized at once, but got more confused.

He asked the question in his heart, "Qing Shu, using the Wood Charm Gu like this, aren't you afraid of turning into a dead treeman? So what if you win me? You're destined to die!"

"Bai Ning Bing..." Gu Yue Qing Shu's voice became low, "I understand you like I understand myself. You and I are both orphans, adopted by the clan leader. Yet we walk on such different paths. A tree dying in a forest is nothing, for as long as the forest exists, numerous trees will continue to grow and rise up. Let's have our final battle, my nemesis!"

Saying so, hundreds of green vines assaulted Bai Ning Bing like giant pythons.

"For the clan? What a fool!" Bai Ning Bing retreated in a rush.

But the green vines' speed was faster than before by several times, quickly chasing up to Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing controlled his body and dodged nimbly. Green vines thick as an arm swept near his body, hitting the soil or the mountain rocks, causing the soil to fly and the rock fragments to scatter.

Water Shield Gu!

Bai Ning Bing could not dodge in time, and created his shield.

Qing Shu had seen through the weakness of this Gu worm. He did not attack forcefully, but manipulated the vines to wrap around the shield.

Next, he pulled back his strength, and the water shield came into contact. The surface water current moved quickly as it hit the green vines, causing water to splash everywhere.

The water shield could not endure the strength of the green vines' restriction, and shrunk in size, on the verge of collapsing.

"Not good! If the water shield breaks and I get entangled in the green vines, I will get killed by Gu Yue Qing Shu!" Bai Ning Bing in the water shield was sure of his situation.

In the next moment, the water shield exploded.

Bam!

An ice blade storm exploded from within, becoming larger and larger.

Bai Ning Bing purposely withdrew the Water Shield Gu's defense—since defending couldn't work, he had to fight offense with offense!

At once, the temperature fell and cold air emanated.

The white ice blade storm flew towards Qing Shu. The vines could not stop this tornado, and were cut into numerous segments by the ice blades.

"Nice timing." Gu Yue Qing Shu had no fear, his large body bravely entering the ice blade storm.

With a bam, he knocked onto the white colour tornado.

He opened both hands, wrapping around it.

Crack crack...

The sharp ice blades cut through his body, and numerous leaves and tree bark were sent flying.

The delayed sense of pain assaulted him as Qing Shu growled in pain, but did not let go, using all his strength to grip the tornado.

The ice blade storm was actually shrinking under his strength.

"Damn it! This maniac that doesn't care for his life..." Bai Ning Bing scolded internally. In this situation there was no other way, he could only create more ice blades and rotate faster, competing with Gu Yue Qing Shu.

The ice blades slashed on Qing Shu's body and gradually became blunt, but under the Ice Blade Gu's power, they sharpened once again.

The battle was at a stalemate, out of their control, and no one could hold back and stop.

Either Gu Yue Qing Shu kills Bai Ning Bing, or Bai Ning Bing kills Qing Shu. Pitting offense with offense, the battle was filled with bravery and intensity.

Chapter 142: Gu Yue Qing Shu vs Bai Ning Bing (Part 3)

Fang Zheng stood far away, not even daring to take a deep breath as he watched.

The battle had reached the climax, the winner and the loser decided from this showdown.

"Lord Qing Shu, hang in there!" Fang Zheng was so nervous his body was shaking, he knew that going over would only cause trouble, thus he could only cheer for Gu Yue Qing Shu loudly.

As if he heard Fang Zheng's voice, the ice blade storm got smaller, forcefully suppressed by Qing Shu.

"Damn it, I can actually get into a situation where my primeval essence is insufficient..." Bai Ning Bing gritted his teeth, rotating slower as his primeval essence recovery could not keep up with his expenditure, getting into a helpless situation.

The Northern Dark Ice Soul physique's primeval essence recovery was very fast, but the recovery speed at Rank three was still slightly inferior to the tree spirit's ability to extract natural essence. If Bai Ning Bing could cultivate to Rank four, his recovery speed would greatly surpass the Wood Charm Gu.

Except, in life and death battles, there were no "ifs".

No matter who was the victor, the results had to be accepted.

Eventually the ice blade storm stopped, but Gu Yue Qing Shu also paid a heavy price.

His arms were large like a horse carriage, and at the moment on his left arm he had two fingers left and three on his right. Both his palms were sliced off by half due to the ice blades.

But when his palms gradually gathered together towards the middle, new tree branches grew again rapidly from his palm, interweaving together.

The two palms formed a wooden cage, trapping Bai Ning Bing within.

"Damn it!" Bai Ning Bing gritted his teeth. His primeval essence was running dry, he could only be at Qing Shu's mercy.

"We won!!" Far away, Fang Zheng jumped at this sight.

"Am I going to die...?" Bai Ning Bing shouted in his heart, his eyes widening as he saw the two palms approaching. When both palms clasp together, he would be smashed into a bloody meat pie.

But the palm's speed became slower, and slowly stood in mid-air.

Bai Ning Bing was stunned momentarily, before realizing that Gu Yue Qing Shu's body had developed problems, instantly being overjoyed.

"Damn, I was so close..." At this moment, Gu Yue Qing Shu's heart was filled with helplessness. His hands had lost all senses, completely turning into wood.

At the same time, he gradually lost the connection to his intestines and lungs. The Wood Charm Gu's ability had corroded his entire body, bringing him to the brink of death.

"No, it cannot end like this! I can still use the Green Vine Gu!" Gu Yue Qing Shu forced himself to focus and activated the Green Vine Gu.

Numerous thick vines appeared and attacked Bai Ning Bing through the openings of the cage.

Bai Ning Bing dodged quickly but he had undergone several battles, and his stamina was greatly depleted. Furthermore, there was little space in the cage, and he could not move much, thus eventually a vine entangled onto his right leg and tripped him.

"It's over." Qing Shu sighed in relief, as he quickly moved tens of green vines to follow up.

At his moment of life and death, Bai Ning Bing's aperture finally recovered enough primeval essence for his usage requirement.

He used all the primeval essence without further thoughts, sending it all into the Ice Blade Gu, and formed a new ice blade.

The ice blade was sharp and cut off the green vine on his right leg. Bai Ning Bing rolled in a sorry state, managing to avoid tens of vines.

The green vines hit the ground and penetrated the thick earth. The soil flew around, and the green vines attacked once again.

Bai Ning Bing breathed heavily as he used the ice blade to defend desperately.

The green vines attacked from all directions, as if he was walking on thin ice. A single mistake by Bai Ning Bing would cause him to be instantly killed by the vines.

But he was after all a top tier genius. With the stimulation of death, he squeezed out all the potential in him, and his evasive actions became quick and clear.

Although he was tripped sometimes by the green vines, he managed to avoid the danger and eventually kept his life.

The green vines were cut by the ice blades, and their amount became less and less.

It was not that Qing Shu did not want to activate the Green Vine Gu and produce more vines, but it was because the surrounding natural essence had been almost fully absorbed by him.

Although outside, there was still essence in the air gathering, the diluted essence in the air was no longer able to fulfill the Green Vine Gu's needs.

There was an even worse piece of news—the Wood Charm Gu's strength had completely corroded Gu Yue Qing Shu's body, and was starting to take over his consciousness.

Gu Yue Qing Shu's consciousness started to become dazed, and he had intermediate blank outs.

The aura of death was blowing on his face.

"Is it going to end? No..." He was indignant, forcing his mind to focus and put in the last ditch effort in killing Bai Ning Bing.

He could no longer see anything, for the Wood Charm Gu had taken over his eyes, and he could not hear any longer either, his ears merely an accessory now.

He only had a meager sense of touch.

Relying on Bai Ning Bing's retaliation, he judged the distance and position, and attacked.

His efforts were rewarded, as Bai Ning Bing was finally captured. A vine wrapped around his neck and raised him up, gradually tightening.

Bai Ning Bing could feel difficulty in breathing, it was no use even if he opened his mouth. Along with Qing Shu, they was progressing towards death.

Fang Yuan breathed roughly, an intense battle had ended.

On the floor lay five corpses with opened eyes, they were all Bai clan Gu Masters.

Relying on the Stealth Scales Gu to sneak attack, with the advantage of the Moonglow Gu and the strength of two boars along with his 500 years of experience, he displayed shocking abilities.

Although he told Qing Shu he was going to return to the village, it was just an excuse.

After leaving for a distance, he used the Stealth Scales Gu to hide himself, moving around the battlefield and going to the area where Man Shi and Xiong Li died.

He collected the Gu worms in Man Shi and his group mates' corpses, and when he got the Xiong Li's corpse, he found that the corpse was missing, not to mention their Gu worms.

"It seems that Xiong Lin collected their corpses. What a waste, I wanted to get Xiong Li's Brown Bear Innate Strength Gu." Fang Yuan sighed.

Leaving Xiong Lin alive was not what he wanted.

But back then, after he had killed Xiong Jiang, Xiong Lin was already vigilant, thus killing the latter would expend much effort.

At that time, Bai Ning Bing was close by. If Fang Yuan and Xiong Lin fought, Bai Ning Bing would be overjoyed.

"But the Brown Bear Innate Strength Gu might not be on Xiong Li's body. He already has the strength of a bear, he might have given the Gu back to his clan already."

Fang Yuan focused his gaze and escaped the mountain path battlefield.

Qing Shu and the others fighting against Bai Ning Bing would cause a huge commotion, and it will be detected by the surrounding wolf packs and Gu Masters.

Although Fang Yuan was not optimistic about Qing Shu's group, he had seen firsthand the power of the Wood Charm Gu in his previous life. Against Bai Ning Bing, there would at least be an intense struggle.

He was unwilling to give up such a chance, thus he chose to wait at the surroundings.

At times, Gu Masters were attracted by the sounds of the intense battle, so Fang Yuan lured some wolf packs over and restrained them.

Those that he cannot stop, Fang Yuan would strike with his own hands.

"The mountain path battlefield's noise has come to a halt, it seems they are deciding the victor already." His right ear had roots growing out, digging into the mountain walls, allowing Fang Yuan to hear some things from the battlefield.

Honestly speaking, Qing Shu's performance was better than expected. After Bai Ning Bing lost his right arm, the effect on his battle strength was much greater than Fang Yuan had expected.

But soon, Fang Yuan's expression changed.

He heard large amounts of footsteps from two directions, heading towards the battlefield.

One direction was from Gu Yue village, while the other direction was from the Bai clan village.

Each group had at least twenty people. It was not something a bold lightning wolf pack could block, and Fang Yuan could not lure two groups of wolf over anyway.

"It seems the news about this battle has been found out by someone, so these are the reinforcements sent by the two clans, I have to enter the mountain path immediately."

Fang Yuan's distance was shorter, thus being the first to enter the mountain path.

The battlefield's scenario was not out of his expectations.

From the cage's opening, he could see Bai Ning Bing hanging by the vines on his last breath, but was still barely alive.

"The ice muscles' defense are stubbornly sustaining Bai Ning Bing's life. Hmph, unfortunately, you have encountered me." Fang Yuan's killing intent surged as he took a few steps forwards, sprinting towards Bai Ning Bing.

Swish swish swish.

Suddenly, a flurry of pin needles surrounded Fang Yuan like rain droplets.

It was Gu Yue Qing Shu's Pin Needle Gu, attacking Fang Yuan.

"What's going on?" Fang Yuan retreated immediately, avoiding the pin needle rain.

He focused the gaze at the large tree, realizing at once, "It seems that Gu Yue Qing Shu's consciousness had been blurred to the point where he can no longer differentiate between friend or foe. He's merely relying on his will and attempting to kill Bai Ning Bing. Anyone that intrudes the battlefield would be regarded as an interferer by him."

At this moment, Bai clan Gu Masters appeared from the mountain path.

Seeing such an intense battlefield, their faces showed a shocked expression.

"The lad over there, don't make any unnecessary movements!" A Rank three Gu Master shouted towards Fang Yuan, his tone full of warning and threat.

"This Bai Ning Bing is such a cockroach." Fang Yuan seeing this scene, laughed coldly in his heart, knowing that he could not have the last strike.

Firstly, Qing Shu's consciousness was blurred, a green vine was insufficient to kill Bai Ning Bing who had the ice muscles.

For Fang Yuan to get close to Bai Ning Bing, he had to break through Qing Shu's trap, but this way, it would divert much of his attention and might even help Bai Ning Bing in escaping his predicament.

Even if they broke through by force, Bai clan's Rank three Gu Masters and Rank two elites were not for show, they would definitely stop him.

Furthermore, fighting against Bai Ning Bing had danger as well.

Bai Ning Bing's aperture had recovered primeval essence sufficiently to at least use the Blue bird ice coffin Gu.

Even if Fang Yuan managed to kill Bai Ning Bing, these Bai clan elites would not let go of him, they would definitely kill Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan sighed in his heart, "The distance is too long, there are at least twenty steps to get to him, and my Moonglow Gu's attack range is only ten steps, furthermore... to kill this Bai Ning Bing who is destined to die anyway, I would need to put my life at such risk, greatly interfering with my rebirth plans, it is not worth it."

Thinking so, Fang Yuan took a few steps back.

This was evidently a weak and cowardly movement, causing the Bai clan Gu Masters to breathe a sigh of relief.

Chapter 143: Answer

Soon after, Fang Zheng rushed over as well.

"Lord Qing Shu!" He had an exhilarated expression, stupidly running towards Gu Yue Qing Shu, but soon was forced to retreat by the pin needles.

"Group leader, it's me Fang Zheng!!" He shouted in shock, sensing something amiss for the first time.

But how could Gu Yue Qing Shu answer him.

"Brother, what's wrong with Lord Qing Shu?" Fang Zheng, under confusion and shock, could only turn to Fang Yuan.

But Fang Yuan ignored him, squatting down and grabbing with his right hand, making a claw shape towards Bai Ning Bing.

Plunder Gu!

He secretly activated this Gu, quickly sensing that he had grabbed something.

He quickly pulled back, and a Gu worm flew out of Bai Ning Bing's body.

It was a red steel Relic Gu!

This was given to Bai Ning Bing by the Bai clan leader, but Bai Ning Bing never used it as he quickly reached Rank three cultivation.

Now, it became Fang Yuan's loot.

Seeing the red steel Relic Gu coming out of Bai Ning Bing's body and flying away, landing in Fang Yuan's palm, the Bai clan Gu Masters were anxious until their eyes turned red, starting to scream.

"Scumbag, if you don't want to die, stop right now!"

"Stealing our Bai clan Gu worm right in front of us!!"

"It's a red steel Relic Gu worm..."

Fang Yuan laughed coldly. Once the red steel Relic Gu was obtained, he used the Spring Autumn Cicada to instantly refine it but did not keep it in his aperture, putting it in his clothes instead, giving the impression that he had not refined them yet.

He grabbed once again; this time a grey coloured beetle flew out.

"Stone Aperture Gu..." Fang Yuan recognised this Gu immediately. As his eyes shone, he refined it once again and kept it in his arms.

"Damn it, yet another Gu worm!"

"Stop him, stop him, he dares to do so openly, he does not hold any regard for our Bai clan."

"Save Bai Ning Bing, kill these guys!"

The Bai clan Gu Masters growled, running furiously from the mountain path.

Bai Ning Bing had the full support of his clan, so every Gu worm in his possession was outstanding. Now that they were snatched away by Fang Yuan in public, they all could feel their hearts bleeding.

This felt worse than killing them.

Seeing these people approaching with their imposing aura, Fang Zheng took a step back in fright, but Fang Yuan was unfazed.

In the current scene, he and Fang Zheng were at the east side of the mountain path while the Bai clan Gu Masters were at the west, and in the middle of the two sides were Gu Yue Qing Shu and Bai Ning Bing.

Whoosh whoosh!

Pin needles rained like cats and dogs.

"Damn it..." Bai clan Gu Masters started scolding, as they were blocked by Gu Yue Qing Shu.

"Gu Yue Qing Shu is going to die anytime, the remaining time only allows me to use the Plunder Gu once, what would it be this time?" Fang Yuan calmed down, using the Plunder Gu again.

Every time the Plunder Gu was used, it expended a large amount of primeval essence. It depended on how strong the target Gu worm was. The harder the process, the more primeval essence is expended. If the plunder fails, the Gu Master would even face a backlash.

Thus, the Plunder Gu was a rather unreliable Gu, with little usage.

But at this moment, Bai Ning Bing was almost dead, his consciousness was hazy and he was almost at his limits. Plundering his Gu worm was not hard at all.

Among the Gu worms in Bai Ning Bing's possession, the most valuable is the Frost Demon Gu. This Gu was on par with the Wood Charm Gu, allowing a person to transform into the frost demon. But if used for extended periods, it would cause the Gu Master's life force to dwindle, turning into an ice statue.

Bai Ning Bing knew this weakness, thus he had never been like Gu Yue Qing Shu, using the Gu to such an extent.

Other than the Frost Demon Gu, the second most valuable is the Blue bird ice coffin Gu, a Rank three Gu. Right now, it resides in Bai Ning Bing's throat.

If he can plunder the Blue bird ice coffin Gu, it is the best scenario. But the Plunder Gu is only a Rank two Gu, even if the Gu Master wills it, it does not have to ability to do so.

Eventually, Fang Yuan caught Bai Ning Bing's Water Shield Gu.

This was not bad at all. The Water Shield Gu together with the White Jade Gu could provide Fang Yuan greater defensive power.

The tree spirit that Gu Yue Qing Shu turned into was eventually felled by the Bai clan Gu Masters.

They split open the wooden cage and saved the Bai Ning Bing who had fainted after losing his right arm.

Just as they were about to slaughter Fang Yuan and Fang Zheng, the Gu Yue clan reinforcements arrived.

The two were at a stalemate for a while, before both retreated in mutual understanding.

Qing Shu's death and Bai Ning Bing's injury, with the threat of the wolf tide, such a loss is already horrifying. If a large-scale fighting broke out, for each clan their pressure for survival would intensify greatly.

Regardless of which world, people always compete for their own benefits.

And the greatest benefit in the world, is undoubtedly "survival".

Eventually, Gu Yue Qing Shu's corpse and Gu worms, were brought back by the Gu Yue clan's Gu Masters.

The two sides held caution as they retreated from the battlefield.

The sky was raining, and the entire area was gloomy.

A group of people stood at a slope behind the village, this was the graveyard.

Every now and then, there would be a few more gravestones erected here.

In this world, it was tough for people to survive, and whether it is due to external threat or internal cause, there would always be a few sacrifices.

The clan elder's voice was low as it entered everyone's ears, making them feel even more down.

"We have the same surname, we come from the same clan, the same blood flows in our bodies."

"We are so close together in distance, yet we are forever separated by life and death."

"This pain aches in my heart."

"Wait for me."

"Someday in the future, I will lay beside you as well."

"Let us turn into ash and soil, as we support our future generations..."

On a newly erected gravestone, a group of people hung their heads low. Some were crying softly, and some were staring at the name on the tombstone as they were filled with sadness.

The cruelty of death was like a white bony arm, slashing a bloody injury on everyone's heart.

Except that some were already numb from the pain, while others were still too inexperienced.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was among these people, his drooping eyes staring at the tombstone with "Gu Yue Qing Shu", these four words.

Dead?

In his eyes, there was endless uncertainty.

Yesterday's battle, the entire process and situation was still imprinted deep in his heart.

His experience was limited, he did not understand Gu Yue Qing Shu's moving and tragic bravery as well as his sacrifice.

But now that the truth was in front of him, he could not accept it suddenly.

"Dead? That kind Lord Qing Shu that always smiles, advises, shows concern and takes care of me.... Is actually dead?"

"Why did this happen?"

"Why is it that in this world, good people die easily, while bad people live long?"

"Is this a dream, am I having a dream right now?"

Fang Zheng clenched his fists, and the realistic feeling of touch caused him to feel ever more upset.

The discussions of the surrounding Gu Masters entered his ears.

"Sigh, I can't believe that this time, even Lord Qing Shu sacrificed himself."

"Humans will eventually die, but it is too much of a pity, I heard that Bai Ning Bing still had a breath of vitality left, he was eventually saved."

"May he rest well underground, and bless us with the hopes of surviving this wolf tide..."

The crowds slowly dispersed, until Fang Zheng was the last one left.

The young man's lonely shadow, facing the graveyard full of tombstones alone.

"Lord Qing Shu!" He suddenly kneeled on the ground, his tears falling on the ground.

He was lost, he was regretful, he was in pain!

Drip. Drip drop, drip drop...

Bean-sized raindrops fell from the dark clouds, hitting on the ground, causing the leaves and tree branches to bend.

The smell of the earth rushed into Fang Zheng's nostrils, and he wept in painful grief. The sound of his crying and the raindrops mixed together; his ten fingers grabbed the soil, trying to retrieve Qing Shu's life, but eventually he only had two handfuls of soil.

It started raining, and Bai Ning Bing lay upon a soft bed, staring at this rain blankly.

His right arm which was broken was already taken care off, wrapped with a white bandage. His eyes also returned to black, but his cultivation was Rank three, he had no longer suppressed it to Rank two.

When he woke up from his slumber, he suddenly lost all spirits, feeling extremely empty.

He laid on his bed peacefully, his eyes opened for over ten hours. He let the Rank three white silver primeval essence nurture his aperture; he couldn't bother to care about it.

This rain triggered the deepest memories in his heart.

It was under such a summer rain that he was officially adopted by the Bai clan leader. The clan leader's benevolent and hopeful gaze fell on him, as the surrounding clan elders gave their words of congratulations, gushing in like tidal waves.

The young him stood on the icy ground barefooted, and he stared at the rain outside the window, but all he felt was being lost and lonely.

"What is the meaning of living?" This question troubled him for twenty over years, and could continue to trouble him, until the problem of his self-explosion surfaced again.

"Is it for kinship, for the clan..." Bai Ning Bing unavoidably thought of Gu Yue Qing Shu.

From young to adulthood, he had seen such a sacrifice many times—sometimes it is a Bai clansman, sometimes they were from Gu Yue clan or Xiong clan.

He could not understand these fanatics, he was born as a cold and emotionless person.

Gu Yue Qing Shu could not give him answers, thus Bai Ning Bing thought of Fang Yuan.

The first time he saw Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan was sitting by a tree, eating a wild fruit he picked, emotionlessly starting at the battle below.

He was excited until his body shuddered, shivering with excitement. The reason was that he saw himself from Fang Yuan's similar eerie abyss-like iris.

But now that he thought about it, Fang Yuan's gaze had something more than him.

That thing, is the answer to his questions.

The rain got heavier and thunder rumbled while lightning flashed in the sky.

"What is the meaning behind living?" In the dark room, Gu Yue Fang Zheng asked the same question.

Gu Yue clan leader, Gu Yue Bo sighed. He stared pitifully at the young man who had lost his soul, and then looked outside the window, at the rain.

Fang Zheng's doubt was understandable; an unavoidable death always urges people to think behind the true value of existence.

"You know something? More than ten years ago, there was another young man with a similar situation as you, and asked me the same question." Long after, Gu Yue Bo started to speak.

"That person, is your clan leader's... my adopted son—Gu Yue Qing Shu."

Fang Zheng was momentarily stunned, raising his head. A pair of swollen red eyes, showing an intense urge for answers.

Chapter 144: Sacrifice is common, and faith is undying

"I said to him, a person has a thousand and one reasons to live. Why are you alive, I cannot answer that, only you have the answer. Go find it yourself," Gu Yue Bo said.

"Then clan leader, what is your answer for yourself?" Fang Zheng blinked in confusion, asking.

Gu Yue Bo laughed. In his eyes, Fang Zheng and Qing Shu's images were overlapping, Gu Yue Qing Shu had asked the same question in the past.

Clan leader thought for a moment, recalling the past, then repeating the same answer he gave back then, "An organisation is bound to have sacrifices. From the moment a person is born, death is imminent. Between life and death, humans are fragile, but one thing can warm the heart, and shine upon our souls. That is love—this is my answer."

Sacrifice is common.

Gu Yue Qing Shu is he, Gu Yue Bo's adopted son, and after raising him for so many years, his current sacrifice brought great pain to this foster father.

But as clan leader, he had seen far too many sacrifices.

When one has the resolution of life and death, pain and grief becomes more acceptable.

Fang Zheng lowered his head, keeping silent; it seems he was thinking.

Clan leader laughed, taking a letter from the drawer in his desk. He handed it to Fang Zheng.

"This is Gu Yue Qing Shu's letter. It records the answers to questions he's been thinking about for years, I am handing it to you now, you can take a look. This is his answer."

Undoubtedly, Fang Zheng's current heart had intense attraction to this letter.

He opened it on the spot, and after seeing the first line, his tears could not help but flow out.

It was Gu Yue Qing Shu's familiar handwriting, in his words there was his unique amicable aura.

The starting paragraph recorded his perplexity and pain.

Next was the situations that had given him some ideas through continuously thinking about them these past years.

Fang Zheng looked at the letter, and felt like he had experienced Gu Yue Qing Shu's entire life. He followed Gu Yue Qing Shu's footsteps, until he finished the entire letter.

At the end, this was recorded.

"The clan is like a forest, and we members are like the trees in the forest. The old trees extend their branches and shelter the young from rain and wind. When the young trees grow into large and tall trees, the old trees will turn into the nutrients in the soil, fertilizing the land and nurturing new trees. People will always die, and heaven and earth will not remember us. But new trees are the proof that the old trees have existed. Under this continuous testament, the clan forest becomes larger and spreads further, walking towards the path of prosperity and flourishment."

"People are bound to die. As Gu Masters, we cannot hide from impending death. Even Rank seven and eight Gu Masters can merely live a little longer. Towards death, I feel fear as well. But I understand deeply, eventually, one day I Gu Yue Qing Shu will die too. I might die of old age, illness, or the battlefield. But at that moment, I can leave peacefully with no regrets."

At the end of the letter.

"Lord foster father, the question I asked you before, I think I have found the answer."

After seeing the letter, Fang Zheng wept soundlessly.

In his mind, it was filled with memories of Qing Shu. When he committed a mistake, Qing Shu did not blame but instead comforted him. When facing trouble, the gaze of encouragement was given, and when in a loss, the hands of Qing Shu would warmly touch Fang Zheng's head.

Gu Yue Bo kept the letter and said, "In future, when you think of the answer, you can also write a letter and tell me. Go, return and have a rest. The danger of the wolf tide is not over, we need you to contribute your strength as well."

"No." Fang Zheng slowly raised his head, clenching his fists.

"What?" Gu Yue Bo asked.

"I've found my answer." Fang Zheng's tone was filled with indescribable determination as he continued, "I want strength! To protect my family, and protect them from any harm. I want to protect the clan, and strengthen the clan! I want the wolf tide to no longer be able to torture us, I want to see the happiness of joy of my companions! This pain, I do not want it to repeat. I want to use my pair of hands, my body, my soul, to protect those around me!"

Gu Yue Bo showed an expression of surprise, and at this moment, he felt that he saw Gu Yue Qing Shu.

"Qing Shu, you did not die in vain..." Seeing Fang Zheng's shining eyes, clan leader sighed emotionally in his heart.

An old tree has fallen, and just as it gradually decays away in the soil, a new sprout is already starting to grow rapidly.

...

Ren Zu was unable to endure the heart of loneliness, thus he dug out both eyes, turning them into a son and daughter. This alleviated his sense of loneliness.

But good things do not last, for his children started to crave the scenery of the outside world, forgetting all about their father Ren Zu and always going out to play until they forgot the time, and even forgot to take care of Ren Zu.

Ren Zu could not see anything, it was total darkness.

But at time, he could see a little bit of light.

To this, he felt perturbed, and asked the Attitude Gu.

Attitude Gu told this to him, "Oh, this is the eternal light given out by the Faith Gu."

"Faith?" Bai Ning Bing seeing this, laughed and threw the book that recorded the ancient legends out.

The door was opened at this moment, and the person entering was almost hit in the face by the book.

"Ning Bing, what are you doing?" The one entering was the Bai clan leader.

He frowned, consoling, "I know your mood is bad, but losing your right arm is nothing. In this world, there are many Gu worms that can heal such an injury."

"In the past, I got the clan elders to stay by your side and protect you, but you always rejected it, and even attacked the clan elders. You've finally suffered a loss this time huh?"

"But this is a good thing. Since young you've had too smooth of a path, but as long as it is not death, such a loss is no big deal. Your injuries are already healed, but the wolf tide is getting more ferocious, the clan needs your strength!"

"A bunch of wolf cubs, what can they amount to?" Bai Ning Bing shut his eyes, lying on the bed and answering nonchalantly.

Clan leader's face showed a serious expression, "The situation is not looking good, or rather, it is pessimistic. According to our reconnaissance, there are already three frenzy lightning wolf packs moving near the village. Your failure brought a great influence to our clansmen. I hope that tonight, you can come out and show yourself. As long as you are standing, it can greatly motivate our clansmen. Do you understand?"

"I get it, I get it. It's a small matter." Bai Ning Bing responded, showing impatience.

If it was any other person acting like this to the clan leader, they would have gotten heavily punished, but Bai Ning Bing was different.

Bai clan leader sighed helplessly, closing the door and leaving.

When the room had only Bai Ning Bing left, he opened his eyes, showing a gaze full of loneliness and perplexity.

He did not tell the others about the problem with his body, and the premonition of death that he was feeling.

From the clan's ancient records, he found out the name of the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique. In that limited information, the ten extreme physiques were also known as the absolute death talents, for when the aperture walls reach their limits, the self-destructive power would be extremely great.

It is true that the Bai clan leader had raised Bai Ning Bing for many years, being so lenient to him. However, if the matter of the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique was exposed, Bai Ning Bing had no doubt that the first person to kill him would be this Bai clan leader.

"What's the point of a person being alive?"

In the past, when he considered this question, Bai Ning Bing would feel lost, feeling emotions like boredom, frustration and anger... all these negative emotions.

But now, his heart felt a sense of peacefulness.

People would grow up, not to mention a genius like him.

In the past, he knew that he was going to die, thus in his despair he longed to live, and he felt a sense of fear towards death deep in his heart.

But now, after he had almost died, he had gotten over it.

Allowing the Rank three white silver primeval essence to nurture his aperture, he was no longer worried.

After all, he was no longer afraid of death.

Even though he was still lost about the meaning of living, he knew where the answer was.

This answer, was already in Fang Yuan's heart.

This feeling was indescribable; it was like an instinct, but he was clear of it.

Moreover, the Stone Aperture Gu was in Fang Yuan's hands.

"Fang Yuan... we will meet again," he lightly muttered, his eyes shining with a brilliant light, like the glimmer of a diamond.

"Stone Aperture Gu..." In the rented house, Fang Yuan held the Gu worm in his hands, falling into deep thought.

Stone Aperture Gu was like a dice, cubic and had a grey white body, extremely sturdy.

This Gu was an expenditure type Gu, gone after one use. Its use was to turn a Gu Master's aperture wall into a sturdy rock wall.

This act completely squeezes the aperture's potential and growth dry, allowing the Gu Master to reach peak stage cultivation.

For example, Fang Yuan was now a Rank two middle stage, so after using the Gu, he can instantly become Rank two peak stage.

But the price is, Fang Yuan would no longer have the possibility to advance to Rank three. At the same time, he would lose the ability to regenerate primeval essence, thus he would only be able to use primeval stones to replenish them.

The Stone Aperture Gu was for some Gu Masters who were at their wits end. For some Gu Master's aperture that suffered an unrecoverable injury, developing cracks and can't be healed, they would have to use this Gu.

Or in special situations, the Gu Master has no hopes of advancing and need to raise their cultivation quickly to live. Thus they will use this Gu.

"The cost of refining this Stone Aperture Gu is very high. Seeing that Bai Ning Bing refined this Gu worm, he probably wants to convert his aperture into a stone aperture to prevent the imminent death. Unfortunately this method can only delay his death, but cannot stop his destruction. If the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique is so easily broken, how can it be called a ten extreme physique?"

This Stone Aperture Gu was useless to Fang Yuan, but the red steel Relic Gu he got from Bai Ning Bing's body as well as the Water Shield Gu were very useful.

As for the Gu worms Fang Yuan extracted from Gu Yue Man Shi and the other's bodies, they were not outstanding, and once he returned to the clan he had them exchanged for large amounts of merit points.

Because of the wolf tide, the issue of Qing Shu and Bai Ning Bing's battle was suppressed by all three clans, controlling their urges. The three clans needed each other's power to survive this ordeal first.

Xiong Lin's report, exposed the fact that Fang Yuan possessed the White Jade Gu. But he used the reason of buying it from the caravan to get through for the time being.

Chapter 145: Sacrifices are encouraged

As a person involved, Fang Yuan had to go through the clan's investigation.

It was not an in-depth investigation; the ever growing severity of the wolf tide had attracted almost all the attention of the clan's higher-ups. Fang Yuan's Earth Communication Ear Grass and Stealth Scales Gu were still concealed but even if they were exposed, Fang Yuan could just attribute it to the caravan.

In any case, communications had already been severed due to the wolf tide; the caravan won't be coming. Under such circumstances, the clan couldn't obtain the confirmation from the caravan and could only delay the investigation.

When the results of any investigation truly came out, Fang Yuan would have already become a Rank three and left Qing Mao mountain.

Of course, if the Four Flavors Liquor worm and Spring Autumn Cicada were exposed, it would be a completely different matter.

Either of them could cause a huge commotion in the village if exposed.

Four Flavors Liquor worm represented a whole new fusion recipe and had extremely significant meaning. Fang Yuan wouldn't be able to explain it even if he pushed it onto the caravan, and would be thoroughly investigated by the clan.

And Spring Autumn Cicada? If it was discovered, the wolf tide would be greatly sidelined. This is a Rank six Gu after all! Even the clan head Gu Yue Bo would immediately dispense with the civilities; the nonsense of kinship and the clan head position could all be given up. There was no doubt that it would be forcibly seized.

July was month of a scorching hot summer, and the hot air was filled with the iron smell of blood.

The wolf tide was growing more serious and fights were becoming more intense.

Many had begun to realize that the wolf tide this time was of a rarely seen enormous scale among all of past history.

Bold lightning wolf packs had fallen to a supporting role now; thousand beast king frenzy lightning wolf packs had started to roam nearby the village.

Mankind's living space had shrunk down to an extreme level.

Even Gu Yue clan headquarters were as such; there was no need to mention the village at the foot of the mountain.

Nine out of ten houses were empty and a portion of fortunate villagers were living in the clan by utilizing all kinds of connections. But the majority of the villagers could only leave their homes and make an arduous journey to evade the wolf tide.

Their destination was another mountain village. But the fierce beasts, wild Gu and the lightning wolves that filled the whole mountain reduced their hopes to an almost negligible amount.

This was a hopeless journey.

Gu Yue clan could only give up on these mortals, they would all die before they even reached halfway to their destination. Either because of the fierce beasts or due to attacks from insects.

No matter if it was mortals or Gu Masters, they were all struggling between life and death. Even the elders who usually had a high position, had no choice but to don their armors and go to the battlefield.

The Gu Masters that had retired were enlisted again. When the wolf tide ends, those that manage to live on would definitely not surpass even one tenth.

The cruelty of nature was displayed in all its glory at this moment. It was the survival of the fittest and in no way could it be avoided by speaking words of warmth.

Fang Yuan sat cross-legged on the bed; his eyes were closed as he looked at his aperture.

In his aperture, 44% of red steel sea waves were surging up and down. These primeval essence were all dark red. It was the Rank two peak stage dark red primeval essence.

Rank two primeval essence were collectively called red steel primeval essence. But it had four different small realms: initial stage, middle stage, upper stage and peak stage. There were also slight differences in the red steel primeval essence.

Rank two initial stage primeval essence was light red; middle stage primeval essence was scarlet; upper stage was crimson and peak stage was dark red.

Many days ago, Fang Yuan had advanced to upper stage. His crimson primeval essence went through Four Flavors Liquor worm's refinement and along with the replenishment from primeval stones, it had completely changed to the current dark red primeval essence.

Right now, the aperture wall was no longer a watery membrane with the flowing light, but it was instead a thick stone membrane formed by layers upon layers of piled up white light.

White Jade Gu and Stealth Scales gu were in the depths of the red steel sea.

Four Flavors Liquor worm was playing around in the sea but when the Spring Autumn Cicada slowly showed up, it immediately sunk towards the depths of the sea.

Under the aura of the Spring Autumn Cicada, the surface of the whole Primeval Sea became as calm and smooth as a mirror without the slightest wave.

Spring Autumn Cicada's condition was getting better.

Its two wings were completely recovered, appearing like a pair of tender leaves. Only its main body was still withered.

Fang Yuan would check on Spring Autumn Cicada every so often; he could clearly sense the recovery speed of Spring Autumn Cicada increasing rapidly.

The Spring Autumn Cicada was like a dying patient before, one who couldn't even open their mouths to eat and could only take in liquid food to preserve their life force.

Now, this patient could get off the bed and eat much more food to nourish itself; the recovery speed would naturally become faster.

Besides the Spring Autumn Cicada, there were two new members in Fang Yuan's aperture.

They were both taken from Bai Ning Bing; one was Water Shield Gu which looked like a jellyfish as it floated in the sea. Another was red steel Relic Gu.

Fang Yuan's advancement to upper stage was because of the purified primeval essence by the Four Flavors Liquor worm and continuous nourishment of the aperture wall, causing a qualitative change. Fang Yuan hadn't used the red steel Relic Gu.

Just based on cultivation level, Fang Yuan would already be the third highest person among Rank two Gu Masters of Gu Yue clan. Xiong Li and Qing Shu were dead; Fang Yuan was in the top five even among the whole Qing Mao Mountain.

As for Chi Shan and Mo Yan, they originally were at Rank two upper stage but had advanced to peak stage not long ago. This could be said to have aroused the morale of the clansmen who were down after Qing Shu's sacrifice.

Fang Yuan was progressing and others naturally were also progressing.

Chi Shan and Mo Yan had been in upper stage for quite a bit of time and had continuously been pressured by the peak stage Qing Shu.

The intense stimulation of death brought by the wolf tide caused Gu Masters to have a deep thirst for power, squeezing out their potential and leading to cultivation advancement.

"But if we count fighting strength, I am the number one among the Rank two Gu Masters of the whole Qing Mao mountain. Now, after I use this red steel Relic Gu, my cultivation will rise to peak stage and when combined with my deep experience, I can even battle Rank three Gu Masters to a certain degree," Fang Yuan calculated.

His low profile and patience had brought him plentiful gains now.

He could advance to this stage with just C grade aptitude, the whole clan would be shocked if they knew this. Even the A grade aptitude Fang Zheng was only at Rank two middle stage.

Naturally, even if he advanced to peak stage, Fang Yuan couldn't win against Rank three Gu Masters.Bai Ning Bing was able to surpass levels and kill a Rank three Gu Master because of his Northern Dark Ice Soul physique. Gu Yue Qing Shu also could do that because he had the Wood Charm Gu, a powerful and special Rank three Gu worm.

In actuality, Fang Yuan had a much stronger trump card than them—Spring Autumn Cicada.

However, this Rank six Gu was very special, and Fang Yuan forced himself to not use it. Spring Autumn Cicada hadn't fully recovered and if it was forcefully used, whether it could rebirth would be a huge question mark.

The red steel Relic Gu was only effective to Rank two Gu Masters; there was no value in keeping it.

Fang Yuan was just about to use this Gu when there came a knock on the door.

Dong, dong, dong.

"Lord Fang Yuan, it is me, Gu Yue Jiang Ya," a voice shouted after the knocking.

Fang Yuan frowned, this Jiang Ya was getting more overbearing recently; he would repeatedly look for him to ask for vitality leaves.

The number of deaths and crippled people were increasing, causing the price of the vitality leaves to become increasingly higher and even becoming a situation of high demand but no supply.

"How many times have I told you that I don't have more vitality leaves. Get lost." Fang Yuan coldly snorted. How could he give up his cultivation time for trifle primeval stones earnings.

Outside the door, Jiang Ya had a flattering smile on, "Lord Fang Yuan, please appease your anger. You are aware of the current situation, what choices do I have? Many Gu Masters know I sell vitality leaves and they all look for me. It is not easy for the little me to pass my days. How about this, I will pay ten percent more. Lord Fang Yuan, please be kind and give me a dozen vitality leaves."

After speaking, he started begging and his sound carried some sobbing.

Fang Yuan was indifferent, "That is your affair, what does it have to do with me? Hmph, your guts are getting bigger these days, you forgot the agreement between us and actually brought someone else."

"Ah....." Jiang Ya gave a bitter smile outside the door. He looked at the old Gu Master beside him. He had no other way, this Gu Master was very powerful and had stubbornly followed him here.

"Little friend Fang Yuan." This old Gu Master spoke, "I am Gu Yue Ye, I believe you have heard of me. I came to purchase some vitality leaves and hope you, little friend, can show me some respect and give a little time to produce some."

"Give you respect. Heh, what reputation do you have?" Fang Yuan sneered. This Gu Yue Ye was somewhat famous, he was a retired Gu Master but had been brought back by the clan due to the wolf tide.

At his peak period, he had reached Rank three. However, because of injuries, his cultivation dropped down to Rank two peak stage and now due to his old age, his cultivation had further dropped down to Rank two upper stage.

Although his cultivation was the same as Fang Yuan, his fighting strength could not be compared to the latter.

Gu Yue Ye's expression was ashen, he had long heard of this eccentric loner Fang Yuan; a lad with a vicious and stubborn temper, arrogant and rude, considering everyone beneath him. He had prepared his heart before he came here, but to think that he had still underestimated Fang Yuan.

He wanted to use his reputation, but this usually successful method had no effect on Fang Yuan.

He felt his face burning and his heart filled with anger. He had lost all his honor right now!

"This disrespectful son of a bitch!" He cursed inwardly, but didn't leave.

He needed the vitality leaves!

He was an experienced man and deeply knew the importance of the vitality leaves. In times, a vitality leaf could mean the difference between life and death.

As one gets old, their courage starts to shrink.

Back when he was young, he was hot-blooded and easily excited. He wanted to protect the clanspeople, he wanted to change the world, he wanted to become a great hero! In those times, he had the resolution to view death as a return home!

However, right now he was old and was much more cool-headed. He had seen through many aspects of life in these years and could be said to have reflected on himself.

Especially after several of his children died, his heart had grown more cold.

Any organization needs sacrifices.

Resources are limited. Although they are produced all the time, they are also consumed. As such, this add and decrease limits the total amount.

Humans need food, clothes and lodging to survive; these are resources. Gu Masters need Gu worms, primeval stones and food to cultivate; these are also resources.

Becoming strong requires even more resources. But if you don't sacrifice, then where can I get more resources?

I rather compromise others than sacrifice my benefits!

Protecting, honor, family love, dreams, hot blood; they are all honorable reasons for sacrificing.

There are no organizations that do not encourage self-sacrifice. However, the higher-ups would never say that, they would instead talk of 'protecting, honor, family love, dreams, hot blood, happiness' and so on, and give all kinds of material benefits.

However, the material benefits are just nonsense once one dies. What could a dead 'great hero' enjoy?

Look at Gu Yue Qing Shu.

He 'blissfully' died and was buried in the soil; his name carved in the gravestone as his spirit continues to influence future 'heroes'.

Chapter 146: Oppressive

Jiang Ya looked at the Gu Yue Ye whose face was grim, the former secretly feeling happy in his heart.

This old man had forcefully made Jiang Ya bring him to this place. Jiang Ya only had Rank one cultivation and was a junior, thus he had to lower his head to Gu Yue Ye and bring him here.

But now that he had been humiliated, Jiang Ya's heart was envious of Fang Yuan's unrestrained personality.

Gu Yue Ye wanted to give Fang Yuan a few tight slaps, to lecture this arrogant junior. But for the vitality leaves, he had to control himself, "Junior Fang Yuan, you can't say that. You are still young, you don't know the importance of human relationships, there will come a time when you need to beg others. Just think, in future when you come to ask me for a favour and I treat you like this, how would you feel?"

"Bullcrap human relationships!" Fang Yuan laughed in disdain in his heart.

The so-called unity was just because they were individually weak.

Human relationships, it was important on earth. After all, there was no difference in personal strength among people. But in this world where people cultivated, things were inherently different.

Human relationships were just a byproduct of strength—if one is strong, their human relationships would thrive.

But for those who pursue relationships, they definitely have something to ask others of.

As for not needing relationships—if one is overly powerful, they can snatch anything they want, give it away or die, why would they need people's relationships?

These were demonic path thoughts, and Fang Yuan would naturally not advertise them publicly.

But since he was disturbed like this, Fang Yuan might as well do this business.

Thus, he said, "It's not that I can't sell it either. One vitality leaf for sixty-eight primeval stones. How many do you want?"

"Huh!" Gu Yue Ye outside the door was shocked by this price, quickly saying, "Junior Fang Yuan, this price is too expensive!"

Fang Yuan snorted, "Then don't buy it. Among the resources provided by the clan, there are also vitality leaves, you can exchange it with merit points."

Gu Yue Ye laughed bitterly, "How would I not know that, but these vitality leaves are all sold to those with relationships, the medicine hall clan elder Gu Yue Yao Ji has complete control over it, how can I interfere? Junior Fang Yuan, sell me a favour, I will definitely repay you. From what I see, sixty primeval stones is a just price."

"I do not anticipate people's repayment, you have wasted enough of my time. Seventy primeval stones, if you don't want to buy it, leave." Fang Yuan responded.

Gu Yue Ye was furiously stomping, "Junior Fang Yuan, how can you do business like this?"

Fang Yuan snickered, "Times are different, it is seventy-two primeval stones now, every sentence you say wastes some of my time, and when I feel unhappy I will raise the price, I hope you can make the right decisions."

Hearing this, Gu Yue Ye's face became furious; he wanted to say something, but every time he opened his mouth, no words came out.

His hagged face was green and red, and Jiang Ya who was beside him saw this and cheered internally.

Finally, he gritted his teeth, saying, "Okay, I'll buy it, I need five vitality leaves."

"You can hand the primeval stones to Jiang Ya. As for the vitality leaves, collect them from him three days later." Fang Yuan said.

This was overbearing, trading goods and money was the most basic fairness.

But Gu Yue Ye still paid the money, handing multiple bags to Jiang Ya on the spot.

His movements were slightly trembling, for this was his meagre savings, the savings from him scrimping throughout the years, and now they were all taken by a shrewd merchant!

Finally, he walked out of this bamboo building with an endless feeling of indignance.

"Lord Fang Yuan, what you did was really cool revenge! But I'm afraid you have completely offended Gu Yue Ye. This old man, when he was young he always took revenge on people, he would not let go of this easily." Outside, Jiang Ya said carefully.

"Let him be, an old man relying on his seniority, he is bound to get eliminated by the clan." Fang Yuan opened the door, and Jiang Ya handed him the bags.

The clan wants to resist the wolf tide, so that requires large amounts of resources. With less resources, they cannot maintain the large organisation structure, thus they would need to get rid of members.

These old men being alive were wasting precious scarce resources, they were destined to go.

The wolf packs eliminated the old and sickly, expelling the crippled wolves. In human society, they would not be so obvious, always masking their evil with a shield of light, thus they called these old Gu Masters to fight.

So what if Gu Yue Ye understood the intention?

Being in the system, a person in society, they had no choice.

The clan uses the reason of protecting their family and clan to call them to fight and sacrifice, how can they refuse?

On Earth there is a sentence, if the Emperor wants the subjects to die, they cannot do otherwise. But still countless people fight for the positions of being the emperor's subjects. This was the allure and cruelty of the system.

"Every round of the wolf tide in the past, those old Gu Masters who come out to fight, how many can survive? Let's not say five vitality leaves, even if we give this Gu Yue Ye fifty pieces, he might not make it out alive." Fang Yuan stood at the door, laughing coldly.

When Jiang Ya heard this tone, his heart was freezing.

He could feel an aura from Fang Yuan, full of coldness and frost, like the northern winds blowing until he cannot raise his head.

Fang Yuan looked at Jiang Ya, his eyes dark and black, continuing, "From now on, other than the arranged timings, you cannot look for me! If you break my rules, be prepared to face the consequences. Letting you sell the vitality leaves for me, is on account of your brother. But respect is given by others, and thrown away by ownself. Think over your own actions."

Jiang Ya heard Fang Yuan's lecture, not daring to speak. Thinking of Gu Yue Ye's sad state, sweat poured from his forehead.

"Also, from now on, raise the price of the vitality leaves to seventy primeval stones." Fang Yuan said again.

"Seventy?!" Jiang Ya was shocked as he gulped, his eyes shining, as if he can see an endless supply of primeval stones.

But he was also rather afraid, asking meekly, "Lord Fang Yuan, raising prices like this, will it cause others to think that we are growing a fortune through the misfortune? Would we have the suspicion of taking advantage of the clan's state? If we do this, we might incur public outrage."

"Public outrage? Hmph, what can they do, do what I order, don't talk crap. If someone finds trouble, tell them the vitality leaves are sold by me." Fang Yuan snorted.

"Yes, yes, yes." Jiang Ya nodded furiously, Fang Yuan's words were what he wanted to hear, he was going to do this as well.

He was just a Rank one small fry, he cannot offend too many people. Throwing all these problems to Fang Yuan, he had already started doing so.

A small fry also has his own survival methods, and towards Jiang Ya's intention, Fang Yuan was clear at heart.

But cultivation difference and era difference, results in Fang Yuan living a different lifestyle.

After using that red steel Relic Gu, he would be Rank two peak stage, near to Rank three. That means he has finally grown past the initial step, and having this strength means his life and future would be different.

In the past he needed to lay low, but now he needed to be oppressive.

Only when he is oppressive can he obtain the biggest benefit.

As for this Jiang Ya, he still has some value to make use of. Even with his petty acts, as long as it does not infringe on Fang Yuan's benefits, he can tolerate it.

Even revealing some unimportant trump cards is not a big deal.

During peacetime, those higher-ups have nothing to do, thus they might find problems. But now that there is the wolf tide, who has the energy to care about such minute details?

After the wolf tide, it is not guaranteed that the Gu Yue village still exists.

Half a month later.

Lightning wolves attack like tidal waves, causing the Gu Masters to retreat in a hurry.

"Xiong Yuan Zhen, you must hang in there! Gu Yue village is not too far away." Xiong Jiao Man stared at the clansmen on the ground, her eyes turning red as she shouted.

"Leader big sis, I can't take it anymore. I have something in my heart I want to tell you..." Xiong Yuan Zhen was at his dying breath, his injuries were severe and his face was full of death.

"Okay, speak!" Xiong Jiao Man sobbed. She knew in her heart that although this Xiong Yuan Zhen was normally quiet, but he was secretly in love with her. At this moment, she knew what he wanted to say.

But when Xiong Yuan Zhen opened his mouth, he did not manage to confess and say "I love you."

He had died, died of blood loss, injuries too severe to cure.

His body was full of injuries, all from the bites of the lightning wolves. The most fatal blow was at his chest, from his right shoulder all the way to his belly button—this was caused by a bold lightning wolf.

"Big sis, the situation is bad, another bold lightning wolf group came!" The recon Gu Master shouted, his voice filled with panic.

Xiong Jiao Man's cries ended, placing Xiong Yuan Zhen's body down. She was the group leader, her group members need her!

The dead has passed, and those alive has to continue facing the cruelty of this world.

"These goddamn wolves, is there an end to them!" Xiong Jian Man cursed fiecely. Her body figure was hot and she had a nice pretty face, so when she said these swear words there was a unique flavor about her.

Hearing her words, the others calmed down internally.

As Xiong Jian Man cursed, she observed.

The investigation result made her slightly distressed. She could kill a group of bold lightning wolves, fight her way out of two groups, but against four bold lightning wolf groups, the wisest decision is to retreat to the valley behind her and use the Signal Gu, hoping for reinforcements.

"Retreat to the valley," Xiong Jiao Man shouted as she activated both her giant bears to protect them.

These two giant bears were well-raised by her. One brown and one black, with smooth and shiny fur, but they were both full of injuries all over their bodies.

When Xiong Jiao Man and the others successfully retreated to the valley, these two bears were left with one; the black one had been engulfed by the lightning wolves' pack after killing tens of lightning wolves, having run out of energy.

A Gu worm shot out from the bear corpse, returning back to Xiong Jiao Man's hand in an instant.

This was the Bear Enslavement Gu.

It can be planted into bears to allow the Gu Master to manipulate giant bears.

Of course, it can only be an ordinary bear, for the Bear Enslavement Gu is a Rank two—it cannot enslave a bear king.

If it can enslave a bear king, they would be strong. Because a bear king, even if it is the weakest, has at least a hundred bear subordinates.

If a Gu Master can enslave a bear king, it means they have a beast group to manipulate as well.

"Now we wait for reinforcements, hopefully they can get here soon!" Xiong Jiao Man panted as she sighed.

They had retreated to the valley, thus the area they had to defend against greatly decreased, causing the pressure from the wolf packs to also decrease. But it also meant they had no way out, and the blood and continual battle would attract more wolf packs.

The crisis was not resolved.

"Eh." At this point, from the cliff above their heads, a voice was heard.

Everyone raised their heads to look, and saw that there was a young man.

"It's him..."

"Gu Yue Fang Yuan!"

The seven Xiong clan Gu Masters were first invigorated, but then showed a complicated expression.

Chapter 147: This Fang Yuan is too arrogant

Ever since Bai Ning Bing and Qing Shu's intense battle, Fang Yuan who had chased after Bai Ning Bing the entire way had become well-known, and his popularity rose.

These days, Fang Yuan had shown his strong side in the wolf tide, heading alone to hunt lightning wolves and showing shocking results.

He was the new generation's rising star. If not for his strange personality and bad reputation, his status would be on par with Chi Shan and Mo Yan.

But to the Xiong village members, Fang Yuan was also Xiong Jiang's murderer.

Thus, when Xiong Jiao Man and the others saw Fang Yuan, they showed a complicated expression.

Fang Yuan stared at them from above, waving his tree vine, saying slowly, "You can continue to wait for reinforcements, or escape using the vine in my hand and climb up the mountain."

Who knew when the reinforcements would come?

Matters on the battlefield were ever changing.

Xiong Jiao Man and the others obviously chose the tree vine in front of them, but Fang Yuan actually asked them for remuneration.

This caused the Xiong clan Gu Masters to be furious.

"Fang Yuan, we are alliance mates. How can you do this!" Someone shouted furiously.

"Asking for the Bear Enslavement Gu, how shameless can you be!" Someone sneered.

Fang Yuan calmly retorted, "One Bear Enslavement Gu and seven hundred primeval stones, in exchange for all seven of your lives, this is a cheap price. You can reject me, and I will go back to the clan to report your circumstances. Hehe, but when will the reinforcements come, will they encounter a wolf pack on the way here, that I cannot guarantee."

Everyone became quiet.

Their expressions were ugly.

"Alright, I promise you. Fang Yuan, you really live up to your reputation." Finally, Xiong Jiao Man chose to give way for the sake of everyone. Her words were full of spite towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan shrugged nonchalantly, the result was as expected.

He threw down the tree vine, and laughed coldly in his heart.

These four bold lightning wolf packs were lured here by him, he wanted to wait for them to die before retrieving their Gu worms and get a huge amount of merit points. But their Signal Gu had attracted the attention of the surrounding groups of Gu Masters, and they were all rushing over to help.

To not waste his effort, Fang Yuan could only act as a reinforcement Gu Master for once.

Xiong Jiao Man and the others used the tree vines and successfully escaped from the wolf pack. Not long after, three Gu Master groups arrived, and one of them was the Chi Shan group.

This caused the seven Gu Masters to become even more upset.

Xiong Jiao Man was extremely regretful. Not long ago, she had withdrawn her consciousness from the Bear Enslavement Gu and cooperated with Fang Yuan in refining the Gu worm, thus even if she wanted to go back on her words now, it was impossible.

"Fang Yuan, I will remember you." Xiong Jiao Man stared at Fang Yuan fiercely in the eye.

"Remember or not, that's your business." Fang Yuan laughed plainly, turning around and leaving.

"Miss Xiong, we meet again." At the other end, Chi Shan group arrived, speaking with a courteous tone.

Ever since the Bai Ning Bing incident, Gu Yue clan lost a Qing Shu, and Xiong clan's Xiong Li died, thus the two clans got closer. Politically, Bai clan became resisted by the other two clans together, even though the alliance was still in place.

"Little sister pays respects to elder brother Chi Shan." Xiong Jiao Man lifted her frowning brows, cupping her fists towards Chi Shan, continuing, "This time, we are asking the Gu Yue clan for some reinforcements, Xiong clan has been surrounded by wolf packs for six days and six nights already."

These days, the wolf tide was getting more severe. The lightning wolf packs have already started to surround the villages with the intention of attacking.

Xiong clan had the lowest position among the three clans—situated at the mountain foot, they would be the first to get attacked by the wolf packs. In fact, this is the third time they had gotten surrounded, and they needed reinforcements. With the coordination of offence from the outside and inside together, they would then be able to scatter and defeat these lightning wolf packs.

"The matter about reinforcements is not issue, didn't we cooperate well the last two times? But this matter, I have to report to the clan leader first. Come with me," Chi Shan said.

Xiong Jiao Man and the others followed Chi Shan group, coming to Gu Yue village.

Gu Yue village already had layers of defences. The outer walls were strongly reinforced with dozens of towers. Below the village walls were trenches dug and filled with sharp bamboo poles.

The village walls had been planted with the Steel Vine Gu and Poison Flower Gu; at one glance, the walls were covered in sharp vines and the beautiful poisonous flowers were all budding, over hundreds or even thousands of them.

Entering the main door, one could see that the surrounding buildings, whether it was a residence or tavern, had been all transformed into temporary forts.

Xiong Jiao Man and the other six, after leaving the Xiong clan, their journey was filled with difficulty. Traversing through wolf packs, they all had different injuries. Thus, they were led into a bamboo building to receive treatment.

There was over ten healing Gu Masters in the bamboo building, mostly Rank one Gu Masters, but also a few Rank two Gu Masters. But what caused Xiong Jiao Man and the others to be shocked was, the person in charge was not a Rank two healing Gu Master, but a young girl.

"Put this unconscious one on the vine chair."

"The one here has a fracture on his leg, Gu Yue Xing, come here and give him treatment."

"Superficial injury, Ah Feng, come here and stop the bleeding, Ah Xing come here and apply the disinfectant, Xiao Hua go place a fracture board on that leg fracture, then come here to bandage the injury.

The young girl had black hair, a peach-like small mouth, both eyes shining like crystals and her face was slightly chubby, with a alluring voice. But when she handled the patients, she was very experienced, causing others to look in amazement.

Xiong Jiao Man suddenly thought of one person, asking, "This little sister, are you Gu Yue Yao Le?"

"Xiong clan's sister Jiao Man, hello. To think you know of my name." After assigning the Gu Masters to their stations, Gu Yue Yao Le walked over and introduced herself.

"Sister Yao Le, you are a famous character. Inheriting Lord Yao Ji's benevolent heart, and also extremely talented in medical skills, even with your Rank one cultivation, you are known as the top ten rising stars in Qing Mao mountain. Even at the Xiong clan, there are numerous people admiring you, sister." Seeing her strong background, Xiong Jiao Man politely praised as she was on a trip to ask the Gu Yue clan for help.

"I'm flattered, sister Jiao Man." Gu Yue Yao Le is still young, and her face turned red as she looked down in embarrassment after being praised.

At this time, a Xiong clan Gu Master complained, "Although you're both the top ten rising stars, that Gu Yue Fang Yuan seriously cannot compare to you, little sister."

"Don't mention Fang Yuan, my blood boils thinking of him!"

"Times without heroes, lad gains fame! Sigh..."

"This person's morals are lacking, to think he is also a top ten rising star, and even the number one position. Thinking about it makes me want to vomit."

This sentence immediately attracted the attention of the people nearby, including the Gu Yue clan's Gu Masters.

"Gu Yue Fang Yuan? What did he do this time?" Someone curiously asked.

"Hmph, he took one of my Bear Enslavement Gu, and even seven hundred primeval stones, as a reward for saving us. I've never seen anyone so shameless, and corrupted by greed!" Xiong Jiao Man snorted, venting her unhappiness.

"This is nothing, there are worse things."

"His heart is blacker than coal, selling a vitality leaf for eighty primeval stones, he is taking advantage of the situation, this person is greedy and extremely shameless!"

"He is too arrogant and proud. My friend wanted to join his group, however not only was he rejected, but he even got insulted in public. What's his deal, he's merely a C grade talent."

"He is a living prodigal son, wasting the inheritance both his parents left him to buy a red steel Relic Gu from the caravan. Next he snatched another red steel Relic Gu from Bai Ning Bing. If I had these two Gu worms, I can also have his cultivation!"

"Lord Gu Yue Qing Shu is the best after all, humble and kind, too bad he died early."

"But his brother Fang Zheng has a sense of justice, helping those in need and is kind hearted, also having Lord Qing Shu's humble attitude, he is completely the opposite of his brother."

Xiong Jiao Man did not expect her ranting to cause so much reaction from the Gu Yue clansmen.

She was shocked. To think this Fang Yuan was such a failure as a human, being hated by so many people.

She felt strange, asking, "Since he is so hated, why did no one teach him a lesson?"

The bamboo building instantly became silent.

The Gu Yue clansmen all looked at each other, not saying a word.

In truth, many people could not stand Fang Yuan's mannerisms, as well as his act of maximising profit under such circumstances. Many people found problems with him, but the result everytime was that the person finding fault got into an even bigger mess themselves.

After many times, no one came to find fault with him anymore.

And Fang Yuan also became publicly known as the head of the top ten rising stars that emerged from the wolf tide.

All these statuses, originate from strength.

Fang Yuan's battle strength was the strongest, so he was the head. Regardless of how bad his reputation is, or how poor his human relationship is.

"That Fang Yuan again..." Gu Yue Yao Ji lightly frowned, muttering.

She had never seen Fang Yuan, but had already heard much about him. Towards Fang Yuan, she had a poor impression of him.

"This Fang Yuan, although my senior, the things he does are unforgivable, and he is so extreme. He dared to extort sister Jiao Man this time and got the Bear Enslavement Gu, not giving a hoot about our two clan's agreements. No, I must tell grandma and let her teach this Fang Yuan a lesson, otherwise our Gu Yue clan will be humiliated."

Thinking of this, the young girl suddenly felt that there was a need for a clan higher-up to come out and teach this Fang Yuan a lesson.

She naturally did not have this ability, but she felt that her grandma, medicine hall's Gu Yue Yao Ji could.

In her eyes, her grandma was omnipotent.

"You want me to deal with Gu Yue Fang Yuan?" Yao Ji looked at her granddaughter, her expression blank, and soon after that she started getting nervous.

"My dear granddaughter, did he bully you?" She hurriedly asked.

"He did not bully me, but he bullied others. This time it is the Xiong clan sister Jiao Man, he extorted her, getting a Bear Enslavement Gu and seven hundred primeval stones. This is too much, if this goes on, the clan's reputation would be completely ruined by him," Gu Yue Yao Le said.

"Mmm, grandma knows this matter. Darling granddaughter, leave first, grandma will not disappoint you." Yao Ji said after deep considerations.

"Thank you grandma! Grandma you do not know but this person is too wicked, raising the price of his goods and bullying the weak, he is a true villain."

After the young girl left, Yao Ji fell into deep thoughts.

She had wanted to deal with Fang Yuan for a long time, however it was naturally not a naive reason like Yao Le's, but because Fang Yuan possessed enough profits for her to strike.

First was the Liquor worm.

Although previously, Yao Ji had bought one from the caravan. But that was given to her granddaughter Yao Le. She herself still needed one Liquor worm as an ingredient to refine a Rank three Gu worm she wanted to fuse.

Next was the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass.

The clan's Nine Leaf Vitality Grass were mostly in Yao Ji's control, and by relying on selling the vitality leaves, she could consolidate her authority and status in the clan.

"This Fang Yuan is too arrogant! First I wanted to buy his Liquor worm, but he refused, what guts. This time he raised the price of the vitality leaves and earned a fortune. Does he really think I, the medicine clan elder, is thin air? Hmph!"

Chapter 148: Circumstance

Two giant banners fluttered in the wind with a ringing noise.

One was the battle merit board; Fang Yuan was now among the top ten in the list. Another banner listed all kinds of goods which could be exchanged with battle merits.

However, most of the Gu Masters in the crowded plaza had their attention on a newly announced decree.

The content of the announcement was: The wolf tide is becoming more fierce and the casualties among the clan's Gu Masters are increasing day by day. To reinforce the treatment methods, the medical hall orders all the Gu Masters who possess Nine Leaf Vitality Grass to temporarily hand them over to the clan. The medical hall will organize staff to unify all the productions.

There were a list of names in the notification. They were the names of the Gu Masters that possessed Nine Leaf Vitality Grass in the clan.

Naturally, Fang Yuan was also listed.

Right now, he was standing in a distant corner looking at this notification; his expression couldn't help but turn ugly.

At first sight, he had realized this to be Gu Yue Yao Ji's move against him.

"Hmph, this Gu Yue Yao Ji has been indignant since she failed to purchase the Liquor worm from me. I already accumulated enough battle merits to exchange for that Three Steps Fragrant Grass gu, but she prevented this from happening in the dark. Now, she is actually coveting my Nine Leaf Vitality Grass….."

Gu Yue Yao Ji's actions were understandable.

People of the same trade were natural enemies.

By controlling the sale of the vitality leaves, Gu Yue Yao Ji could consolidate her authority, deepen her influence and maintain her connections. However, Fang Yuan sold them in increased price, so this imperceptibly was infringing on her benefits and shaking her influence.

"I have a lot of Gu worms on me now; White Jade Gu, Moonglow Gu, Plunder Gu, Water Shield Gu, Earth Communication Ear Grass and more. Nine Leaf Vitality Grass is my most important economy source; if I lose this Gu, it will be like receiving a checkmate. Gu Yue Yao Ji made a really fierce move," Fang Yuan frowned.

The discussions of the surrounding Gu Masters entered his ears.

"Medicine hall made a truly great decision! There are very few vitality leaves and they simply can't meet our needs. Every time a batch appears in the goods board, they will immediately be purchased by others."

"Elder Yao Ji is truly gentle and kind. Look at the name list, it includes several Gu Masters from both Chi and Mo factions. She has no doubt offended many powerful elders with this action."

"Elder Yao Ji is thinking for the clan, she is worthy of respect!"

"Ai, only Lord Yao Ji has such courage. If it was any other elders, who would dare to take such action?"

"Eh! Look, the notification contents have changed. Chi and Mo faction's Gu Masters have handed over their Nine Leaf Vitality Grass."

The crowd was boiling.

Nine Leaf Vitality Grass being consolidated and unified production meant the availability of much more vitality leaves. This was a great news to the crowd.

Fang Yuan watched the notice with rapt attention and sure enough saw: Beside the name list of these Gu Masters, there were new words 'handed over'. His own name had thus become conspicuous.

His heart felt increasing pressure.

Gu Yue Yao Ji was an old veteran with deep schemes; with this move, she was borrowing the momentum to pressure Fang Yuan. If Fang Yuan resisted or disobeyed, that would be attracting even bigger troubles, giving people a hold over him; it was absolutely not a sensible act.

This was the power of the system.

If the clan wanted you to sacrifice, it won't directly say so. Instead it will drape a shiny cape of righteousness, and give you no choice but to submit.

An example was the recruitment of those retired old Gu Masters and making them sacrifice their lives, how could they resist?

The current movement of collecting the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass was asking Fang Yuan and other Gu Masters to sacrifice their benefits to satisfy everyone, and was basically to Yao Ji's benefits. Anyone that dared to disobey was going against the clan and alienating themselves! They were traitors and rebels!

"To resolve this, small schemes like delaying tactics won't work and will instead put oneself into an even more passive state. Yao Ji's move carries righteousness and the public opinion; any small schemes will be destroyed. Only by using an even bigger momentum, fairly fighting back and defeating her momentum openly will resolve this."

Fang Yuan already had a solution.

This plan was simple but grand; advance to Rank three!

Rank three and Rank two Gu Masters had completely different status. In the clan, any Gu Master that advanced to Rank three would immediately become an elder and join the decision makers circle. Even the clan head couldn't lightly infringe upon their benefits.

Don't think that the Gu Masters of the Mo and Chi factions obediently handed over the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, seemingly sacrificing their own benefits. Behind the scenes, Gu Yue Yao Ji should have already completed secret transactions with Gu Yue Chi Lian, Gu Yue Mo Chen and other elders.

This was political transaction.

However, the majority couldn't see this truth and were hoodwinked by Yao Ji.

If Fang Yuan was a Rank three Gu Master, even if he had to hand over the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, he would definitely obtain enough compensation in other aspects.

Why was Gu Yue Yao Ji so anxious to deal with Fang Yuan?

On the one hand, it was because of benefits; Fang Yuan's actions infringed on her benefits and similarly she wanted some Gu worms that was on Fang Yuan's body.

On the other hand, Fang Yuan was already at Rank two peak stage; if she didn't make any move now and waited for him to become a Rank three elder, there would be no more opportunities.

"Advancing to Rank three is a must. The clan can sacrifice Rank two Gu Masters, but Rank three Gu Masters are its pillars and each loss would incur a huge damage. Moreover, I have accumulated too many troubles. Qing Shu died but the clan didn't do a careful investigation. I have the Water Shield Gu, Plunder Gu and other Gu worms, but the clan has turned a blind eye to it. My cultivation is advancing so fast, the higher-ups clearly know about it, but are enduring it and haven't examined the secrets on me."

Fang Yuan was very clear on his current situation.

On the surface, he looked to be strong and well off, but he was actually surrounded by danger.

The clan didn't move against him because their attention was completely on the wolf tide. If they can't resist the wolf tide, the clan would be destroyed. In front of such pressure, Fang Yuan's situation was only a minor detail to them.

However, once the wolf tide is gone, the clan's higher-ups would regain their energy; how could they not look for him to settle the account?

Before in the academy, the clan elders didn't move against Fang Yuan because he was too weak. He was taking small steps and didn't infringe upon their benefits, thus not attracting their attention.

But, it was different now.

Fang Yuan's cultivation was already at Rank two peak stage, if he took one step further, he would become an elder.

Simply this cultivation had already touched the elders' nerves. His every movement was observed and noted by the elders.

Any newly advanced elders could influence the whole political situation of the Gu Yue clan. This resulted in continuous suppression of Fang Yuan. What's more, Fang Yuan hadn't joined the system and entered any factions, thus these made the suppressions become even more intense.

Neutral faction was also a faction.

No one could tolerate the current Fang Yuan, someone who was roaming beyond the clan system.

"If I advance to Rank three, the suppression will definitely be much lower than now, though they will still be there. Rank three is a point of qualitative change, a threshold. Stepping through it will bring one to a whole new world. Similarly, with Rank three cultivation, I can freely move about. At worst, I will simply leave the clan." Fang Yuan was clear on this.

However, advancing to Rank three was not an easy thing. Especially considering Fang Yuan's C grade aptitude, it was almost an impossible barrier.

In his previous life, he had stalled at Rank two peak stage for over a hundred years. Until afterwards, he paid a painful price to obtain a Gu and promoted his aptitude. Only then could he step through this difficulty.

In a Gu Master's cultivation, it was easy to advance through small realms, they only needed enough time and patience. However, every large realm had a barrier, and the higher you go, the harder it is to cross. Especially the difficulty in advancing from Rank five to Rank six was beyond imagination, harder than ascending heaven!

Fang Yuan already had a lot of difficulties in advancing from Rank one to Rank two. Now, to advance from Rank two to Rank three, there was no possibility of success by following the traditional route.

Fortunately, in Fang Yuan's five hundred years of life experience and vast memories, there were two to three methods. Saying it nicely, they were alternative paths but saying it coarsely, they were demonic practices.

This option was very suitable for Fang Yuan's current situation.

With this option, advancing to Rank three required one to refine a peculiar and bloody Gu—Man-beast Life Burial Gu. An ancient devil path sect leader had made painstaking efforts and invented this recipe to strengthen his subordinates' cultivation.

The Man-beast Life Burial Gu was specialized for Rank two Gu Masters to breakthrough to Rank three realm.

In his previous life, Fang Yuan explored unknown places and coincidentally found this recipe. It had made a deep impression on him and he had firmly kept it in mind.

The crucial point was that the materials required for the fusion were not rare.

If it were normal times, Fang Yuan might need two-three years to collect them, given his circumstances. However the wolf tide gave him a great opportunity.

He had already collected sufficient primeval stones and Gu worms. The only remaining thing was to wait for an opportune moment.

"Everyone, quickly look at the notice the medicine hall has just issued."

"They want to collect Nine Leaf Vitality Grass and unify the production of vitality leaves?"

"This is great news."

In the bamboo building, a group of Gu Masters gathered near the notice pasted on the wall. They were all filled with delight when they read it.

"Hahaha, I reckon Fang Yuan is close to tears."

"Hmph, serves him right for selling the vitality leaves at such a high price, exploiting our hard earned money!"

"I really want to see what expression Fang Yuan has now… it would definitely be very ugly."

Many people were taking joy in the misfortune of others.

"Hehehe, this really lets us vent our resentment. We really need to thank Miss Yao Le for this, if she didn't persuade Lord Yao Ji, how could there be such a day?"

"Right, we are really grateful to Miss Yao Le."

"Miss Yao Le is not only beautiful, she is also kind-hearted, upholding justice and fairness for us. She has the demeanor of Lord Yao Ji."

As she heard the continuous praises, Gu Yue Yao Le shyly lowered her head, she felt happy.

"Little sister Yao Le." Right at this time, Xiong Jiao Man walked in through the door, "I came to say my goodbyes. I saw the medicine hall's notice, I am really thankful to you for letting me vent out my indignance. People like Fang Yuan are black sheeps and need to be controlled."

"Big sister, you are leaving?" Gu Yue Yao Le threw a concerned look.

Xiong Jiao Man put one hand on her hip and pointed the thumb of her other hand to a group of Gu Masters standing outside the door, saying, "I have already asked for reinforcements, I must hurry back. Let's meet again next time."

Yao Le's heart was filled with grief.

Xiong Jiao Man had ten Gu Masters when she had left her clan, but there were only seven left when she reached here. Now, these Gu Masters were going to step into the cruel battlefield again, how many of them could safely return?

Chapter 149: Wolf pack attacks the village

Yao Le sent Xiong Jiao Man and the others to the door with her gaze as they got further apart.

But this separation was extremely short lived; merely fifteen minutes later, Xiong Jiao Man and the others returned to the bamboo building.

"We are unlucky, there's a wolf tide," Xiong Jiao Man laughed bitterly, explaining.

When the Gu Masters in the bamboo building heard this, their expressions tensed.

Xiong Jiao Man's group had great numbers, yet they were forced to retreat to the village—it showed the intensity of this wolf tide.

"Everyone get ready, the lightning wolf pack is about to assault the village," Xiong Jiao Man said.

Once she finished her words, sirens resounded in the entire village.

The village went quiet for a moment, then in the next instant noise erupted.

"This alarm... there is a large-sized wolf pack attacking the village!"

"Quick, quick, gather all our group members here, there's a huge battle incoming."

"Damn it, I just got back, I wanted to get a good sleep..."

Gu Masters cursed as some showed a cold expression. At once, in the bamboo building and on the streets, Gu Masters could be seen moving quickly, gathering towards the four doors of the village as well as the outer walls.

On the interior side of the village outer walls, there was a large wooden ladder at every interval for Gu Masters to climb up.

And the many defensive towers were made higher than the outer walls, like brave courageous defenders of the village.

Fang Yuan was among the crowd, arriving at the base of the outer wall. A Gu Master was treading on the wooden ladder, and as he was about to head up, Fang Yuan pulled him down and ascended himself.

"Which bastard..." That Gu Master was about to scold out, but saw that it was Fang Yuan and immediately shut up.

Fang Yuan climbed up the wooden ladder, then he expedited the White Jade Gu and peeked at the front lines.

Just outside the village, there were roaming lightning wolves everywhere, thousands of them!

Taking a glance, there was an endless number of glimmering green wolf eyes, causing one to break out in cold sweat.

These wolves were all starving, and some were so hungry even their bodies were shrinking.

The lightning wolves' amount was too much, it became a moving disaster. The surrounding wild beasts were either chased away or eaten, and for the wolf packs, they were getting less and less food.

To them, a village full of people was a fatal attraction.

Wolves were full of wildness, and a hungry wolf is even scarier, more dangerous, and crazier.

A lightning wolf that is full would not attack the village.

Other than these normal lightning wolves, there was also the bold lightning wolf.

Although mixed in with the wolf packs, the bold lightning wolf was still easily recognised.

Their bodies were as large as a calf.

There was at least thirty!

Many people upon seeing this, drew in a deep breath.

This was the second time Gu Yue village had been attacked by wolves this year, but this size was almost twice or even more than that of the last time.

These bold lightning wolves were all at the peak of their health, strong like bulls. Ordinary lightning wolves might not get food, but these hundred beast kings definitely had ample nutrition.

Resources were naturally given to the higher-ups first.

The benefits of the lower rank members would be stripped, sacrificed and given to the higher ranks.

Be it human society or wild beast groups, it worked the same way.

"These bold lightning wolves are not the real threat." Fang Yuan's gaze moved, continuously finding and quickly saw three large wolf shadows at the back of the wolf pack, hiding under the shadow of the trees.

Thousand beast king, frenzy lightning wolf!

Each frenzy lightning wolf was as large as an elephant.

When Fang Yuan saw this, his pupils shrunk slightly, but went back to normal immediately. He continued observing, only finding even more bold lightning wolves coming in from all directions.

Fang Yuan did not see the lightning crown wolf.

Fang Yuan breathed out a sigh of relief secretly, for without the lightning crown wolf, the village was relatively safe.

In his memory, the lightning crown wolf appeared at the end of August. It caused great damage to the Gu Yue clan, and if not for the clan leader and elders joining forces to block them relentlessly, along with Gu Yue Qing Shu sacrificing his life to raise his strength, Gu Yue village would've gotten wiped out already.

Ever since his rebirth, Fang Yuan changed many things. Gu Yue Qing Shu had already been sacrificed prematurely, so Fang Yuan dared not be careless. There was even a possibility of the lightning crown wolf appearing now. Thus, he rushed to the site to observe the scenario.

Howl!

Three frenzy lightning wolves raised their heads as they howled long and loud.

In their cries, numerous lightning wolves received their orders, and started to attack the village.

On the village's end, the Gu Masters had already prepared themselves, getting into formation.

Rank one Gu Masters were all at the wall's corners, both hands supporting the cold walls.

Rank two Gu Masters, some climbed the wooden ladders while others gathered at the top of the towers.

Right behind them, the temporary forts that were remodelled from buildings were filled with Gu Masters, some were support teams, some were healing Gu Masters from the medicine hall, and recon Gu Masters were moving between them providing the battle information to the back end staff.

Some clan elders were at the back end, some ascended the tower buildings, and others watched at the sidelines, reserving their strength and being a pillar of mental support to the clansmen.

"They're here." Fang Yuan stood on the wooden ladder, his eyes glimmering.

LIghtning wolves moved from the entire mountain, forming into a tidal wave and assaulted the village.

Rumble rumble...

They first fell into the pre-dug pitfalls outside the walls, their bodies penetrated by numerous bamboo spears, like dumplings inside a pot.

Some died on the spot, while others had some life remaining, crying out pitifully.

The wind blew, and the smell of blood entered everyone's noses, while wolf cries entered their ears.

The wolf packs attacked in a frenzy. Not only did they not stop, they were in fact stimulated by the blood and attacked even more furiously.

Lightning wolves fell into the trap one by one, using their lives to pave the way for the others. Stepping on their companions' corpses, and crashing up onto the village walls.

At once, thudding sounds were heard.

A lightning wolf was powerlessly against the wall, but with the endless hordes, the impact caused the outer wall to shake.

Rank one Gu Masters below the outside wall held in their tremendous fear, and risked their lives injecting primeval essence into the Steel Vine Gu and Poison Flower Gu.

The village walls' numerous thorns stabbed into the lightning wolves' body. The Poison Flower Gu gave these steel vines a poisonous touch as the poison invaded the lightning wolves' body.

Lightning wolves scratched and attacked the village walls, opening their mouths and biting, but as their injuries intensified and the poison accumulated, their movements gradually turned sluggish.

Pewpewpew.

Rank two Gu Masters stepping on the wooden ladders, along with those at the tower buildings, shot out moonblades.

The moonblade shot into the wolf packs, and instantly blood splashed everywhere, and wolf limbs went flying.

The bold lightning wolves began to enter the battle, immediately bringing injuries and deaths to the Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan's corner.

A thin long blue lightning current moved about and hit onto the village walls, instantly penetrating and creating a hole. It electrocuted an unfortunate Rank one Gu Master inside as well.

That bold lightning wolf that killed a Gu Master quickly received heavy attention.

Numerous moonblades flew towards it, but it dodged left and right, relying on the surrounding lightning wolves to provide cover, thus suffering only minor injuries.

Howl!

It opened its mouth, and between its sharp teeth, sparks flew, quickly forming an electric current that flew through the air towards Fang Yuan.

Water Shield Gu.

Fang Yuan snorted, and from his nose, two lines of light blue water vapour flowed out.

The water vapour expanded, forming a water ball shield, protecting him.

The lightning current hit the water shield and caused it to shake, almost breaking.

Moonglow Gu!

Fang Yuan kept the water shield, and from his wrist, three moonblades shot out.

The moonblades' angle was tricky. The bold lightning wolf dodged the first, but its right front leg was hit by the second, causing its movement to slow down, and the third hit its head, causing a severe injury that crushed its left eye.

It cried out in pain, but other Gu Masters saw the opportunity and quickly, a flurry of moonblades enveloped it.

Pewpewpew!

This bold lightning wolf was instantly pelted, its body bathed in blood, and injuries were so deep its bones could be seen. Its body shook a little before collapsing completely. The surrounding wolf packs went into a panic, like ripples in a pond.

But at this point, there were three frenzy lightning wolves behind holding the fort, and the wolf packs only went into chaos for a while before raising their claws and attacking the village walls again.

Fang Yuan shot a few more moonblades out before getting down the wooden ladder. With just this, his deep red primeval essence had already gone below half, needing replenishment.

Seeing him coming down, a Rank two Gu Master quickly replaced his position and ascended the wooden ladder.

Normally, Gu Masters that had long range attacks would ascend the wooden ladder, or gather at the tower building's roof. Their emphasis was on the bold lightning wolf, as its threat was greater than any ordinary lightning wolf.

Some bold lightning wolf had a Gu worm that assisted with jumping in their bodies, allowing them to leap into the village.

Fang Yuan walked down the ladder, and continued towards the back.

Surrounding him, there was people walking around, similar to him, those that had expended their primeval essence and were recovering. Another group of Gu Masters replaced their positions and entered the battlefield, providing their strength towards defending the clan.

This was a battlefield.

Strength below Rank two peak stage was meagre. Only Rank three Gu Masters were the important pillars, able to control the situation.

Fang Yuan came to a bamboo building. This was a modified building and was heavily reinforced. He squeezed his way in, where many Gu Masters were sitting inside, holding primeval stones and recovering their primeval essence.

Some healing Gu Masters moved among the crowd; some squatted on the ground, some bandaged injured Gu Masters, and the first aid kits were placed at the side.

Fang Yuan found a spot to sit down, and a healing Gu Master immediately came over.

He shook his head towards her, and she understood, approaching another Gu Master instead.

...

Such a rotational strategy, all the way till ten o'clock at night, Fang Yuan had already entered battle five times. But the lightning wolf packs did not seem to reduce, in fact, they could see even more wolf packs, hurriedly arriving upon hearing the frenzy lightning wolf's call.

"It seems this wolf tide will sustain through the night," said a clan elder who stared outside the village, his face full of worry.

At night, Gu Masters' vision was poorer, but on the other hand, the lightning wolves had superior vision and were unaffected by the darkness.

"This is only the second wolf tide this year, and it is already so intense. The situation is not optimistic." Another clan elder sighed.

Gu Yue Yao Ji's face was sullen.

She was the medicine hall clan elder, leading the healing Gu Masters. First-hand injury reports would be sent to her.

On that thin piece of bamboo paper, it recorded the injuries and deaths of the day. Yao Ji held it in her hands, feeling solemn.

The death toll was far greater than previous years.

But she understood, this was not due to the decline of quality of Gu Masters, but because the wolf numbers were too great, and too ferocious.

"Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, how's the acquisition?" Seeing the blood red sun setting, Yao Ji sighed, asking faintly.

Her subordinate quickly reported—three people had not given up theirs yet, and Fang Yuan was among them.

Yao Ji listened and snorted, then asked, "Where is Yao Le?"

"Miss Yao Le is near the east door, leading the healing team. I've advised her many times, but she refuses to stay at the back, insisting on going to the frontlines to battle." Saying so, he kneeled down in horror.

Yao Ji thought for a while before nodding, waving her hand to send off the subordinate.

Near to her granddaughter, there was a clan elder. Xiong Jiao Man and the gang were also there, fighting at the village walls. It could be said that the frontlines was the safest place.

Although Yao Ji doted on her granddaughter, she supported her courage as well.

The ones in power have their considerations.

These experiences will become Gu Yue Yao Le's political advantage when she inherits the medicine hall!

Chapter 150: I am only helping myself

The golden full moon hung in the sky, the drifting clouds casting a gloomy shade.

There were desperate battles going on outside the village and the bright moonlight was great news to the Gu Masters in the dark night.

Wolf corpses piled up in the traps and were already reaching the midpoint of the wall. This gave a good platform to move on for the charging lightning wolves.

Some ordinary lightning wolves jumped, clawed and even directly leaped across the wall.

However, these lightning wolves usually fell or staggered due to the height disparity and were immediately disposed off by the standby Gu Masters.

At this time, Fang Yuan was standing on top of a tower, along with many other Gu Masters; they were endlessly throwing out moonblades and other attacks at the wolf packs.

In the whole battlefield, these towers were the most important source of damage. The combination of the Gu Masters and the towers had eliminated a large number of bold lightning wolves.

"Kill, kill, kill. Annihilate these wolves!""Nana, I will take revenge for you!!""Persevere, just a bit more. The clan's safety lies in our hands."

The surroundings were a cacophony of noises; some people were madly screaming, some were shouting revenge, some were shouting in pain, and some were shouting slogans.

Fang Yuan indifferently stood there, his hand tossing out moonblades occasionally while continuing to observe the battlefield.

Although there was a bright moon, the visibility couldn't be compared to daytime after all. The three frenzy lightning wolves were at the rear, unmoving; their figures indistinct.

As long as they were unharmed, the lightning wolves were just cannon fodders and even bold lightning wolves were only high level sacrifices.

Suddenly!

A frenzy lightning wolf unhurriedly took a step forward, it opened its large mouth and threw a thunderball.

Rank three thunderclap Gu.

This thunderball was not big, it was only the size of a millstone. However, a large amount of eerie blue electricity was condensed in it and its speed was strangely fast.

Almost immediately, the thunder ball fiercely collided with the tower Fang Yuan was on.

The progress of the fierce battle had been in a deadlock, many Gu Masters were mindlessly fighting and they were not able to react to the thunderball.

Water Shield Gu, White Jade Gu!

Fang Yuan was only able to put up his defense before white light covered his sight.

BOOM!

The huge sound from the explosion nearly ruptured his eardrums.

A formless force erupted out from the explosion and sent him flying.

The devastating thunder destroyed the water shield within two breaths of time. The surplus electric current struck Fang Yuan and even with the White Jade Gu's defense, he still felt bursts of numbness.

Bang.

He fell to the ground from a height of three to four meters. White Jade Gu was not the Raiment Gu; it couldn't lessen the force on impact. Fang Yuan's back hurt all over.

He quickly got up from the ground, his eyes repeatedly blinking as teardrops fell from it.

After three breaths of time, he slowly recovered his sight.

The tower that had been built with thick stones was half-destroyed. There were many burnt black corpses scattered around on the ground. The thunderball attack had opened a huge hole on the outer wall, and an unending stream of wolf packs charged into the village like a tide.

The frenzy lightning wolves finally entered the battlefield!

Thousand beast king level strength was extraordinary.

The many Gu Masters that were around Fang Yuan in the tower just a moment ago were completely dead, some left without intact corpses. Only Fang Yuan alone had survived.

The jellyfish-like Water Shield Gu appeared very dull inside his aperture.

If the water shield was continuously destroyed many times, the Water Shield Gu would also be damaged and could even perish.

White Jade Gu was also in a similar state.

Gu worms were strong and yet fragile.

Take this Thunderclap Gu for example; its thunderball was very powerful and fast, also difficult to resist. But it also had a weakness—it couldn't be used repeatedly and needed some time before the second thunderball could be shot out.

BOOM!

But Fang Yuan had just stood up when another thunderball flew over.

"To think this wolf king has two Thunderclap Gu on it!" Fang Yuan's complexion turned pale and he hurriedly dodged.

He tried not using the Water Shield Gu and only relied on the defense from the White Jade Gu.

"Beast, stop your insolence!" At this critical timing, a figure appeared in mid-air, golden light bursting out from the figure as he resisted this thunderball.

The elders had made their moves!

However, one elder was still not enough. Soon, the elder was joined with two other elders.

A frenzy lightning wolf needed at least three groups with great teamwork to join hands, or at least three Rank three Gu Masters to face it.

The frenzy lightning wolf took heavy steps forward, emerging from the indistinguishable wolf packs, as the surrounding wolves gave way.

It gradually started from a slow run, and then got faster and faster, charging at the village wall with its head lowered.

Seeing this scene, all the Rank one and Rank two Gu Masters fled in terror.

Only those three elders still remained on their spots.

Everyone tacitly vacated this part of the battlefield and left it to them.

The intense battle between the three elders and this frenzy lightning wolf unfolded.

Not long after, the other two frenzy lightning wolves also charged towards the village; opening another two battlefields.

Nine elders and three frenzy lightning wolves formed into three great battlefields. Thunder and lightning burst out everywhere, destroying the bamboo buildings. Most of the Gu Masters or the lightning wolves who were caught in these three great battles didn't have a good end.

Lighting wolf packs were still charging towards the village, but Fang Yuan didn't fight anymore and moved to a corner of the battlefield, observing the three great battle stages from a distance.

No doubt, the attacks from these wolf packs had reached the climax.

"Three frenzy lightning wolves; one has two Thunderclap Gu and has high offensive power; another has Thunder Wings Gu and can fly for a short moment, giving it very high flexibility in the battle; another holds the Thunder Roar Gu and can kill its enemies with the soundwaves." Fang Yuan slowly got the details on these three frenzy lightning wolves after observing for a moment.

A thousand beast king usually has three-four Rank two and a Rank three wild Gu worm residing on it.

The Gu Masters could give proper response as long as they were clear on these Gu worms. Once the frenzy lightning wolves suffered targeted attacks, with their low wisdom, they wouldn't change their monotonous attack styles, and the battle outcome was certain.

Sure enough, soon the several elders retreated and other elders replaced them.

With the mutual coordination between them and superior tactics, they were soon able to occupy the upper hand. After a short moment of intense battle, they controlled the battle situation.

Victory was only a matter of time.

"The outcome is set." Just when Yao Ji puffed out a sigh, a roar sounded out from the eastern gate.

A lightning wolf was growing bigger, from the size of a normal lightning wolf—as if air was blown inside it—it swelled up to a size of an elephant.

"There is actually another frenzy lightning wolf!" Many elders were alarmed at this scene.

Their attention had all been on the three battle stages. As their entire battle formation was heavily emphasized on these three areas, the forces at the eastern gate was somewhat thin and weak.

"Not good, Yao Le is still there!" Yao Ji suddenly turned pale, and she immediately shot out towards the eastern gate.

"Eh, to think there was still such an unforeseen event. This frenzy lightning wolf should have a Rank three Aura Restraint Gu; it used this disguise to mix in with the lightning wolf packs and deceive the Gu Masters at the eastern gate."

Fang Yuan observed carefully; the situation at the eastern gate was far from good.

A frenzy lightning wolf suddenly appeared and directly smashed the eastern gate, creating a huge hole.

Countless lightning wolves flocked behind the bold lightning wolves, howling savagely as they charged into the village.

Gu Yue Yao Le was numb with fear as she saw the lightning wolf packs charging in like a tide.

Fortunately, she had veterans like Xiong Jiao Man beside her. At this critical timing, Xiong Jiao Man took it upon herself to control the scene and ordered, "Quick, close the doors and the windows. We need to defend this place till the reinforcements arrive, and only then will we have a fighting chance!"

She had just finished speaking when—BANG—the roof of the bamboo building collapsed under the attack of the frenzy lightning wolf.

Gu Yue Yao Le screamed. The abrupt twist in events had caused her to lose her composure.

She was after all too young and only had Rank one cultivation. She had stubbornly stayed here because she felt safe and had never thought she would fall into such a dangerous state.

"Brute beast, stop at once!" Gu Yue Yao Ji shouted while frantically running.

She helplessly looked as the frenzy lightning wolf rammed into the bamboo building. Her beloved granddaughter was in a dangerous situation but even though she had the power, she couldn't help her because it was beyond her reach.

At this dangerous moment, it was again Xiong Jiao Man who stepped forward.

She willed in her mind and her remaining brown bear charged towards the frenzy lightning wolf with a roar.

The frenzy lightning wolf swatted with its right paw, sending this four-hundred-kilogram-over brown bear flying.

It opened its mouth and bit the brown bear's head to pieces. How could an ordinary wild beast resist a thousand beast king level's strength?

Xiong Jiao Man took this time when the frenzy lightning wolf was tangled up with the brown bear to rush out with Gu Yue Yao Le in tow, managing to pull apart a small distance.

The frenzy lightning wolf roared. It naturally wasn't willing to see its prey run away like this. It leapt and crossed a dozen meters at once, landing in front of Xiong Jiao Man.

Suddenly seeing this frenzy lightning wolf appear in front of her, Gu Yue Yao Le's legs went soft.

Xiong Jiao Man dragged her but didn't dare to rush forward recklessly; she could only change her direction and run towards the outside of the village.

The frenzy lightning wolf was just about to pounce on them when Gu Yue Yao Ji arrived and threw a light purple moonblade at the wolf's back; the moonblade quietly changed into a ball of miasma and bore into the frenzy lightning wolf's nose.

The frenzy lightning wolf immediately coughed twice; it was poisoned!

This was the Rank three Moon Poison Gu.

The frenzy lightning wolf was furious, and it raised its head and roared; its fierce roar formed into an invisible force and smashed into the surroundings.

Thunder Roar Gu used the vibration of the soundwaves to kill, but this was not Thunder Roar Gu—it was the Soundwave Gu which formed invisible pushing force.

Xiong Jiao Man and Gu Yue Yao Le were sent flying into different directions by this pushing force. Xiong Jiao Man struck a bamboo building; no more movements could be seen from her, whereas Gu Yue Yao Le was sent flying past the broken eastern gate and out of the village.

The fall stunned her and as she tried getting up, she saw a lightning wolf opening its bloody mouth and trying to bite her.

Aah—!

She gave a shrill scream and at this critical juncture, a moonblade flew over and killed this lightning wolf.

She hurriedly stood up and saw the benefactor who saved her; he was a young male Gu Master. The lower half of his body had been buried under the collapsed wall.

The male Gu Master vaguely smiled at her with his blood-drenched face; the next moment, his throat was ripped open by the swarming lightning wolves.

Tears flew down Gu Yue Yao Le's face, and she cried as she ran.This part of the battlefield was extremely chaotic.

Because of Gu Yue Yao Le's identity and background, there were Gu Masters who helped her out from time to time. But they were powerless to even protect themselves, much less help her out of this predicament. Gu Yue Yao Ji was also tangled up with the frenzy lightning wolf and couldn't attend to her.

Gu Yue Yao Le was perplexed and fully at a loss within; there were only the images of claws and teeth of the lightning wolves in front of her. In her frantic state, she suddenly heard a voice speak, "Move a step back!"

She subconsciously followed the voice and was able to luckily avoid a lightning wolf's bite.

"Roll to the right." That voice came again.

Yao Le's consciousness was still blank, but her body had already made the move. There was a snapping sound of a wolf's mouth; she had escaped the bite by a hair's breadth.

The voice arrived unceasingly and the young girl meticulously followed them. There were mistakes made sometimes, but at those times a moonblade would fly over from seemingly nowhere and get her out of the trouble.

Only when there were no more lightning wolves around her, did Yao Le discover that she was already safe.

It was only when she had unconsciously drifted far away from the village and was in a remote forest.

A human figure appeared in front of her.Her eyes immediately opened wide, "Gu Yue Fang Yuan, you were the one who helped me?""No, I am only helping myself." Fang Yuan grinned, revealing an evil intent.

Chapter 151: Demonic nature

"What?" Gu Yue Yao Le was shocked when she heard this.

Fang Yuan had already struck at lightning speed, his hand chopping her neck! She fainted immediately.

The young girl fell down helplessly, and Fang Yuan's hand quickly moved, holding her by the waist. Next, he activated the Stealth Scale Gu, and their bodies vanished on the spot.

When Gu Yue Yao Le woke up in a sleepy state, she found herself in a dark mountain cave.

She shrugged her head, trying to stand up subconsciously.

But she soon found out that her arms were tied behind her back, the rope looped around her neck; she was tied tightly on a large rock.

All the Gu worms on her body had been plundered away by Fang Yuan, refined and turned into his.

She was merely a fifteen year old young girl—with that frail body, how could she break free from that thick ropes wrapped a few times around the rock, even tied with knots?

Being trapped in this remote and unfamiliar place, the young girl started to feel frightened.

She thought about the moment before she had fainted; even the most naive person would also know that Fang Yuan was going to do something bad to her.

"But how would Fang Yuan deal with me? What is he planning to do? Is it because I complained about him to grandma, thus he is taking revenge?" The young girl was tied helplessly, but her thoughts quickly flipped like pages of a book.

The more she thought, the more frightened she got, and she started sobbing uncontrollably.

"Grandma, where are you? Quickly come and save me..." As she cried, she felt an intense fear and loneliness.

Fang Yuan was nowhere to be seen, and the cave was filled with her cries.

"Is Fang Yuan planning to trap me here? For seven, eight days, and make me suffer in hunger, so I will never speak ill of him again?" After crying for a while, Gu Yue Yao Le thought of a possibility.

Too evil!

Fang Yuan, I will never forgive you!!

She gritted her teeth as her impression of Fang Yuan, which was bad from the start, fell into negatives.

Since her birth, Gu Yue Yao Le had not hated a person so much.

At this moment, footsteps were heard.

Soon, Fang Yuan's silhouette was seen emerging from the shadows.

"Fang Yuan, what do you want, let go of me now! Otherwise my grandma will deal with you." Seeing Fang Yuan, Gu Yue Yao Le struggled intensely, her slim legs stomping on the ground like a small deer that fell into a trap.

"You sure are lively," Fang Yuan coldly snorted.

Gu Yue Yao Le was about to open her mouth and continue crying in a rage, but she soon saw a large bear moving behind Fang Yuan.

"B-bear..." Her widened eyes showed shock as she stuttered.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, stretching out his hand and caressing the bear's black fur, his voice filled with coldness that flowed in the cave like ominous winds, "Because of the wolf tide, it was not easy to find such a wild bear, it took me lots of time and effort to find it."

Gu Yue Yao Le reacted instantly. Her quick-witted thoughts soon remembered that Fang Yuan had once taken a Bear Enslavement Gu from Xiong Jiao Man.

"So that's it..." She laughed coldly and was about to speak, but Fang Yuan suddenly squatted in front of her.

"What are you doing?!" The young girl tried to move away, but Fang Yuan easily used his right hand and grabbed her cheeks firmly.

"Such a cute appearance, lovable indeed," Fang Yuan plainly commented.

Swoosh!

His right hand moved quickly, grabbing Yao Le's shirt, and pulled.

The shirt was instantly torn, showing her pink undergarment.

"Ah—!!!" The young girl was stunned momentarily before shrieking loudly, frantically struggling. Even though her tender muscles bled due to friction from the ropes, she couldn't care less.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, continuing to pull and tear her clothing apart.

Rrrrrip.

Soon, the young girl's ragged garment was only left with a few torn strips of cloth, showing off large areas of her milky, delicate flesh.

"No, no!" She was extremely frightened, crying out loudly. As she thought of all the various possible ways Fang Yuan was going to deal with her, her whole body shook and trembled.

However, Fang Yuan did not continue on as she expected, but instead he stood up and moved backwards.

The young girl's loud cries turned into sobbing.

But at this moment, the black bear moved its paws, and got closer.

The young girl was frightened as her iris shrunk into pin-size, for at this moment, she felt an intense sensation of death.

Whoosh!

The bear paw struck, and the sound of it breaking air could be heard.

With a crisp sound, the young girl's skull was hit, and the intense force broke her thin neck.

Her head was twisted at a creepy angle, broken and hanging on one end.

One moment ago, she was still an alluring beauty, and the next moment she was a corpse. Her warm body tied to the huge rock, was like a broken toy doll.

At this moment, even without Fang Yuan's control of the Bear Enslavement Gu, with its craving for food, the black bear had already lowered its head, enjoying this sumptuous meal.

It first started to gnaw at the young girl's throat, and fresh blood immediately bubbled out, splashing onto its black fur.

Next was the young girl's white and tender breasts, like flower buds that were unopened.

The black bear bit on her right breast in one whole mouthful, tearing away the skin and flesh, exposing her deathly pale ribs.

At this moment, the black bear used its paw to break these bones. The young girl's internal organs were crushed, and immediately blood poured out endlessly.

Without the skeleton's interference, the black bear placed its mouth further into the girl's body. It nipped at the girl's heart that was still beating, then proceeded to swallow it in one mouthful.

The heart passed through its throat and into the stomach, and this bear that had to hide around and couldn't eat due to the wolf tide, howled out in satisfaction.

After another cry, it lowered its head again and started to consume her internal organs wantonly.

Chomp chomp chomp.

The black bear's mouth opened and chewed, large amounts of blood gushing out from its mouth, issuing a watery sound.

After a good while, the black bear finally moved its head out.

The young girl's chest was already empty, the immense injury extending to her stomach. But towards the shining, white intestines, the bear did not seem to have much interest.

It started to focus on the young girl's white slim legs.

The girl's jade-like fingers were all bitten away by the black bear at once, and with a few rounds of chewing, the fingers were swallowed with a crisp sound.

The girl's thighs were also a delicacy.

The tender skin and flesh of her thighs emitted a virgin fragrance. When the bear had finished, all that was left was the white leg bones.

Among the swaying movements, the girl's skull finally dropped onto the ground.

To be honest, she did have a cute appearance. Those black lustrous eyes with a round nose slightly pointing up, and her skin blushing like peach blossoms, with a small mouth and two rows of white clean teeth.

But now, her face had lost the colour of blood, her skin turning deathly pale. Her fine black hair was left hanging, covering half of her face, with those pair of eyes staring wide-open, filled with fear and anger.

A death full of grievance!

NOTE: The following is religious text that may make no sense to most, but read it with a pinch of salt.

Fang Yuan folded his arms as he observed Gu Yue Yao Le's expression, thinking of a Buddhist saying on earth: 'Without a sense of self, without a sense of person; to be detached of all living things, detached of the sense of time. Void is the red skull and white bones, skin and flesh!'

I am namely myself, without individuality. Breaking the sense of self, realizing that one is common and ordinary. 'Without a sense of self' means 'everyone is equal, there is no difference.'

Man is humanity no longer treating humans as a superior race and demeaning other living beings. 'Without a sense of person' means that 'the world is equal, there is no difference.'

'Living things' refers to all life, no longer recognising life as superior and thinking that non-living beings like rocks and water have cognition. This is 'detached of all living things', which means 'all in the world is equal, there is no difference.'

Any object or creature has their respective lifespan, and 'detached of the sense of time' namely means 'regardless of whether it exists or not, they are all equal without difference.'

No matter how beautiful the guy or girl, they eventually turn into a skeleton. Bones, skin and flesh are one, but people favoured skin and flesh while fearing bones—this is being fixated on appearance, not recognising that all is equal.

This Buddhist term is calling for humans to break through all forms, seeing the truth.

Beauty is superficial, and people, me, the world, and time, is all superficial. If one goes past the superficial aspect, they would see Buddha.

Recognising and going beyond, treating all as equal, all is equal.

Thus, Buddha sacrificed his body to feed tigers, cutting off his flesh to feed eagles. This was the benevolence in his heart, seeing all in this world as his own, loving everything, and his great love for everything.

No matter if it's me, others, animals or plants, or even the lifeless rocks and water, even those that do not exist, we have to love them.

If a mortal standing there watches the bear eat a person, some hot-blooded teenager would jump out and scream, "You beast, don't you dare eat a person!" or "Beauty, do not fear, uncle is here to save you!" etc.

This was the mortal's love and hatred, loving young girls and hating large bears. Not going beyond and still fixating on the superficial, not able to see her red human skeleton.

If Buddha stood there and watched the bear eat a person, he would sigh, chanting, "If I do not enter hell, who would enter?" He would save the young girl and feed himself to the black bear.

This was Buddha's love and hatred, loving the young girl and loving the bear, treating all as equal.

But right now, Fang Yuan was the one standing here.

Seeing the young girl's tragic and violent death, his heart was unmoved.

This was not because of his numbness to death, but he had gone beyond the superficial, having no obsessions. Without a sense of self, without a sense of person; to be detached of all living things, detached of the sense of time...

Seeing all living things as equal, the world is equal.

Thus, the girl's death is no different from a fox or a tree's death.

But to a mere mortal, the girl's death would trigger their anger, hatred, and pity. If it was the girl eating the bear, they would not feel anything. If an old lady was eaten, the pity in their hearts would be greatly reduced. If it was a villain, a murderer getting eaten, they would clap their hands in joy, praising.

In actuality, all beings are equal, and heaven and earth is just.

Nature is fair, disregarding love or hate; it is emotionless, and never gives differential treatment.

Rule of the strong, victor takes all!

The disappearance of a lifeform, towards the entire natural realm and the infinite cosmos, to the long river of history—what does it amount to?

Death means death, who can choose not to die? What talk about a girl, bear, ant, fox, tree, old lady, murderer, they are all lowly! Humble! Mongrels!

Only by recognising this and going beyond the superficial, arriving at the truth, does one gain divinity.

This divinity, taking a step towards the light, it becomes Buddha. If it takes a step towards the darkness, it becomes a demon.

Demonic nature!

Chapter 152: Advance to Rank three

An hour later, Gu Yue Yao Le was almost completely eaten by the black bear.

The black bear was unwilling to eat the intestines and the girl's brains, but Fang Yuan did not want that to happen.

According to the Man-beast Life Burial Gu's recipe, a wild beast must consume the entire person up to the tiniest scrap for the greatest effect. This can ensure success to the greatest rate.

To refine this Man-beast Life Burial Gu, about ten ingredients are needed.

And the most important two, are man and beast.

The human has to be a virgin girl, and has a Gu Master's aptitude. Furthermore, she has to be at least C grade talent, but of course A and B grade would be better, and can greatly enhance the chances of success.

This beast refers to the Beast Enslavement Gu. The Bear Enslavement Gu, Wolf Enslavement Gu, Tiger Enslavement Gu etc, even Deer Enslavement Gu or Bull Enslavement Gu can work. However only bears, wolves and tigers—these carnivores have it easier eating meat. Otherwise, if forcing a herbivore like a deer or bull to consume this human, the Enslavement Gu's manipulation would be required to force them to do so.

After the beast consumes the human, the refinement has to begin immediately. Otherwise, when the beast digests the person's bones and meat, the refinement would no longer be possible.

Seeing that the black bear refused to eat Yao Le's intestines and brain, Fang Yuan snorted in displeasure and willed in his mind, activating the Bear Enslavement Gu that was planted in the black bear's body.

The black bear growled, and under Fang Yuan's oppression, was forced to swallow the intestines and brain. At the same time, it broke the girl's bones to bits and swallowed them piece by piece.

The bone shards were sharp and pointy, but under Fang Yuan's control, it swallowed them and many of the shards stabbed into its mouth and throat, the pain causing the huge bear to tear up.

But Fang Yuan only strengthened his control, and the bear's body was no longer under its own control.

Seeing the black bear stuffing the spine into its throat, Fang Yuan knew the time was ripe.

He flicked his finger, and a Single Aperture Charcoal Gu flew out.

The Gu worm flew into the black bear's mouth and burrowed its way in.

The black bear suddenly cried out painfully, as the Charcoal Gu's power was burning its internal organs.

The black bear's body was shuddering intensely; it cried painfully and wanted to roll around on the ground, but the Enslavement Gu had a steady grip on its movements.

After burning for fifteen minutes, Fang Yuan's finger moved again and three Kerosene Gu flew out.The Kerosene Gu was a Rank one expenditure-type Gu, and upon entering the black bear's body, it exploded into large amounts of kerosene and intensified the fire burning inside the black bear's body.

The black bear cried until its throat was dry, but Fang Yuan timed it well and threw several more Gu worms out into its body.

These Gu worms were all exchanged using merit points.

The black bear laid on the ground, completely motionless.

A moment later, from its eyes, ears, nostrils and mouth as well as its butt, small sparks of flames were seen. Then, the fire got bigger and quickly enveloped its entire body, turning it into a giant fire pillar.

The entire dim cave was lit up by this fire.

But this fire was not the usual orange, but instead an eerie blood colour.

Fang Yuan patiently waited for a moment, until the fire was about to extinguish, then he threw out the final Gu.

This was a Rank two poison Gu.

Throwing it into the fire, an intense reaction occurred.

A white lump of light emerged from the fire, initially only fist size.

Fang Yuan quickly took out primeval stones from his money bag and threw them into this light lump.

The white lump digested the primeval stones and became bigger.

After throwing up to a thousand primeval stones, the light was around the size of a room door, and then suddenly shrunk.

Huff!

The fire on the bear's corpse extinguished at once, and the cave returned to darkness, while a Gu worm wobbled its way to Fang Yuan.

Man-beast Life Burial Gu.

Rank three, expenditure-type Gu.

It looked like a black spider with furry long legs, but it had the head of a bear, and on its back there was a blood coloured tattoo, drawing the outline of a young girl's beautiful face.This was Gu Yue Yao Le's face.

It resembled a smile yet wasn't, it looked like a crying face and yet was not, but she seemed to be staring at Fang Yuan with a gaze filled with utter hatred!

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, not minding it at all.

Death is the end of all, even in life she was merely so, what more can she do to Fang Yuan after death?

He opened his mouth with no hesitation and swallowed this Man-beast Life Burial Gu.

The Man-beast Life Burial Gu moved along his throat into his esophagus, turning into a black and red mix of water flow.

The water flowed from above, like an inverted heavenly river, pouring into his aperture.

Entering the aperture, this gush of black red water entered the red steel Primeval Sea immediately.

At once, the entire primeval essence was turned into an eerie black-red colour, filled with the smell of blood.

Fang Yuan's thoughts moved as he activated this black-red primeval essence, rushing it towards the aperture walls.

10%, 20%, 30%, when 38% of the primeval essence was expended, the aperture had a loud boom as the white crystal walls broke into pieces.

What replaced it was an entirely new round ball-shaped light membrane aperture wall.

At this moment, Fang Yuan advanced to Rank three!But Fang Yuan did not loosen up, and instead forced the remaining black red primeval essence out of his body.

This primeval essence was not usable, and if injected into Gu worms, they would die. If left remaining inside the aperture, the longer it stayed, the more it would pollute the light membrane aperture walls, and cause one's aptitude to decrease.

After expelling all of the black-red primeval essence out of his body, he grabbed a primeval stone and started to recover his primeval essence.

First, a white silver fog appeared, then it condensed into water droplets, finally forming his white silver coloured Primeval Sea.

For a Gu Master, Rank one is green copper primeval essence, Rank two is red steel, and Rank three is white silver.

But this white silver Primeval Sea was not pure, as there was a trace of black-red mixed in—this is the side effect of using the Man-beast Life Burial Gu.

Fang Yuan was not surprised. He calmed his mind and expelled this white silver primeval essence out of his body, before forming new primeval essence.

The second time round, the black-red coloured substance was reduced by half.

But Fang Yuan was not satisfied, and expelled his white silver primeval essence again, forming new primeval essence for the third time.

After several tries, the black-red substance was reduced to a barely observable amount, and even if Fang Yuan attempted more tries, this substance would remain.

This was an unavoidable consequence of using the Man-beast Life Burial Gu.

The Man-beast Life Burial Gu's effect was extraordinary, able to turn a Rank two peak stage Gu Master with no hopes of advancing his entire life, into a Rank three. This was literally changing fate, thus there had to be some imperfection.Getting rid of this black-red substance, there was a method. The most common would be to use the Cleansing Water Gu.

Cleansing Water Gu can completely wash away impurities in the aperture; it appeared once in the tree house, but was bought by the Chi faction.

In this short term, Fang Yuan could do nothing about the black-red substance.

...

"You bunch of useless idiots, what are you all doing! Not able to find such a large, lively person?!" In the medicine hall, Gu Yue Yao Ji flew into a furious rage, and her screaming caused even the window lattices and curtains to tremble.In her heart, she was worried, frightened, anxious and enraged.

It had been three days and three nights, the four frenzy lightning wolves were exterminated and Gu Yue village was relatively safe at the moment. But her granddaughter Gu Yue Yao Le was nowhere to be seen.

Even after she mobilized all her relationships and combed the battlefield, there even being large-scale search parties around the village, there was still no trace of her.

The ones who saw Gu Yue Yao Le for the last time were the battling Gu Masters. What they saw was—Gu Yue Yao Le falling into the encirclement of the wolves, and had to run away frantically, in a worsening predicament.

These showed that Gu Yue Yao Le was not in an optimistic situation, most likely consumed by the wolf packs.

But Gu Yue Yao Ji was indignant.She could not accept such a cruel truth.

If it was any other girl, so what if they die. But this was her own blood-related granddaughter, someone she had nurtured since young to be the inheritor of her medicine faction!

She was so well-behaved and intelligent, loved by everyone. So lively and cute, bringing others joy.These days, Gu Yue Yao Ji could not sleep at all, for in her mind, it was all images of her granddaughter.

Gu Yue Yao Ji had originally maintained her looks well, but in these three days, she seem to have aged over ten years. It was like her heart was dug away, and she felt an endless pain of emptiness.In her screaming, tens of Gu Masters lowered their heads, enduring the cruel insults of the old woman.

"Reporting to medicine hall clan elder, this subordinate has something to report." At this time, a Rank two Gu Master walked in.

"What! Is it news about Yao Le?" Gu Yue Yao Ji's eyes shone, asking quickly.

"Someone advanced to Rank three, the clan leader is holding an elder meeting at the clan leader pavilion, to confirm the situation." The Gu Master quickly reported.

Gu Yue Yao Ji's eyes dimmed, waving her hands, "Not information about Yao Le, and still disturbing me? Wait... wait, what did you say... Someone advanced to Rank three and became a new clan elder?"Halfway through, she reacted and lightly frowned.

This was too sudden, with zero premonition.

The appearance of a new clan elder would influence the entire Gu Yue clan's political situation. This was a huge hit on the medicine faction who has lost its inheritor.In the medicine hall, the standing Gu Masters started to discuss among themselves, guessing the identity of the new clan elder.

Gu Yue Yao Ji frowned, asking immediately, "Who advanced to Rank three?"

"Reporting to Lord Yao ji, it is Gu Yue Fang Yuan," the Gu Master answered.

"What? It's him!" At once, Gu Yue Yao Ji's iris shrunk; this was the worst of news to her.

In the hall, the Gu Masters also started to discuss violently."They couldn't have made a mistake could they, to think it's Fang Yuan?"

"Isn't he a C grade talent? How can he become a Rank three Gu Master so quickly?"

"Once he's Rank three, he will be a clan elder, a higher-up in the clan. When we see him next time, we have to bow and greet him!"

"How can this be.... This is literally soaring through success!"

"Earlier, didn't they say he's dead? He went missing for three days and three nights, and his corpse could not be found on the battlefield. We thought he was eaten by lightning wolves already..."

They were stunned, jealous and confused."Missing for three days and three nights, without a corpse on the battlefield, isn't this the same as Yao Le's situation?"

Gu Yue Yao Ji's ears twitched, and her woman instinct caused her to have intense suspicion towards Fang Yuan for no reason!

She suddenly changed her mind; she is going to the clan leader's pavilion.

Chapter 153: Really aged

"He has truly advanced to Rank three!"

"This Rank three aura is genuine, and there is the white silver primeval essence; there is no mistake."

The atmosphere in the clan hall was solemn.

The clan head Gu Yue Bo was sitting on the highest seat, with many elders seated in rows by his left and right.

Whispers could be heard here and there, and dozen of people's attentions were more or less gathered on a young man who was standing upright in the center of the hall with his head held high.

The young man was Fang Yuan.

"To think this Fang Yuan advanced to Rank three."

"If I hadn't personally seen it, I would never have believed it....."

"Doesn't he only have C grade aptitude? How could he advance so suddenly?"

"Actually, it can't be said to be sudden. Did you forget that he obtained two red steel Relic Gu?"

"Right, it was two whole Relic Gu, they can completely raise his cultivation steeply. Just thinking back when I cultivated, sigh....."

The group of elders were both amazed and puzzled; this matter had caught them completely unprepared.

"This Fang Yuan was able to advance to Rank three! He is merely of C grade aptitude, but could actually have such accomplishments in this short time. This is really a surprise." Gu Yue Mo Chen who was seated on the frontmost seat in the left row exclaimed inwardly.He thought of two-three years ago, when Fang Yuan was still in the academy, and killed a servant of his family.He had already forgotten the name of this servant. But the minced corpse Fang Yuan sent over had left a profound impression on him.

From that day, he saw Fang Yuan in new light, but didn't expect much from him due to his aptitude.

Now, this young man actually had such accomplishments!

According to the clan system, all Gu Masters who advanced to Rank three were new elders.

A new elder was bound to have a huge impact on the old political structure.

"If I had recruited him before, I would be able to use this impact and gain political dominance. Sigh, it really is a pity....." Thinking of this, Gu Yue Mo Chen couldn't help but glance in front of him.

His old rival Gu Yue Chi Lian was seated on the frontmost seat in the right row. Right now he had a gloomy expression and obscure light flashed in his eyes.

"This Fang Yuan definitely has secrets on him. Although he had the help from the two red steel Relic Gu, he couldn't have had advanced to Rank three so fast, this is something even Qing Shu couldn't accomplish," Gu Yue Bo was also pondering.

He unavoidably thought of his adopted son Qing Shu, and sighed.

Were Gu Yue Qing Shu alive, he might also have Rank three cultivation by now. Unfortunately, reality is cruel.

"Medicine hall elder Lord Gu Yue Yao Ji has arrived—!" At this moment, the doorguard suddenly announced loudly.

Following his announcement, an old woman walked in through the door. Her face was pale and filled with wrinkles, but under her weary eyelids were extremely sharp eyes that locked onto Fang Yuan in an instant.

Gu Yue Yao Ji spoke as she walked forward quickly, "Fang Yuan, you advanced to Rank three? I don't believe it! I will personally verify it, let me inspect your aperture!"

The aperture was a Gu Master's most important secret and was also their personal affair. How could they let others inspect it so easily?

Fang Yuan slightly turned his body and looked at Yao Ji who was walking over. He replied with a sneer, "Gu Yue Yao Ji, on what basis are you demanding to inspect my aperture?"

Back then, when he had just begun cultivating, his aperture would be inspected at fixed intervals by the academy elder. But it was different now, he was already a Rank three Gu Master, someone who was on equal footing with other elders like the academy elder and the medicine hall elder.

Moreover, it was very simple to verify one's cultivation.

White silver primeval essence couldn't be faked easily, and similarly, his Rank three aura was a fact.

"Outrageous! You, a junior dares to call me by name?" Yao Ji's eyes widened, "Why can't I inspect you? With my identity as the medicine hall elder and also as your elder, I have the right to do so!"

"Hmph, old hag, calling you by name is giving you respect. I still have yet to settle the scores between us. You harbored a grudge towards me when I didn't sell you my Liquor worm, and actually wanted to plunder my Nine Leaf Vitality Grass? Hmph, I also wanted to exchange my merits for that Three Step Fragrant Grass Gu, but you prevented it in the dark. Now, I am also a Rank three Gu Master, so you had better stop putting on airs!"

Fang Yuan's eyes were narrowed and his words sharp as a blade. He was very clear-cut with his words, completely showing off his hostility towards Yao Ji.

If he said this with a cultivation of Rank one or Rank two, he would definitely be suppressed and even attacked. However, the situation was completely different now; he was a Rank three and his position was already equal to the elders.

Towards Fang Yuan insulting Gu Yue Yao Ji, the other elders' strategy was to wait and see.

Being at a high position, their considerations were profound. Even if they weren't born shrewd, the years of political struggle had trained the shrewdness in them.

They didn't have much understanding of Fang Yuan, so they could take this opportunity to observe him.

"Brat, you have the cheeks to slander me!" Gu Yue Yao Ji was furious due to the humiliation. What Fang Yuan said was true, but why would she admit it in front of everyone?

The elders present were all silently observing the situation unfold. Most of the elders present here knew of the matter regarding the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass and even had transactions with Gu Yue Yao Ji.

However in politics, there are only eternal benefits; never eternal enemies or eternal friends.

Upon hearing Gu Yue Yao Ji retort herself, Fang Yuan coldly laughed and didn't reply.

Gu Yue Yao Ji's sound echoed and lingered within the hall.

This old woman was slightly trembling, this silence made her feel like she was alone!

Something had changed.

The situation was no longer the same.

Were Fang Yuan to be a Rank one or Rank two, these elders would immediately jump out to stand on Gu Yue Yao Ji's side and unitedly punish Fang Yuan. The authority of higher-ups absolutely didn't allow the lower levels to challenge it!

However, Fang Yuan was Rank three now, and even if the clan head hadn't officially announced it, his position as an elder was already set in stone. Thus, his contradiction with Gu Yue Yao Ji was now the internal conflict between higher-ups.

Fang Yuan was a newly advanced elder, his foundation were not yet deep and didn't have any background, but this was also his strength as he had nothing to lose in the first place, thus having no fear.

By contrast, Gu Yue Yao Ji was old and though she was in control of medicine hall, had a high position and broad connections, this was also her weakness.

She was old and she couldn't afford to lose. Her medicine faction's inheritor Yao Le was missing and the enormous assets she controlled were coveted by many.

It would not be bad if it were peaceful times, but now was the time of the wolf tide and even elders had the possibility of dying.

Things were turbulent, newcomers climbed up in position and old timers stepped down.

This was a time of change, there weren't any elders that could guarantee their own safety. Even the clan head could fall down.

In the history of Gu Yue clan, the number of clan heads that died in a wolf tide weren't few.

As for the elders, they couldn't even guarantee their own safety, so unless there were enormous benefits involved, they wouldn't meddle in other people's fights.

Gu Yue Yao Ji felt like the situation had turned thorny.

The hall was silent.

Due to the matter regarding her granddaughter, she hadn't slept for three days and three nights. Right now as she stood there, she felt an invisible pressure shrouding her body and mind and it caused cold sweat to form on her forehead.

She felt like a crippled old wolf, standing alone in the wolf pack.

The surrounding wolves were standing in the shadows, observing her through their deep, dark green eyes.

Fang Yuan who was in front of her was like a stoic wolf who had revealed its brilliance in the battle. He was so young, energetic and also ambitious.

It really was the saying—Old waves push the new waves forward, and a new generation replaces the old!

At this moment, Gu Yue Yao Ji felt that she had really aged. Very much so!

Her eyelids jumped even more severely as her imposing aura gradually lowered.

However, Gu Yue Yao Le's figure appeared in her mind; she forcefully opened her blurred eyes, her aura increasing suddenly.

She opened her mouth, "Fang Yuan, why did you disappear for these three days? If you hadn't shown up, your name would have been listed in the casualties announcement in the medicine hall, in the list of the Gu Masters who died in battle. You disappeared for three days and three nights, and when you come back, you are already a Rank three Gu Master. What happened during these days? Heh heh, I believe everyone here is interested in your explanation."

After realizing she could no longer easily create troubles for Fang Yuan, her tone became more mild, no longer as forceful as before. However, her words were still very strong, with treacherous intentions hidden within.

After all, she had the highest seniority as a high-ranking politician!

The elders' eyes brightened when they heard this, revealing clear interest. No one was a fool among those present here, Fang Yuan's sudden advancement to Rank three was indeed strange.

His C grade aptitude was after all known by everyone.

Gu Yue Yao Ji's words brought those elders to stand by her side again.

However, since Fang Yuan dared to return so grandly, he naturally had made preparations.

Under everyone's gazes, he raised his head and laughed, "Old woman, what you want to know, am I obliged to tell you? However... hearing the pitiful news of your granddaughter's death, I will benevolently tell you. During the past few days, I have been in closed door cultivation in Elder Chi Lian's manor, trying to breakthrough to Rank three. This point can be verified by Elder Gu Yue Chi Lian!"

"What?" Gu Yue Yao Ji revealed a startled look.

Other elders were also shocked, all kinds of complicated expressions appearing on their faces.

Immediately, everyone's gazes were cast towards the gloomy-faced Gu Yue Chi Lian.

The Chi faction head, who held one of the two most powerful influences in the Gu Yue Clan, now appeared so gloomy that water could drip out from him.

However in front of everyone's gazes, he knew he needed to give an explanation, thus he reluctantly replied, "It is indeed so. I can testify that Fang Yuan has been in a closed door cultivation in a secret room in my manor during these past few days."

The instance these words came out, the whole crowd went in an uproar.

The elders possessed deep restraint, they wouldn't lose their bearings and make a scene. However, there were many whispers and mutterings.

"To think Gu Yue Chi Lian actually had relations with Fang Yuan!"

"Fang Yuan's advancement is related to Chi Lian?"

"There is a great probability! Didn't people speculate that Fang Yuan had someone supporting him from behind the scenes? To think it was the Chi faction."

"Maybe the reason for Fang Yuan's fast cultivation speed is because of Chi faction pouring resources to him. Fang Yuan is Fang Zheng's older brother, Elder Chi Lian's actions have a very profound meaning."

Some elders discussed whereas some elders' mind were flipping over.

"It turns out this Fang Yuan wasn't a junior with no one to guide his steps, he has the help from Chi faction. We need to be cautious towards him in the future."

"Fortunately, we didn't interfere and jump into the fight between Fang Yuan and Yao Ji."

"Yao Ji is in a dangerous predicament, she wanted to deal with an elder who didn't have any backing, but she could never have had expected that his background was so solid. It's actually the Chi faction!"

Gu Yue Yao Ji's face was very pale. When she had heard Gu Yue Chi Lian confirming it, she took a step back in shock, her whole body trembling faintly.Opposing a lone elder compared to an elder backed by the Chi faction, these were two utterly different concepts!

Chapter 154: Vomit blood out of anger

Gu Yue Mo Chen's heart was very heavy.He had planned to recruit Fang Yuan, but stopped himself due to Fang Yuan's aptitude.

But now his old rival Gu Yue Chi Lian actually got affiliated with Fang Yuan already. All the evidence points to Chi Lian providing support for Fang Yuan since over a year ago.Now, his investment had received such a great reward, and the Chi faction has a new clan elder. How can his heart not be heavy?

Except, other than solemness, Mo Chen was also confused.

He was Gu Yue Chi Lian's old rival, having competed since they were young. He had such a good understanding of his rival that he even knew what colour of underwear his rival liked to wear.

Logically speaking, Gu Yue Chi Lian would've started gloating by now, throwing mocking and smug glances towards Mo Chen. But right now, his face was grim like he had suffered an injustice.

This was too strange!

Just what had transpired between him and Fang Yuan? What sort of agreement did they reach?Gu Yue Mo Chen could not get an answer.

"This Fang Yuan, his guts are greater than the heavens, to think he would actually threaten me!" Gu Yue Chi Lian's heart was filled with anger and perplexity.

Last night, Fang Yuan had secretly approached him and used the matter of 'Gu Yue Chi Cheng's fake aptitude' to threaten him.

Heavens!

How did this important secret that only he, Gu Yue Chi Lian and his grandson Chi Cheng knew about, come to the knowledge of this outsider Fang Yuan?!

Gu Yue Chi Cheng was only a C grade talent, but for the sake of the Chi faction's benefits, Chi Lian had to take a risk and show a facade of Chi Cheng being B grade.

If this matter was exposed, its impact towards the Chi faction would be unforeseen. The Chi faction family head's integrity would be questioned for his cheating personally, and this would ruin his reputation completely. More importantly, the Chi faction inheritor is only a C grade, this means that the Chi faction would have no political outlook anymore. Who would be dumb enough to rely on this type of faction?

Fang Yuan knowing this secret, was equivalent to grasping the fatal weakness of the Chi faction.When Fang Yuan threatened him, Gu Yue Chi Lian almost couldn't control himself from attacking and eliminating this threat on the spot!

But he forcefully stopped himself, as he did not know who else got ahold of this secret, and whether Fang Yuan told anyone or left behind any paper evidence at some secret location."Pacify him first, understand the situation, then eliminate him! I cannot leave this threat hanging!" That was his thought at the time.

But soon after that, Fang Yuan displayed his Rank three cultivation.

Chi Lian, while shell-shocked, could only change his plan to cooperation.

Rank three is a clan elder, and if he murdered a clan elder, this matter would just be as serious as cheating.

Furthermore, fighting against a Rank three Gu Master would take some time, and the commotion it creates is even harder to deal with.Falling out with Fang Yuan would not have any benefits for the Chi faction—in fact the risk was even greater.

"Although Fang Yuan has a hold on me, a shared secret is also a form of collaboration." Finally, Chi Lian could only convince himself to comfort his heart. Fang Yuan's threat was so sudden, so he could not tell how many safety nets Fang Yuan had in place, thus he could only go along with it.

But now, Fang Yuan fearlessly implicated him, letting him attract the attention in Fang Yuan's place, it was really throwing him under the bus!

However, even if Gu Yue Chi Lian knew this, what could he do?This time, Fang Yuan slowly spoke again, "Gu Yue Yao Ji, I know your heart is in a mess now. Yes, that B grade talent granddaughter of yours is dead, and without a proper corpse, your medicine faction is now without an inheritor. But a C grade talent like myself advanced to Rank three instead, so you feel anxious and indignant, thus your fury is directed at me. I understand that."

"What did you say?!" Gu Yue Yao Ji stared widely, uncontrollable anger rising, "You little wretch, I'm telling you Yao Le is not dead."

Fang Yuan laughed loudly, shrugging nonchalantly, "Her matter of life or death, what does it have to do with me? Yao Ji, you don't have to emphasize that."

"But!" He suddenly twisted, "Gu Yue Yao Ji, in order to find your granddaughter, you assembled search parties and wasted much human and material resources. That concerns me, the clan elders here, and even the clan leader. Gu Yue Yao Ji, letting you lead the medicine hall, that is because of our trust. But what have you done? You dispatched the medicine hall's healing Gu Masters out to search for your granddaughter, leaving those injured and crippled Gu Masters in distress. You are too selfish! Yao Le's sacrifice, it is indeed the clan's loss. But you further worsened our loss, you are not fit to be our medicine hall clan elder at all!!"

Fang Yuan's words hit the nail on the head, tearing at Yao Ji's weakness, her pain.

But what he said, was very true.Upon hearing Fang Yuan's words, many clan elders started frowning secretly.

Whose faction did not have injuries? Gu Yue Yao Ji's actions were indeed overboard, dispatching Gu Masters on her own and not attending to the urgent business at hand, but instead searching for her granddaughter.

"You... you!" Gu Yue Yao Ji was so angry her body was trembling, her finger pointing to Fang Yuan, unable to say another word. Her eyes were like blowing fire, having a strong urge to strangle this bastard Fang Yuan on the spot.

Fang Yuan's gaze was cold and indifferent, staring at her with no fear.

He was returning the favour to her. Gu Yue Yao Ji's earlier words were all righteous and caused the many clan elders to get curious about Fang Yuan's secret to advancing, causing a huge commotion. Fang Yuan's words were the same, and with reason backing him, standing at the highest point of the clan rules, it caused the clan elders to subconsciously defend him.

To the clan elders, protecting the clan's rules were akin to protecting their own interests.

Gu Yue Yao Ji's actions these days did infringe on their interests!

"This Fang Yuan... bastard! Fucking bastard!" Gu Yue Yao Ji shuddered, not knowing that Gu Yue Chi Lian was also angered to the point of fuming.

Fang Yuan was offending Gu Yue Yao Ji to the limit, and her hatred towards him will also spill to the Chi faction since Fang Yuan was now 'a part of them'.

But the truth was, Chi faction is innocent!Was he, Gu Yue Chi Lian a fool? Why would he offend Gu Yue Yao Ji who is the most senior and has the greatest social network.

Gu Yue Chi Lian subconsciously shrunk his body, praying in his heart: May the other clan elders not direct the attention to himself. Fang Yuan doing this, is his own idea, it has nothing to do with the Chi faction!

But Fang Yuan's next sentence, broke this illusion of his to smithereens.

He turned around and reported to the clan leader Gu Yue Bo, "Clan leader, I highly doubt Gu Yue Yao Ji's ability to continue leading the medicine hall. I suggest, we temporarily revoke her title of medicine hall clan elder and hold a thorough assessment of her. Each one of the clan's healing Gu Masters are precious to us. We cannot let her waste them like this. Otherwise, the ones that suffer the most are the brave Gu Masters that fight using their lives for our precious clan!"

Pausing momentarily, he continued, "This suggestion of mine, elder Chi Lian is also very supportive of."

"What?!" Gu Yue Yao Ji's iris shrunk as her face changed colours.

"What?!" The clan elders were all taken aback. To hear of Gu Yue Chi Lian's forthright attitude like this, does it mean that he was unhappy with Yao Ji from long ago and has been lusting after the huge benefits in her possessions, wanting to get a piece of the pie?

"WHAT?!" As the person in question, Gu Yue Chi Lian nearly jumped from his seat.

How could he not be angry?He was going to go crazy from Fang Yuan's antics!

This Fang Yuan had not only offended Gu Yue Yao Ji, he even dragged him into the boat.

His original political intent towards the medicine faction was closeness and cooperation. But now, his efforts were all thwarted by a single sentence from Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan was framing and harming him. In front of the person himself, framing, harming, and spreading false rumors!But he, Gu Yue Chi Lian, the grand Chi faction family head, was held hostage by Fang Yuan, and had no way to fight back!!

"Oh, Elder Chi Lian, you support this?" Gu Yue Bo's gaze shone as he asked.

Gu Yue Chi Lian gritted his teeth, slowly getting up.He stiffened his neck, resisting the urge to look at Fang Yuan; he was afraid he could not control his rage.

At this point, he can do nothing to Fang Yuan, and can only carry on the show.

"Revoking Yao Ji's title, this is Fang Yuan's sole idea. With the threat of the wolf tide, suddenly changing people is not appropriate. However, I do agree that elder Yao Ji has deviated from the role of the healing Gu Masters due to her personal feelings. If these efforts were placed into the right areas, it would reduce our clan's loss to a great extent."

Saying so, his heart was bleeding.

He would definitely not follow through with what Fang Yuan said, as he had his own interests in mind. These words, he had already exerted the greatest effort to find a balance between Fang Yuan and Yao Ji.

But even so, after he finished speaking, he heard a thump.

He turned his head around and saw that Gu Yue Yao Ji had vomited blood out of her intense anger, and fell on her back.

It's over!"I've completely offended Yao Ji!" At this moment, Gu Yue Chi Lian felt like he had fallen into a chasm, his heart icy cold.

"Lord Yao Ji!""Someone, quickly diagnose her."

"She just lost consciousness, it's not an emergency. Lord Yao Ji had not rested at all for these three days and three nights, her body and mind is exhausted and needs to rest."

The hall was in a mess, but slowly quietened down.

Gu Yue Yao Ji was carried away by a stretcher.

She was already old, and had worried for so many days. With a weakened heart, now that she was triggered by both Fang Yuan and Chi Lian, adding on to her misery, it was no wonder that she fainted.

"Lord Yao Ji had led the medicine hall for so many years, she had worked hard for so long, she is truly tired. Letting her rest is also for her own good. Now that she is unconscious, the medicine hall cannot be without a leader. I advice that we let Fang Yuan take over," Gu Yue Chi Lian suddenly said.

This old man stood before his seat. Seeing Gu Yue Yao Ji being carried out, his eyes shone coldly.

Since he had already offended her, then why not go the entire way and continue the mistake! To prevent the medicine faction's revenge, he might as well suppress them entirely. This is someone in power, the resolve and wisdom of an expert in politics.

The hall fell into temporary silence.

Yao Le's death, Yao Ji's downfall, it showed that the medicine faction was on an imminent decline. The cruelty of politics is even more heartless than the wolf tide.

Fang Yuan was silent as well.

Letting him be the medicine hall clan elder, heh heh, Gu Yue Chi Lian was only saying it casually.

Letting a newly advanced young clan elder to hold such an important role. Maybe if the clan elders and clan leader were all retarded.

Gu Yue Chi Lian saying this intentionally, had deep meaning.

As expected, in the next moment, Gu Yue Bo declared, "The medicine hall's role shall temporarily be held by elder Chi Zhong. Fang Yuan's cultivation has indeed reached Rank three, thus according to the clan rules, he shall also assume the role of clan elder. Send out the news, and let the entire village rejoice."

Saying so, Gu Yue Bo stood up and left."Congratulations, congratulations..." After the clan leader left, the clan elders all walked towards Fang Yuan, cupping their fists with faces full of smiles.

Fang Yuan cupped his fists as well, replying with a warm smile.

Chapter 155: Borrow

"Congratulations, congratulations."

"Elder Fang Yuan is young and promising. You are definitely a role model for the young generation!"

"Haha, we truly anticipate Elder Fang Yuan's brilliance as we work together from now on."

The group of elders surrounded Fang Yuan and spoke customary words.

The academy elder stood at the edge of the crowd, his expression complicated as he looked at Fang Yuan.

He had never expected Fang Yuan to become an elder. In his class, he had been the most optimistic of Fang Zheng, and then Chi Cheng and Mo Bei.

But to think that the one who was the first to achieve success, was actually Fang Yuan!

"How could these little achievements of mine be compared to the elders? I still need to thank the clan's teachings for today's achievements. Academy elder, I have always engraved your words in my heart," Fang Yuan had a warm smile on, and he spoke modestly and prudently.

The academy elder hadn't expected this punk to take the initiative to greet him.

He was blank for a moment before a gratified expression appeared in his face, "Looks like you have matured a lot in these years, Elder Fang Yuan. Keep up the good work, I am proud of your achievements. The clan needs new blood like you."

Fang Yuan sincerely thanked the academy elder again and also replied to the other elders.

With his five hundred years of experience, putting on such an act was very easy.

He had a sense of propriety, his words were gentle and his attitude was humble, making all those who heard him feel like they were basking in a spring breeze.

Gu Yue Chi Lian was indifferent at this scene, but the more he observed, the more frightened he became. This Fang Yuan knew how to deal with the situation adequately, and every sentence and word were as if spoken by a veteran. Was he really just in his teens? Could he be a born politician?

The academy elder was astonished too. He thought of the academy times; Fang Yuan was so rebellious, even exploiting his own classmates. He had countless headaches due to this, but the current Fang Yuan seemed to have completely changed.

On the contrary, Gu Yue Mo Chen wasn't baffled by Fang Yuan's behaviour. After all, he already had a taste of Fang Yuan's schemes.

Right now, as he looked at Fang Yuan's cultured and gentle behaviour, becoming a focal point of the crowd, he kept on sighing that Gu Yue Chi Lian had made a great move.

The exchanges continued on for some time. But, regardless of what thoughts the elders had, the ones present there couldn't help but look at Fang Yuan in a new light. They continuously sighed that rumors were really unreliable!

In the end, Fang Yuan tactfully rejected some of the elders' invitations and left the clan head pavillion with a smile together with Gu Yue Chi Lian.

"Hmph, are you satisfied now? After pulling down Gu Yue Yao Ji, you even dragged my Chi faction into hot water!" When they reached the study room, Chi Lian couldn't pretend anymore, and the smile on his face was replaced by fury.

Fang Yuan was sitting in front of him and leisurely smiled, "You need to thank me for this. Gu Yue Yao Ji is down, this is a great benefit to your Chi faction."

Gu Yue Chi Lian's gaze flashed, "Hmph, young man, your thoughts are too simple. Chi Zhong is my Chi faction's member but his wife is of Yao faction. The clan head appointed him as the temporary medicine hall elder precisely because he wants to balance out the internal strife between my Chi and Yao faction. You, how did you find out about Chi Cheng's matter?"

At the end, Gu Yue Chi Lian suddenly asked this.

He closely watched Fang Yuan with a gaze like that of an eagle's.

Fang Yuan unconcernedly shrugged his shoulders and said, "Old man, I don't have much primeval stones on me left, give me three thousand primeval stones."

Bang.

Gu Yue Chi Lian fiercely slammed the table; he lowered his voice and roared, "Fang Yuan! Don't even think that you can extort my Chi faction just by knowing that secret. I am old and don't have long to live, so at worst I will just give up my life! Hmph, I can accept cooperating, but I will absolutely not receive any threats!"

"I won't allow what happened today to happen again! If you recklessly make enemies and pull my Chi faction into your mess, you will regret it! You really think that secret can destroy my whole Chi faction? Heh, don't be so naive."

Fang Yuan didn't reply, his gaze was ghostly as he let Gu Yue Chi Lian continue to berate him.

When Gu Yue Chi Lian had slammed the table, his aura was astonishing like that of a tiger, but as he continued to speak, his aura started getting weaker and weaker and in the end, he appeared to be in deficiency of energy, showing a lack of confidence.

Only when he no longer spoke did Fang Yuan leisurely smile and say, "Old man, don't get so angry. I am indeed short of money recently, and I am not asking these three thousand primeval stones for free, I am just borrowing them. I can even sign the receipt for loan."

Gu Yue Chi Lian snorted, he spoke slowly, "You won't lack primeval stones, you have just become an elder and don't know the preferential treatment the clan gives to the elders. As long as you are an elder, you will receive a hundred primeval stones every week. This is the amount you receive in ordinary times, but as this is the time of the wolf tide, you will receive three hundred primeval stones as allowance."

"Not only that, you can also freely take a Rank three Gu worm. Similarly, the clan's Rank one to Rank three recipes will be opened to you. You can choose any recipe that you like and refine your Rank three Gu worm. There are also other privileges, for example: Ordinary Gu Masters can only marry one wife, but an elder can have one wife and two concubines."

"So that's it." Fang Yuan knew this of course, but he pretended it was the first time he heard it.

"But even if it is so, I still want to borrow three thousand primeval stones. You also know that I just advanced to Rank three. Refining a Rank three Gu worm consumes a great amount of primeval stones," Fang Yuan 'sincerely' said.

Gu Yue Chi Lian reflected on this.

He pondered, "With Fang Yuan's identity as an elder, he wouldn't go so far as to not pay his debt. Does he not want his reputation? If in case, he dies in the wolf tide, then wouldn't my three thousand primeval stones go to waste? Wait, won't it be better if he dies? We can continue to hide the matter regarding Chi Cheng's aptitude. But how did he learn this secret? Is there still anyone else who knows about it? I had better lend the money to him first and lower his guard, then I can probe his secret."

As he thought up to this point, Gu Yue Chi Lian didn't insist anymore and immediately took out a brush and paper.

Fang Yuan wrote the receipt for loan and signed with his fingerprint.

Gu Yue Chi Lian called his butler and gave some orders. Soon, several money bags full of primeval stones were brought over.

Fang Yuan weighed each money bag and didn't find any problems.

He truly needed these primeval stones.

He had spent almost all his savings in refining the Man-beast Life Burial Gu. These three thousand primeval stones could be considered a timely assistance.

He had just advanced to Rank three. He needed to refine a Rank three Gu worm. Only then could he truly possess the battle and survival ability of a Rank three Gu Master.

He already had a rough plan regarding this. Three thousand primeval stones might not be enough. However, it wasn't urgent, and the Chi faction would be his great money farm.

The primeval stones he borrowed this time was only the start. If it happened once, it will happen twice; first time is difficult, but subsequently gets easier.

As for paying the debt, hehe....

Fang Yuan wasn't in a hurry to leave after getting these primeval stones, but instead smiled, "I still want to borrow something."

"Don't go overboard." Gu Yue Chi Lian was grim, but in the end, he still said, "Speak, what is it?"

"Cleansing Water Gu," Fang Yuan's eyes narrowed as he said candidly.

There was a Cleansing Water Gu on sale previously in the caravan, and if you consider who was most likely to purchase this Gu, it would be Gu Yue Chi Lian.

He used his own primeval essence to nurture his grandson's aperture and advance his cultivation. This led to there being mixed auras in the aperture, which needed to be purified by the Cleansing Water Gu.

"That is impossible!" Gu Yue Chi Lian firmly refused.

He indeed bought that Cleansing Water Gu, but he prepared this Gu for his grandson Gu Yue Chi Cheng. If he wanted to buy it again, he could only rely on fate.

"Don't refuse me so fast." Fang Yuan laughed, "I believe you—Lord Gu Yue Chi Lian, the head of Chi faction—know which is more important, a Cleansing Water Gu or Chi faction's reputation."

Gu Yue Chi Lian's face darkened completely, the aura around him turning cold as he fiercely looked at Fang Yuan, gnashing his teeth, "Fang Yuan, know what you are trying to do. You are blackmailing me, blackmailing the head of the grand Chi faction!"

"No, no, this is not blackmail, it is a discussion. I am only borrowing the Cleansing Water Gu and will return you a new one in the future. I can sign the receipt of loan for this too," Fang Yuan chuckled. However, his tone was firm and it showed his determined will.

"Don't even imagine it!" Chi Lian's attitude was also firm.

...

After an hour, Fang Yuan walked out of the Chi family manor with three thousand primeval stones and a Cleansing Water Gu.

And Gu Yue Chi Lian was sitting in the study room, looking at the two receipts—written by Fang Yuan—on the table. The indignance in his heart was like a surging river, overflowing endlessly.

Fang Yuan had a hold on Chi faction which put Chi Lian in an extremely passive situation, thus his victory was reasonable.

Three days later.

Fang Yuan sat cross-legged on the bed, white light shining upon his face.

A white ball of light was floating in mid-air—the fusion process had reached its end stage.

Fang Yuan used his consciousness to maintain the ball of light while throwing primeval stones into it.

The ball of light suddenly faded away and a whole new Gu worm flew into Fang Yuan's palm.

Its appearance was like a big ladybug. Its semi-circular milky white carapace was decorated with dark spots.

It was quite big, about the size of an adult's fist.

Rank three Sky Canopy Gu!

"I've finally succeeded." Fang Yuan satisfiedly nodded his head, this was his second time trying this fusion.

The Sky Canopy Gu was refined from the fusion of Rank two White Jade Gu and an aqua defense Gu.

In the first try, Fang Yuan used the Water Shield Gu and White Jade Gu. But the fusion ended up a failure, resulting in the death of the Water Shield Gu.

The aqua defense Gu he used this time had been exchanged with his battle merits.

However, this Sky Canopy Gu wasn't Fang Yuan's first Rank three Gu worm. His first Rank three Gu worm was directly obtained from the clan.

After advancing to Rank three and becoming an elder, the clan would bestow them with a Rank three Gu worm.

Fang Yuan used this chance to pick a Thunderwings Gu.

This Gu was gotten as spoils of war after the elders had killed a frenzy lightning wolf. Its ability was to materialize a pair of thunder wings and give Gu Masters the ability to fly for a short duration.

With the Thunderwings Gu to assist with movements, Fang Yuan's final combat shortcoming was fixed.

Chapter 156: Digital Shade Recipe, Flower Wine mystery

"Lord Fang Yuan, this way towards the secret room, please enter." In the dark eerie tunnel, a Rank two old Gu Master walked in front, leading the way for Fang Yuan.

The secret room that held all the Gu worm combination recipes of the clan, was not far ahead.Fang Yuan advanced to Rank three, thus his status had a 180 degree change. All the fusion recipes kept in the clan—as long as they were not Rank four or five recipes, he had the authority to look through.

If it was a Rank one or two Gu Master, to look through the recipes, they would need to pay primeval stones or exchange using merit points.This secret room was in the basement of the village, at a very hidden location. Even if the village was eradicated, this secret room would still remain.

Back then, the Gu Yue clan's creator, the first generation clan leader, found a primeval essence spring inside this underground cave, thus deciding to build his village here.

Through the generations of development and growth by the clan leaders, Gu Yue clan's underground cave had become the Gu Yue clan secret base.

Normally, ordinary Gu Masters did not have the rights to appear at this location. Only clan elders, the clan leader, and the Dark Hall's Gu Masters in charge of protecting the place had such authority.Many Gu Masters had only been there once in their lives.

That is during the awakening ceremony, where the youngsters would come to the primeval spring sea, hoping to awaken their aperture.

Other than this, unless there is a special reason, entry to this underground cave is prohibited for all people. Even the Gu Master guarding the place is picked after careful consideration.

After all, the primeval spring in this underground cave is the entire foundation of the Gu Yue village. From the spring center, large amounts of primeval stones are produced, and that sustains the Gu Master cultivation of the entire clan.

In the tunnel, two sets of footsteps could be heard.

Far away, the sound of river water flowing sounded—that is the underground river in the cave.

A moment later, the Gu Master leading the way brought Fang Yuan to a rock door.

He patted his belly, and a Gu worm flew out of his aperture. As sparks flied, it knocked onto the rock door.The rock door's surface rippled, like a rock thrown into the water. Soon after, the rock wall blinked and gradually faded away, showing the secret room behind.

The secret room's size was rather small, being only 666 2⁄3 m2. Every few steps, there would be a rock table half the height of a person. Tens of rock tables had a white jade plate on them, and on the plate there was a Gu worm silently resting.

These Gu worms had all sorts of colours, being around the size of a fist; they had very similar appearances, like silkworms. On its head, there were two compound eyes like bees or dragonflies, it was colourful and looked like shiny glass. However the surface was not soft, but covered in a layer of insect shell, and the shell even had golden lustre.

"Lord Fang Yuan, this is your first time to the secret room, so let me explain. These are Rank two Digital Shade Gu, all have recipes recorded in them. In the green Digital Shade Gu worms, almost all the Rank one recipes can be found in them. As for the red-black coloured Gu, there are Rank two recipes. White contains the Rank three recipes, and orange has the Rank four recipes. As for Rank five, it is contained in the most central purple Digital Shade Gu worms."

Beside him, the old Gu Master introduced appropriately.Digital Shade Gu was a recording type of Gu worm. Just one step further in advancement, and it would be the Rank three Photo-audio Gu.

After the Photo-audio Gu is refined, it not only can store a recording, but can also record the voices as well. In the rock crack secret cave, the Flower Wine Monk used a Photo-audio Gu to inform Fang Yuan of the inheritance details.

But to record down recipes, voices are not necessary, thus the Digital Shade Gu is enough.

Fusion recipes, these were very precious. Using normal bamboo paper to record them, if they were stolen, not only can they refine the Gu Yue clan's specialty Gu worms, it is also a huge leak of the clan's information.

Knowing the enemy leads to easier battles, and experienced Gu Masters can learn about the strengths and weaknesses of a Gu worm from the refinement recipe.

Once it is leaked, towards a clan the loss would be severe. In future when they battle, the Gu Masters from that clan may also be disadvantaged in Gu worms.

Thus, recipes were strictly controlled, and as classified by ranks, stored appropriately.Digital Shade Gu was easier to refine and had a low cost, thus it was a common method to contain recipes.

"Lord Fang Yuan, these Digital Shade Gu all belong to the Secret Hall clan elder. But it would not impede you from using primeval essence and browsing through. Just that with your current identity, you cannot browse the Rank four and five recipes. There's also two more things—the secret room is the clan's red zone, your every action here is observed fully in secret. Everyday, you can only stay here for fifteen minutes. Once the time is up, you must leave," the Gu Master continued speaking.

"Mm, I understand." Fang Yuan nodded.

"Lord Fang Yuan, this subordinate has no authority to enter, thus I will wait at the door. Once the time is up, I will bring you out," the old man bowed.

Fang Yuan walked into the secret room. Once he entered, the rock door turned from virtual to solid, trapping him in the room alone.Walking in the secret room, it was peaceful. The echoes of his footsteps could be heard bouncing off the walls as the surrounding walls had Water Light Gu in them.

Their bodies emitted a light, wavering like water, interchanging between light and shadow, with layers after layers shining indefinitely.

Fang Yuan took a red-black coloured Gu worm and injected his white silver primeval essence inside. Immediately two beams of light shot out from the Digital Shade Gu's compound eyes.

He raised the Gu up, and pointed the eyes at the white jade plate on the table.

Two beams of light hit the white jade plate, and after some fluctuations, words started to appear.This was the recipe on how to refine the Moonscar Gu.

First it listed the Moonscar Gu's strengths, which was the increase in attack distance, twice of the Moonlight Gu. The weakness was the subpar attack.

Next was the refinement recipe—Moonscar Gu is refined from fusing the Moonlight Gu and Scar Rock Gu.Next is the important points for refining this Gu, the crux was—if during the refinement, some jade rock is added in, or done during a night when there is abundant moonlight and exposed to it, there would be a higher chance of success.

Lastly, it is the experiences of the Gu Masters who had attempted to fuse this Gu. This had the greatest content, almost up to ten thousand words.

Fang Yuan took a look and memorised some things to heart.

It was after all countless people's experiments and tries, and the experienced gathered from numerous attempts. Some information, even Fang Yuan did not know.

After all, Moonlight Gu is a unique Gu to the Gu Yue clan. In his previous life, he had never become a clan elder or came here to browse the recipes.

Time was limited, so Fang Yuan quickly took a look and placed the Digital Shade Gu back to its spot, then picked up a white coloured Gu to observe.

In the white Digital Shade Gu, there was the Rank three fusion recipes.Most of the recipes did not suit Fang Yuan, as they needed Gu worms like Moonwhirl or Moonscar Gu as the base.

Fang Yuan did not look through closely; to save time, he skimmed through.

He first used the Moonlight Gu to fuse with the Little Light Gu to form Moonglow Gu. On that basis, there was only three refinement recipes worth using.

First was the Rank three Golden moon, with the same ten steps of shooting distance, but the attack power is increased once again. Once shot out, the golden coloured crescent moon would nearly be half a man tall, and had a strong imposing aura.

Second was the Frost Moon Gu. The moonblade becomes eerie white and icy, having an element of ice to it. Whoever it hurts will be invaded by the coldness, moving slowly.

The third is the Illusory Moon Gu. This Gu was more unique—it is not used to attack, but once activated, it can allow the Gu Master to create a shadow clone to attract attacks and confuse the enemy.

Especially when this Illusory moon Gu, once refined, can be used as the basis for the Rank four Moonshadow Gu."Moonshadow Gu can be implanted into a Gu Master's aperture and suppress them from using primeval essence." In the information on the Illusory Moon Gu, there was only some vaguely explained information about the Moonshadow Gu, as reference.

"Moonshadow Gu... isn't that the Gu worm used by the fourth generation clan leader to sneak an attack on the Flower Wine Monk?" Fang Yuan seeing this, frowned deeply.In this world, there are countless Gu worms, and even with his five hundred years of experience, he only knew less than 0.001% of all the Gu worms in this world.

He originally had a rough idea of the Moonshadow Gu, but now that he knew the Gu worm's effect, suspicion rose in his heart.

Moonshadow Gu had a unique use. It was able to suppress 30% of the primeval essence in a Rank four Gu Master's aperture, 15% of a Rank five, and 60% of a Rank three Gu Master. That means, with a C grade talent like Fang Yuan, only having 40~50%, if they were hit by this Moonshadow Gu, they would be unable to deploy a single ounce of primeval essence, losing all their battle strength and were as good as crippled.

Of course, if it were Fang Yuan, if the Moonshadow Gu was used on him, it would be 'throwing a meatbun at the dog'—what's gone can never come back.

That is because once the Moonshadow Gu enters his aperture, the Spring Autumn Cicada will demonstrate its dominance, and under its aura, the Moonshadow Gu would be instantly refined by him, and become his.

What puzzled Fang Yuan, was not the Moonshadow Gu's effect, but the Flower Wine Monk.

"I remember that on the shadow wall, the Flower Wine Monk was bathed in blood, full of injuries. Firstly, his battle with the fourth generation clan leader and elders only gave him mild injuries. I thought those severe injuries were caused by this Moonshadow Gu, but to think that this Moonshadow Gu is only used to suppress primeval essence, crippling the Gu Master. Then where did the Flower Wine Monk get his severe injuries from?"

Fang Yuan's thoughts were meticulous, thus becoming more suspicious. Back then, when the Flower Wine Monk lost to the clan elders and escaped, what actually happened?

Moonshadow Gu was not the cause of his death. So then, what was?

At once, the originally clear Flower Wine Monk inheritance, became a complete mystery to Fang Yuan again.

"Lord Fang Yuan, it has been fifteen minutes, I believe you have had some gains. No matter what, please come again tomorrow." At this point, the door turned into an astral state again, as the old Gu Master stood outside and said respectfully.

"Okay." Fang Yuan's gaze shone as he put down the Digital Shadow Gu, leaving the secret room.

Regardless of whether it is the Golden moon, Frost moon, or Illusory moon, these refinement recipes were not what he wanted. That is because they all consumed large amounts of moon orchid flower petals.

Moon orchid flower petals were hard to store, only able to live for a few days. In Fang Yuan's plans, he wanted to leave the Gu Yue clan and roam the world. If he refined these Gu, without any food they would die in half a year. He might as well not refine them.

However, there were still Rank three recipes that he did not manage to see.

"I'll come again tomorrow, I guess." Such a thought flashed across his mind.

Chapter 157: Blood Moon Gu

Second day, secret room.

On the shiny white jade plate, there was a recipe —

Blood Moon Gu.

Using Rank two Moonglow Gu and Blood Essence Gu to combine and form the Rank three Gu worm.

Once activated, the moonblade glows blood red, with the size of a face. If one gets injured by it, there would be a continuous bleeding effect.

"That's it." Fang Yuan's gaze swept through the information and memorised this recipe at heart. Then he closed his eyes and recited again, and opened his eyes to check. After several times, he checked that he had completely memorised this recipe in his heart, with no margin of error.

Compared to the Golden Moon, Frost Moon and Illusionary Moon Gu—the three classics, this Blood Moon Gu was much more unorthodox.

The former three's refinement recipes had almost a hundred thousand words of refinement experience. But this Blood Moon Gu barely had a few thousand.It can be seen that through history, Gu Masters who chose this Blood Moon Gu were rare.

The Blood Moon Gu's attacking capability was average. It only had a ten meter range, and even the bleeding effect after attacking isn't optimal.

Gu Masters from Rank one to five had limited primeval essence, and could not sustain for a long battle to decide the victor. A bleeding effect, in the real battlefield, was only a small problem. Against a Gu Master experienced in healing, they could even have the ability to counter this.

Furthermore, the Blood Moon Gu had the biggest flaw.

Every few days of the month, it would ooze fresh blood out. The blood would flow uncontrollably and during this period, its attack power would be reduced to a third of the original.

But it had the greatest advantage that Fang Yuan liked.

It was easy to feed.Much easier than the Golden Moon, Frost Moon and Illusionary Moon.

The food it needed was no longer moon orchid flower petals, but fresh blood.

Although the blood required was a lot, it was not limited to one type. In the Western Desert it might be a problem, but the Southern Border had all sorts of wild beasts in its forested and mountainous areas.

Killing them would allow easy extraction of blood. To the Blood Moon Gu, its food was all over the Southern Border, everywhere.

"Next, all I have to do is refine this Blood Moon Gu." Fang Yuan decided in his heart.

The refinement steps, as well as things to take note of, were all memorised by him. In his hand, there was already the Moonglow Gu, but the Blood Essence Gu was slightly harder to get a hold of.

The Blood Essence Gu was precious, being able to replenish the blood of a Gu Master. Those Gu Masters with it were always energetic and even if they got injured and lost a lot of blood, they could replenish it easily. Thus, their survivability in battle was much higher than others.Xiong Jiang once desired a Blood Essence Gu badly.

If the Blood Essence Gu was paired up with the Roaming Zombie Gu, it would greatly reduce the side effects. It would allow him to be a zombie for a longer period without any worries for backlashes.He was already a well to do Rank two Gu Master, and had a rather high position, but until he died, he did not get his wish fulfilled.

In the secret room, Fang Yuan looked at the Digital Shade Gu on the rock tables again.

There was still ample time today. Out of the fifteen minutes, he only used five minutes, so there was still ten minutes left.

The yellow Digital Shade Gu recorded the Rank four recipes. The purple Digital Shade Gu recorded Rank five recipes.

The owner of these Digital Shade Gu had always been the generations of each Secret Hall clan elder. But the one responsible for feeding them, is the clan.Gu worms can be borrowed, as long as the will on the Gu worms concedes to it.

The will in the Digital Shade Gu is one with the Secret Hall clan elder. Fang Yuan as a newly advanced clan elder, is recognised by the Secret Hall clan elder thus he can freely use a portion of the Digital Shade Gu.

But the Secret Hall clan elder does not think Fang Yuan has the authority to browse the Rank four and five recipes, thus the yellow and purple Digital Shade Gu, even if he used primeval essence, there would not be any reaction.The truth is, even if it's a wild natural Gu worm, it is possible to gain their recognition as well.

Those beast kings are like this, thus able to borrow the Gu worm's ability. Among humans, such situations occur as well, like the story of the Rank five River Swallowing Toad and Jiang Fan.

Of course, Fang Yuan could rely on the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura to refine these Gu worms and obtain the recipes, that was definitely possible.

But the consequences of doing that, is something Fang Yuan cannot handle yet. The benefits involved is not sufficient for him to act either.

"Actually the most precious recipe is not these Rank four or five recipes, but how to reverse engineer a Moonlight Gu. This Gu originated from the first generation clan leader, and on that basis, after hundreds of years, developed into such a scale and structure," Fang Yuan thought.

Gu fusion is to turn low ranking Gu worms into higher ranking ones, while reverse fusion is to turn the high ranking Gu worms, back to their lower forms.

Between rising and falling, because of different processes, what is obtained can be entirely different Gu worms.The Moonlight Gu is not a natural Gu worm, but something gotten from reverse fusion by the first generation clan leader.

The Gu worms in this world were mostly new species created by many Gu Masters on the basis of natural Gu worms. Thus, even with Fang Yuan's five hundred years of experience, he still had limited knowledge of the entire Gu worm ecology.

And for the clan, they would definitely have one or a few unique Gu worms. These Gu worms were not the rare natural species, but a new species created through reverse fusion.On this basis, Gu Masters can develop a strength unique to their clan.

Gu Yue clan's Moonlight Gu, Xiong clan's Bear Strength Gu, Bai clan's Stream Gu, these were all the same.

If they used a common and well-known Gu worm, they would be easy to deal with, and easily targeted.A clan's foundation lies in the primeval spring, as it can produce primeval stones. Next is a unique Gu worm that can prevent one's strength from being completely deciphered. Lastly it is bloodline, bloodline and kinship are an important chain that ties a clan together.

Thus, don't look down on the Rank one Moonlight Gu—the worth of its reverse fusion recipe is far greater than Rank four or five recipes.The recipe to reverse fuse the Moonlight Gu is normally kept by the clan leader. Other than the clan leader, the most loyal clan elder of that generation would also know the recipe's secret. At the same time, the Moonlight Gu recipe's Digital Shade Gu is also hidden appropriately.

Fang Yuan could obviously not obtain the recipe from this secret room.

"This recipe's value is very high, thus if I can obtain it before I leave, that would naturally be the best. But I do not have to force it." Fang Yuan was very plain about this matter.

For starters, he was not planning to create an organisation or force. The Moonlight Gu's recipe to him, was not a necessity.

"However, the Blood Moon Gu and the other Rank three recipes are what I need."

Although Fang Yuan was Rank three now and had white silver primeval essence, not all his Gu worms were Rank three, thus he could not display the true fighting power of a Rank three Gu Master.

"I have the Thunderwings Gu and Sky Canopy Gu, so if I manage to refine the Blood Moon Gu, I will have three Rank three Gu worms. But that is nowhere near enough."

Ordinary Gu Masters can rely on the clan. With the cooperation of their clansmen, as well as ample resources, they only needed three to four Gu worms.

But Fang Yuan wanted to roam the Southern Border and leave his homeland, thus he needed at least six Gu worms to deal with all situations.

With his experience, the six Gu worms had to be attack, defense, healing, storage, recon and movement—six attributes to provide him ample support.

For attack, the Blood Moon Gu barely qualifies. For defense he has the Sky Canopy Gu. Movement wise, even though the Thunderwings Gu uses a lot of primeval essence, it can allow temporary flight and is very powerful.

For healing, the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass is slightly weak. It is afterall a Rank two Gu, and even the advancement option is not satisfactory to Fang Yuan.The Rank two Nine Leaf Vitality Grass did not have outstanding healing abilities. Its only advantage was creating the Rank one vitality leaves and from selling that, Fang Yuan can get a continuous supply of primeval stones, akin to a money tree.

But thereafter, Fang Yuan is going to travel to places where there are no inhabitants, so even if he creates the vitality leaves, no Gu Masters would buy them using primeval stones.

For recon, Earth Communication Ear Grass had a huge range, so even as a Rank two, it was still usable.

For storage, Fang Yuan had no such Gu. This was however, the Gu of the utmost importance. This is because after he starts travelling alone, the supplies are the most important, it can single-handedly become the basis of the other five categories.

Storing food to feed the Gu worms, his own food, and storing primeval stones.

Without primeval stones, Gu Master lose the power to cultivate.

On this matter, Fang Yuan had no progress. Before he obtains a satisfactory storage-type Gu worm, he will not leave the village.

"Gu worms for storage, the first condition is a wide utility, able to store food and primeval stones. Next, they have to be easy to feed, and lastly, it is best if they have the ability to prolong the expiry date of the items stored. But even in the resource board of the three clans, there is no Gu worm that I like. It seems I can only make use of the Chi faction and squeeze out the last of their savings."

Once fifteen minutes was up, Fang Yuan walked out of the tunnel as he continued to ponder.

"Lord Fang Yuan, hello." A middle-aged Gu Master stood outside, specifically waiting for Fang Yuan.

"You are?"

The person smiled, "I am Gu Yue Chi Zhong, the current acting medicine hall clan elder."

"So that's him," Fang Yuan realized, starting a close inspection of this person.

Gu Yue Chi Zhong had a proper appearance with a squarish face, and he showed an aura of stability. Similar to Fang Yuan, he was also a clan elder, but his cultivation was Rank three middle stage.

After Fang Yuan caused Gu Yue Yao Ji to faint, Gu Yue Chi Zhong had been ordered to temporarily lead the medicine hall, and his wife was an important member of the medicine faction, thus this was Gu Yue Bo's political approach to balance the two faction's rivalry.

But no matter what, Gu Yue Chi Zhong still managed to ascend to this role.

"This is three hundred primeval stones, the payout to the clan elders for this week. I know that you are here, thus I brought this over as well. I hope you do not mind me taking matters into my own hands," Gu Yue Chi Zhong said, handing a money bag to Fang Yuan.

"This man..." Fang Yuan squinted, taking the bag.

The clan elders' payout needed to be collected by the clan elder themselves. But Gu Yue Chi Zhong could collect it for him, so in some ways, this was hinting to Fang Yuan his status in the clan as well as his social network.

But this hint was also well-timed, as it showed a sign of goodwill, and was not aggressive.

"To speak the truth, I took the initiative to find Lord Fang Yuan this time, because I have a matter to ask of you."

Soon after, he went straight to the topic and mentioned his intention.

"Oh, you want me to turn in the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass?" Fang Yuan showed a deep profound expression.

Chapter 158: Times have changed

Gu Yue Yao Ji had longed after Fang Yuan's Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, and thus, she exploited her authority to set a policy for the transfer of Nine Leaf Vitality Grass.

However, Fang Yuan advanced to Rank three and became an elder, responding with a powerful counterattack which caused Gu Yue Yao Ji to faint on the spot and let Gu Yue Chi Zhong take the stage.

A new officer in power has to display his authority, Gu Yue Chi Zhong took the initiative to find Fang Yuan and persuade him to hand over the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass.

"Handing over the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, it's not that it cannot be done," Fang Yuan said after muttering to himself for a bit.

There was a saying: what was true then isn't true now.

And now, the situation was different from before... Previously, Gu Yue Yao Ji wanted Fang Yuan to hand over the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass; that was an order, you had to hand it over whether you wanted to or not.

However, Fang Yuan was already an elder now and his status was equal to Gu Yue Yao Ji and others, and only lower than clan leader Gu Yue Bo. Thus, Gu Yue Chi Zhong asking Fang Yuan to hand over the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass was not an order, but instead it was a type of transaction with equal benefits.

Nine Leaf Vitality Grass was indeed very precious; with its ability to produce vitality leaves, it was by itself a micro-scale source of revenue and was in high demand. Fang Yuan was now raising many Gu worms and a large part of their food expenses was supported solely by it.

However, this world didn't have anything that couldn't be sold. It was only a matter of the profits being too small to move the heart.

Nine Leaf Vitality Grass was precious but if an appropriate price was provided, why couldn't it be sold?

Gu worms were only tools; methods to achieve one's desires and ambitions. So what if it was the Spring Autumn Cicada? As long as the circumstances were suitable, why couldn't one give it up to exchange for an even larger benefit?

If one wants to obtain benefits, they need to learn to give up first.

Naturally, Fang Yuan had the awareness of this and looked at Gu Yue Chi Zhong.

Gu Yue Chi Zhong understood and smiled, "If sire is willing to hand over the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, I will willingly compensate you with this command token."

Saying so, he took out a token.

This token's design was simple; it was triangular-shaped with smooth corners. There were words written on the front, piling up in a pyramid shape —'Prize Token'; similarly on the back said —'Reward Contributions'.

Prize Token, Reward Contributions.

"Sire is a newly promoted elder, and may not be clear on some matters. This Prize Token is issued to the Gu Masters who have made great contributions to the clan. Even among elders, few possess it. With this token, you can go down to the clan's underground Gu cave and choose any Gu worm you like. The underground cave holds many rare, precious Gu worms. Among the top ten Gu worms in the exchange board, four of them have been selected from the underground Gu cave," Gu Yue Chi Zhong explained.

Fang Yuan was instantly moved.

He wasn't surprised about this, for Gu Yue Clan had stood high for centuries and it was impossible for there not to be any trump cards and accumulations.

In fact, any long-established clan would also have secret places to store Gu like the Gu underground cave.

But to obtain such Gu worms, one needed to have made great contributions and also should be loyal to the clan.

Fang Yuan only recently became an elder, so he was very far away from having such qualifications.

"I want to leave the clan so I need a storage Gu. This token is a good choice, but..." Fang Yuan had some worries.

If he had to give up the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, so be it; it was a great help to Fang Yuan, but he wouldn't have any use for it in the future.

Its healing ability was not outstanding and one couldn't continuously use the vitality leaves to heal.

Fang Yuan's worry was that there might not necessarily be his ideal Gu worm in the Gu underground cave.

Gu Yue Chi Zhong had been observing Fang Yuan's expression and he misunderstood the latter's hesitation, saying, "The underground cave holds not only Rank three Gu worms but also Rank four. Elder Fang Yuan, you won't be at a disadvantage. But, if somehow you regret it, we could re-exchange them. That can be done after some time, secretly."

Fang Yuan raised his eyes, unable to refrain from looking at Chi Zhong again.

This is an outstanding guy. He sighed inwardly.

A new officer in power has to display his authority, Chi Zhong clearly understood why he was promoted; he had to strike a balance with not only the clan leader but also Chi and medicine faction. And at the same time, he needed to display his ability.

Fang Yuan transferring the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass over, held a special significance to him and he was willing to pay a high price for it.

"The world is vast, countless outstanding talents are everywhere! Under the wolf tide, the old timers are being sacrificed and newcomers are advancing. From a certain point, this can also be said to be a reform which allows the clan to preserve its vitality and stand high without falling," Fang Yuan thought inwardly.

Too many old timers will only create a rotting organization. Thus the process of elimination is the only way for an organization to continue working.

Gu Yue Chi Zhong was a representative of this.

The world was all about the survival of the fittest. A human body continues to live through the process of metabolism. A Gu Master shouldn't stick with the same Gu worms, only with change could they progress.

At this thought, Fang Yuan accepted the token from Gu Yue Chi Zhong and then handed over the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass. As he had transferred it himself, Chi Zhong could quickly refine the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass.

Only after keeping this grass Gu into his aperture did he let out a big sigh of relief.

He had his own ambitions and being able to act as the temporary medicine hall elder was an extremely important opportunity to him. If he could grasp this, he might even assume the official post instead of temporary.

However, he would have to make compromises with the three sides if he wanted to achieve this. After all, politics was an art of compromising.

Yao Ji couldn't do anything to Fang Yuan while she was reigning. But after taking the seat, he was able to get Fang Yuan to hand over his Nine Leaf Vitality Grass. This not only showed goodwill to the medicine faction, being able to handle the political matters left behind by Yao Ji and subtly display his own ability.

Thus, he didn't hesitate to give up the prize token which he had gotten with great difficulty.

"Lord Chi Zhong, it's really delightful to chat with you. I wonder if you still have some time now?" Fang Yuan asked as he stored the token.

Gu Yue Chi Zhong's eyes flashed; he was puzzled.

After a while.

In a hall.

"We pay respects to the two elders!" Fang Yuan's uncle and aunt bowed and greeted. They were very respectful and even a little afraid.

After the news of Fang Yuan becoming an elder was announced, he became a model example for young Gu Masters, whereas it brought astonishment and panic to the uncle and aunt pair.

He was clearly a C grade talent, how could he advance to Rank three and become an elder so fast?

Even Gu Yue Fang Zheng, who was an A grade talent, was only at Rank two upper stage currently.

After the astonishment was fear.

They couldn't help but be afraid.

When they thought of how they had bullied and been so hard on Fang Yuan, their hearts trembled with fear.

What goes around comes back around!

It was not the same once he had an elder's identity.

They were afraid of Fang Yuan taking revenge on them after achieving success.

But still, in the end Fang Yuan came to their door, and also brought another elder with him.

"They came with bad intentions, bad intentions!" Gu Yue Dong Tu sighed in his heart.

Fang Yuan chuckled, "Uncle, Aunt, no need to be so courteous. Although I have become an elder, I am still your nephew. Come, let's all take a seat."

Saying so, he sat down on the main seat.

Gu Yue Chi Zhong sat beside him.

These two positions were usually where Uncle and Aunt sat; the seats of the family heads.

Uncle and Aunt, however, weren't the least bit discontent with the seatings. They were even full of hesitation and fearful when sitting in the lower seats.

This was the power of the clan elders.

Uncle and Aunt glanced at each other, they were on tenterhooks as they sat stiffly; only sitting near the edge of the chairs.

The servants came in with some tea.

Gu Yue Chi Zhong maintained his silence and didn't drink. Fang Yuan, however, took a sip calmly and asked, "How has Uncle and Aunt been these days?"

Fang Yuan was smiling as he asked, but in Uncle and Aunt's eyes it felt even more terrifying than him flying into a rage.

It was especially so for Aunt; when she thought of how she had insulted Fang Yuan, she started trembling with fear.

"Sigh, life had been in upheaval due to the wolf tide. The tavern was forced to close down and the rent of the bamboo houses has been decreasing. In fact, we are so poor that we're reaching the point of starvation," Uncle said, and then tears fell down from his eyes unexpectedly.

He used to maintain his health very well before, but now his face was no longer ruddy, while the hair near his temples had gone white and the wrinkles on his face had increased. His predicament was even more obvious due to the forceful enlistment.

However, Fang Yuan knew his uncle had managed the tavern for many years, so he definitely had some savings. The miserable appearance he was putting on now was because he was afraid of Fang Yuan's revenge, and wanted to use his pathetic look to gain Fang Yuan's sympathy.

"Uncle is usually so astute, but how could he be so stupid when the matter involves himself? If I had come to take revenge, why would I bring Gu Yue Chi Zhong with me?"

Fang Yuan sneered in his mind. He greatly disliked and had no respect towards his uncle and aunt, but this didn't mean they had no use.

"Uncle, Aunt, you have taken good care of me for so long, all my current accomplishments are due to your nurturing. I have just received the elder payout from the clan; these three hundred primeval stones, please take them." Saying so, Fang Yuan handed the money bag to uncle.

"What? This...." Gu Yue Dong Tu's expression was really wonderful at this moment.

His astonishment contained unease, the unease was close to fear, and beneath the fear was incredulity.

Aunt who was at the side was also dumbstruck as she blankly looked at the money bag in Fang Yuan's hand.

What in the world was going on?

There was none of the revenge they had imagined, but instead, they were being gifted three hundred primeval stones?

Fang Yuan's words were ear-piercing, no matter how they looked at it. The words 'taken good care' and 'nurturing' were full of sarcasm which made them feel the whole situation was even more bizarre.

"What is he scheming?"

"What the heck does he want to do? How does he want to torment us!?"

Uncle and Aunt glanced at each other. Both were hesitant and didn't dare to receive the money bag.

"It is Elder Fang Yuan's filial piety, do accept it," Gu Yue Chi Zhong expressionlessly spoke from his seat.

"Yes, yes, yes." Uncle repeatedly nodded his head and hurriedly accepted the money bag. Even if he was called the hidden elder, that was nothing in front of the medicine hall elder.

He used both hands to hold the bag full of three hundred primeval stones. He normally loved money, but right now, he felt like the money bag was scalding hot and wanted to immediately throw it!

"Since uncle has received it, I will take my leave," Fang Yuan said and started leaving.

Uncle and Aunt immediately tried to see them off, but were stopped by Fang Yuan.

"Don't look anymore," At the corner, Matron Shen let out a breath of relief and said to her daughter Shen Cui.

Shen Cui's expression was gloomy, and she looked at Fang Yuan and Chi Zhong's figures from behind until they were completely gone.

"Matron, did I make a wrong choice?" she said.

An elder could take in a wife and two concubines; if she had been faithful from the start, who is to say that she couldn't be Fang Yuan's concubine at this moment.

"I really hadn't expected this. This Fang Yuan advanced to today's stage with only a C grade aptitude!" Matron Shen helplessly shook her head, "Daughter, cheer up. Fang Zheng has an A grade aptitude, his accomplishments won't be any less!"

"Yes," Shen Cui responded, and some luster emerged within her dark pupils.

In this world, the status of a common mortal was so petty and low!

How many things did she have that could move the great Gu Masters' hearts? She had already given her body to Fang Zheng, that was the gamble of her life and she couldn't turn back anymore.

Chapter 159: This Fang Yuan......

Howl—!

Four frenzy lightning wolves raised their heads and howled loudly.

Pit pat pit pat.

The rain poured from above as the curtains of water interweaved, and dark clouds roamed the sky. It caused the weather to turn dark, obstructing the vision of many.

"Quick, the northern gate has a breach, quickly go there, Sheng Nan group!"

"Healing Gu Master? We have a heavily injured person here!!"

"Kill, kill, kill! Kill all these bastard wolves!"

The wolves' cries were countered by the Gu Masters' shouting.

Almost everyone was bathed in blood as they battled ferociously.

Surrounding the village, battles ensued, spreading like wildfire.

The people's cheers, the wolves' cries, the sound of the rain, mixed in with the sound of the wind.

Uncountable number of lightning wolves rushed towards the village walls. The pitfall trap before the walls had already been flattened by a thick layer of wolf corpses, and as they were led by the numerous bold lightning wolves, the lightning wolves had a strong charging force together.

Rank one and Rank two Gu Masters fought bravely on the frontlines. Large amounts of moonblades flew towards the wolf packs, slaughtering numerous lightning wolves.

But the wolf packs still sent out lightning currents and lightning balls towards the village, bringing injuries and fatalities to the clan.

"Elder Fang Yuan, this is the medicine hall's newest injury report, please take a look!" A Gu Master in charge of transmitting information quickly arrived, and after seeing Fang Yuan, greeted him and handed over the report with both hands.

Fang Yuan was now a Rank three Gu Master, thus as a clan elder, his mission by the clan was to lead the Gu Masters in suppressing the western area.

Fang Yuan removed his attention from the battlefield and took the report, saying to the Gu Master, "You may leave."

The Gu Master paid his respects before taking his leave.

His speed was fast, and by using Gu worm to accelerate his body, he quickly left to the next area.

Any Gu Master in charge of information dissemination had at least one movement assist-type Gu worm, while some even had two.

Fang Yuan opened the report, taking a glance.

The injury toll on the report gave a feeling of considerable shock.

Until now, the wolf tide had attacked the village over ten times. The injury and death of the clan's Gu Masters was very severe. This led the clan elders to be so frantic, and the Gu Master that took over the medicine hall, Gu Yue Chi Zhong, felt even greater pressure. As a middle-aged man, he even had several white hair growing out some days ago!

But Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories and was mentally prepared, thus he was not surprised.

"This wolf tide is one of the most severe ones in the Gu Yue clan's history. Such injuries and death is unavoidable."

He thought this in his heart, and as moonlight gathered in his palm, he reduced this report to ashes.

This report, only clan elders had the authority to view it. If it was released to the masses, it would cause social instability.

Despite this, the Gu Yue clan was already in a panicky state, as the feelings of instability got stronger by the day.

At this point, the moonlight in Fang Yuan's palm was no longer the eerie blue colour, but of blood colour.

This is the Rank three Blood Moon Gu.

To refine this Gu, Fang Yuan had failed once, and only on his second attempt did he succeed.

As for the refinement ingredients, he naturally extorted Gu Yue Chi Lian for it.

Fang Yuan closed his eyes, his mind entering into his aperture.

In the aperture, the aperture walls were shining and dimming at regular intervals without a single drop of impurity; it was a pure white state.

His primeval essence was fully white in colour, but also emitted a lustre of a silver metallic glow—this is the Rank three Gu Master's white silver primeval essence.

Water gathers into a sea—in his aperture it was a white silver Primeval Sea.

On the surface, there was originally a black red residue, but now it was no longer there.

The Cleansing Water Gu he forced out of Gu Yue Chi Lian had long been used. The Man-beast Life Burial Gu's side effect was completely eliminated.

But this was not without a price.

Fang Yuan's aptitude lowered a little from 44% C grade—due to the Man-beast Life Burial Gu, it dropped by 2%, to a maximum capacity of 42%.

But this price, Fang Yuan was prepared for it.

In fact, it was all thanks to Gu Yue Chi Lian. If not for the Cleansing Water Gu and letting that black red residue corrupt the primeval essence any longer, Fang Yuan's aptitude would decrease even further.

A white-shell, black spotted ladybug danced in the air above the sea. This was the Sky Canopy Gu.

The Stealth Scales Gu with a stonefish appearance was deep inside the Primeval Sea.

Four Flavors Liquor worm was playing with the waves above the sea surface.

As for the newly refined Blood Moon Gu, its appearance was similar to the Moonlight Gu, residing in Fang Yuan's right palm, turning into a red crescent insignia.

As for the Rank three Thunderwings Gu, it resided in Fang Yuan's back as two lightning bolt tattoos.

To be worth mentioning is the Spring Autumn Cicada.

Its condition was getting better, and was recovering quicker. This situation caused Fang Yuan to rejoice and at the same time worry.

Spring Autumn Cicada is Rank six, but he is still Rank three, and at this time his aperture is unable to hold a fully recovered Spring Autumn Cicada.

The Spring Autumn Cicada's aura was getting stronger. Like using a paper tube to contain rocks, the aperture would not be able to handle the load.

"If I'm left with no choice, I can only raise it outside of my body," Fang Yuan sighed.

That had great implications.

Rank six Gu worms are implicated with Dao, containing the law fragments of heaven and earth. If left outside for extended periods, it would create a resonance with the natural laws, unless the Gu worm is slumbering. Otherwise the commotion would be huge, as it would cause all sorts of natural phenomena, attracting the attention and greed of other experts.

But this was a solution out of necessity.

Howl!

At this point, a loud shrill wolf howl suddenly entered everyone's ears.

Fang Yuan gathered his spirits.

"Lord clan elder, the frenzy lightning wolf has entered the battle! Gu Yue Jiang Jian and two others elders are at the eastern gate blocking them, they hope you can go and assist," a Gu Master frantically reported.

Crack!

The sound of lightning cracked as two wings sprouted from Fang Yuan's back.

These two wings were formed by blue lightning, the form abstract and simple. But with a flap, it brought Fang Yuan high into the sky, and with a fast speed, he sped towards the eastern gate.

Flying in a straight line in the air, Fang Yuan got to the battlefield in a few breath's time.

The frenzy lightning wolf was trying to break through the eastern gate, and a few clan elders were near the door aggressively engaging in battle.

The frenzy lightning wolf jumped abruptly out of the battlefield and with a swing of its tail, swept at a female Rank one Gu Master at the corner.

This Gu Master's face went pale. She could only hear the sound of the winds blowing as the wolf tail swept at her, and in her heart she screamed—"I'm doomed!"

With her ability, she could neither dodge nor take the hit.

But at this crucial moment, a shadow descended from the sky, hugging her.

The young girl felt the world spinning before her. When she finally recovered, all she saw was that she was flying in mid-air, while the wolf tail swept right below her; a two storey bamboo building took the hit and was shaking violently.

Her expression got dimmer. If she was hit right on by this tail, she would've turned into meat pulp.

Soon after, she realized that she was saved.

Who saved her?

She stared at this person, and was stunned.

It's him?

Gu Yue Fang Yuan!

At once, the young girl's heart was filled with complexity; it was impossible to describe with words.

She and Fang Yuan were classmates. Fang Yuan had formerly extorted her primeval stones, thus she hated him greatly.

But she had to be amazed at his achievements, especially after news of him advancing to clan elder spread, causing her to be in shock and admiration.

Compared to Fang Yuan, she was also a C grade talent, but was now only a Rank one.

Now, she was saved by Fang Yuan once.

He was a true lifesaver!

She was filled with gratitude towards Fang Yuan, and under her shock and admiration, her lingering hatred was also gone with this.

"The battlefield here is dangerous, retreat far away." Fang Yuan's wings flapped, landing on the ground and placing her down gently.

He had some impression towards this young girl. They were possibly classmates, but he could not remember her name.

Saying so, he turned around and left, no longer flying. Instead he sprinted, entering the battlefield.

The Thunderwings Gu's speed was fast, but its primeval expenditure was faster. Fang Yuan being only C grade talent, among the Rank three Gu Masters in terms of purely primeval essence storage, he is the lowest tier possible, thus he needed to conserve his primeval essence more than others.

Blood Moon Gu!

He threw a moonblade out.

The moonblade was blood red in color, and upon hitting the frenzy lightning wolf's body, it caused an injury that bled continuously.

The young girl's sight remained on Fang Yuan, staring at his shadow blankly. Slowly, her eyes started to shine in a mysterious manner.

Seventeen to eighteen years of age, this is the prime of youth.

"This Fang Yuan, what do you think of him?" Far away, Gu Yue Bo looked at this scene and asked a close aid.

The aid replied, "I heard that elder Fang Yuan had already answered the call of the medicine hall and handed in the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass in his possession. After getting the first payout, he gave it all to his uncle and aunt as a filial gesture. These days, he had struck personally and participated in killing lightning wolves. His aggressive and ruthless attacks have gained him much battle merits. Not only that, after saving many clansmen this time, his reputation is improving. The clan already has rumors—him turning over a new leaf, the Fang faction's new clan elder etc."

"This subordinate thinks that, although he is only a C grade talent, with his impressive battle capabilities, he had gotten great opportunities. First with his parents inheritance, the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass became a continuous source of income. Using two red steel Relic Gu, he managed to cultivate to Rank three, but also had an element of luck."

Saying so, this close aid showed an expression of slight jealousy.

He was also a C grade talent, but was only Rank two. Getting to this stage, he spent half his life doing so. But that Fang Yuan was merely seventeen years old, yet he was already a clan elder.

Competing with others, is really infuriating.

Hearing his aid's words, Gu Yue Bo nodded unnoticeably.

His close aid's words represented the view of majority of the people in the clan, but was slightly shallow.

Gu Yue Bo had been the clan leader for many years, thus he had greater foresight.

Fang Yuan handing in the Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, he had obviously struck a deal with Gu Yue Chi Zhong. Handing his payout to his aunt and uncle was not out of goodwill, but a political show.

The person who spread news on this matter, was Gu Yue Chi Zhong.

As for saving people... whether it's true and sincere, there remains doubt.

But no matter what, Fang Yuan no longer isolated himself, and his actions were indeed worthy of praise.

Him advancing to clan elder and his actions thereafter, this was an initiative to get close to the clan and contribute to the clan. The clan's prosperity requires these contributions and relationships.

Thinking so, Gu Yue Bo instructed, "Those people in the Hidden hall, these few days they also did not find anything from their investigations. Forget it, withdraw the investigations on Fang Yuan for now."

"Yes, this subordinate shall inform them now." Saying so, he took his leave.

Gu Yue Bo stood on the ground, squinting.

He thought in his heart, "No matter what's the reason, his cultivation still rose too quickly. This Fang Yuan, he has a great secret on him! However in this period, with the severity of the wolf tide, every bit of strength is needed, and wasting it on Fang Yuan is too wasteful. Investigation is still necessary, but this can only wait after the wolf tide."

Chapter 160: Astounding applause

With a bam, the frenzy lightning wolf fell on the ground like a giant elephant.

It opened its mouth wide, but its eyes lost focus as life slowly exited its body.

On its body, there were injuries all over. As wolf blood poured out endlessly, the environment was dyed red.

The rain continued to pour as it diluted the wolf blood, and caused the blood to spread further into the ground.

The ground was muddy, and some elders were standing beside the frenzy lightning wolf corpse, taking deep breaths as their bodies were drenched by the rain. They were also covered in wolf blood and mud, looking like beggars.

"Finally killed it!"

"This frenzy lightning wolf actually had a defensive Gu worm in its body, and was so difficult to take down..."

"Luckily we had elder Fang Yuan's Blood Moon Gu accumulating injuries on it, or else it would have been even more difficult trying to kill it."

When the elders said this, they looked towards Fang Yuan.

Initially when they heard that Fang Yuan had refined the Blood Moon Gu, they felt disapproving towards it. But it seems now that, it was very effective in dealing with frenzy lightning wolves.

"I am flattered, fellow esteemed elders, if not for your assistance and protection, I would not have been able to attack so relentlessly." Fang Yuan wiped the rain water off his face as he said politely."No, no, it is our duty."

"We are old people already. We didn't feel it before, but after fighting together with elder Fang Yuan, we feel that we have truly aged."

"Indeed, indeed."

The several elders laughed together.

In this earlier battle, Fang Yuan had a strong grasp of when to attack and retreat. With his ruthless and savage attacks, many times his methods were even more effective than normal elders, causing the clan elders to see him in a different light.

Especially with his polite and humble attitude and no sense of arrogance, he is definitely not what the rumors said—that aloof and unruly person—thus the elders had a good impression of him.

"I still have many aspects that need to be learnt from all of you," Fang Yuan said respectfully, but his eyes shone with a dark light.

The Blood Moon Gu had pros and cons.

After using it for so many times, he had some insights about it.

The Blood Moon Gu specialized in prolonged battles, causing unhealable injuries. As time passed, the enemy's injuries would get more and more severe.

But this is established on the fact that there is no healing-type Gu worm.

Nature is balanced, there is no strongest Gu worm. Each Gu was bound to have strengths and weaknesses.

"Blood Moon Gu's greatest drawback is the few days of the month where it oozes blood and faces a rapid drop in battle strength. It is my main attacking method, so this makes it too unstable. But, after I get the Chainsaw Golden Centipede in the Flower Wine inheritance ground, I can cover this weakness."

These few days were a high alert period where the wolf tide continued to attack the village, so as a clan elder, Fang Yuan attracted even more attention than before and had no chance to go to that rock crack's secret cave.

"Quick, save our clansmen!"

"Sweep the battlefield, don't miss a single Gu worm!"

Seeing the frenzy lightning wolf fall, a group of healing Gu Masters immediately came forth.

"Esteemed elders, you all have exerted yourselves, please accept special treatment from our medicine hall." The leading Gu Master bowed towards Fang Yuan and the elders.

"Oh... medicine faction's Li Chen." The few clan elders recognised this person, nodding and changing their expression.

They were courteous to Fang Yuan, putting on a face full of smiles. But towards this person, they kept their emotions and displayed the authority of a higher-up.

This is the difference in status!

This Gu Yue Li Chen, is only a Rank two Gu Master.

"I have no injuries, I do not require treatment. Elders, let's talk again when we are free." Fang Yuan nodded to the elders.

"Elder Fang Yuan is so outstanding, he's not even injured from such a battle, what a true young hero!"

"Sigh, compared to elder Fang Yuan, we are really old."

"Hehe, take care of yourself elder Fang Yuan."

The few elders started to laugh as they said.

"Elder Fang Yuan, please pardon my rudeness, but do allow our medicine hall healing Gu Master to do a check up for you," Gu Yue Li Chen insisted.

He was a member of the medicine faction, and after Fang Yuan angered Gu Yue Yao Ji to the point of fainting, causing her downfall, he naturally had hatred towards Fang Yuan. But with his position and job, as the leader he cannot ignore Fang Yuan.

"Thanks for your goodwill, but it's fine. I'll see everyone again!" Fang Yuan patted Gu Yue Li Chen's shoulder, leaving with a smile.

The elders smiled or nodded to reply him.

Only after he left did their expression change rapidly, turning solemn.

This Fang Yuan, although only C grade, had grown to this point, it is truly hard to come by! Fighting together with him, they could feel his heartlessness and ruthlessness, but when thinking about it, they felt threatened. When they were seventeen, did they have such achievements?

Especially when they saw him smile as he patted the medicine faction member's shoulder, such talent in politics and scheming, it is truly stunning!

...

"Lord Fang Yuan, do you recognise me?" Along the road, a person showed a respectful expression as he greeted Fang Yuan.

"You are..." Fang Yuan squinted, recognising this person as his classmate. Only that he could not remember the name, but when he extorted primeval stones from him, this person always handed them up nicely. It shows his brilliance under that meek personality.

"Lord Fang Yuan, I am Gu Yue Ding Zong. To have the fortune to be your classmate, that is my honor. Actually, after news that you had advanced to a clan elder spread, many of our classmates admired and were envious of you lord, wanting to find an opportunity to discuss cultivation experiences with you. Are you free tonight, lord?" Gu Yue Ding Zong rubbed his hands, his eyes smiling into a line.

"Oh, is that so..." Fang Yuan's eyebrows raised, nodding, "Okay, but let me change my clothes first, this drenched attire is making me uncomfortable."

"I have already prepared warm water and new clothes, and several beautiful attendants are waiting for serve you Lord!" Gu Yue Ding Zong smiled, his expression very eager.

Fang Yuan shook his head to reject, "No, before that, I have to go to the underground tunnel."

"Ah I see." Gu Yue Ding Zong expression changed. The underground tunnel was only accessible to the clan elders, and to people like them, it was a forbidden ground in the clan.

Next, his smile become even more subservient, and his back was arched even further, as his tone carried a servant feeling, "Lord, go ahead with your business, this lowly one's time is not valuable, waiting for you is also an honor of mine."

Fang Yuan nodded, not speaking anymore and continued to walk away.

Gu Yue Ding Zong took a step back quickly, opening a path as he bent his back and sent Fang Yuan off with his gaze.

Entering the underground cavern again.

This secret room that contained precious Gu worms was very large, almost as big as the village square.

But the Gu worms contained inside were not many; there was only a few dozen.

Cave Declaration Grass, Air Return Cicada, Dried Bone Dragonfly, Phoenix Wing Butterfly... there were Gu worms varying from Rank two to four.

It was only that there was very little Rank two Gu, and among them was a Love Separation Gu—this is the number 1 poison Gu among the Rank twos, and injuries caused by it cannot be healed even by a Rank three healing Gu.

This Love Separation, is the one Wang Er owned back then. After obtaining it, the clan kept it here.

The most was Rank three Gu, while Rank four Gu was relatively little.

Fang Yuan did not have high hopes. Although the clan had some fortune, it is still a middle-sized clan and has competition with two other villages, as well as the pressure of the wolf tide.

But to think that, he actually found a desirable Gu.

Tusita flower.

This was a Rank three grass Gu shaped like a red lantern, and had round green leaves. The leaves were thick and fat, a total of three pointing at three directions in symmetry.

This tusita flower is the same as the tusita grass. Not only was it able to store food, but it could also store primeval stones and is one of the most ideal Gu in Fang Yuan's mind.

"To think that this Gu Yue village had the tusita flower. With it, I can cover the weakness of storage," Fang Yuan rejoiced, choosing it immediately.

"Actually, in the village there definitely is a Rank five Gu. Gu Yue clan had two Rank five experts in history, they were bound to leave behind some Gu worms. Except they cannot be placed here, these Rank five Gu are the trump cards of the village, fed by the village with all their resources. Though to say 'feed', it is actually more like offerings."

Fang Yuan left the tunnel. The rain had stopped but the weather was still gloomy. The air was also not fresh, as there was the smell of blood.

Fang Yuan changed to a clean shirt and slowly moved towards the gathering point.

"Elder Fang Yuan, you are here, it is our greatest honor to have you with us!" Gu Yue Ding Zong stood at the door, staring with wide eyes. From afar he could see Fang Yuan walking across the street, and he quickly smiled and received him.He brought Fang Yuan into the bamboo building. There was already a feast prepared as many people were sitting there.

On seeing Fang Yuan, they quickly got up.

Soon after, all sorts of praises and flattering rushed like water towards Fang Yuan.

"Greetings to lord Fang Yuan."

"After so long, elder Fang Yuan's glamor is greater than ever, this lowly one truly admires you!"

"To be lord Fang Yuan's classmate, it is my luck from three lifetimes! Even thinking about it now, it feels like the experience of a dream..."

Fang Yuan's gaze swept across the table, seeing all his classmates; they were familiar faces, all of them people who he had extorted.

"My pleasure." He lightly smiled, sitting at the highest position.

"Serve the dishes, serve the best wine!" Gu Yue Ding Zong shouted, and the servants quickly got to work.

All sorts of dishes were served, their flavors top notch; this Gu Yue Ding Zong's family sure had some assets. To be able to serve such dishes during the wolf tide, it showed that he really paid a big price, showing his sincerity.

"Elder Fang Yuan, this lowly one toasts you!"

"Elder Fang Yuan, take your time to drink, I'll down this first!"

Fang Yuan was really very casual. With a cup of wine, he only took a small sip every time, but the people had no complaints towards this.

After toasting almost everyone and having drunk a decent amount, he suddenly held his cup and stood up, laughing, "The young are foolish, I was immature in the past and did some horrible things, I hope everyone can forgive me, and do not mind the past."

Once he stood up, no one else dared to continue sitting, and all of them quickly got up.

Everyone knew that the matter Fang Yuan was referring to was the primeval stone extortion.

They quickly shouted, "Not at all, not at all!"

"Elder Fang Yuan truly has character, a true hero!"

"To have my primeval stones eyed by elder Fang Yuan, that is our greatest honor!"

"That's right, that's right, elder Fang Yuan's glamor and heroism has always been engraved in my heart..."

Fang Yuan drank this cup of wine in one mouthful, as everyone cheered and clapped.

Chapter 161: Willingly exploited

Fang Yuan put down his cup, sitting down.

Only then did everyone dare to sit down. Among them, not all the classmates were present. For example, Mo Bei, Chi Cheng, and the others with strong backgrounds, were not among the ones present.

"It's about time, I have to go. This was a well-organised meetup." Fang Yuan showed his inclination to leave.

Gu Yue Ding Zong upon hearing the praise, was overjoyed and quickly stood up, taking out a money bag from his pocket.

The bag was filled with primeval stones.

He smiled and bowed, "Upon hearing lord's wisdom today, I've felt a strong sense of enlightenment, reaping a great reward. This is a small gift, but I hope lord can accept my token of gratitude."

He talked a bunch of crap, and from the start of the banquet, he had been flattering Fang Yuan non-stop, so how could he have gotten any enlightenment?

But everyone else acted as if this indeed really happened, shouting loudly and urging Fang Yuan to accept his gratitude.

Fang Yuan did not reject, smiling lightly and naturally taking over this money bag.

Next, was the second, and the third, simultaneously coming up to offer their gifts, all primeval stones!

"Alright, alright." Fang Yuan smiled as he accepted them all.

Tens of bags filled with primeval stones, how could Fang Yuan carry them all? Gu Yue Ding Zong on seeing this, quickly summoned a few family servants to carry his load for him.

In this short amount of time, Fang Yuan gained almost ten thousand primeval stones!

Lastly, Fang Yuan slowly stood up, raising his cup once again, "Our encounter is by fate; this classmate relationship, both you and I remember it at heart. This is truly worth drinking over."

"Yes!""Well said, Lord Fang Yuan."

"Such perfect phrasing, taking the words right out of our hearts, this is talent no doubt!"

Everyone stood up, praising as they raised their cups.

They either had no background, or their background was not strong enough. Fang Yuan advanced to clan elder, and they were afraid of his revenge, but at the same time they also wanted to enter Fang Yuan's social network.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, raising his hand and toasting with his wine cup.

At this point, the dark clouds dissipated, showing the lustrous moonlight enveloping the garden outside. The cool air was mixed with the smell of blood, and reality was extremely cruel.

But in this hall, it was exquisite with beautiful lights and decorations, overflowing with wine and fortune, and everyone smiled superficially as if they were in heaven on earth.

"This is the allure of the system." Fang Yuan's eyes glinted; as he stared at the wine in his cup, his mind thought about it.

Back then, when he extorted his classmates, it was only several primeval stones, but he incurred public outcry.

However right now, he didn't even have to say a word. Yet these people were all willing, fighting to be the first to give him primeval stones, each bag having over a hundred primeval stones!

This differential treatment—on the surface it looked like the result of Fang Yuan's elder status.In reality, the truth was because he had previously been outside the system. Right now however, he had entered the organisation's higher management.

Under the system, the members are all exploited willingly. Even without any hints from Fang Yuan, they would come forth and bribe him. Some would use their network to get into his faction, while women used their charms to get closer.

It works this way in this world, and the same goes on Earth as well.

"This world's people are hilarious. Being robbed and extorted only for a meagre loss and they resist violently, screaming injustice. But bribing the higher-ups, sending gifts, bodies and virginities, they do it willingly. And they are even afraid that it's not enough! Being able to get so many primeval stones today, this is all borrowing the power of the system."

Fang Yuan laughed coldly in his heart, thinking of Gu Yue Qing Shu, Mo Yan and Chi Shan.

Talented people like Gu Yue Qing Shu having B grade talent, they had much greater cultivating talent than Fang Yuan!

But all of them cultivated slowly, staying at Rank two realm for a long time.

Did they not work hard enough?

Hehe.

Let's laugh a little.

This is the deprivation and pressure from the system.

Such deprivation and pressure, it is invisible. Ordinary people cannot even feel it!

Taking Fang Yuan's situation for example. The primeval stones these people gifted, if used on themselves, would definitely be a driving force towards their own cultivation.

Thus, bribery is a form of deprivation!

Numerous lower rankers fight to bribe the higher-ups. This was a form of gathering resources and fortifying the authority of the higher ups.

Other than monetary fortune, there is also the deprivation of time.

Elites like Gu Yue Qing Shu did not need to bribe others, but their time was used up. Telling you to do this and that on a daily basis, running errands, doing missions, but acting rightfully so—this is for the higher-ups' attention and favor!

If this time was used to cultivate, Gu Yue Qing Shu would've broken through Rank two peak stage and reached Rank three. Then using the Wood Charm Gu, he might've even been able to kill Bai Ning Bing!

The amazing part was that, the clan elders did not want this junior Gu Yue Qing Shu to advance to Rank three so quickly.

For such a useful pawn piece, if he really became Rank three and was on the same status as them, how can they make use of him?

Who is willing to have their authority shaved?

Thus, they consciously dragged and suppressed him, even using the reason of —— I think well of this lad, but he needs to train. Only by refining can he become a true jade...

Hehe.

"This is the truth of the system. If one cannot see beyond this, regardless of how heroic they are or how talented one is, they are merely tigers and dragons chained up, only being slaves. People like Gu Yue Qing Shu and Chi Zhong, no matter how intelligent or talented they are, so what?"

Although he had so many thoughts, his thoughts flashed in an instant, and only a second passed in real life.

"Everyone, please drink up!" Fang Yuan moved the cup to his lips, downing the drink in one mouthful.

Everyone quickly toasted him, not daring to leave behind a single drop.

"Goodbye." Fang Yuan cupped his fists, taking his leave. The family servants held the primeval stones as they followed behind him.

Everyone quickly sent him off.

"Please continue drinking, you don't have to send me off," Fang Yuan said, but everyone did not do so. Instead, they left their seats and continued their flattery.

Fang Yuan continued, "I like peace and quiet."

Seeing his expression, everyone finally got his intentions and remained in the hall.

Seeing Fang Yuan's figure leaving, some people sighed, while others remained silent, and someone exclaimed, "Elder Fang Yuan truly is a legend, such elegance..."

They were all frogs in the well, only able to see the moon from below, thinking about Fang Yuan's unrestrained position but not being able to see beyond the system's restrictions.

Actually, as long as one joins the system, they would be weakened, and their benefits would be sacrificed.

Even the clan leader has to sacrifice. He needed to manage the clan, and with this he contributed much of time and effort.

It is just that the members at the bottom of the chain are deprived more severely. The higher one's status is, the more benefits one will enjoy.

Initially, when Fang Yuan extorted primeval stones, he worked against the system, acting alone and not even sparing his own brother. That was to avoid this deprivation. Thus, he had ample time and energy to advance to Rank three and become a clan elder, causing numerous people to scream in wonder.

But now that he had undergone a huge transformation, becoming a clan elder, his temperament became mild and respectful with authority and status, enjoying the benefits of a clan elder, causing many to be filled with envy.

This separation and joining, entering and leaving, is filled with deep wisdom and knowledge.

But how many people can see clearly across this fact?

Fang Yuan was not exploited, but he still enjoyed the benefits. In the eyes of mortals, this is unrestrain and elegance.

...

"Alright, put the things on the table and you can go," Fang Yuan said.

The family servants did not dare to have an opinion, quietly placing down the items and bowing to Fang Yuan before taking their leave.

This is no longer the rented apartment Fang Yuan stayed in before.

After advancing to elder, the clan allocated him a brand new bamboo building.

There was a study room and a secret room for closed door cultivation in the bamboo building, but there were no family servants; Fang Yuan needed to find them himself.

"Tusita flower, come out."

Fang Yuan willed in his heart and with the injection of his white silver primeval essence, the tusita flower residing on his tongue as a tattoo came alive immediately.

He opened his mouth and spit out, only to see red light appearing as the tusita flower rotated gradually like a lantern in mid-air, floating and appearing in front of him.

Fang Yuan activated the tusita flower. Instantly, red light flashed and caused the entire area to be lit in a red hue.

When the red light shone upon the pieces of primeval stones, there was a formless attraction and all the stones flew out of their bags and entered the tusita flower.

A moment later, the red light dissipated and Fang Yuan opened his mouth. The tusita flower entered his mouth once more, landing on his tongue and turning into a red flower lantern tattoo.

"This tusita flower is a Rank three Gu, able to store primeval stones and other things. Among the Rank three storage Gu, this is one of the better ones, being able to store a max of thirty thousand primeval stones. But considering that I have to store other things as well, the most would probably be around fifteen thousand primeval stones."

Although it was his first time using this Gu worm, with his previous life's experience, he could quickly estimate the limit of the Gu.

Primeval stones are the most basic resource for a Gu Master's cultivation, undeniably.

Without primeval stones, Gu Masters would lack a driving force severely.

And primeval stones also help in quickly restoring primeval essence, so in battle it has a lot of help.

Especially for Gu Masters who travel alone, primeval stones are the most basic assurance for travelling. Normally, they would need at least ten thousand primeval stones to ensure that a Gu Master has the basic needs covered for a period of time. And every once in a while, they require replenishment.

A saving of fifteen thousand primeval stones, to Fang Yuan, was still too little, but also at an acceptable range.

"First I borrowed three thousand primeval stones from Chi Lian, and with today's earnings, I do not have to fret over primeval stones for a while. In the six classifications, I have the Blood Moon Gu and Sky Canopy Gu for attack and defense, Thunderwings for movement, tusita flower for storage, and Earth Communication Ear Grass for recon. I only lack a healing Gu," Fang Yuan calculated.

He previously had a Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, but Fang Yuan handed it up already, thus being able to get the tusita flower.

But for this Rank two Nine Leaf Vitality Grass, even in Fang Yuan's possession, the healing ability was not satisfactory.

"Rank three healing Gu worms, there are a few desirable ones. Endless Vitality Gu can sustain healing and expends little primeval essence. On this note, it is the best for Gu Masters like me with low aptitude. There's also the Undying Grass, a Gu that can save me as long as I have a single breath left, this is the best life-preservation type of Gu. The most optimum is the Self-reliance Gu, relying on the Gu Master's own strength. The larger the Gu Master's strength, the more it can stimulate the metabolism of the Gu Master and thus recover injuries faster."But for these three Gu worms, how can Fang Yuan obtain them?

In the Gu Yue clan, he even checked the underground cavern, but found no such Gu.

On the resource board, they would also not display such a precious Gu.

The only hope lies in the Flower Wine Monk's inheritance.

But the chances were slim, Fang Yuan barely held any hope. He could feel that the Flower Wine Monk's inheritance was coming to an end. How could there be the exact Gu that Fang Yuan needs right at the end?

If that was the case, it would be too perfect, too idealistic.

But Fang Yuan knew how cruel this world was. Placing your faith in such a thing, that's naivety!

"But even so, I have to finish exploring this inheritance ground. At least for that Chainsaw Golden Centipede, I have to subdue it," Fang Yuan thought in his heart.

Chapter 162: Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus

Although he had planned to investigate the Flower Wine inheritance ground, Fang Yuan couldn't find the time to do so. With his elder status, many were watching him, and with the busy schedule of the wolf tide, many battles had to be fought and he did not have an opportunity to leave.

By the time he returned to the rock crack's secret cave, it was over ten days later.

The end of summer, night time.

The rain just stopped, bringing the atmosphere of autumn itself.

In the sky, a golden moon was hanging, round like a plate, high up in the sky.

Hearing vague wolf cries mixed with the remaining crickets, Fang Yuan stood on a slope, turning back and observing.

Gu Yue village was bright with numerous lamps lighted. The torn walls had been fixed over and over, losing the peace and tranquility it once had. It was almost like a huge beast that had undergone numerous battles, lying on the ground gasping for breath.

"After my rebirth, even the wolf tide's progress has changed much. In my memory, the thunder crown wolf arrived three days ago, but now it is nowhere to be seen."

Fang Yuan took a look, before moving his sight. Tonight he had managed to squeeze out some time, and had to make good use of it.

A moment later, he entered the rock crack's secret cave again.

The cave entrance was purposely covered with grey ash. There had never been any footsteps on it, showing that this place was yet undiscovered.

This small kind of detection method could not be called professional, but Fang Yuan's experience placed them to good use.

Of course, he did not only have one method of precaution, and after several layers of checking, he finally confirmed that this secret cave was still safe for the time being.

He breathed a sigh of relief. After all, since his rebirth, many things had been altered. Especially during the wolf tide, Gu Masters moved around more frequently, so someone might have discovered this place.

He entered the tunnel and went into the second secret room. Pushing open the rock door, he entered the rock forest.

In the rock forest, the path that he once excavated was filled with jade eye stone monkeys again.

But the Fang Yuan now, is already a Rank three Gu Master. Although the Blood Moon Gu did not have the highest attacking power among the Rank three Gu worms, it was definitely far superior than the Moonglow Gu.

Fang Yuan spent six hours, exterminating almost ten groups of monkeys, reopening a path for himself.

He came to the most central area and stepped down the rough rock stairs, entering the third secret room. A rock door blocked his path, and on the rock door there was a carving —"Golden Centipede's cave is precarious, Earth Communication is the way to avoid the disaster." Last time, he had been stuck at this step.

But this time, he opened the rock door with no hesitation, striding into the darkness.

He held a torch that illuminated the surrounding ten steps.

This centipede cave was wide, having a height of three metres, and breadth of two metres. There were also many narrow paths that extended all over the place.

Wherever Fang Yuan walked, the fire would proceed to light up the place and dispel the darkness. Initially the cave only had the sound of his footsteps, but soon all sorts of noises came from all over the place.

The sound gathered into one collective body, continuously sounding. At the edge of the lighted area, he soon saw a large number of centipedes.

They were ferocious. It was only due to the bright fire that they did not attack Fang Yuan. But Fang Yuan knew that as time passed, the centipedes would increase in number, and with the back pushing the ones in front, this stalemate would soon be broken.

But he did not mind it.

If he was still Rank two with only the White Jade Gu's defense, he would definitely not cause such a commotion, attracting the movement of the centipede group. But now that he was Rank three, the Sky Canopy Gu's defense was enough for him to withstand the bites of the insects, and his only concern was the insect king of the place—Chainsaw Golden Centipede.

It had appeared!

Fang Yuan purposely used a trace of his white silver primeval essence from his aperture, releasing it into the air, exposing his Rank three Gu Master aura.

This aura caused the Chainsaw Golden Centipede to feel a strong threat. To it, Fang Yuan had stepped into his territory, and this "wild beast" needed to be eliminated immediately.

Fang Yuan stood on guard against it.

This Chainsaw Golden Centipede was around a metre long, its body as wide as two fists. It first landed at the fringe of the lighted area, coiling its body around it, like python ambushing its prey.

But in the next moment, it moved slowly with numerous legs sustaining its weight as it gradually got closer towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's Rank three aura only made it alert, and not afraid. If he was Rank four, it would not pressure Fang Yuan like this. If he was Rank five and only revealed a bit of that aura, it would run for its life.

Fang Yuan raised the torch high. As the fire burned, it illuminated the surroundings and the shadow's movements.

Under the glow of the fire, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede's exoskeleton emitted an eerie light. At the side of its body, there were silver coloured sawteeth. As it got closer, the sawteeth moved as well, looking like a slowed chainsaw, emitting a buzzing sound.

The other centipedes gathered towards Fang Yuan from the walls and the ground.

Some centipedes climbed to the ceiling, then dropped down, landing on Fang Yuan's shoulder and back.

Fang Yuan did not mind it; he activated the Sky Canopy Gu, and a thick white crystal light appeared on his body, the form of an armor subtly showing as it covered him fully.

The centipedes' poisonous limbs could not do anything against this white crystal armor.

The twisting and turning centipedes climbed on his face or behind his ears; it was a little disgusting, but Fang Yuan's endurance level was way beyond this, thus ignoring them completely. In his previous life, he had eaten almost anything in the wilderness, and even non-poisonous centipedes were eaten raw. In fact the taste was not that bad, almost a bit strange initially, but he got used to it after eating them for a while.

He only placed his attention on the Chainsaw Golden Centipede.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede moved gradually, reducing the distance between Fang Yuan and itself.

When there was a distance of three to four steps between them, Fang Yuan stopped the white silver primeval essence from leaking and this caused his aura to instantly weaken.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede acutely felt that, thus instantly increasing its speed, moving like a golden line.

Pew!

In the blink of an eye, it had shortened the distance, and coiled around Fang Yuan's stomach.

This speed was really fast. It first appeared motionless, then on the very moment it moved, it dashed through like a golden light.

When Fang Yuan managed to react, this Chainsaw Golden Centipede had already coiled around his waist like a snake, opening its mouth and attacking towards Fang Yuan's face.

Fang Yuan quickly stretched out both arms, grabbing the head of this golden centipede.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede struggled, and Fang Yuan who had the strength of two boars, felt that his strength was insufficient.

Especially when the Chainsaw Golden Centipede's two bladed edges started to move rapidly.

Clank clank clank!

A strong pulling and slashing force grinded at the white light of the Sky Canopy Gu.

At once, Fang Yuan's white silver primeval essence was rapidly used up as the white light grinded with the chainsaws, causing sparks to fly.

Fang Yuan's primeval essence was only initial stage light silver primeval essence, and with only 42% in storage, it could not support such an expenditure.

However, Fang Yuan was unfazed; even though he could not get free from the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, he had a trump card!

Spring Autumn Cicada!

He willed in his heart and the Spring Autumn Cicada's shadow appeared from his aperture.

The Spring Autumn Cicada was gradually recovering; its two wings were tender and new like fresh leaves, and at the same time its body had a royal wooden lustre. But overall, it still gave off a withered feeling of death.

It had recovered around 20%, thus its aura was much stronger.

Once this aura was leaked, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede that was struggling intensely immediately surrendered!

It was only a Rank three wild Gu worm. Against the aura of the Rank six Spring Autumn Cicada, it did not dare to move at all.

Fang Yuan felt it most evidently. Previously he was still gripping the Chainsaw Golden Centipede like a poisonous python, using all ways to prevent it from biting; the next moment, it had become a soft and harmless rope.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, using his white silver primeval essence onto the Chainsaw Golden Centipede that had basically given up. Fang Yuan's will worked without obstacles, completely eliminating the wild consciousness it had.

In a few breath's time, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede was already refined by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan let go of both hands. The Chainsaw Golden Centipede's numerous segments moved with rhythm, moving across the white protective armor and around Fang Yuan's waist, finally twisting and coiling around his arm.

The surrounding centipede groups went away like a receding tide.

The wild Chainsaw Golden Centipede, because of its natural consciousness, was able to dominate the insect group. But now that Fang Yuan's will replaced it, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede lost its ability to communicate and control the group.

Fang Yuan did not eliminate these centipedes, instead letting them leave. Maybe in another dozen plus years, a new Chainsaw Golden Centipede might be born. But this no longer had anything to do with Fang Yuan.

He let the Chainsaw Golden Centipede hang on his shoulder as he investigated deeper into the cave.

This centipede tunnel had a lot of paths, and after moving for a while, the main path split into three branches.

Fang Yuan first used the Earth Communication Ear Grass, and after a while, he eliminated the center path. Choosing the path on the right, he moved for half an hour and found a dead end. He could only backtrack and go through the left path.

By keeping the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, he could deter the centipede groups and cause them to move away from wherever he goes with the golden centipede's aura.

This greatly aided his search.

Not long after he entered the left path, the centipede group that moved away revealed a cave, and he found some clues there.

"These are signs of human construction!" Fang Yuan's heart was moved.

Very evidently, this path was dug out by the Flower Wine Monk initially using the Thousand Li Earthwolf spider.

Fang Yuan moved along this path at a slow pace, patiently investigating.

There were a lot of centipedes in this path, and this was another piece of good news for Fang Yuan.

This is because areas with insect groups living there allowed him to eliminate the possibility of placed traps.

This tunnel was longer than he expected, Fang Yuan spent over twelve hours and walked over three Li worth of distance!

The slope gradually moved down as Fang Yuan approached a deep underground area.

Every once in a while, he stopped and used the Earth Communication Ear Grass to eliminate any possible threats.

Swoosh swish!

"What sound is this?" Fang Yuan eventually heard a weird noise.

Immediately, he noticed what it was.

"This is water... don't tell me?" His thought moved quickly as he had an idea.

At the end of the tunnel, he saw a crystal wall.

And behind the crystal wall, was water.

In the water, there was an ash-gray coloured river that flowed in a spiral, like a mini tornado, endlessly swirling in a self-sufficient system.

"As I thought, this is a natural essence spring!" Seeing this, Fang Yuan's attention was piqued.

Soon after, he saw that behind this watery crystal wall, there was something else in the spring.

A flower bud with the colours of blue and white following one another, was leisurely floating in the spring water.

"This... is actually the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus!" Fang Yuan was shocked!

Note: > This tunnel was longer than he expected, Fang Yuan spent over twelve hours and walked over three Li worth of distance! Li is 500 meters, I don't know why he took twelve hours just to walk 1.5km lol? It's not even an exaggeration.

Chapter 163: Thunder Crown Wolf

As Fang Yuan looked at the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, many doubts in his heart was cleared. He could roughly speculate what had happened.

Going back in time, a millennium ago.

A solitary Rank five Gu Master came upon Qing Mao mountain and incidentally found this underground natural spirit spring.

He was exulted and settled down here. He began merging the mortal villagers living around the foot of the mountain together, forming the prototype of Gu Yue village.

He took in over a hundred wives and concubines, wantonly spreading his bloodline.

He was the ancestor of Gu Yue clan, the founder of Gu Yue village.

Time passed by, and he passed away ending the first generation, then it was the second, third until it reached the fourth generation.

The fourth generation clan leader possessed an A grade aptitude and cultivated to Rank five, creating another golden age for the clan.

One day, a demonic path Gu Master came to the village.He was bald and muscular, dressed in pink clothes and moved alone; his favorite hobby was to defile innocent women. It was the famous devil of the demonic path: Flower Wine Monk.

Who knew what fortuitous encounter this Flower Wine Monk had, to be able to know the recipe to refine Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus. After many preparations, he only lacked a natural spirit spring to refine this flower Gu.

After looking all around, he finally chose Gu Yue village's spirit spring.

At first, he used the pretence of buying moon orchid to slowly approach the Gu Yue clan's higher-ups and get the details on Gu Yue clan.

Afterwards, in the battle with the fourth generation clan leader, he was able to achieve complete victory with his formidable strength. He had not only killed the fourth generation head, but also downed a large majority of the elders. However, his body was infected by the Moonshadow Gu.

Moonshadow Gu's ability was to restrict primeval essence and wasn't enough to be fatal. However, Flower Wine Monk couldn't wantonly slaughter if he wanted to refine the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, as that would attract a lot of attention and hinder the progress. Thus, he chose to do things from the dark.

He used the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider to dig out a tunnel, secretly advancing to this area. Due to the thorough preparations he had made before and with the sufficient materials, he was able to refine Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus in the spirit spring.

The Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus has an extraordinary background. Its fusion recipe had been created many millenniums ago by a Gu Master of the righteous faction: Immortal Venerable Genesis Lotus.

Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus was only a Rank three flower Gu, but it had its advancement route and could become the Rank six Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, which was ranked sixth among the list of Top Ten Great Immortal Gu rankings. Its worth was about the same as the Spring Autumn Cicada!The Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus had a reputation as a portable spirit spring, because it could produce primeval stones.

However, its fusion process had an extremely high price.

To refine the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, there must be a natural spirit spring. This spring should be full of primeval energy, and cannot be a spirit spring that has been used for many years, with its reserves drying out.

After the fusion succeeds, this spirit spring will be thoroughly useless and will lose its ability to produce primeval stones, becoming just an ordinary spring.

A natural spirit spring is extremely valuable. One only needs to look at how this spirit spring has sustained countless Gu Masters of the Gu Yue clan for close to a millennium to realize this point.

Refining a Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus would completely destroy this spirit spring. But that was just the beginning. If it was to be advanced to Rank four, it would need seven spirit springs, nine at Rank five, and eleven for Rank six!

Apart from this, many extremely precious Gu worms would be needed as auxiliary ingredients.

"If I take this Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, it would be like carrying a mini-scale spirit spring with me. The Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus is only a Rank three Gu, so its daily primeval stones production can't compare to a normal spirit spring, but the amount will be enough to sustain my cultivation expenditure!"

This was just one of its benefits.

The primeval stones produced by Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus were a lot more than the earnings from the Nine Leaves Vitality Grass.

Primeval stones can not only help in advancing cultivation—they are also an exchangeable form of currency.

With the treasure lotus, Fang Yuan could decrease the amount of primeval stones he carried. The tusita flower could then be used to store various stuffs which could greatly decrease the burden on him.

"However....I heard that the fusion process of the treasure lotus is quite mysterious; it appears from nothing during which it transits between the astral and physical form. Ordinary people can't see it, and it can only be seen clearly through the crystal. This Gu is quite delicate and needs to be nourished within the spirit spring for nine days and nine nights until it grows out nine intact leaves, before it can be plucked and put into the Primeval Sea in the aperture. If one picks it up before the time is ripe, all their efforts would be completely wasted."

Fang Yuan didn't know the detailed recipe of Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus and only knew some insider rumors. He had no idea on how to advance it in the future.

Even so, this Rank three Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus would be of an enormous assistance to him.

He looked beyond the crystal wall and carefully observed; to his surprise, the flower only had eight and a damaged half leaf. There was only half a leaf left for the nine complete leaves.

Fang Yuan wasn't baffled by this.

Centuries had passed, the spirit spring's reserves had been consumed for four generations of time.

This Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus condensed the majority of the spirit spring's essence, constantly consuming the primeval stones produced by the spirit spring, and causing the spirit spring's reserves to further decrease. As a result, the treasure lotus slowly began to reverse the absorption, instead replenishing the damage to the spirit spring. By doing this, it was damaging itself; this was the reason for the damaged leaf.

"Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus must have nine complete leaves before it can be plucked. It only has eight leaves and a half now. I need to throw in primeval stones to the spring if I am to pluck it!"

Primeval stones were the crystallization of the spirit spring, they could provide the nourishment to the treasure lotus and let it grow again.

However, don't underestimate this half damaged leaf. It was sure to require large amounts of primeval stones for it to grow back!

"If I am not wrong, this crystal wall should be produced by a Moat Gu...." Fang Yuan tried to touch the wall, and found that this wall was real but also virtual, just like light and shadow; his hands went through the wall without any obstruction.

But he quickly took back his hand and didn't dare to go deep into the spirit spring.

Spirit springs should never be polluted.

He poured his primeval essence into the tusita flower and took out a primeval stone.

He threw the primeval stone through the crystal wall. As if the wall didn't exist, the primeval stone went through it and dropped into the spirit spring, striking onto the phantom figure of the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus transited between blue and white and started shaking like water ripples. It digested the primeval stone in almost an instant.

After waiting for the flower to turn calm, Fang Yuan observe it attentively, but found no change in that damaged leaf.

His expression was calm. He started throwing in dozens of primeval stones but there was still no change to the damaged leaf.

Fang Yuan continued to throw in primeval stones while silently counting the number. When over five hundred primeval stones were thrown, the damaged leaf finally grew by a little.

After the sight of this scene, Fang Yuan couldn't help but feel slightly gloomy.

From this calculation, he had to throw in at least over fifty thousand primeval stones in at one time.

If he did it in batches and the time gap was long, Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus would consume itself to replenish the spirit spring as the clan continuously extracted primeval stones.

"Over fifty thousand primeval stones... I only have just over ten thousand with me and lack forty thousand more."

With his status as an elder, raising these forty thousand primeval stones wasn't really a problem.

The true problem, however, lay elsewhere. Once he took out this Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, the spirit spring would be completely useless and this was bound to attract the whole clan's furious and frantic investigation.

Fang Yuan had plentiful experience, but he had limited methods. If the clan investigated without any considerations, they were sure to find some clues. In fact, the clan's higher-ups were already suspicious of him, but their suspicions were temporarily suppressed by the wolf tide.

If the Flower Wine Monk's inheritance was exposed, Fang Yuan would definitely be the primary suspect.

Even if Fang Yuan secretly escaped, he would suffer the whole clan's reckless chase.

"I can't give up over the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus. Even if I don't have its fusion recipe, who knows what the future holds? The problem is that once I take this Gu, it is akin to stabbing a hornet's nest and bringing calamity upon myself."

Fang Yuan secretly considered every situation and decided he had to wait for the best opportunity to appear, to take this Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.

"This Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus should be the last inheritance of Flower Wine Monk. But there are many suspicious points to this; Flower Wine Monk would have come to this place to refine the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, so what kind of accident did he encounter to be so seriously injured that he had to hurriedly set up this inheritance before dying?"

Fang Yuan already knew the reason for the Flower Wine Monk to set up the inheritance.

It was to take revenge against the Gu Yue clan.

If Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus was to be taken out of the spirit spring—whether it was a success or failure—this natural spirit spring was bound to be useless.

Without the natural spirit spring, Gu Yue clan would have no foundation to stay here. It was only a matter of time before the clan broke apart.

"Forget it, I won't make any headway in my doubts without any new evidence. I should return to the village now." In the end, Fang Yuan shook his head and began to return back the way he came.

When he had just exited the rock crack, a loud and clear wolf howl continuously resounded.

"This sound!" Fang Yuan turned grim and quickly moved.

When he reached the riverbank outside of the rock crack, he could smell a thick odor of blood.

Sounds of cries, yells, wolf howls and explosions could be heard even though there was still some distance to the village.

Fang Yuan concealed his figure and climbed a hill.

It was early in the morning and the first rays of sunlight had just broken out of the sky.

Countless wolf packs were rushing towards the Gu Yue village like a flood.

Fang Yuan's gaze swept past them, then his body trembled.

In the rearmost part of the wolf packs, he saw a lightning wolf that was as large as a small hill.

Myriad beast king: Thunder Crown Wolf!

It was tall and slim, had strong limbs and its whole body was covered with eerie blue scales. Tufts of golden wolf fur could be seen on its claws and tail.

The fur on its head were all stiff and upraised, forming a towering crown.

It was crouching on the ground and was still like a sculpture. The frenzy lightning wolves and bold lightning wolves around it constantly howled, serving to show its elegance and nobility.

Just by sitting there, it had already brought a great mental pressure to the Gu Yue clan.

"The myriad beast king has finally arrived, it is the decisive moment for the survival of the Gu Yue village!" Fang Yuan gazed towards the village; innumerable Gu Masters were in fierce battles, using all of their strength to block the frantic charge of the wolf tide.

Suddenly, around ten figures flew out of the village and rushed against the wolf tide, charging towards the Thunder Crown Wolf.

They were all elders and in front of them was the clan leader Gu Yue Bo!

Chapter 164: Intense Battle

If one wants to fight against the thunder crown wolf, one must strike first. Its strength is just too great, and if it was let into the village, it would definitely cause great losses and damage.

This group's capabilities were huge. With the Rank four clan leader Gu Yue Bo as the leader, and his elders as his support, they were a strong attacking force.

The wolf tide was surging violently, yet they went against it with careful and compact cooperation. As if the group was a warship, splitting the waves apart, advancing bravely forward.

Wherever they went, they were practically sweeping everything away in their path!

The closer they got to the thunder crown wolf, the more the pressure coming from the wolf tide increased.

Gu Yue Bo was calm and composed. Suddenly he stretched out his right palm, and slashed in front of him.

Swoosh!

A golden coloured moonblade, as big as a grown adult, formed in a split second and flew out towards the front.

Swooosh swoosh swoooosh!

After flying out for a few meters, this moon disk suddenly went through a change, and from one blade it turned into three.

Three moonblades flew alongside each other, bringing about the sound of the wind whistling as it plowed open three bloody paths like knives cutting meat apart.

Many wolves fell without exception. Broken limbs flew into the air, and blood-curdling cries sounded non-stop.

A frenzy lightning wolf roared and started rushing over fiercely towards the Gu Masters from the right side."Let me!" A clan elder suddenly went from a thin and dry appearance, turning into a huge fat man in one breath.

With a bang, he used his round belly and sent the frenzy lightning wolf flying away.

The frenzy lightning wolf had come in a torrential rush, and the greater the strength of collision the stronger the bounce back was. It was thrown across high into the air, cutting an arc and then finally falling down hundreds of meters away.

The other elders were displaying all sorts of abilities.

There were some with long hair like needles, continuously shooting out and sweeping away lightning wolves.

Some of them had their bodies covered in light armor, forcefully bearing through the wolves' tearing and biting.

The thunder crown wolf went from a half-sitting state, and slowly got onto its feet. It firmly stared at the Gu Masters rushing towards itself, and the wolf's dark eyes flashed with warning.

It opened its mouth and let out a low roar, revealing its sharp and jagged wolf fangs.

Each of the frenzy lightning wolves and bold lightning wolves that heard its roar immediately got up and rushed towards the Gu Masters.

The Gu Masters were instantly slowed in their charge, receiving great obstruction.

"Clan leader!"

"I'll leave it to all of you, clan elders!"

"You have to win..."

Numerous eyes flashed and gathered on them. Unknown number of rallying cries and shouts sounded from the depths of the clansmen's hearts.

This was the most crucial battle.

If they lose the battle, the entire clan would face the danger of being wiped out. If victory was assured, then they would have held against the hardest moment of the wolf tide.

This was the battle that would decide the life and death of the Gu Yue clan!

None of the elders backed off. They pushed forward, while drenched in blood. Even though they did not lose any numbers, none of them were spared from injury.

They eliminated all the obstacles around them, until they faced the thunder crown wolf, then charged towards it.

Therapy Light Gu.

Suddenly a middle-aged female clan elder stretched out both her hands, and a pure white, warm light bubbled forth. The light first flowed onto the clan leader's body, and then reflected onto each of the other clan elders.

This was a Rank three healing Gu with area-of-effect properties, and it could instantly cause the wounds on Gu Masters to stop bleeding. Light wounds would recover completely, while heavy wounds would be healed by half.

"Continue fighting!" Gu Yue Bo roared loudly.

Five clan elders swiped their arms as they heard the signal, and sent a moonblade flying towards the sky.

Suddenly a clan elder roared as all the muscles on his body erupted and expanded three times, becoming a white fur giant ape.

It jumped in front of the group, its hands joined together.

Gu Yue Bo stepped onto its two hands, and with a low roar, the ape kicked from the ground and stretched out its waist, using all the strength in its body to toss Gu Yue Bo into the sky.

Moon-invite Gu.

Gu Yue Bo spread out his left hand; it was giving out a hazy, whirlpool-like purple moonlight.

The moonblades that the clan elders had shot towards the sky were all absorbed and annexed by this purple moonlight.

"SLASH!"

Gu Yue Bo's eyes shone as he shouted in a thunderous volume, splitting the air with his palms from up to down.

Pew!

Winds and thunder resounded as a purple moonblade, larger than a horse carriage, flew towards the thunder crown wolf.

This moonblade looked slow but was actually fast, and in a split second, it struck its target.

The thunder crown wolf howled and at the last moment, a thunder light armor appeared on its body.

Bam!

In the next moment, an intense explosion occurred as the sky was engulfed in eerie blue lightning pitting against the purple alluring moonlight.

Numerous people squinted as the shockwaves spread from the impact, sending the ordinary lightning wolves in the vicinity flying.

When the intense light dissipated, the Gu Masters were already engaging in battle with the thunder crown wolf.

The clan elders were all extremely experienced and well coordinated with each other.

An aged old master with floating white hair shot out needles from it endlessly like rain.

On another side, a female Gu Master blew out flames from her nostrils like lingering snakes, and she spouted a wave of orange flame and assaulted two sides at the same time.

There were another three Gu Masters—one turned into a white ape, while another turned his muscles into steel from head to toe as they both tried to curb the thunder crown wolf. The other Gu Master tossed out unending numbers of Puppet Gu, pouring his primeval essence and turning them into vine armoured grass soldiers or wooden servants with red spears, using them as fodder to attract the incoming assault.

Healing Gu Masters stood at the outer circle, using Therapy Light Gu from time to time. Beside them were defensive Gu Masters, giving them care and protection.

The thunder crown wolf had been beaten badly. Its right front limb had a huge wound, the blood flowing non-stop. This was the outcome from the attack of the purple moonblade a moment ago.

It roared continuously as it had fallen into the Gu Master's well planned trap. Even if it had the spirits to fight back, there was not much it could do.

The Gu Masters weaved and jumped around it like fleas on a cat or dog. They continued to move around and pulled space as they worked with completely chemistry.

But the good situation did not last, for the thunder crown wolf slowly began to adapt, while the wound on its body did not stop healing.

It was clear that it had a healing Gu on its body. This was very bad news.

The healing Gu's existence would mean that this is a war of attrition.

Wild Gu could just use the natural essence straight from the air, while Gu Masters could only use primeval essence from their own apertures.

After the battle reached fifteen minutes later, the thunder crown wolf suddenly howled towards the sky, and a torrent of lightning flashes enveloped its whole body, while its speed sharply increased onefold.

The elder who had turned into a white ape could not dodge in time. Unable to react to this change, he was bitten by the thunder crown wolf and his skull was torn into two by the wolf's tugging.

The thunder crown wolf had torn a line in the battlefront, and with continuous swipes of its tail, purplish blue electric currents rushed forth; the Gu Masters could only back away non-stop.

In this dangerous moment, the clan leader Gu Yue Bo stood out.

He was a Rank four expert with powerful attacks and superior defense, like the center pillar of the group, using all his strength to salvage the situation.

Mountain rocks broke and shadows dissipated as group battles enlarged. The aftermath ravaged the battlefield, and not a single lightning wolf dared to enter battle.

The situation of the battlefield only became more desperate. The thunder crown wolf's injuries became heavier and worse, the bleeding unable to stop, and bones could be seen in the deeper wounds. At the same time, the Gu Masters also suffered heavy losses—so far they had already lost six clan elders. If not for the village's clan elders' immediate and urgent dispatch, coming in to aid the fight, the battle might have long collapsed.

"Everyone, stand strong, holding is the key to victory!" Gu Yue Bo killed until his eyes were red, and his voice was hoarse as he gave his all to arouse morale.

But at this moment, the thunder crown wolf suddenly went berserk, and its body was enshrouded in a layer of bright red light.

Rank four Berserk Gu!

The thunder crown wolf's strength, speed, agility and other attributes suddenly rose to twice the original base.

Boom!

There was a loud noise as it swiped its right claw, turning a clan elder into complete meat mush.

With a flick of its tail, the sound of wind erupted and an electrical net flew out, trapping a field of grass and wooden puppets, then burning it all into charcoal.

"I can't keep up, my puppets are already used up!" The elder cried out, frightened.

With the situation rapidly changing for the worse, the terror of the myriad beast king was fully unleashed, leaving everyone in despair.

Gu Yue Bo's eyebrows were locked tight, and it seemed like he was about to break his teeth from gritting, when he suddenly yelled, "Trap it, use the Iron Chain Snake!"

As the clan elders heard this, they were awed in their hearts.

Early during the start of the wolf tide, they had already displayed countless battle tactics; this was a method that must only be used when there was no other choice!

"Wind Snare Gu!" An elder cried out, and from his nostrils came a green breeze, wrapping around the thunder crown wolf's claws.

"Swamp Gu!" Another elder roared and crouched down, bringing his two hands down and slamming on the ground. Instantly, the earth below the thunder crown wolf turned into mud.

With these simultaneous attacks, the thunder crown wolf's movements were slowed at that moment.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, the other elders all stretched out their hands, and from their sleeves and pants, waves of black shadows shot out.

The black shadow was about the size of a fist, and each length was around two meters long. Upon close inspection, one would see that each black shadow was a snake Gu.

This snake was shaped like an iron chain, its whole body a gloomy black. Coils of metal rings were strung and connected together, and only the snake head looked normal.

As it flew out, the snakes wriggled on the ground, quickly climbing onto the thunder crown wolf's body.

Their heads and tails then connected and mutually fit together, forming a metal net in the blink of an eye, taking root from the ground and trapping the thunder crown wolf on the spot.

But this situation was only temporary, for as the thunder crown wolf struggled continuously, one by one, the iron chains would break off. In just five to six minutes, these metallic snakes would completely disintegrate away, no longer trapping the thunder crown wolf.

"Chi Guang, Suo Ping, stay here and stop the wolf pack from attacking the metal chains. The rest of you, fall back to the village with me!" Gu Yue Bo shouted. He actually had chosen to retreat.

However the other clan elders did not show any surprised expressions; they had already known the clan leader's intention.

They hurried back to the village, and immediately a clan elder came up towards them and said, "Lord clan leader, everything has been prepared!"

Gu Yue Bo nodded, commanding the group to go to the clan pavillion.

In the plaza before the clan pavillion, there was already up to a hundred Gu Masters seated on the ground.

These Gu Masters were mainly those who were seriously hurt and could not enter battle in a short period of time. Each of their faces carried a calm expression of facing death without fear. Meanwhile for those who still had the ability to battle, they were fighting on the front lines.

With the battle reaching this moment, the clan had already given its all. In this dire situation, even the mortals had been mobilized. Using each and every single human life to be turned as a meat wall, obstructing the wolf tide for the time being, this gave the Gu Masters some time to recuperate and regroup.

Gu Yue Bo and the clan elders went into the ancestral halls of the clan pavillion.

Under the memorial tablets of their ancestors, they all sank to their knees on the floor."To the great ancestor above me, we descendants are greatly ashamed! The wolf tide is turbulent, and the village has fallen into the situation of life and death. We beseech our great ancestor to come and give us a hand!" When Gu Yue Bo finished speaking in a low voice, the ancestral hall fell into deep silence.

Drip drop.

A few of the clan elder's blood seeped out from their hastily bandaged wounds, dripping onto the floor.

Gu Yue Bo and the rest of the clan elders held their breaths, not even daring to pant or breathe loudly.

Back in the day, when the first generation clan leader felt his death approaching, he set out to leave the village. Before his departure, he left a testament behind. He said that if the clan would ever fall into the danger of perishing, they could pray before his memorial tablet. At that moment, Gu worms would descend from the sky and help the village through the difficult situation.

Throughout history, the Gu Yue clan had suffered through major crisis a few times, and they had dealt with the calamity this way.

This was the Gu Yue clan's last trump card!

Chapter 165: Blood Guillotine

In the ancestral hall, it was deadly silent. The clan elder and clan leader lowered their heads like a big rock was weighing on their heart.

After a Gu Master dies, the Gu worms they leave behind will still have the person's will remaining. They cannot be considered wild Gu worms, and have had lost their ability to use the natural essence in the air.

These Gu worms can be considered a extension of life of that particular Gu Master.

Everyone's heart was uneasy.

The first generation clan head had passed on for at least a thousand years, so were the methods that he had left behind still effective? No one knew.

After all, since the last crisis, it had already been two hundred years.

"Why did they retreat?" On the slope, Fang Yuan saw this scene and grew suspicious.

In his previous life, his cultivation was too low, thus he could not learn about the clan's secrets.

But soon his body shook, discovering that a group of flying worms had descended from the sky.

"This is..." Fang Yuan eyes squinted as cold light shone.

There were up to a hundred Gu worms flying around in a cluster, forming a red cloud, descending and landing on the village square.

Buzz buzz buzz...

The noises emitted by the insect group entered the ancestral hall, and the clan elders raised their heads, showing a frantically overjoyed expression.

"Thank you great ancestor, for the protection!" Gu Yue Bo's heart felt at ease as he paid his respects before getting up.

"Go, go and see," the clan leader sighed. On his face, there was happiness, solemness and grief, a complicated expression.

Leaving the ancestral hall and standing on the building's stairway, everyone could see that on the village square, there was a red tornado rampaging.

These Gu worms were only around the size of a fingertip. They were shaped like locusts, with a scary face and was red all over.

They entered the bodies of the Gu Masters sitting on the square, extracting their blood and primeval essence. In a few breath's time, one insect multiplied into more worms.

Thus, the Gu increased greatly in numbers as time went by. There were constantly new Gu worms being produced, flying into the Gu Master's skin and flying out, and then digging in again.

In the village square, miserable cries and cold groans sounded, but not one Gu Master fled.

Before they came, they were already informed by the clan elders. For the clan, they willingly tributed their bodies to feed the Gu, using their own sacrifices to bring about the survival of the clan.

"These are all good lads of our clan!" Gu Yue Bo seeing this muttered in a low voice, as the hand holding onto the railing shivered slightly.

The other elders showed a painful expression, but did not say anything.

This situation was exactly as recorded in the clan memorials. The first generation ancestor had left behind these Gu worms, and they required Gu Master's lives to feed. Only then are they satisfied and will help the clan to defend against external enemies.

After these flying Gu were full and satisfied, they flew up again with an even greater presence; in the blink of an eye, they had grown in number over tens of times!

What was left on the square were piles of white bones as the Gu flew out like a tornado, rampaging through the wolf packs outside the village.

"The Blood Guillotine indeed..." Fang Yuan who was standing on the slope saw everything and thought in his heart.

This Blood Guillotine is a Rank five Gu. Its usability and feeding are fused into one; it was a very strange Gu.

They specialized in consuming a Gu Master's life-bound origin blood, and after feasting, they would start to multiply, from one to two, two to four...

If they were hungry and couldn't find food, they would start to eat each other, reducing the size of their group to sustain the expenditure they needed in moving around.

At its peak the Blood Guillotine could engulf the skies and lands, destroying villages in their path, and were more fearsome than many Rank six Gu worms. When it was weak at only one or two in number, they would barely have any power and is worse than a Rank three Gu.

Especially when this Blood Guillotine Gu advances into the highly acclaimed Rank six demonic Gu, Blood Deity. Among the Top Ten Great Demonic Gu in the world, it ranks 7th.

In his previous life, when Fang Yuan created the Blood Wing demonic sect, he first wanted to refine the Blood Deity instead of the Spring Autumn Cicada. However, because of circumstances and many other reasons, he could only reduce his expectations and refine the Spring Autumn Cicada.

This group of Blood Guillotines numbered up to tens of thousands. Like a tornado sweeping the battlefield, everywhere they went, wolf packs howled and wailed.

They flew left and right, entering the lightning wolves' bodies and in a few breaths' time, the lightning wolves' blood would be completely absorbed.

But this beast blood could not allow the Blood Guillotine to multiply. Only a Gu Master's origin blood that contains primeval essence could achieve this effect.

One after another, lightning wolves were reduced to dry corpses, lying on the ground and losing their lives.

Only the bold lightning wolves and frenzy lightning wolves' lightning currents could resist this Blood Guillotine.

However, they could only electrocute a small number of flying insects, before an overwhelming number of Blood Guillotines would rush up and suck them into dry corpses.

Howl!

The steel web broke completely as the thunder crown wolf regained its freedom, howling in anger.

The Blood Guillotine detected it and it gathered quickly, forming a large red cloud and engulfing the thunder crown wolf completely.

The thunder crown wolf's tail swung around as blue lightning currents shot out and turned hundreds and thousands of Blood Guillotines to crisps.

The popping sound was just like firecrackers going off.

A gust of wind blew, bringing along the horrible burnt smell of the roasted Blood Guillotines.

The Blood Guillotine was indeed a Rank five Gu, but without a user, it could only attack head on. The thunder crown wolf had several Rank four Gu residing in it, and some had a wide area attack method, countering this Blood Guillotine.

The flying insects moved like a red cloud as the thunder crown wolf's hill-like body howled and struggled, creating a havoc.

At this moment, the thunder crown wolf's large body became its weakness as the fingertip-sized Blood Guillotine took advantage of it.

The battle was intense. As large numbers of Blood Guillotines fell on the ground, the thunder crown wolf's armor was broken through, and some Blood Guillotines drilled their way in and started to suck blood wantonly.

Without any other choice, the thunder crown wolf could only spray lightning plasma on its own body, electrocuting these Blood Guillotines.

But this way, its surface muscles were all fried, emitting a fragrant cooked meat smell.

The wolf tide's attack on the village had already stopped.

Under the thunder crown wolf's command, numerous lightning wolves attacked the insect group instead.

The Gu Masters could be said to have escaped death, and many held their breaths as they watched this intense and tragic battle nervously.

The insect group was like a death plague. Numerous lightning wolves would rush in and drop dead soon after.

However, the lightning wolves' sacrifice also caused the insect group to face high expenditure.

The Blood Guillotine dropped in numbers. The original dense cloud had turned into a thin fog, and soon it was reduced to a small tornado still flying in the air.

The thunder crown wolf struggled and escaped, its mouth howling as it ran with all its speed.

The blood in its body was almost half gone. Now its body felt soft and tired, while its running speed was not even 10% of the usual speed, and the lightning currents flowing on its body also became extremely scattered.

As the leader of the wolf packs, the escape of the thunder crown wolf caused the other lightning wolves' fighting spirit to diminish, and they also escaped all over the place.

"We finally did it..." The Gu Masters seeing this, became blank as some just collapsed on the ground, unwilling to get up.

"I'm actually still alive!" Many Gu Masters' expression was complicated; some were filled with happiness while also in grief.

Through the wolf tide, many clansmen were sacrificed!

Buzz buzz buzz...

The scattered Blood Guillotine group flew high into the sky, flying one huge round around the Gu Yue village before vanishing into the clouds.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan's eyes shone with a complex thought.

The defeat of the thunder crown wolf meant the village was now safe. In fact, most of the wolf packs were dead or injured, so they no longer had such a huge number.

This wolf tide, could be said to have been over.

However, wolf packs bear grudges, and as long as this myriad beast king is not dead, during the next wolf tide it would attack once again. After many years of recuperating, it would become even shrewder and stronger.

In the current situation, it was at its weakest. Killing it now and getting the Gu worms on its body, can help replenish some of the clan's losses.

"Yao Zhong, Ge Yan, you two stay behind and take care of the situation. Other clan elders, follow me and assault the thunder crown wolf!" Gu Yue Bo hurriedly ordered, before leading the remaining seven elders capable of fighting out of the village and towards the direction that the thunder crown wolf escaped in.

Fang Yuan's gaze shone, weighing in his heart, "Although the clan's power is greatly reduced, the current situation is not in a mess. Moreover, this Blood Guillotine has a suspicious origin, I better follow the clan leader and check out the situation."

Saying so, he went into stealth mode and went down the slope.

The Stealth Scales Gu and the Thunderwings Gu cannot be used concurrently. Thunderwings Gu was a Rank three Gu, and once activated it forms a pair of lightning wings that cannot be hidden by the Rank two Stealth Scales Gu.

Against the Rank three clan elders, the Stealth Scales Gu's hiding ability was not effective.

Fang Yuan could only follow their tracks and keep a distance between them, not daring to get close.

When the thunder crown wolf attacked, he was still in the rock crack secret cave and did not participate in the battle. If he appeared now, it would attract the rage of the clan head and clan elder, and if they questioned him, he would have not been able to explain himself.

The injuries of the thunder crown wolf were very severe, so it could not move fast. After half an hour, Fang Yuan could hear that there was the sound of fighting and scolding ahead of him.

He went there in stealth, getting onto a mountain rock, observing the Gu Masters' fight.

The thunder crown wolf lay on the ground with many new injuries on its body. Blood was flowing non-stop as it was gasping for breath. Its dim eyes showed that it was very near death.

"Old geezer Bai, you and your guys sure have the face, coming here to take advantage of the situation!"

"Hehehe, Gu Yue Bo, that's not the right thing to say. This thunder crown wolf was obviously stopped by us, get a clue and fuck off!"

Gu Yue Bo and the Bai clan leader were at a standstill, wary against each other.

The wolf den had three thunder crown wolves, all myriad beast kings, each having their packs of tens of thousand lightning wolves. But they did not glue together, and neither could they suppress one another.

The wolf packs' movements relied on working together. The three thunder crown wolves had intelligence, each targeting the three large "beast groups" to hunt.

In their eyes, humans were also wild beasts, and even prey.

In their understanding, the wolf tide was a massive hunting session.

On Qing Mao mountain, the Xiong, Gu Yue and Bai clan were able to live for hundreds of years. Naturally, they all had their trump cards.

Xiong clan was the weakest, still resisting the wolf tide with difficulty even now. The Bai clan had risen these years, and their cumulative strength had exceeded the Gu Yue clan. After killing a thunder crown wolf and pushing back the wolf tide, the Bai clan leader brought his clan elders to Gu Yue village, trying to find some opportunities.

To think that there really was such a chance! Thus they blocked the thunder crown wolf in this valley.

The thunder crown wolf's body had many Gu worms, and some were even Rank four. The thunder crown wolf's blood, bone, eye and fur were all precious refinement material. The Gu Yue clan naturally would not let go of them, and under intense anger, they attacked.

"Hehehe, Fang Yuan you really came. I've waited for so long!"

On the mountain wall, a cold laughter was heard.

Fang Yuan raised his head, only to see a white clothed young man descending from the sky as an iceblade slashed towards his face with resolution.

Chapter 166: Second Battle versus Bai Ning Bing

His hair snowy white and his orbs blue, a one-arm figure in white.

Who else could it be but Bai Ning Bing?

Before the ice blade touched his body, Fang Yuan could feel a cold eerie feeling assaulting him from behind like a comet striking the earth, full of cold killing intent.

Fang Yuan's irises were black in contrast, unmoving in danger, leaping backwards and injecting primeval essence into the Sky Canopy Gu, creating a white armor to protect himself.

Bam! The iceblade struck the ground heavily, and at that instance a bunch of white icicles grew from the ground, erupting upwards.

Swoosh!!

The sharp icicles stabbed upwards at the direction Fang Yuan was retreating towards, creating an icy path.

Fang Yuan easily somersaulted and avoided them.

The mountain path was narrow, so he slid down towards the valley along the edges.

"Hehehe, Fang Yuan oh Fang Yuan, why is it that everytime I see you, I feel that intense urge to kill you? Mmm, tell me!" Bai Ning Bing excitedly shivered as he laughed maniacally.

His laughter attracted the gaze of the other Gu Masters in the valley.

Seeing Bai Ning Bing and Fang Yuan, their expressions were different.

"Lord Bai Ning Bing, let me assist you!" A Bai clan Gu Master who originally stood at the side shouted and struck towards Fang Yuan.

"Clan leader, it is our clan's Fang Yuan!" Gu Yue clan's Gu Masters shouted.

"I know." Clan leader Gu Yue Bo's expression was uncertain, and he dodged the Bai clan leader's attack as he decided, shouting, "Get the materials into our possession first!"

Fang Yuan had mysteriously vanished before the wolf tide arrived, causing the Gu Yue higher-ups to feel highly doubtful of him. In addition, the intense pressure from the Bai clan Gu Masters resulted in no one going to reinforce Fang Yuan.

Bai Ning Bing saw help arrive and flew into a rage, shouting at the person, "Scram, this is my battle, don't interfere!"

"Lord Bai Ning Bing, you lost an arm and have reduced battle potential. You are the hope of our Bai clan, you cannot be lost. Let me sweep this obstacle for you!"

The Bai clan Gu Master shouted as he leapt, charging towards Fang Yuan.

He activated his Gu worm, both hands glowing with a orange yellow light.

Bam!

He lightly patted the ground, and the light entered the earth. Instantly, a lump grew from the earth.

The mud lump advanced towards Fang Yuan as it got bigger.

Suddenly the mud lump exploded, revealing a yellow mud arm.

This arm was humongous, as tall as an adult as it grabbed towards Fang Yuan. Its power and presence caused others to feel suffocated.

Fang Yuan snorted in disdain.

Seeing this arm grab at him and about to succeed, a dark golden light suddenly shot out from his aperture, turning into a shiny ribbon of light, wrapping around Fang Yuan's body.

The big arm reached his body but was twisted by this dark golden light, breaking and collapsing.

"Oh? What Gu worm is this?" Bai Ning Bing showed shock on his face.

The dark golden light dispersed, revealing the true form of the Gu.

It was over a metre long, as wide as two fists. Its dark golden exoskeleton displayed dominance as its sharp razor blades at the side of its body shone with cold light.

Chainsaw Golden Centipede!

"Come," Fang Yuan shouted, extending his right arm, his fist clenched.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede's numerous segments climbed up his body nimbly, its body twisting and turning like a snake, coiling around his right arm.

Its mouth opened and swallowed Fang Yuan's right fist in one mouth, all the way until half his forearm was swallowed.

Fang Yuan's arm swung, and the metre-long golden centipede moved its tail. In the air, it drew an arc, emitting a crisp sound.

At this moment, the golden centipede shrunk its body to the max, its near-two metre length shrinking to one meter and a half. At the same time its feet shrunk into the exoskeleton, leaving behind only two rows of razor blades.

At one glance, Fang Yuan looked like he was holding a dark golden-silver bladed, giant hiltless sword!

The reinforcement Gu Master was shocked, he had never thought that the Chainsaw Golden Centipede could be used like this.

The Gu Master's raising Gu, refining Gu, using Gu—all three required deep research. Fang Yuan's method was innovative and unheard of, using his imagination to the limit.

But actually, this method was not invented by Fang Yuan.

Three hundred years later, a new demonic faction talent, the 'Chainsaw Mad Demon' would use the Rank four Chainsaw Killer Centipede, one of the advancement paths of the Rank three Chainsaw Golden Centipede.

But in this life, Fang Yuan using it at this point is really unprecedented.

"I shall let you guys have a taste," Fang Yuan smirked, using the primeval essence in his aperture and injecting them into the Chainsaw Golden Centipede's body.

Buzz buzz buzz!

The Chainsaw Golden Centipedes' two rows of razor blades started to move violently, emitting a wild sound, causing others' heart to shiver upon hearing.

Thunderwings Gu!

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with determination as a pair of eerie blue thunderwings formed on his back with a crisp sound.

Whoosh!

The thunderwings flapped, causing Fang Yuan to shoot out like lightning.

Fast! Fast! FAST!

The speed was so fast that the Bai clan Gu Master's iris shrunk as he felt a chill.

The smell of death was so close, and he shrieked as he used his strongest Gu; a thick yellow light appeared on his body.

The yellow light was like armor, except that before it fully materialized, Fang Yuan had already gotten close.

His black hair danced in the wind, his eyes like lightning, looking like a demonic god that emerged from nightmares, killing his way into the mortal realm!

His movements were violent, and he completely exerted his muscles. As they tightened up, he used the strength of two boars to their limit.

The golden centipede-like sword, waved like a golden shadow in the air. The razors rotated violently, slashing towards the Bai clan Gu Master's waist.

Crack!

The yellow light armor broke under the slaughter of the chainsaw—it was never fully formed in the first place. At this moment, it scattered instantly.

The razors entered the meat as if it was cutting butter, and as Fang Yuan flicked his wrist, the chopped up meat flew all over the place along with the blood. The Gu Master's spine smashed and his intestines were grinded to a pulp.

The Bai clan Gu Master's upper half of the body flew into the air, while his lower half remained on the spot.

Plop.

He stared with wide-opened eyes, staring in fright at his lower half, dying in extreme fear and shock.

This commotion caused the fighting among the two clans to stop temporarily. They all looked towards Fang Yuan, sending shocked, angered gazes.

This Bai clan Gu Master was also a Rank three elder, and was slightly famous.

But under Fang Yuan's aggressive, dominant attack, he was instantly killed.

Fang Yuan's body was still blood bathed, with the Bai clan Gu Master's flesh still sticking to his clothes. The Chainsaw Golden Centipede's two edges were still rotating violently, and with such ferocity, it caused everyone to look away.

"What a great Gu worm!" Bai Ning Bing shouted, his eyes showing insanity and excitement.

"Fang Yuan, you did not let me down indeed! Come battle!" He shouted, his passion blazing like flames, striking towards Fang Yuan.

"Noisy fucker." Fang Yuan's expression was cold as ice, turning around to counterattack.

Bam!

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede and the iceblade collided. With a cracking sound, the razors cut into the iceblade and caused it to shatter into pieces.

In the next moment, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede broke through the iceblade and swept across Bai Ning Bing's face.

Bai Ning Bing's expression changed as he resolutely let go of the iceblade and retreated backwards, almost two metres of distance away.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede when shrunk was only 1.5m. Adding on Fang Yuan's right arm, there was still a little distance before it could reach Bai Ning Bing. But Fang Yuan willed, and the Chainsaw Golden Centipede suddenly extended itself.

"This?!" Bai Ning Bing was dumbstruck and did not anticipate this turn of events.

He was hit on the chest by the centipede's tail. Even with his ice muscles protecting his body, there was still a large cut on his body.

At that instance, he felt a strong force assault him, and he was unavoidably sent flying, landing on a huge rock behind him.

Blood splattered on the rock's surface, but his ice muscles soon stopped the bleeding.

Bai Ning Bing coughed intensely and was about to get up, but suddenly he heard a thunderous sound.

The sound was right beside his ear, and an unprecedented sense of danger entered his heart.

Bai Ning Bing's iris shrunk as he did not even raise his head, but frantically rolled away.

BAM!

In the next moment, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede descended from the sky. With its imposing aura, it struck the ground that he was at a moment ago.

The razors rotated violently, and the huge rock broke into pieces.

"If this hit landed on my body... I'm afraid..." Bai Ning Bing's heart chilled, and a sense of anger stemming from his indignant nature rose.

Ever since his battle with Gu Yue Qing Shu, he had stopped suppressing his cultivation, and let it rise naturally.

Although he lost a limb, he had his complete cultivation, but was still suppressed by this Rank three initial stage Fang Yuan!

Indignant! Humiliation! Rage!

"KILL!" He growled, his wrist turning and injecting primeval essence into the iceblade Gu, forming a brand new iceblade.

Seeing Bai Ning Bing come closer, Fang Yuan laughed coldly and attacked with all he had.

He had obtained the Black and White Boar Gu, thus his strength was greater than Bai Ning Bing. At this point when waving the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, it was as light as a tree branch.

Cut, slash, hack, twist, turn, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede rotated violently, moving as agile as a bee in Fang Yuan's hand. At times it appeared heavy like an elephant, sometimes ferocious as a tiger, and sometimes flexible like a snake.

The most crucial point was, the golden centipede followed Fang Yuan's will, extending and shrinking at times, sometimes longer and sometimes shorter, sometimes straight sometimes curly. That made it hard for Bai Ning Bing to adapt, and he could barely defend himself.

He cried and screamed as he retreated gradually, his body filled with injuries. His white battle robe had turned into a beggar's attire.

Fang Yuan moved like a black wind, his expression cool as he displayed an extremely profound sword technique, saber art, axe and rod skills. He fused all these skills into one, turning the Chainsaw Golden Centipede into a lethal weapon!

A Gu depends on who the user is.

"Good on you, Fang Yuan!" Bai Ning Bing shouted after numerous iceblades broke; he finally realized that he could not go head on against Fang Yuan.

His body was bathed in blood and the ice muscles' defense was almost broken, but this led out his immense battle passion.

If close range won't do, then long range it is.

Blue bird ice coffin Gu!

Bai Ning Bing pulled some distance and spit out several times.

Several flying birds flapped their wings and flew towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not fluster. With an unchanging expression, his left arm moved and the blood colored moonblade stopped these ice birds in their tracks, causing them to explode in mid-air.

People were normally proficient in using moonblades on only one arm, but Fang Yuan had such a rich battle experience, and even his left arm could completely shoot out moonblades without any deviation.

Bai Ning Bing seeing that did not work, used the Icicle Gu.

Icicles flew and mixed in with the blue birds to form a barrage attack.

Fang Yuan's long range attack was solely moonblade, thus he only chose to block the most dangerous ice birds. Against the icicles, he dodged some while tanking the others with his Sky Canopy Gu.

Bai Ning Bing finally had a bit of an upper hand and wanted to increase his advantage, but Fang Yuan suddenly laughed coldly and shrugged his right hand, causing the Chainsaw Golden Centipede to detach and burrow its way into the ground.

This hidden threat was too much.

Bai Ning Bing was dumbfounded at this, scolding loudly as he quickly took steps back!

Chapter 167: A fourth one?!

"You forced my hand!" Bai Ning Bing gritted his teeth, forming an iceblade.

At the same time, he activated his Swirl Gu and Fierce Wind Gu.

The white iceblade storm appeared once again!

At first it was just a small gust, but very quickly, the size expanded and the icy winds roared as the blizzard spread. The floor was slowly covered in hard ice, preventing the Chainsaw Golden Centipede from emerging and attacking.

This iceblade storm is a unique move of Bai Ning Bing's. Evidently it showed the battle talent of the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique.

This was formed by the Iceblade Gu, Swirl Gu and Fierce Wind Gu. When used together, it created something that could attack and defend. Without two or more defense Gu working together, one cannot resist it.

The fierce winds roared and the ice blades froze all in its path. The white storm assaulted like a huge beast awakening, opening its mouth and devouring Fang Yuan.

These three Gu together form a ferocious offensive technique that can freeze all life. Even with the Sky Canopy Gu's defense, Fang Yuan would probably be unable to block it.

The storm approached, but Fang Yuan showed a look of disdain.

The thunderwings behind him instantly flapped, pulling a large distance away from this iceblade storm.

Times were different now. If this was the past, his movement speed would be lower than this storm, but now the storm could no longer catch up to him.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance as he turned his direction in mid-air, and flew towards the valley.

The iceblade storm chased him relentlessly.

"Don't come here!"

"Fuck off!!"

Whether it was the Bai clan Gu Masters, or Gu Yue clan, both were scolding and shouting.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, continuing his charge.

The iceblade storm had an imposing aura as it continued to chase Fang Yuan while Bai Ning Bing's laughter was heard from within.

"Don't think of getting any further!" A Bai clan Gu Master blocked Fang Yuan's path.

Fang Yuan's hand hooked, and from the ground a thick and long golden line jumped out and landed on his right arm, like a large sword.

Buzz buzz buzz!!

The rampaging sound from the razors caused the Bai clan Gu Master's eyelids to shiver.

Fang Yuan held the Chainsaw Golden Centipede in his right hand as blood light shone in his left—he was using the Blood Moon Gu but not shooting it. His body was covered in a white coloured armor, and thunderwings sparked behind his back. His black hair flew in the wind, and behind him there was a mountain-sized white storm.

His presence was overwhelming with his eyes emitting sharp killing intent, as if he was charging through the desert, a general with seven victories under his belt. Stomping all his enemies into minced meat, and chopping any opponents into broken bones.

"AHHH!" The Bai clan Gu Master felt an impossible pressure as veins popped on his forehead, and he suddenly shouted loudly, edging himself on.

But as he shouted, seeing Fang Yuan was rushing towards himself without pause, he suddenly shut up and ran away.

He was scared!

The fear in his heart eroded his fighting spirit.

Fang Yuan did not care about him, instead rushing over towards the thunder crown wolf who was on the verge of dying.

Winds blew as his charging was fearsome, and everywhere he went, Gu Masters avoided.

The thunder crown wolf forced itself to focus, turning its head towards Fang Yuan. Lightning gathered on its teeth; the myriad beast king's pride refused to let itself die so easily. Even through death will it retaliate!

Fang Yuan was seemingly about to collide onto the thunder crown wolf like a meteor hitting earth, but at the last second he suddenly jerked his leg and rushed up into the sky, flying out of the valley at a steep angle.

He had just flown out of the valley when an intense explosion occurred behind him.

The thunder crown wolf's cries fused with the sound of the ice blade storm.

A move like the iceblade storm could be said to be Bai Ning Bing's masterpiece, but it had weaknesses too—it could not be easily displayed or stopped.

Of course, this storm knocking into the thunder crown wolf was also due to Bai Ning Bing's personality.

The thunder crown wolf was heavily suppressed by the white storm.

It was already going to die, but now it could resist no further. Its armor was cut into pieces and blood and flesh flew all over the place, revealing its white skeleton, which was quickly minced into bone matter.

"Damn it!" Seeing this, the Gu Yue clan's side all swore.

The Bai clan Gu Masters also showed a pained expression.

With Bai Ning Bing doing this, after the thunder crown wolf dies there would no longer be any valuable loot left on its body.

But Bai Ning Bing did not mind it. Instead he rotated even faster, enjoying the feeling of devastating a myriad beast king.

Gu worms turned into rays of light one after another, flying out of the thunder crown wolf's body.

These wild Gu worms had all resided in the thunder crown wolf's body, using each other to work together and survive. Now that the thunder crown wolf was dying, they were like crewmen on a ship, abandoning the sinking ship and escaping for their lives.

"Catch them!"

"Quick, stop these Gu!"

The two clans shouted at once.

The situation went into chaos again as clan elders attacked each other in attempt to hinder the other. The two clan leaders could not split themselves, thus finally, only two or three clan elders with movement-type Gu managed to fly out of the valley.

The wild Gu worms ran everywhere and Fang Yuan focused and observed, trying to discern them.

"What a pity my recon Gu is Earth Communication Ear Grass, it cannot increase my vision. There is definitely a healing-type Gu on this thunder crown wolf, but whether I can catch it or not, it's up to fate!"

This was betting purely on luck, but Fang Yuan had no choice.

Recon-type Gu worm, there were all sorts of them, but right now he only had the Earth Communication Ear Grass.

His thunderwings spread and he rushed towards the closest Gu worm.

This Gu's body was covered in a blue light, trying to fly far away.

Fang Yuan rushed up, opening his hand and grabbing it.

Whoosh!

Its body emitted an intense electric current and assaulted Fang Yuan.

Thunderwings are formed by lightning, it has speed but is not flexible. Fang Yuan groaned as he used the Sky Canopy Gu to endure this attack.

He could forcefully grab this Gu, but he wisely chose to give up.

The ability of this Gu was already exposed; it was able to use electric currents to attack enemies, so this was obviously an attack-type Gu, but Fang Yuan wanted a healing Gu instead.

Fang Yuan gave up on it and approached another Gu worm.

When he got close, he saw this Gu's appearance, a body that seemed to be made of light blue glass, flying in the air with a semicircle shell that had turtle shell markings.

Thunder Shield Gu!

This was a defensive Gu, able to form a semicircle lightning shield.

Fang Yuan gave up once again, looking around and finding his third target.

But at this time, a white shadow came from the valley, holding an iceblade and shouting Fang Yuan's name.

Fang Yuan sighed, knowing that lady luck was not on his side. He could only take the best alternative, reaching and grabbing towards the Thunder Shield Gu right next to him.

Thunder Shield Gu created a lightning shield, its eerie blue lightning sparking as it tried to resist Fang Yuan's hand.

Fang Yuan sneered, releasing the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura. Suddenly the Thunder Shield Gu became tame like it died, dispersing its shield and falling towards the forest.

Fang Yuan waved and grabbed it in his hand, releasing his primeval essence and instantly refining it.

Stealth Scales Gu!

Ripples formed all over his body as he vanished on the spot.

"Fang Yuan!" Bai Ning Bing shouted, as his eyes shone with lightning.

This is the Rank three Lightning Eye Gu, using the power of lightning to break through stealth.

But it did not have see-through vision. Fang Yuan noticed this, and although he was stealthed, he could also use the forest to conceal himself. Bai Ning Bing's gaze swept through the environment and angrily growled as he had no findings.

Fang Yuan found a hidden spot, instantly sitting down and activating the tusita flower, making it spit out primeval stones.

Although he was Rank three, his aperture only had 42% primeval essence storage, and though he had the upper hand during the previous battle, it could not be sustained. Right now, his aperture only had a thin layer of primeval essence left, being around 3%.

Gu Masters needed primeval essence to activate Gu worms.

Without primeval essence, Gu Masters' battle strength would drop drastically. In fact in extreme situations, they were even worse than mortals.

The primeval stones continued to shrink, the natural essence injecting into Fang Yuan's body. The Primeval Sea in his aperture started to rise gradually.

Back then, when he was Rank one or two and using the primeval stone to replenish his primeval essence, it was very noticeable. But now that he was Rank three, as the Gu Master's primeval essence quality is greatly improved, more primeval stones are required and a longer time is needed to replenish it.

Sounds of Gu Masters battling continued to be heard. After eight or nine minutes, Fang Yuan replenished the primeval essence in his aperture back to the limit.

He came out of his hiding spot, discovering that five clan elders had died.

Among them, three were from Gu Yue clan, two from Bai clan.

Each clan elder was the clan's asset. To think that so many were sacrificed this time.

Gu Yue Bo and the Bai clan leader's battle was very intense. They were feeling heartache from their respective losses, thus getting more aggressive in their attacks.

Other than this, there were three fighting groups surrounding the wild Gu worms.

Ordinary Gu Masters do not have the Spring Autumn Cicada's help to capture wild Gu worms, thus it was troublesome.

To catch the Gu worm, they cannot deal heavy blows. Instead, they need to gauge the strength they use.

Eight to nine Gu worms had flown out of the thunder crown wolf. It was not certain how many Gu worms they had captured, but three still remained right now.

The clan elders surrounded these three Gu worms, striking as they blocked the worms while facing obstruction from the other party. This caused the scene to be at a stalemate, neither sides able to gain anything.

"Water Cage Gu, trap it!" A Bai clan Gu Master shouted, spitting out a water ball.

The ball increased in size until it was over two metres, covering the Gu worm completely and trapping it inside.

Bam!

In the next moment, a golden moonblade flew towards the water ball cage and burst it open by force.

The Gu worm flew away, escaping with its life.

Seeing this Gu worm fly away, the Bai clan Gu Master cursed. To think that a Gu worm at his mercy got away just like that!

The Gu Yue clan Gu Masters were even more furious. These Gu worms were originally their battle rewards, but now that the Bai clan interfered, they could not gain anything.

"Bai clan scoundrels, shameless dogs, go to hell!"

"Gu Yue clan, you guys are finished. Our Bai clan will definitely rise up and stomp you all to the grounds!"

Both sides were furious, full of hatred and madness. They had battled till their eyes turned red, and only fighting remained in their minds.

Fang Yuan saw the Gu worm fly away, thus he had no choice but to look at the other two groups. There was still a Gu worm at each of their encirclement. There might be a healing Gu worm, but it was unlikely.

Fang Yuan knew that this world did not have things like 'a wish coming true', but even so he wanted to try.

Just when he was about to rush up and attack, he heard a wolf's howl like a military horn, spreading out in rhythm, rising and falling in succession.

Soon after, tons of lightning wolves rushed down like tide water.

There was no lack to the sound of bold lightning wolves and frenzy lightning wolves, but the one that made everyone's expression change was the mountain-like giant wolf.

Thunder crown wolf!

"There's a fourth thunder crown wolf?!" The clan elders shouted as they could not keep their calm anymore.

Chapter 168: Lightning lycan

Wolf packs were on the move, rushing in like the tide.

The situation turned for the worst, and the two clan leaders and their elders' expressions changed.

Although both clans managed to resist the wolf tide, it was through a dangerous battle and were pyrrhic victories. Now that there is a new strong wolf tide, they had no way left to resist it.

At once, both clans subconsciously stopped battling.

"The reports said there were three thunder crown wolves right?" A clan elder screamed in panic.

"No, this thunder crown wolf has lots of injuries, and the size of the wolf pack isn't very large either," Gu Yue Bo forced himself to remain calm and analysed.

"Don't tell me, this is the thunder crown wolf that attacked the Xiong village?" A clan elder slapped his forehead as he shouted.

This was very possible, and most likely the truth.

The clan elders were feeling solemn as one said, "The fact that they appeared here, doesn't that mean the Xiong clan already...""That goddamn Xiong village, how can they be so useless? Not even able to resist a wave of wolf tide!" someone scolded.

But some were optimistic, "You see, this thunder crown wolf's forelegs are injured, the muscles have all shrivelled!"

They followed the voice and observed, regaining some lost morale.

It was true.

This thunder crown wolf's hind legs were developed, but its forelegs were smaller, with shrunken muscles. This caused it to only use the back legs when running, jumping forward like a kangaroo.

"Wait, this doesn't seem like a thunder crown wolf..." Bai clan leader suddenly thought of something, shivering.

"Lightning lycan!" Fang Yuan had an answer already.

Five tigers one lamassu, three hounds one molossus, ten wolves one lycan.

The lycan was also a type of wolf, but it was far smarter than a wolf by many times, and was usually the strategist of a wolf pack. The lightning lycan before them seemed like a thunder crown wolf in appearance, thus a recon Gu Master's confusion is very common. But it was a true blue myriad beast king, and had intelligence no less than men!

This lightning lycan, although inferior to an ordinary thunder crown wolf in terms of physical strength, had human intelligence and was far more dangerous than a thunder crown wolf. With a huge army of lightning wolves to command, it was no wonder that the Xiong clan was exterminated by them.

"Go!" Fang Yuan spread his wings and flew into the sky.

These elders here had undergone long battles, and their battle strength was greatly eroded. They could not deal with the wolf packs, and more crucially, their misgivings towards each other made it hard for the two sides to work together.

Fang Yuan turned around and left; the myriad beast king was no joke. Even though there were still two wild Gu worms flying around, he couldn't care less.

He had to leave immediately, for any later and he might not have the chance!

Knowing one's limits and being able to let go and give up, this is the number one criteria to roam the world.

"Retreat, the wolf tide is huge, we cannot do anything to it."

"Get back to the village and plan our defenses!"

Even though the clan elders have not realized the lightning lycan's identity, they all had retreating thoughts.

But at this time, the lightning lycan growled, opening its huge mouth.

Its wolf fangs were sharp as a dagger, and in between, a black lump appeared out of nowhere, forming into a black ball in an instant.

Pew!

The black ball shot out, drawing a curved black trajectory in the air before smashing into the ground.

"It missed?"

"This thunder crown wolf is finished, its aiming sucks!"

The clan elders shouted about, but Fang Yuan flew even faster.

Bam!

The black ball of mist exploded and under that intense impact, the black mist spread all over the place.

The speed was faster than the eye could see. In a short moment, it covered over a hundred li[1] of radius."This is the Rank four Wolf Smoke Gu!" Fang Yuan's heart sank; he had made the most logical response at the first moment. But the black wolf smoke spread too fast, completely enveloping him.

At once, he felt like he was standing in the middle of the night sky, seeing nothing but darkness. Everywhere was thick smoke, making breathing difficult, and was extremely uncomfortable.

But thankfully he had the Thunderwings Gu, so as long as he flew up, he could get out of the wolf smoke's range.

Crack!

In the next moment, a lightning bolt struck, splitting the thick black smoke apart like a thunder snake or a raging dragon, travelling over a hundred li and assaulting Fang Yuan head on.

The lightning lycan attacked.

The lightning was so fast a person could barely react to it.

But at this crucial moment, Fang Yuan's battle instinct surpassed the speed of his thoughts, reacting in advance.

Thunder Shield Gu!

Sky Canopy Gu!

A round lightning shield appeared in front of Fang Yuan, and on his body a white armor appeared as well.

The raging lightning shone at an eye-piercing brightness like a heavenly dragon roaring, ramming onto the lightning shield.

The shield lasted less than a second before it broke under the intense force of the lightning.

The lightning landed on Fang Yuan. At that moment, even though he already shut his eyes, he still felt the light piercing through his pupils.

An intense force assaulted him, causing him to fall.

He was about to faint as the electric currents moved, paralyzing his muscles, almost causing him to forget to breathe!

Plop, he landed on the ground.

He finally only managed to regain consciousness after intense pain surged through him like waves.

He endured the intense pain and numbness, and tried to get up.

The Thunder Shield Gu was already dead, while the Thunderwings Gu was hit and barely held onto life; it was impossible to use anymore. The Sky Canopy Gu was injured heavily too, looking rather dispirited. After all, it was hit by such a strong electric current.

The lightning lycan's attack emitted a Rank four Gu worm's full power.

The more a Gu worm advances, the bigger the difference between realms.

For the attack of a Rank four Gu worm, at least two Rank three Gu would be needed to defend against it. However, the Lightning Shield Gu died because the previous battle had already caused it to sustain many injuries.

"To think that this lightning lycan thought so highly of me..." Fang Yuan laughed bitterly, observing the surroundings.

His surroundings were dark, full of thick smoke; Fang Yuan was unable to tell directions.

"Be careful, that thunder crown wolf became smaller, it is now as small as a normal lightning wolf and is hiding among the pack," A clan elder shouted at this time from the smoke.

Fang Yuan heard it and his iris shrunk.

This lightning lycan was too crafty, and very sinister. It probably wanted to eliminate all these Gu Masters, and when it attacked Fang Yuan, it showed that it did not want to let a single one of them off.

The surroundings quickly shone with countless wolf eyes.

The sounds of their growls and the sound of the wind from wolf packs running about were all heard by Fang Yuan.

Under such a dark environment, the Gu Masters' vision is greatly obstructed. But the wolf packs were unaffected, because they had given up on smell and gained excellent vision.

"I have to get out of here quickly. Who knows if I will encounter that lightning lycan? Even if I do not meet it now, just being surrounded by the wolf packs when I only have 40% primeval essence, it is insufficient to sustain my expenditure!"

Fang Yuan quickly considered in his heart, then he activated the Earth Communication Ear Grass.

Over ten roots grew out from his ear and extended outside.

Many voices were heard. There were wolf cries, battle noises, clan elders' frantic growling and lightning wolves' sad cries when dying.

Too confusing!

The Earth Communication Ear Grass' range was huge, but it could not discern small details.

Fang Yuan frowned, only listening to a direction with less noises.

But quickly he encountered a pack of over one hundred wolves.

Lightning wolves ran from the black smoke, each ferocious as ever.

Fang Yuan summoned the Chainsaw Golden Centipede and activated the Sky Canopy Gu.

The razors rotated violently and the centipede was like a large sword, cutting through the black smoke and landing on the wolf's bodies, causing a rain of blood and bones.

Fang Yuan attacked like a boat trying to row uphill, eliminating his obstacles.

Numerous lightning wolves died under the Chainsaw Golden Centipede. But then the second, third... they continued to assault him.

"This lightning lycan is too sinister and diabolic, actually making the lightning wolves surround us from the back." Fang Yuan had been moving in one direction, and after rushing for a while, he realized the truth at once after he kept encountering lightning wolves.

He battled as he retreated. After a while, he was bathed in blood.

The pressure was too large, the surroundings were covered in darkness; he was unable to see anything. Wolf packs rushed in from all directions, and it was difficult for him to deal with it alone.

"Gu Yue Bo, what do you say?" At this time, the Bai clan leader said from within the dark smoke.

"Alright, let's work together and get out of this first!" Gu Yue Bo shouted, quickly replying.

This was the forced circumstance of the situation—only through cooperation can they have a chance of survival.

Otherwise, by fighting alone, they would soon expend all their primeval essence on the lightning wolves and be turned into food. That would surely be a bad ending.

Howl!

"Fuck!"

In the next moment, with a wolf's cry, an intense explosion was heard and the two clan leaders shouted, no longer able to organise the clan elders.

Evidently, the lightning lycan came out and did a sneak attack.

It had a man's intelligence after all. Once it attacked, it was able to interfere with the two clan leader's plan, and ruined the flow of the clan elders' resistance.

Without the two clan leaders to suppress the scene, how can the clan elders work sincerely together?

This was a huge question.

"I'm unable to go on. My primeval essence expenditure is too high, I need to borrow strength from others!" After killing for a while, Fang Yuan felt exhaustion.

He had the strength of two boars, but now he felt extremely sore all over.

His primeval essence was no longer enough. He had injuries all over him, but he was forced to stop using the Sky Canopy Gu.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede's body was dim, its razors already in bad shape. In a short period of time, it had killed up to a thousand wolves, and within that number, there were bold lightning wolves as well.

A few of them were harder than steel, because they had a defensive Gu.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede was not invulnerable, and without razors, its attack strength would be greatly reduced, quickly becoming useless.

Fang Yuan did not prolong any battles; he quickly moved as he fought.

He relied on the Earth Communication Ear Grass to analyze the situation. Once he heard a frenzy lightning wolf's footsteps, he would change directions and try to avoid them.

The frenzy lightning wolf was a thousand beast king, he could not fight it alone. Once he was pulled into battle, he would fall into encirclement, and that would be a dead end.

"I'm not satisfied!" From the thick smoke, a clan elder cried as his voice came to an end.

From the black smoke, the wolf packs attacked, and many clan elders died by the wolf's mouths, growling in helplessness and indignance.

"I can't hold on much longer either!" Fang Yuan felt the aura of death, but he was still calm; the more dangerous it is, the calmer his mind.

His heart did not waver at all. In his previous life, he had been in worse situations.

The situation right now was still not that bad. With the two clan leaders fighting the lightning lycan, Fang Yuan still had a chance.

"Oh? Fighting sounds ahead." Fang Yuan heard the noise and changed his direction. He was at his limits, so no matter if it was the Gu Yue clan or the Bai clan Gu Masters, they were useful to him either way.

"Kill! Kill! Kill!" Far away, he heard this Gu Master screaming, battling relentlessly.

Fang Yuan sprinted over, and suddenly came to a stop.

Bai Ning Bing!

[1] one li = 500m Back

Chapter 169: Finding a path

Bai Ning Bing's body was laden with injuries. He was breathing raggedly and looked like a mess.

When Fang Yuan got there, both were stunned.

Fate was indeed, a mysterious thing. Just not long ago, they were still mortal enemies, wanting to kill each other. But in this moment, they had to work together for the chance to survive.

Working together with Bai Ning Bing?

Fang Yuan's eyes shone like the abyss, evaluating, "Although Bai Ning Bing is batshit crazy, along with the fact that he also recognised his own fate, that does not mean he gave up on living."

A will to live was a person's natural instinct, the most basic requirement of all.

The truth is, because of Bai Ning Bing's intense will to live and because he was facing an unavoidable path of destruction, he developed such a personality.

In this world, there are no eternal enemies. Working together with Bai Ning Bing was the best solution. But how can he ask it in a way that can convince him?

"Hehehe, Fang Yuan, to think it's actually you!" Bai Ning Bing spoke first, laughing loudly, his tone becoming aggressive, "Then die together with me. With you dying alongside me, it shall be an interesting end to my life."

"Interesting?" Fang Yuan had a thought. Smiling lightly, he approached Bai Ning Bing.

The surrounding lightning wolves attacked, but Fang Yuan shrugged his hand, the chainsaw centipede swinging and killing three lightning wolves on the spot, sending them flying.

Up till now, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede's two rows of razors were already greatly damaged. Its cutting strength was greatly diminished. It could only be used as a blunt object.

"Under the pressure of these wolves, let's have an intense life and death battle, isn't that more fun?" Fang Yuan got closer to Bai Ning Bing, his mouth curling into a cruel smile.

Bai Ning Bing's eyelids trembled, he did not expect Fang Yuan to be a greater maniac than him.

But this was in tandem with his wish. If Fang Yuan's attitude had gone softer, and in order to survive Fang Yuan wanted to work together and escape, he would instead look down on Fang Yuan, even feeling humiliated and wanting to kill Fang Yuan himself.

In this world, some people are like this. If you be kind to them, they will feel that you are easy to bully, and look down on you. By having a strong attitude towards them, you can gain respect instead.

"You really want to die? Then I'll grant your wish!" Bai Ning Bing squinted his eyes, emitting a dangerous aura.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, his steps slow as he spoke in a old and experienced tone, "Humans only live for a hundred years, it is as unreal as a dream that ends in an instant. What is the point of a person living in this world? No more than just being on a journey, and witnessing interesting things. Although I do not want to die, I do not fear death. I am already on my right path, I have no regrets even if I die."

This was Fang Yuan's true feelings.

Since the start of time itself, who could live forever?

Even if it was a Rank nine Gu Master. Or even Ren Zu himself who could only live longer, but not forever. They eventually face destruction.

So be it if one dies, what's the big deal? Even if in the next moment, Fang Yuan dies in this wolf tide, he would have no regrets.

Because he had already worked hard for his goals. He had given it his all, and lived all according to his will!

Being able to look beyond life and death. Only then can one live unrestrained, only then can life have true freedom.

Bai Ning Bing heard this, and his entire body shuddered.

He kept saying he was not afraid to die, but he was still never free and at ease. Because he could not see beyond death, and was unable to let go of this life.

When a person fears, he becomes a slave.

Bai Ning Bing himself was just a slave to life and death.

However, this was not his fault, since he was still way too young. Many things needed to be experienced by themselves; only then can one gain enlightenment.

But now, Fang Yuan's words gave him a new path, to go beyond the truth that he is struggling with.

"Witnessing interesting things... already on your path... no regrets even if you die?" Bai Ning Bing muttered, then suddenly asked, "Path, what's a path?"

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, getting closer, "Everyone has their own paths, I don't have to tell you mine, and how would I know yours?"

In this world, many people do not have a path through their entire lifetime, while some walked on their path constantly struggling, trying to find the sanctuary within the darkness.

Bai Ning Bing's blue eyes suddenly shone with a blinding light.

"Path... that's right, I must find my path!"

In this moment, the excitement in his heart was impossible to be understood by others.

He was like a man, bitterly searching for a girl but to no avail, yet one day he finds the correct method. Or like a treasure hunter, blocked at the last puzzle for a long time, but one day he finds the method to solve the puzzle. Or like a difficult question, thinking for years without an answer, but suddenly finding the method to solve it.

Bai Ning Bing had no path and couldn't find the meaning of his life, thus he felt lost.

Fang Yuan cannot solve his feeling of being lost, but from the sidelines he can give him hope. Giving him a consolation to face death—as long as you are on your path, even if you die there are no regrets. Thus, death is no longer so scary.

"I feel that I am about to find my own path!" Bai Ning Bing clenched his fists, his expression becoming extremely excited.

He looked towards Fang Yuan, saying meaningfully, "I finally understand our difference. You are on your own path, but I am still trying to find mine."

"Hehehe!" He suddenly laughed, his expression turning crazy, "Fang Yuan, if you want to fight, I'm all for it. But not now! Let's work together. I have the Lightning Eye Gu, but my vision is obstructed, only able to see thirty steps ahead. Once we escape from here, let's have a battle another day. Being able to work together with my mortal enemy, don't you find that more interesting, more fun?"

"Oh, how can I believe you?"

"I'm not asking for you to believe me. You can choose to trust me, or not. You can entrust your back to me, or you can strike at any time, and sneak an attack on me. Hehe, it all depends on your mood!" Bai Ning Bing shrugged as he smiled, showing an inborn nonchalance.

The thick smoke was all over, and their surroundings were lit with wolf cries.

Fang Yuan's eyes narrowed as he considered Bai Ning Bing's suggestion.

Convincing a person is very difficult, yet very simple. The important thing is accurately understanding their thoughts.

"Alright." Fang Yuan stretched out his hand and caressed the Chainsaw Golden Centipede's armor, raising his head, "But be on guard for my sneak attack anytime!"

"Hehehe." Bai Ning Bing's mouth curled, smiling very deviously. A wave of air blew as the black smoke dispersed, and the broken arm's sleeve swayed in the wind.

In the thick smoke, to decide the direction, it was difficult. The more narrow their vision, the more easy it is to get lost.

Bai Ning Bing had the Lightning Eye Gu and could see up to fifty steps ahead. But now, it was restricted by the thick smoke, so he could see less than thirty steps ahead. However, this was already much better than Fang Yuan's normal vision.

While Bai Ning Bing had the Lightning Eye Gu, he could not see the entire topography, and had no clear understanding of the situation.

He could only see what was ahead of him, and at times he even ran into a wolf pack and got surrounded by them.

Fang Yuan on the other hand, had the Earth Communication Ear Grass.

The smoke reduced vision, but could not block sound from being transmitted.

The surroundings were noisy, and the Earth Communication Ear Grass could hear up to two hundred steps away, but Fang Yuan could only move according to the noise. His vision was too narrow, only able to see a tree or a rock right in front of him. Without anything to compare to, he could not discern his direction.

Cooperation!

Bai Ning Bing's Lightning Eye Gu, together with Fang Yuan's Earth Communication Ear Grass.

The two Gu together, complementing each other, caused the situation to be easier.

"This is the southern side. Going this direction, we'll get to the Gu Yue village." Bai Ning Bing's eyes glowed with lightning as he said.

"No, there's too many wolf packs there, we have to take a roundabout route." Fang Yuan's right ears had roots flying around.

"Hehe... then we'll go around the southeast direction, how about that?" Bai Ning Bing licked his lips.

Fang Yuan squatted down, extending the roots into the soil and listening attentively.

During that period, the lightning wolves that rushed up were all killed by Bai Ning Bing.

Fang Yuan listened for a while, before standing up, "There's an opening in the southeast direction, but we have to hurry, the opening is going to be filled!"

"Let's charge then." Bai Ning Bing said, but did not move immediately.

He still had some guard against Fang Yuan. He did not dare to attack ahead and reveal his back to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly; he was also full of qualms towards Bai Ning Bing.

Eventually, the two killed their way through shoulder to shoulder, with a distance of five steps between them.

The lightning wolves howled, attempting to kill them.

But relying on the Lightning Eye Gu and Earth Communication Ear Grass, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing could avoid strong enemies and continue to roam, finding an opportunity to break through.

The advantage of having information was unveiled here.

Bai Ning Bing and Fang Yuan, if alone, they would be trapped by numerous wolves. But now that they worked together, they could control the initiative and started to have an easy time.

After charging for a while, the path ahead of them was suddenly clear, and the bright sunlight caused both of them to squint.

"We're out!" Bai Ning Bing laughed loudly.

Fang Yuan looked back, only to see a thick black veil behind him, as if a black pot had covered the entire mountain.

The intense smoke continue to emit sounds of explosions and screams. Evidently the two clan leaders were still fighting the lightning lycan.

"To think that working with you is actually quite pleasant." Bai Ning Bing turned his body, smiling lightly.

"I feel the same way too," Fang Yuan also smiled lightly.

But in the very next moment, both of their eyes shone sharply.

Iceblade Gu!

Chainsaw Golden Centipede!

The long iceblade cut through the air with a cold light.

The thick golden centipede attacked head on and carried the howling of the wind.

Bam.

Both sides collided. The iceblade cut a wound on the golden centipede's body, but broke right after.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing both took a step back, both of their eyes emitting intense killing intent.

Their temporary cooperation could not change their enemy status.

Fang Yuan's black hair danced in the wind, while Bai Ning Bing's white shirt swayed; both had too much in common. Precisely why they became natural enemies.

Black iris against blue orbs, almost creating sparks in the air.

Both of their killing intent slowly dispersed.

"Hmph, this is but a dying man. Even without me interfering, heaven will take his life. What's most important now isn't Bai Ning Bing but the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus! Once the lightning lycan attacks Gu Yue village, its most likely game over. I have to strike before that, while I have the chance..." Fang Yuan analyzed, his eyes narrowing.

Bai Ning Bing's eyes became even brighter, muttering, "Path... no regrets... that's right, even Ren Zu has to die. Humans live and die. So as long as I can live an interesting life, what harm is there even if I die?"

Thinking so, his eyes glowed with an intense brilliance.

"Hahaha. I've finally found my path, and that is to witness this world's brilliance! Fang Yuan, we will battle another day. I hope that by then, your death can bring some light into my life!"

Saying so, he leapt backwards continuously. After pulling apart some distance, he turned around, leaving.

Although he was in a mess, his body full of injuries and his face covered in soot, with only one arm left, but his back was straight like a sword; he was no longer lost.

He had found his path.

In other words, he had truly become himself!

Chapter 170: Can the blood of Incorruptible Justice be cold?

Fang Yuan watched Bai Ning Bing's figure walk until he was far away.

"Witness this world's brilliance...." His two black pupils flashed with an imposing light. The Bai Ning Bing who was no longer bewildered was more dangerous than before.

Life and death no longer bothered him, and the closer he was to death, the more he would display the incomparable grace of the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique.

"However, wanting to fight me later, heh." Fang Yuan suddenly chuckled, "You are bound to be disappointed..."

The instant he came out of that thick smoke, Fang Yuan had decided to leave Qing Mao Mountain.

It would be interesting to fight with Bai Ning Bing, but it was of no benefits to him.

Bai Ning Bing had set the definition of brilliance on Fang Yuan, and that was because he was young and his view of the world was limited to Qing Mao Mountain.

Fang Yuan, however, was different.

In his grand plan since his rebirth, Qing Mao Mountain was only a starting point.

As long as the heart possessed great ambitions, one was bound to be broad minded, not being constrained by small details with others.

"It's time to leave, the lightning lycan is more cunning and more difficult to handle than the thunder crown wolf. Just with Bai clan or Gu Yue clan's current strength, it will be difficult to withstand its attacks. Unless a Rank five expert appears and turns the tide, or maybe if the two clans ally."

Bai Clan and Gu Yue Clan had deep grudges against each other; they would ally if the situation came to that point, but the alliance wouldn't be sincere.

Fang Yuan wasn't optimistic about this prospect.

"Qing Mao Mountain's state will be determined by this battle. If the two clan leaders are both killed by the lightning lycan, Qing Mao Mountain will become the lightning wolves' territory. If one clan leader survives, then with the alliance, the other clan will only become cannon fodder. If the lightning lycan is killed, the two clans will definitely have to rehabilitate due to the severe casualties. The clan will tidy up its internal affairs and I will be investigated."

Fang Yuan could clearly see the changes that could occur through this.

This is the world of Gu, and in here an individual's strength can rule over the group. Thus, the higher the cultivation of a Gu Master, the more power he has to turn the tide.

No matter the Bai Clan or Gu Yue Clan or the lightning wolf packs, as long as another Rank four expert appears among any of them, the outcome would be a foregone conclusion.

However, no matter the situation, they were all disadvantageous to Fang Yuan.

"It is time to leave. Although I still lack the ideal healing Gu, how can one have everything he wishes for? After returning to the village, I will take the Heavenly Essence Lotus and then take out a healing Gu from the clan storage before leaving immediately!"

Fang Yuan gave one last look behind him; the sound of intense explosions were still coming from the black smoke.

He turned around and left, rushing towards the Gu Yue village.

With his status as an elder, he could forcefully open the clan storage and take out primeval stones as well as Gu worms.

There was unrest all around, people were frightened; it was the best time to take advantage of the situation.

If this chance was let go, no matter what the battle outcome is, the general situation would be set, making it difficult to take advantage.

Thunderwings Gu couldn't be used for the moment, so Fang Yuan could only run quickly through the forest.

The wolf tide had ravaged everything in its path, making the once dangerous pathways peaceful and safe.

Soon, Fang Yuan was able to see the Gu Yue village in the horizon.

"Hmm? Who are you!" Fang Yuan swiftly stopped; two strangers had appeared in front of him.

These two were both wearing Gu Master's clothings. One was an elderly man. He was tall and his back was ramrod straight, giving a sense of being as steady as a mountain and as profound as a deep pool. The most eye-catching part was the copper mask that he was wearing on his face.

The mask was of a plain design and gave an antique feeling. There were three openings on it, revealing the wearer's eyes and mouth.

His eyes showed the vicissitudes of life and revealed a grand and righteous aura. His lips were pursed up, the contour in between as sharp as a blade, hinting at this man's firm willpower.

The mask didn't cover his ears, exposing his greying temple hairs and revealing that this man should be of an older age.

The one next to the man was a youth with eyebrows that were as upright as a sword, and eyes that were bright and shining, periodically sending out sharp glances that looked like an eagle or a tiger's.

Looking at this appearance, the youth's age should be similar to Fang Yuan. However, this person's belt had a silver plate on it, carved with the character 'three'.

So young and already a Rank three Gu Master, this showed amazing talent in cultivation!

This was a young genius!

However, Fang Yuan's gaze only paused a moment on this youth, before turning towards the senior.

This youth had a slight dark complexion with similarly pursing lips, the entire body releasing a sharp and professional aura, definitely not someone to be underestimated.

But the slightly bulging chest area along with the structure of the limbs and throat allowed Fang Yuan to instantly see through her identity as a girl.

Fang Yuan would never look down on women, but compared to this heroic girl, the identity of the middle-aged man beside her would shock anyone.

"Tie Xue Leng....." Fang Yuan's mind jolted, he inwardly recalled the identity of this middle-aged man.

The man was wearing a copper mask, and the square amethyst plate on his belt was carved with the character —'five'.

He was the Rank five Gu Master, enforcer of the law, a great detective, the number one investigator of the Southern Border: Divine Investigator Tie Xue Leng!

He was impartial and merciless in upholding justice. Many demonic path cultivators had been arrested by him and many vile characters beheaded. He was the model example of the righteous path, and had made a very high reputation for himself by solving countless cases as he travelled throughout the Southern Border.

"Little brother, please wait." Tie Xue Leng cupped his hands to Fang Yuan.

He had already made a name for himself for a long time and was also a Rank five Gu Master, but his attitude was polite and amiable.

"Seeing little brother's state of injuries and hurried appearance, did your esteemed clan leader and elders encounter trouble?" He asked.

Fang Yuan automatically changed his expression to that of anxiety and astonishment, while mixed within them were doubts and fear. "Who are you guys? How do you know this? Right, we were chasing after a thunder crown wolf but we ran into trouble by encountering a lightning lycan. I am hurrying back to request reinforcements."

"I am Tie Xue Leng, I am an ally, not your enemy. I just came from Gu Yue village. Little brother, you don't need to return for reinforcements, the beast tide concerns all humans and we need to join hands to face it. This Tie shall contribute all he can." Tie Xue Leng immediately took this task upon himself.

...

"Damn it, to think that I, Gu Yue Bo, will die here today!"

"Hmph, even if we die, we can't let this lightning lycan get off so easily."

Gu Yue clan leader and Bai clan leader were full of injuries and had almost exhausted their primeval essence. Right now, they could sense the grim aura of death.

The thick smoke had already dispersed. All the elders had died, and only these two clan leaders were left.

The lightning lycan also didn't fare well. Its body had some deep wounds from which one could see its bones. It barred its teeth and retreated to the back of the lightning wolf packs, its eyes flashing with a sly look as it retreated from fighting in the frontlines.

"Come, you coward!" The Bai clan leader furiously roared.

However, the lightning lycan kept on retreating backwards and then let out a howl, commanding the ordinary lightning wolves to charge towards these two Rank four Gu Masters.

"Cunning bastard..." Gu Yue Bo and Bai clan leader looked at each other, and sighed.

They had prepared to make a strong counterattack before dying, but the lightning lycan had a wisdom that didn't lose out to humans and wasn't fooled.

"My life is over...."

"Damn this, we are going to die in these ordinary lightning wolves' mouths!"

Just when these two clan leaders were becoming extremely distraught, a voice suddenly arrived from a distance, "Two leaders, hang in there for a moment!"

The voice echoed through the mountain forests. The two clan leaders' bodies jolted and they immediately turned to look, noticing a tall figure rushing towards them.

The figure repeatedly flashed, freely moving through the wolf packs. After a few moments, the figure stood beside the two clan leaders.

"You are?" The two clan leaders asked at the same time.

"My name is Tie Xue Leng."

Gasp...

The Bai clan leader drew in a long breath in shock. He was surprised, joyous and also puzzled; why was Tie Xue Leng here?

Gu Yue Bo, on the other hand, was aware of the reason as he joyfully said, "So it is Divine Investigator Tie!"

Just as he said this, the wolf packs charged in.

"A bunch of foul creatures!" Tie Xue Leng's tongue seemed to burst with thunder, and with a low shout he willed a Gu in his aperture.

BOOM!

A formless aura suddenly erupted, radiating and engulfing everything.

This aura was like a mountain, indomitable and unshakeable. It was like the heaven itself as it overlooked the world and saw through everything.

Righteous Gu!

Only a Gu Master who had a righteous heart could use it.

The righteous aura could weaken vile creatures; within its range, the lower the willpower of his enemies, the more the weakening effect.

Tie Xue Leng had once used this Gu to make a Rank four Gu Master lose his fighting strength and surrender completely. This was the supreme art of subduing enemy without fighting.

Howl howl...

The lightning wolves' momentum stopped. Their limbs were trembling under the pressure of this aura, and they didn't dare to move forward.

Houuu!

The lightning lycan gave out a battle cry from the back, trying to command these lightning wolf packs.

"Such nerve!" Tie Xue Leng glared and suddenly stretched out his right hand, making a grabbing motion towards the lightning lycan.

Rumble....

Ripples spread in the sky, and an enormous black iron hand tore the sky apart and grabbed towards the lightning lycan.

Rank five Ironfist Grappling Gu!

The lightning lycan was cunning, but it lacked bravery. In addition to that, its body was riddled with wounds so it didn't dare to resist this move head-on, and instead quickly dodged.

However, this black iron hand had firmly locked onto the lightning lycan, and it kept on chasing.

The lightning lycan wasn't able to escape from it. Its vicious personality was stimulated; it gave a loud roar and fiercely collided against the black iron hand.

The enormous hand shattered but the lightning lycan received serious injuries. Almost all its bones were on the verge of shattering.

It let out miserable whimpers but didn't dare to fight Tie Xue Leng again. Finally, it resentfully looked at Tie Xue Leng and the two clan leaders, before it tucked its tails and ran away.

"It is about to escape!"

"Quick, stop it!!"

The two clan leaders shouted, but Tie Xue Leng stood on the spot and didn't move.

"Divine Investigator, please finish it," Gu Yue Bo cupped his hands and implored.

Tie Xue Leng slightly shook his head.

At this time, Fang Yuan and the young girl finally arrived. They had seen how the lightning lycan had been forced away by the iron hand.

"Dad! Why did you do that? You are injured!" The young girl quickly approached Tie Xue Leng and stamped her feet in anger; her reproaching tone was full of concern.

"Ruo Nan, this lightning lycan is very cunning. Chasing it away by force is the best way to deal with it." Tie Xue Leng spoke, when suddenly his body slightly trembled.

Puff! He spurted out blood from his mouth.

There was a strange, gloomy greenish color in his blood, and as the blood fell on the ground, it immediately corroded a patch of green grass, letting out an unpleasant smoke.

Clearly, he had suffered serious injuries.

"Dad, are you okay?!" The young girl, Tie Ruo Nan quickly lifted her hands and tried healing Tie Xue Leng.

"No need to make a fuss about it, you know of my injuries, I will feel a lot better after letting out some blood," Tie Xue Leng laughed and waved his hands, refusing the treatment.

Seeing this scene, the two clan leaders who had been feeling resentment just before, immediately felt embarrassed.

"Divine Investigator is selfless, you helped us even though you are suffering from serious injuries. We will deeply remember this favor."

"I have heard of Tie Xue Leng's great name, and today I can see that it is fully justified and worthy of admiration! We thank Divine Investigator for saving us!"

The two clan leaders cupped their hands one after another and expressed their thanks.

"Lord Divine Investigator, please honor my Bai village with your presence. This gratitude of saving my life, I will do my best to repay!" The Bai clan leader said.

How could Gu Yue Bo just watch as the Bai village tried to bring Tie Xue Leng away.

He knew why Tie Xue Leng was here, and gave a proud smile, "I know that Lord Divine Investigator is here due to Jia Fu's request and has come to investigate that murder case. Our Gu Yue clan will do our best to cooperate!"

Bai clan leader's expression changed when he heard this.

Tie Xue Leng said, "It is so. However, the one in charge of this investigation won't be me, but my daughter Tie Ruo Nan."

"Eh?" Immediately, everyone present turned to look at the young girl.

Chapter 171: Inbred demonic nature

"What, father, you want me to solve the case?" The girl pointed to herself, her face in utter shock.

"Why, are you unwilling?" Tie Xue Leng smiled gently.

"No, no, of course I'm willing!" Tie Ruo Nan finally reacted, jumping in joy.

Tie Xue Leng nodded, sighing in a complex tone, "You aspire to walk the same path as me. These few years where you were by my side, you have been greatly influenced by me and learnt much. An eagle can only learn to fly by itself, only then can it truly grow up. Your father is old already, my injuries cannot be cured. I cannot continue being with you as you live your life, and as the newer generations replace the old, what happens next is up to you."

"Father... don't give up yet, isn't there still hope for treatment?" The young girl's voice trembled as she choked back tears.

"You and I both know that the chances are infinitely slim. People have to learn to face facts, Ruo Nan," Tie Xue Leng laughed, then turned towards Gu Yue Bo, "Don't worry Gu Yue clan leader, this daughter of mine has learnt at least 80% of my abilities. With my guidance along the way, she will not let your clan suffer any injustice."

"Of course, of course." Gu Yue Bo quickly cupped his fist, "Young heroines are on par with males; such an elegant disposition and the child of a hero, there is no reason for me to worry. Please come to the village and let us feast upon your arrival."

...

The dishes filled the entire table, with the fragrance overwhelming the surroundings. Clear wine was poured out from the wine jar in a straight line into Tie Xue Leng's cup.

The wolf tide was just over, and Gu Yue village was in its toughest period. Large amounts of resources had been expended, causing a food shortage and lack of commodities. Many mortals would starve to death.

But even so, to welcome Tie Xue Leng, Gu Yue clan still assembled this banquet.

As the clan leader, Gu Yue Bo sat at the clan head's seat, while Tie Xue Leng and Tie Ruo Nan were beside him.

Other than that, Gu Yue Chi Zhong, Gu Yue Ge Yan, Gu Yue Mo Chen, Gu Yue Yao Ji, as well as Fang Yuan and the others, all being elders, were present.

Before the wolf tide, Gu Yue clan had over a dozen clan elders. But now, only one table remained, and there were less than ten elders.

Moreover, the clan elders present were all injured to varying degrees.

Especially in the case of Gu Yue Mo Chen—two weeks ago when he resisted the wolf tide, he was heavily injured and had been hiding in his private room to recuperate. He was resting in bed, but when he heard about the arrival of Tie Xue Leng, he forced his body up and attended this banquet.

But this also let him escape the crisis, while his old rival Gu Yue Chi Lian had followed the clan leader in assaulting the thunder crown wolf and was killed by the lightning lycan.

"If not for Brother Tie's help today, I might've become the lightning lycan's lunch already. For saving my life, I toast Brother Tie this cup!" Gu Yue Bo stood up, holding the cup with both hands and bending his back, sincerely offering his gratitude.

"I was only doing what I could." Tie Xue Leng raised his cup, drinking the wine in one go.

He had a vigilant and strict lifestyle, refusing to gamble or find prostitutes, standing by his morals and never went greedy on drinking. He had thus, never been drunk.

After drinking this cup, Gu Yue Bo looked at the people in the banquet, his eyes turning red, sighing and sitting down.

Tie Xue Leng had seen such situations many times, and he consoled, "Gu Yue clan leader, my condolences. As long as your clansmen still exist, the village will definitely thrive again one day. That lightning lycan was heavily injured as well, and the lightning wolves have greatly been damaged, they will not attack for the next few years. This wolf tide has been safely endured."

The wolf tide's harshest period is indeed over. For the next few months, although lightning wolves will still appear, their quantity will continue to decrease, and no large groups will be formed. The wolf packs no longer have the ability to directly charge at the village.

The lightning lycan will return to the wolf den and recuperate there, while slowly organising the remaining wolves. Many wolves will be recalled, and many lightning wolves would die, causing the wolf pack's need for food to decrease drastically.

The wolf packs would become self-sufficient, and in the next few years, they would gradually get stronger, during which new hundred beast kings—bold lightning wolves, thousand beast kings—frenzy lightning wolves, and myriad beast kings—thunder crown wolves would appear.

At its peak, it begins to weaken, and at its weakest, it begins to prosper.

Regardless of humans or wolves, they follow such a law.

But although Tie Xue Leng's words were right, humans are not grass or trees, they have feelings. The Gu Yue clan leader understood this fact much better than Tie Xue Leng, but the misery and pain in his heart was unavoidable.

The sacrifice was too big...

Just the higher-up clan elders were already gone by at least half. As for the Rank two and Rank one Gu Masters, they had an even larger amount of casualties. The entire Gu Yue village's strength had fallen to rock bottom, and could no longer endure any more disasters.

"Why is it that you guys do not counter attack, and go wreck their den?" On one side, Tie Ruo Nan could not understand and asked in confusion.

"That is because inside the wolf den, there are over dozens of groups of thunder gas worms, amounting to over a million of them in total. There are also large numbers of wild Gu mixed in. It is hard to cause any damage to them, unless all three clans work together," Gu Yue Yao Ji explained.

Saying so, she suddenly snorted, staring at Fang Yuan, "But this possibility is too small. Even within our clan, there are clan elders shrinking in fear, and during the wolf tide's attack, god knows where they were hiding!"

Saying so, all the other clan elders turned their vision towards Fang Yuan.

Previously, Fang Yuan was inside the rock crack secret cave exploring the Flower Wine Monk's inheritance, causing him to miss the huge battle in resisting the wolf tide. In everyone's eyes, this was being crafty and evasive, as well as being timid and fearing death.

Thus, the clan elders' expression towards Fang Yuan were all full of unhappiness, disdain, and some hidden anger.

Even Gu Yue Bo's expression was looking ugly.

As the clan leader, he was most revolted by people like Fang Yuan, doing things according to their own will, mysterious and having their own little schemes. He could not feel safe with such a person around.

The atmosphere at the banquet immediately transformed.

The Tie father and daughter also felt this change, following everyone's gaze and looking towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's young appearance had attracted the attention of Tie Ruo Nan who was the same age as him.

Fang Yuan drank his wine calmly. Even though everyone's gaze was on him, he acted as if he felt nothing.

His expression was calm, as he already had anticipated such a situation of people finding problems with him.

"Things are getting troublesome," he sighed in his heart. Although worried, he was not frightened.

Tie Xue Leng's appearance had heavily destroyed his plans to leave. If he took the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus and destroyed the foundation of the Gu Yue village, this would cause the Tie father and daughter to arrest him.

The name of divine investigator is not just a myth. With his abilities and strength, as long as Tie Xue Leng commences his chase, there is no possibility of failing.

Even if he does not take the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, his mysterious disappearance would cause the clan to investigate. As it involves Jia Jin Sheng's death, even the Tie father and daughter would get involved.

If he left without notice, in their eyes it would be a thief trying to escape, running from his crimes.

With no choice, Fang Yuan could only choose to stay and observe the situation.

Although everyone reprimanded him, the situation now was still not at its worst. If he left right now, that would be a panicky move, and it would cause the entire situation to worsen.

"Is the wine nice?" Gu Yue Yao Ji laughed sinisterly, staring at Fang Yuan, "Aren't you going to explain?"

Fang Yuan slowly put down his cup, raising his head and looking at Gu Yue Yao Ji's broken arm.

The old are the most cunning, this is extremely true.

To preserve her life, Gu Yue Yao Ji broke her own arm, and under the name of being injured, she avoided the clan mission of entering the battlefield.

This happened in Fang Yuan's previous life as well, but to think she did the same thing once again.

Her act of sacrificing one limb to save her life, was indeed effective. It prevented her from getting killed by the thunder crown wolf and not participating in the chase, thus keeping herself alive. However, right now she was finding problems with Fang Yuan—one aspect was due to old grudges, but mostly was because she wanted to bring the attention to Fang Yuan and reduce people's attention on herself.

"What do you want me to explain? Explain how you broke your own limb just to preserve your miserable life?" Fang Yuan sneered.

"WHAT?!" Gu Yue Yao Ji was shocked and enraged, standing up from her seat.

She stared with both eyes wide open, pointing at Fang Yuan's nose, shrilling, "You little rascal! How dare you accuse me like this, this is blatant defamation, slander!! How can you be so shameless? How can our Gu Yue clan have such a joke like you?"

"Gu Yue Yao Ji!" Gu Yue Bo's expression changed, shouting, "Sit down at once, we have an important guest here, how can you scream and shout freely like this?"

Gu Yue Yao Ji wanted to continue scolding, but on seeing Gu Yue Bo's dim expression, she could only swallow the words she was about to spit out.

She stared angrily at Fang Yuan, sitting down reluctantly.

Gu Yue Bo settled Yao Ji's problem, then turned to look at Fang Yuan, "Elder Fang Yuan, I need an explanation. During the attack of the wolf tide, where were you?"

"Fang Yuan... he's Fang Yuan?" Tie Xue Leng's eyes shone with surprise. In Jia Jin Sheng's mysterious disappearance, Fang Yuan had played an important role. Before coming here, Tie Xue Leng had already gotten much intel from Jia Fu. But to think that this young elder was Fang Yuan himself. At once, Tie Xue Leng's heart became interested.

He had solved numerous cases and could see the peculiarity from all the traces of evidence, to guess the actual fact. From everyone's expression, he could tell the truth behind Fang Yuan's sudden evasion from battle.

But the truth that everyone knew was only scratching the surface, what is the utter reality?

Regardless of what the truth is, Fang Yuan's answer would reveal a fragment of his inner thought. That would be very helpful in solving the case later.

Sensing Tie Xue Leng's attention on him, Fang Yuan's heart tightened, but his expression remained the same.

He looked at everyone plainly, and a mocking smile appeared on his face, "There's not much to explain. Since clan elder asked, I'll just say it out. I was extremely frightened back then. The stressed accumulated during this extensive period, as well as my fear of death that had reached its limits. I could not endure it, I was cowardly and weak, I hid in a corner and no longer dared to enter the frontlines."

Once he said so, everyone was dumbfounded.

They had expected Fang Yuan to use all sorts of excuses and reasons, and were prepared to expose his lies and criticize Fang Yuan. But to think he admitted it directly!

"Any kind of lie, as long as it is not true, will have loopholes. Furthermore, Tie Xue Leng is here..." Fang Yuan's expression was calm, looking down and staring at the wine in his cup.

Tie Xue Leng's expression turned weird. He subconsciously frowned, and a sense of loathing and antipathy rose in his heart.

"This young man, he has an inbred demonic nature!"

Chapter 172: No one more suited than Fang Yuan!

At the banquet, it was utter silence.

Everyone was stunned, staring at Fang Yuan blankly.

They had not expected him to reply like this, directly admitting it so honestly.

"He's too young after all, actually saying such words."

"Hmph, once he said that, it means his entire political career is ruined."

"From now on, this Fang Yuan is no threat anymore..."

The clan elders furiously assessed.

At this point into the wolf tide, the outcome had already been decided. In the next few months, there will only be small wolf packs moving about. As the lightning lycan continues to call them back, as well the the Gu Masters killing them, the lightning wolves would basically vanish completely by the end of the year.

But conflicts never end.

At places with people, there are interests. And where there are interests involved, there are conflicts.

During the wolf tide, it is the struggle between man and wolf. But now that the toughest part of the wolf tide is over, the clan's internal struggles surface above the water, turning into internal strifes.The wolf tide assaulting the village caused many Gu Masters to die. Some factions were destroyed, and the interests they once held, naturally has to be distributed.

Among the Gu Yue clan higher-ups, there were originally many clan elders to divide the interest cake of the entire village. But now that only Fang Yuan and the other elders amounting to less than ten remained, that cake was still whole and intact.

To split this large cake among themselves, they would have to compete against one another. Political battles, although not as flashy or bloody as the wolf tide, was full of schemes, plotting and setting traps; it was difficult and harsh.

At first, Fang Yuan as the only newly advanced elder, had a strong momentum and attracted great attention. But now that he admitted his mistake, it completely ruined his political career; it was tantamount to giving up the chance to compete for this interest cake with the other clan elders.

At once, Fang Yuan's threat level towards the other clan elders became much lower.

Their gaze towards Fang Yuan showed that the pressure they felt towards him had reduced.

At this time, clan leader Gu Yue Bo sighed, "Since Fang Yuan himself admitted to it, as clan leader, I have to punish you for the act of running away from battle. According to the clan ancestor's rules, runaways will be stripped of their clan elder status, but the final result shall be decided by me and the other clan elders. We'll decide on your punishment after a discussion. But regardless of the result, I hope you can accept it."

The others showed a weird expression.

Fang Yuan nodded, not speaking, as if he had submitted to fate.

Gu Yue Yao Ji broke her own arm to save her life, this was decisive and ruthless. Fang Yuan was the same, except he lost even more, giving up his clan elder status.

His greatest problem now, is the sudden appearance of the Tie family father and daughter. If he got involved in the political turmoil now, facing suppression from other elders, his situation would get even more dangerous.

"Letting go, willingness to let go, among taking and letting go, that is life. The identity of clan elder was to cultivate better, that is its only purpose to me. To pursue eternal life I walked on the demonic path, I am willing to discard my own life. What else can I not discard? Clan elder status, hmph..."

Fang Yuan did not feel a shred of regret or annoyance.

This was the wisest decision.Moreover, although there's a punishment, it would definitely be minimized.

After all, there were little clan elders left, and as a Rank three Gu Master, his strength was greatly valued. The clan leader has to punish him on one end, but also needs to borrow his strength to stabilize the entire village's circumstance, thus he also needed to give in to Fang Yuan.

As for the other clan elders, Fang Yuan had stepped out of this political contest and no longer held any threat. They would not offend Fang Yuan anymore. After all, if they force Fang Yuan to retaliate, isn't it finding trouble for themselves?

"Although there is the clan system, but what is a system? Hehe, a system is just a tool to maintain the interests of those in power. On one hand it governs and divides the interest of the lower levels, but it is also the rules that contain the higher-ups as they compete against each other." Fang Yuan laughed coldly. These matters, he was clear as day, the truth was transparent to him.

"The most crucial point now, is the Tie family father and daughter. Fuck, they came much earlier than I had anticipated, even before the wolf tide is completely gone. Hmph! But such a behavior perfectly fits Tie Xue Leng's hatred towards evil, and his selflessness in fighting crime."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan felt a strong pressure.

Even though Tie Xue Leng is injured now, his battle strength was not something Fang Yuan could compete against. A starving dying camel is larger than a horse, it is this logic.

"I need to leave the village, but I also need to avoid the pursuit of the Tie father and daughter pair, how can I get out of this predicament?"

Fang Yuan was vexed.

This Tie family father and daughter was not as easy to confuse as Jia Fu. Moreover, Fang Yuan's cultivation was too low. Even if he had a thousand and one plans, what could he do without actual strength?

Rank three and five, it was a world of difference.

"Everyone, I have something to say." At this point, the silent Gu Yue Mo Chen suddenly said.His expression was pale as he had dragged his injured body to the banquet, and he did not drink wine, only sipping tea.

But what he said next, shocked people to death, "There's something I have to be honest about. Elder Fang Yuan did not manage to enter the battlefield, and that was due to me."

"What?"

At once, the other clan elders were shocked.

"Oh, what do you mean?" Gu Yue Bo asked.

Fang Yuan sent a glance over, hiding his shock.

Why would this Gu Yue Mo Chen stand up for himself?

During this wolf tide, the Mo faction inheritor Gu Yue Mo Bei had already died unfortunately.

Even though the Mo faction had to the greatest of their ability, protected Mo Bei. On the battlefield, surprises were aplenty. Moreover, during the wolf tide, everyone was in danger, sometimes they can't even take care of themselves, what more towards others?

Gu Yue Mo Chen sighed, "To speak the truth, my granddaughter Gu Yue Mo Yan had fallen deep in love with elder Fang Yuan. Before this, she had come to beg me, kneeling on the ground and crying, not willing to see Fang Yuan die on the battlefield. I only have one granddaughter, thus out of selfishness, I kept Fang Yuan in my estate and knocked him out. It was only until we chased the lightning crown wolf that I let him out. Thus, everything was due to me, it is my fault. It has nothing to do with Fang Yuan."

"What?"

"Oh, is that really it?"

The clan elders were suspicious.

Gu Yue Mo Chen's words were quite a stretch; it was rather unbelievable.

"Love and relationship among youngsters is common," Gu Yue Bo nodded, staring at Fang Yuan with deep meaning, wanting to find out some clues from his expression.

But Fang Yuan looked down with a calm expression. There was nothing to see.

Clan leader was disappointed.The other clan elders exchanged glances, not understanding why Gu Yue Mo Chen was so defensive of Fang Yuan.

Him saying this in order to aid Fang Yuan, it meant that he had sacrificed his own reputation and ruined his own political prospect!!

Gu Yue Mo Chen continued, "In order to protect my reputation, elder fang Yuan willingly let himself suffer the injustice. But I have already erred once, how can I make a mistake once more? This is the truth. As for the punishment, I implore lord clan leader to consider. I admit my mistake and as with the rules, if my clan elder status is to be stripped, I have no objections."

Clan leader quickly waved his hand, saying, "Elder Mo Chen has worked hard all these years. What you did was understandable, humans are not grass or wood, how can we not have feelings? Now that our clan is greatly weakened, we need loyal and strong elders like you. But this is still your own selfishness, thus the punishment still needs to be decided. We have an important guest today, let's not talk about this now. Come, brother Tie, I and the clan elders shall offer you a toast!"

Saying so, Gu Yue Bo stood up.

The other clan elders stood up as well, raising their cups.

"Everyone is too kind. I still have to trouble you all later, I hope I can seek your understanding." Tie Xue Leng did not put on airs, standing up and drinking his wine.

...

In the courtyard of the Mo faction, flora and fauna were abundant. The artificial mountain had a spring flowing with crystal clear water.

In the night sky, the moon hung high in the sky like a plate.

The banquet had long ended.

Fang Yuan sat in the cooling pavilion as he listened to the sound of the flowing water, and he placed down his tea cup with a plain expression.

Sitting opposite him was Gu Yue Mo Chen. After the banquet was over, he had invited Fang Yuan over for a discussion.

"Come, have another cup of tea, this bamboo leaf clear water tea is good in eliminating hangovers." Gu Yue Mo Chen laughed, pouring personally into Fang Yuan's cup.

Fang Yuan's expression was calm, and on seeing the cup being filled again, he said, "Indeed a good cure for hangovers."

Saying so, he looked outside the pavilion, only to see that the pale white moon had radiated the grounds with its moonlight. Under the moon, the pavilion was quiet and graceful, but in the wind there were lurking shadows, showing how the Mo faction courtyard was turning from a prosperous state, to a declining one.

During the banquet, Fang Yuan had already understood Gu Yue Mo Chen's intention. Seeing this scene, he was even more sure of himself.

The Mo faction had no inheritor left!

Once Gu Yue Mo Bei died, the entire Mo faction would lose its inheritor.

Although Mo Bei still had his sister Mo Yan, the clan rules was that, since ancient times, it favored males over females, and the assets can only be inherited by a male and not female.

Even if Gu Yue Mo Yan gets to Rank three next time and advances to clan elder, her assets do not represent the Mo faction, but only her own. If she married anyone, this asset will be transferred to under her husband's name.

If they lost their inheritor, a clan's political influence would have no prospects, and no one would join them.

The Mo faction had already fallen into difficult circumstances, on the verge of breaking down.

But heaven always left a way, and the Mo faction was not truly at its wits end; there was still a sliver of hope.

This hope lies in Gu Yue Mo Yan's hands.

Although she is a female, she can marry someone.

If the son-in-law marries into the Mo faction, he would have an acceptable status, and can inherit the Mo faction!

Seeing that Fang Yuan had no inclination to mention it, Gu Yue Mo Chen scolded this crafty lad internally, but had to speak, "I wonder what elder Fang Yuan thinks of my Mo faction?"

He had an unspeakable grief.

Ever since his injury, his cultivation had fallen to Rank two, without any chance of ever regaining Rank three.

He could only rely on his Gu worm to conceal his true aura. But paper cannot cover fire; he would be exposed one day.

His only inheritor had died, while he himself was Rank two and would lose his clan elder identity. Gu Yue Mo Chen needed someone who could hold the fort to sustain their faction.

Back then, he had both authority and status, thus the Mo faction controlled a large amount of the interest cake. But now that the clan's factions were reorganising themselves, he did not want any more interests. As long as he can defend what he already has, that would be the biggest victory.

He pondered left and right, and the most suitable person was Fang Yuan without doubt!

Chapter 173: White form immortal snake

Sunset clouds are blown away as cool wind fills the air, and the jade disc spins silently in the milky way.

Bai Ning Bing looked out from the window and gazed at the night sky.

A bright and sparkling moon was shining in the sky. Occasionally, wolf howls could be heard in the distance, adding some bleakness to the peaceful moonlight.

In the study room, the Bai clan leader was sitting at a side with a dazed expression.

Just a moment ago, Bai Ning Bing told him about the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique.

"Northern Dark Ice Soul....ten absolute aptitudes...." The Bai clan leader mumbled constantly.

"I have already sensed that my end is nearing, my aperture is gradually unable to endure the burden. These past few years, I've truly caused you much problems!" Bai Ning Bing softly sighed.

His expression was calm. No longer was there the abnormal reckless and crazed state as before. What replaced them was tranquility and peace.

This tranquility and peace came from his heart.

He had found his path and was no longer perplexed by life and death.People mature over time, and the stimulation from life and death could further speed up this process.

Moonlight fell down like flowing water, illuminating Bai Ning Bing's fair skin. Under the flowing radiance, his two blue eyes shone with depth.

He was like a beautiful young man from a painting, with white hair and white clothes like the immortals in the clouds, causing people to look intently.

"How could this happen? You were clearly A grade with 99% primeval essence when your aptitude was tested. It absolutely wasn't the Northern Dark Ice Soul." The Bai clan leader was still refusing to accept it.

"It was indeed so. But one day when I was cultivating, my aptitude suddenly advanced. I checked the ancient scrolls and records in the clan and found some information on this; every 99% A grade aptitude has the possibility of advancing to ten absolute aptitudes while cultivating," Bai Ning Bing said.

"All ten defy the heavens, and the heavens can't tolerate them. Even Ren Zu's ten children didn't have a good end. Sigh, is there really no way to salvage it?" Bai clan leader felt pity and regret when he looked at the beautiful boy in front of him.

He was the clan's pride and their hope to rise up in power. However, his life was already nearing its end. Despite glowing brightly, he was like a firework which could only shine splendidly for one single moment.

"There are no ways to evade my impending doom, but there are some ways to delay it. However, all these methods need many years to prepare, which I don't have."

Bai Ning Bing said all this and gave a light laugh, as if the one being discussed about was not him, but some irrelevant outsider.

"Don't worry. Who doesn't die? True immortality doesn't exist! As long as we live our life interestingly, it is enough." He was instead consoling the clan leader.

"I cannot accept this! I absolutely cannot! Damn it, my Bai clan has been suppressed by the Gu Yue clan for centuries, we finally found hope but it ends up like this! No, there is still hope!"

Bai clan leader's voice got louder and louder till suddenly, his expression turned firm as if he had decided on something.

"Follow me, I will bring you to a place...." He stood up and said.

After a while.

The bright moonlight shone upon a deep pool.

"This is the spirit spring?" Bai Ning Bing asked. He had been led by the Bai clan leader as they went through a long secret pathway, and finally arrived here.

"Indeed. This is our clan's restricted area, the location of the spirit spring. You also know this—every clan's foundation is established upon a natural spirit spring, where the primeval stones produced by it will be used to provide for their cultivation. Our Bai clan can only be considered a small-medium scale clan, and only by annexing Gu Yue and Xiong clan as well as possessing at least three springs can we become a large scale clan," Bai clan leader sighed.

"Then clan leader, what did you bring me here for?"

Bai clan leader's face revealed a complex expression, and as he turned around to look at Bai Ning Bing, his expression contained some hesitation, "I had originally never thought of bringing you here. However, the affairs of the world are hard to anticipate. To think, you would end up possessing Northern Dark Ice Soul! Your only chance at living lies within this spring."

"What is in this spring?" Bai Ning Bing asked.

"A great Immortal!" Bai clan leader said with a deep voice.

"Great Immortal?" Bai Ning Bing was flabbergasted.

"Great Immortal is its title. It is a snake Gu left by our Bai clan's first generation ancestor. It likes cleanliness, and its food is the water of spirit spring. It has always been secretly living in the spirit spring," Bai clan leader introduced.

"Before the first generation ancestor passed away, he set up a secret inheritance and left behind this snake Gu as a clue. If you can get the approval of the Great Immortal, it will open the secret inheritance for you. But if you can't receive its approval...." The Bai clan leader stopped his sentence in the middle.

"What happens then?" Bai Ning Bing asked.

Bai clan leader's expression turned grave and he said, "It will kill you!"

At the same time, Gu Yue village.

Inside the room, Tie Ruo Nan kept her recon Gu and nodded with satisfaction, "The environment here is pretty good, it's rather clean."

The 'clean' she referred to wasn't talking about the cleanliness of the room, but was pointing at the lack of surveillance.

It was impossible to say that there absolutely wasn't any surveillance.

After all, Tie Xue Leng was rank five, so he possessed too great of a threat. Hence, there was a necessity for some precautions.

However, Gu Yue clan's defensive and surveillance measures were just at the right amount and the level was quite low too, not creating any feelings of provocation and aversion. It could even be taken as excessively earnest and passionate reception, which was why Tie Ruo Nan gave the assessment of 'rather clean'.

Tie Xue Leng slightly nodded, "Ruo Nan, you have followed me for so long and have learned many things. However, some things can only be learned by taking actions and not just by spectating from the sides. Hence, I handed this case to you."

"Father, I will definitely work hard and give my best!"

"Good. Then, let me ask you, what should your next step be?" Tie Xue Leng was deliberately testing her.

Tie Ruo Nan smiled. She turned around and gazed at the moon through the window, "The moon is beautiful tonight. Dad, can I have the pleasure to take you around this Gu Yue village?"

Upon hearing this, Tie Xue Leng revealed a gratifying smile.

When starting out on a case, it was not urgent to understand the details of the case. The first step to solve a case was to survey the surroundings.

The father and daughter pair slowly walked through the streets. After resisting the most terrifying attacks of the wolf tide, Gu Yue clan was now in a wretched state.

There were collapsed bamboo buildings and bloodstains all around. Junks were piled up all over the place and feeble moaning sounds of crippled people could be heard from time to time.

The Tie father and daughter pair walked around the village without saying any words.

"Fang Yuan, you bastard, fuck off!" Suddenly, a loud roar came from within a courtyard.

The Tie father and daughter stopped walking.

After a long while, the courtyard gate opened and Fang Yuan walked out while rubbing his nose with a vague smile on his face.

"Hello, little brother Fang Yuan." Tie Xue Leng took the initiative to send his greetings.

"Junior pays his respects to lord divine investigator." Fang Yuan constrained his smile and cupped his hands.

"Little brother, we are new here and don't know the place well. Is it possible for little brother to tell us a thing or two?" Tie Xue Leng suddenly asked.

Tie Ruo Nan glanced at her father, but she didn't make any comments.

Fang Yuan's gaze hardened, he was just about to go meet them but this opportunity was delivered right up to him.

"Both of you have travelled a great distance and suffered hardships to come and solve the case, the whole village ought to help you. Please follow me." Fang Yuan spoke directly without showing the slightest evil intention, and walked in front. ...

The spirit spring was raging like the boiling water.

All of a sudden, the springwater rose up like a tidal wave.

After it reached a certain height, the spirit spring scattered and splashed in all directions. A slender white snake, its whole body covered with snow white scales, tread on the waves and revealed its elegant appearance.

Its eyes were like jade, cold and indifferent. On the two sides of its head were a pair of long whiskers, floating like celestial ribbons.

Rank five white form immortal snake Gu!

"I pay respects to Great Immortal!" Bai clan leader emotionally kneeled on the ground, and at the same time anxiously urged, "Bai Ning Bing, why are you not kneeling down?"

"I will never kneel before a Gu!" Bai Ning Bing coldly snorted, his body standing upright and tall.

Although the white form immortal snake Gu released an ethereal cold grandeur with heavy killing intent concealed within, Bai Ning Bing was not the least bit afraid. His two blue pupils directly stared at its snake eyes.

Time seemed to have stopped at this moment.

The spirit spring and the Bai clan leader had become insignificant background objects.

Under the bright moonlight, the picturesque youngster with blue pupils and the silver whiskered white snake gazed at each other.

After a good while, the white snake suddenly gave a long cry and turned into a white rainbow, slamming into Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing's body jolted. The white light entered his aperture and turned into a white snake.

The white snake occupied the central area of his primeval essence, and with its tyrannical attitude, all the surrounding Gu were immediately forced to the side.

"This situation..." Bai clan leader stood up with a puzzled expression, "It doesn't match what the clan's secret records say."

According to the clan's secret records, once a Gu Master obtained approval, the white form immortal snake Gu would fly with the inheritor and open the inheritance in the sky.

However, the current situation was somewhat weird.

The white form immortal snake Gu took the initiative to enter Bai Ning Bing's aperture and didn't kill him, which should mean that it had approved of him. But why didn't it carry Bai Ning Bing and fly to the sky?

Could it be that the secret records were wrong?

Bai clan leader couldn't make sense of it....Time quietly flew by.

"That more or less sums up everything about Gu Yue village. There is the underground cave, but that is a restricted area of the clan and outsiders aren't allowed entry." Fang Yuan said.

He looked at the bright moon in the sky and continued, "It is getting late, please go and rest, you need to have the energy to investigate tomorrow, right?"

"Hahaha, Elder Fang Yuan is correct. We are really thankful for Elder Fang Yuan's directions, please go and take a rest," Tie Xue Leng said.

"In that case, I will take my leave." Fang Yuan cupped his hands before directly leaving.

Tie Xue Leng looked at Fang Yuan's figure with interest, and only after Fang Yuan turned into a corner, did he take back his gaze.

"Ruo Nan, what do you think of this Fang Yuan?" He suddenly asked.

"I don't like him, my intuition tells me he is covered in shadows." The young girl frowned.

Tie Xue Leng nodded his head, "I know you have the Intuition Gu which strengthens your intuition, but we need definite evidence to solve a case. Just relying on intuition alone won't be convincing. Don't always depend on your intuition, I do not want you to use the intuition Gu to solve this case."

"Yes, father."

Chapter 174: Junior divine investigator

Tie Xue Leng said again, "Now, analyze this person Fang Yuan."

"Father, you suspect it is Fang Yuan?" Tie Ruo Nan was stunned, but continued, "He is a very logical and intelligent person, and when he introduced the village to us, every word he said was appropriate and well organised. Gasp!..."

Tie Ruo Nan suddenly drew in a mouthful of cold air.

She frowned, "I didn't notice this earlier, but after you just reminded me, I realised it! This Fang Yuan is too good at speaking. Everything he said is objectively the truth, abandoning his personal feelings. Standing at a bystander's perspective, and describing calmly. Not allowing others to find flaws in his words, thus not able to get additional clues. His words were very.... very.... very clean."

The young girl hesitated, before using the word 'clean'.

Tie Xue Leng nodded, but then shook his head, "He did not abandon his feelings. Everyone has feelings, and even a cold blooded murderer has feelings. He only concealed his personal feelings very well, and was in full control of his emotions. This lad has a demonic nature."

"Demonic nature?""That's right, think about it. He spoke the truth during the banquet, saying he was frightened and did not dare to enter the battlefield. Tell me, if it was a normal person, would they do that?" Tie Xue Leng asked.

Tie Ruo Nan shook her head, "No, Gu Masters put the clan's honor and their own reputation higher than their own lives. But, that might not be certain, for in history there have also been many people who sacrificed their own reputation, right?"

"That's right, but who were those people?" Tie Xue Leng's gaze was deep.

Tie Ruo Nan considered, before her expression changed, "They were all outstanding individuals!"

"That's correct. Throughout history, those who sacrificed their own reputations only had two aims. One was that they had a greater aim in mind, and compared to their aim, reputation is worth nothing. The other is to preserve themselves, defaming themselves to prevent suspicion."

Tie Ruo Nan's eyes shone, "Father, you are saying?"

"You are thinking too much. I just feel that this young man is very interesting, but too bad he is only a C grade..." Tie Xue Leng said.

The moonlight was like water on this night.

Fang Yuan walked on the empty street, his footsteps slightly heavy but filled with determination.

After interacting with Tie Xue Leng earlier, he was indeed what the rumors said. This Tie Xue Leng had a gaze that could see through the world, and his intelligence and wits were deep like a chasm. He swept through the Southern Border for tens of years, establishing his famed name; he really was an outstanding talent.

Wanting to remove his suspicions in front of such a person was extremely difficult. As long as they had enough time, they would definitely discover the truth!

"Now is a race against time. But, Mo faction's recruitment, I can make good use of it."

Not long ago in the Mo faction pavilion, Fang Yuan had given absurd demands. In return for marrying Mo Yan, he wanted a hundred thousand primeval stones, ten rare Gu worms and each at least Rank three.

This made Gu Yue Mo Chen furious.

He was marrying away his precious granddaughter, but Fang Yuan still had more demands?!

Such a shameless way to ask for gifts, and so greedy, it was really the last straw!

Thus, the discussion faltered, and he chased Fang Yuan out.

Fang Yuan left immediately without any inclination to stay.

He knew Mo Chen's intention, thus he would definitely compromise. His absurd demands were just a way of bargaining, paying the lowest price when buying, and asking for the highest price when selling.

"But this matter has equal benefits and demerits. Although with more primeval stones I can feed the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, my original plan to get out of the political spiral would be ruined. In tonight's banquet, Gu Yue Mo Chen sacrificed himself to salvage my political career. From then on, he might face all sorts of elder's suppression."

Gu Yue village's political situation now was: Clan leader was healthy, while for the two important elders, Gu Yue Chi Lian was dead but the Chi faction was not finished yet, as inheritor Chi Cheng was still alive. At the same time there was still Gu Yue Chi Zhong, an elder from the same faction. But Mo faction lost its inheritor and Mo Chen was heavily injured, falling to Rank two, unable to even keep his clan elder status.

The two formerly large factions had already gone downhill. The medicine faction in contrast were mostly healing Gu Masters. As supports they had little sacrifice while still keeping most of their strength, and were on the verge of rising up.

Medicine faction was originally the clan leader's faction, but now it had the ability to be independent. Regardless of whether Gu Yue Yao Ji chooses to be independant or rely on the clan elder, in order to strengthen themselves, they would need to snatch and merge. And the weakened Chi and Mo faction were the best targets.

If they did not strike now, later on when the two factions stabilize internally it would be much more difficult.

"Being in the human world, many things are not up to me, why not just let down my hair and sail away to the seas? Sailing with the winds and breaking waves as I travel thirty thousand Li, that is the true demonic path I take!" Fang Yuan raised his head, looking at the moon as he sighed.

He wanted to get away from the political spiral, but Gu Yue Mo Chen dragged him back by force. He faced pressure from all the factions, and Tie Xue Leng was already starting to solve the case. On the other hand, Bai Ning Bing had already regained his new arm.

Like a boat travelling in the darkness with danger lurking everywhere, how was he to open up a path for himself?

...

The next day.

"What? You said that the person who murdered Jia Jin Sheng had already been found and was killed already?" Tie Ruo Nan felt extremely perturbed.

This morning, she had woken up early and officially started to solve the case.

But to think that the first information she got, was that the killer had already been sentenced.

"That's right, the killer is a demonic Gu Master. He once assassinated our clan's rising star and tried to kill the genius, thus he was killed on the spot." A clan elder provided the information.

"Is that really so? Did he admit personally that he was Jia Jing Sheng's killer?" Tie Ruo Nan frowned deeply. Beside her, Tie Xue Leng wore a copper mask as he stood like a statue.

"He didn't. But, if it's not him, who else could it be?" The clan elder shrugged.

Tie Ruo Nan thought internally, "This is all an assumption, there is no real proof. But whether it is the truth or not, this demonic Gu Master has to be investigated clearly. Most likely, this is a lead that will bring us to the truth!"

Thinking of this, Tie Ruo Nan raised her head abruptly, "Where is he buried? I want to inspect the corpse!"

In a simple and torn coffin, there was a corpse within.

The rotting smell assaulted noses, and clan servants and Gu Masters were so disgusted that they ran far away to hide.

Tie family father and daughter acted as if they were unaffected, and Tie Ruo Nan's eyes glowed brightly, excitedly stretching her hand and inspecting.

A person's corpse has lots of traces. At times, one or two small injuries would be the evidence needed to point out the murderer!

On this corpse, there were many injuries, but the person's appearance was still clear, and he was still wearing his original clothes.

Tie Ruo Nan checked for ages, and only then did she get up with a lingering interest.

"Anything?" Tie Xue Leng asked lightly, testing her secretly.

"Gu Yue clan thinks this person is Jia Jin Sheng's killer, thus they kept the corpse well. There's a huge problem in this corpse," Tie Ruo Nan answered.

"He's a middle-aged man, right arm thicker than the left; both his hands have a thick callus. Seeing how his callus is distributed, they are uneven. There are many injuries on his body, numerous fatal wounds, showing the intense battle he had before death. But on his body there are also a lot of hidden injuries, especially his left foot having three less toes, this is left behind from many years ago."

Saying so, she continued deducing, "He was most likely a hunter. There are many evidences—his disproportional left and right side and the callus on his hands shows that he's an experienced bowman. There are many injures made by wild beasts on his body, like claw marks and bites, showing he often fought against beasts. His clothes are not the traditional Gu Master clothes, and his shoes are even more interesting, weaved from bamboo hemp grass. This kind of grass only grows near Qing Mao bamboo, and Qing Mao mountain only produces Qing Mao bamboo; other than that, in the surrounding mountains, there is no bamboo hemp grass.

"So what are you getting at?" Tie Xue Leng pursued.

"Before this person became a demonic Gu Master, he was a hunter. From his clothes, he was most likely a resident hunter on Qing Mao mountain," Tie Ruo Nan's eyes shone brightly.

"Why do you think he is a resident here? If it is the grass shoes, he could've killed the villagers here and worn them," Tie Xue Leng rebuked.

"That's not it. The most special part of his clothes is the shoes, because if they were taken by force, most would not fit his size perfectly. But look at this, two disproportionate legs and yet the shoes fit nicely, this is made just for him. He has three less toes on his leg feet, thus the left grass shoe is shorter. His stump is very cleanly cut and sharp. I assume it is most likely due to stepping on a trap by mistake," Tie Ruo Nan said.

Tie Xue Leng did not deny it nor confirm it, and did not even give any criticism.

Like what he said earlier, he left it to Tie Ruo Nan to solve the case.

Tie Ruo Nan continued saying, "With this conjecture, we can go to the surrounding hamlets and investigate. We might find more clues... wait!"

Just when she was about to speak, the young girl's expression stiffened.

She suddenly remembered, this Qing Mao mountain had just undergone a wolf tide calamity. Even the villages were heavily damaged, not to mention those hamlets?

She knew that using this method to find out the person's identity and information bore little hope.

"But even if the chances are slim, as long as there is a possibility for success, I must try!" It was the young girl's first individual case, and she was full of drive.

But half a day passed, and she returned empty-handed. This wolf tide was the largest and most horrifying one yet. So many hamlets had zero survivors, and this brought great trouble to her investigations.

"This lead is gone. What are you going to do next?" Tie Xue Leng asked at an appropriate time.

The young girl gritted her teeth, and in her tone there was stubbornness and tenacity, "No, it is not over yet. Father you said it yourself, the true lead is often hidden more deeply, and as long as we continue to excavate, it will appear."

"This demonic Gu Master's death is strange. Firstly, why did he assault Fang Zheng? What did Fang Zheng do to offend him, causing him to assassinate him with his life, under the situation which was basically an assured death? Moreover, he is a local, but after his death, why did no one recognise him?"

Hearing her words, Tie Xue Leng was a little surprised.

"Child, you have truly grown up," the divine investigator sighed, and in his tone there was contentment and gratification.

Chapter 175: Increasing pressure

"You're asking me why that Gu Master came to kill me? How would I know!" Facing Tie Ruo Nan's questioning, Fang Zheng blinked innocently.

"If you have done something, I hope you won't conceal the truth. Because your words, even though they might seem insignificant, can have great help towards solving the case," the young girl said sincerely.

Fang Zheng shook his head. "I'm very perplexed too. During that period, I was cultivating non-stop, so how could I attract any assassinations? But afterwards, the people around me realized that this demonic Gu Master could have been hired by the other two clans, to kill a rising star like myself. You also know the rivalry between us and the Bai clan and Xiong clan. Especially the Xiong clan, they are the greatest suspects as they had once recruited demonic Gu Masters into their clan."

"Xiong clan huh..." Tie Ruo Nan became a little discouraged after hearing this, since the Xiong clan had already been eliminated by the wolf tide. It seems that this lead is lost as well.

Suddenly, murmurs came from outside the room.

"Quick, look there, isn't that people from the Xiong clan?"

"I thought the Xiong clan was exterminated, how can there be any envoys coming here?!"

Xiong clan envoy's appearance caused a vivid discussion among the village, as people talked with one another.

Soon, news came from the clan leader pavilion.

"Xiong clan still has a large number of survivors."

"They retreated on their own, using a Gu that their ancestor left behind, concealing many people at the same time, cheating death!"

"These scumbags, retreating and avoiding battle, causing the wolf tide to come to us."

"Hmph, these Xiong clan people may look rough and large, but their hearts are devious on the inside. Wanting to borrow the power of the wolf tide to weaken us, they are too despicable!"

Gu Yue clansmen were furious.

The appearance of the Xiong clan envoy had caused the Qing Mao mountain's political distribution to undergo a complete shift.

What was thought to be a two-sided competition between Bai clan and Gu Yue clan in the end remained a three-way competition.

But one would understand once they thought about it. The Xiong clan had survived for hundreds of years without falling, they had their own foundations too. Which clan did not have an ancestor, and a trump card?

After the Xiong clan envoy left, Gu Yue Bo immediately called for a clan elder meeting.

"These Xiong clan bastards, they really are nothing good. To think they retreated immediately!"

"Can't look down on anyone indeed. Xiong clan had always ranked behind our clan and Bai clan, and was the weakest among the forces on Qing Mao mountain. But to think they had such a scheme, we have to be more careful from now on."

"They wanted to borrow the strength of the wolf tide to eliminate us. They nearly got us this time, if not for that lightning lycan, we might not have lost so many elders. These people deserve to die!"

"If it wasn't for the Tie divine investigator appearing, two clan leaders might've died. We cannot let them off simply."

"Asking for compensation is a must. It was us and Bai clan working together to settle the problem of the lightning lycan. But to ask for compensation, we need to first discuss and formulate a sum."

The clan elders spoke one after another, discussing until they had a conclusion.

Gu Yue clan would dispatch an envoy towards the Xiong clan. They have to observe Xiong clan's remaining strength.

If Xiong clan was strong, they would join forces with the Bai clan. If the Xiong clan was weak, they might send people to eliminate them and steal the spirit spring.

"So then, who would be suitable enough to be dispatched to Xiong clan?" Gu Yue Bo looked around, asking, "Which clan elder would shoulder this responsibility!"

The hall immediately became silent.

The clan elders look around at each other. No one was willing to go.

The internal conflict was at its peak now, and it was the most crucial moment for the factions to divide the interest cake. If they went to the Xiong clan, their faction would be without a leader and others would make use of the opportunity. When they return, all would've been decided, so by then who would they complain to?

"This old one feels that, to go to the Xiong clan, someone of seniority and experience must go, it has to be someone who can hold his own. Among all of us here, only elder Mo Chen can take on this role!" Gu Yue Yao Ji suddenly said.

Gu Yue Mo Chen snorted, rebuking, "Speaking of qualification, lord Yao Ji has much more experience than me. Especially in terms of fame, I cannot compete at all, I admit complete defeat. Going to the Xiong clan, it seems we will have to trouble lord Yao Ji after all."

"Elder Mo Chen is extremely right, I recommend lord Yao Ji." A clan elder stood up.

"I feel that lord Mo Chen is a more suitable candidate." Another elder immediately rebuked.

The scene was chaotic.

Gu Yue Bo stood at the leader's seat, staring coldly without making a sound.

The medicine faction already had intentions of detaching into its own force, no longer under his control. Thus he did not want to help either, and merely observed the scene.

This was the first contest between the medicine faction and the Mo faction.

The two had their respective political allies, but the current situation was that both leaders made much compromises as well as exchange of benefits. But on a whole, the medicine faction was stronger.

Gu Yue Yao Ji's reputation as well as the Chi faction's inclination, caused this situation.

Gu Yue Bo stared coldly, noting in his heart the factions that each individual belonged to.

As the clan leader, he did not want to see his authority being reduced, and these elders were his competitors. But now he had decided to merely observe, and not strike yet.

"Mo faction controls too much power and resources, and now that they have lost their inheritor, the medicine faction jumped out hurriedly and tried to attack them. Thus, the most crucial aspect of this contest is all on one person."

Gu Yue Bo thought silently, turning his gaze towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had been sitting in his seat, not saying a word.

"It seems this Fang Yuan isn't very close with the Mo faction, and has not gotten a mutual agreement on interest distribution. Otherwise, he'd have helped out already. Is this my chance?" Gu Yue Bo thought.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan suddenly stood up from his seat.

This action, attracted everyone's attention.

What he said next was a shocker. "Going as an envoy, this is an important matter involving the survival of our clan. I am willing to step up, bearing the responsibility of an envoy, and investigate the Xiong clan's current state for our clan!"

"What?"

"Fang Yuan is asking to go?"

"What is the meaning of this? Is he really stupid or acting stupid? Isn't he afraid that when he comes back, all the interests would've been distributed away already!"

The clan elders all showed expressions of shock.

Fang Yuan had his own plans. If he went to the Xiong clan, he might be able to find a chance and instigate a conflict among the three clans. Even if he can't, this is a chance to leave.

"Wait! Anyone here can be the envoy but Fang Yuan alone!" The door suddenly opened and Tie Ruo Nan walked in, barging her way in.

Fang Yuan turned his body to look, and his irises shrunk a little. He saw the Tie family father and daughter walk in, as well as two other people behind them. One looked just like Fang Yuan—it is indeed his brother Gu Yue Fang Zheng, while the other was Gu Yue Jiang He.

"What does Tie divine investigator have to enlighten us on today?" Gu Yue Bo stood up to greet him, his tone slightly unhappy. This was a Gu Yue internal discussion, how could they just barge in like that?

"Gu Yue clan leader, as well as the other elders. My daughter has already investigated the identity of the demonic Gu Master that once assaulted Gu Yue Fang Zheng," Tie Xue Leng spoke.

"Oh? Is that so..."

"That demonic Gu Master, wasn't he instigated by the Xiong clan?"

"Is there a hidden story behind this?"

"Indeed, this demonic Gu Master's true identity is a hunter from a hamlet at the base of the mountain. Only by chance did he manage to become a demonic Gu Master, his name is Wang Er. The reason why he assaulted Gu Yue Fang Zheng, is because of his brother Fang Yuan!" Saying so, Tie Ruo Nan stared intently at Fang Yuan.

"Brother, to think you are such a person!" Fang Zheng standing at one side clenched his fist, showing rage in his eyes.

"What do you mean by this, young lady?" Gu Yue Mo Chen said in a solemn voice.

"Don't tell me, Fang Yuan is the one that hired this demonic Gu Master to assassinate his own brother Fang Zheng?" Gu Yue Yao Ji showed an excited expression.Even Gu Yue Bo was taken aback, as he adjusted his posture on his seat.

"You're all mistaken." Tie Ruo Nan shook her head. "The truth is, Fang Yuan killed innocent people, murdering old man Wang's entire family, causing Wang Er to take revenge. But Wang Er did not know that Fang Yuan had a twin brother, thus he mistook Fang Zheng for Fang Yuan, and assaulted him for revenge."

"Young lady, everything needs proof," a clan elder spoke.

"Of course I have evidence. Gu Yue Jiang He, tell us everything that you know." Tie Ruo Nan was prepared for this, not panicking.

Gu Yue Jiang He sighed. He looked at the Tie family father and daughter in fear, slowly walking forward and kneeling on the ground, crying, "It is this subordinate's dereliction of duty, I seek clan leader's punishment!"

Gu Yue Bo's face was grim as water, "Say everything clearly first, do not hide anything from us!"

Back then, when Fang Yuan killed old man Wang's family, it was under Gu Yue Jiang He's area of jurisdiction, and only when he got to the spot did he discover it. Because of the clan evaluation, he suppressed this matter and did not report it. Never would he have thought that today, the matter would be exposed, dug up by Tie Ruo Nan.

"The truth is like this..." Jiang He stammered as he spoke, not adding any details into his descriptions, very simple and truthful.At this time and place, he did not dare to lie. Fang Yuan was also a clan elder, so he did not dare to exaggerate facts.

"I never would've thought that the truth would be like this!"

"Fang Yuan killed Wang Er's father, and Wang Er came to take revenge, but found Fang Zheng instead. So that's it...."

"Fang Zheng was innocently involved, and blocked the crisis for Fang Yuan."

The clan elders whispered among themselves.

Fang Zheng's clenched fist was even tighter as rage grew in his heart. He could not help but growl at Fang Yuan, "Brother, how can you take people's lives away so easily. That old man and girl, they were innocent mortals. How could you cut them down?!"

Facing his brother's accusations, Fang Yuan was indiffierent, as if he did not hear it.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was not the main point.

Fang Yuan looked at the Tie family father and daughter. Being able to discover the truth in such a short time, they were indeed divine investigators.

Regardless of what Gu worms they used, whatever method to make Jiang He submit and reveal his own secret, they had their ways.

This ability made Fang Yuan even more certain that the matter of him killing Jia Jin Sheng, would definitely be found out by the Tie father and daughter duo. It was only a matter of time. After all this is the Gu world, where Gu can be used to commit crime, and also used to solve crime.

Pressure was intensifying...

Chapter 176: The resolve to sacrifice

"Elder Fang Yuan, is it true that you massacred the whole family of old Wang?" Gu Yue Bo asked with a heavy voice from the main seat.

All the gazes were on Fang Yuan; the young elder coldly smiled, "It is indeed true."

Gu Yue Fang Zheng closed his eyes in grief.He may have killed many lightning wolves, but he had never taken any human lives. And now that he heard Fang Yuan admitting it himself, he suddenly felt that his own brother had become so unfamiliar and estranged.

In this estrangement, he also felt fear towards his brother's cruel methods and anger at the loss of innocent lives.

"Fang Yuan, do you not feel any guilt at slaughtering innocents? If you have any difficulties, you can say them out," Tie Ruo Nan spoke as she frowned. She was someone with extremely righteous character, and hated people like Fang Yuan the most.

"So what if I killed them, I don't find it necessary to tell you my story. However, at that time, I didn't know that the missing Wang Er was a demonic Gu Master. It could be said that Fang Zheng was unexpectedly implicated," Fang Yuan spoke honestly.

"Brother, aren't you going to say something to me?" Fang Zheng opened his eyes; the corners of his eyes had become red.

"What do you want me to say? Comfort you or to apologize? .....Hmph, little brother, you are too soft," Fang Yuan sneered.

"Damn it, brother... don't think you are extraordinary just by becoming an elder. I will tell you that I already have the qualifications to breakthrough to Rank three...." Fang Zheng gritted his teeth, veins popping up in his clenched fists.

"Enough!" Gu Yue Bo couldn't continue looking at this anymore and shouted, "Fang Zheng, go back, what decorum are you showing by making a fuss here?"

His words had other meaning and expressed dissatisfaction. Tie Ruo Nan couldn't sense it, but Divine Investigator Tie Xue Leng reacted immediately; he stepped forward and cupped his hands. "Gu Yue clan leader and all elders, it is indeed improper for my daughter to charge in and rush into the lords' discussion hall. This one apologizes for offending everyone!"

The elders promptly stood up and kept on saying Tie Xue Leng was too kind.

Gu Yue Bo's expression also relaxed.

Tie Xue Leng continued, "Since little brother Fang Yuan is involved in Jia Jin Sheng's case and is also a suspect, I hope he remains at the village and will not leave to the other village."

Gu Yue Bo massaged his temples and sighed, "Our Gu Yue clan really hopes we can provide a suitable explanation to lord Jia Fu. Since Divine Investigator is also requesting, I will have to request Elder Fang Yuan to not leave before you are free of suspicions. I hope you can understand."

Gu Yue Bo looked at Fang Yuan, his expression sincere. But his gaze, however, held deep meanings.

Fang Yuan might have killed the whole of old Wang's family, but they were only mortals. How could it be a crime for a Gu Master to kill these mortals? Especially if this Gu Master was an elder of the clan. Thus, there was no punishment.

"Yes." Fang Yuan glanced at Gu Yue Bo and replied expressionlessly.

...

"Damn it, it's like this again!" Tie Ruo Nan punched a tree, causing the leaves to scatter.

She was very indignant as she said with clenched teeth, "It is clearly a murder, but they are turning a blind eye to it and not giving a damn. Father, are the mortals not humans? Why do Gu Masters feel that they have the rights to kill the mortals?"

Tie Xue Leng was silent like a sculpture.

The weather was somewhat gloomy, and the wind blew and tree leaves rustled.

Tie Ruo Nan suddenly lowered her head, her expression was down. "I am sorry, father."

She apologized, "I didn't listen to your advice, and used the Intuition Gu."

"Sigh....." Divine Investigator let out a long sigh and looked at his daughter with a profound gaze, "Child, you have such hatred for evil and is full of righteousness, just like me when I was young. I am happy but also worried."

"Why are you worried?"

"Your ideals are much bigger than mine was at that time. When I was young, my ambition was to capture all the criminals and cram up the Demon Suppression Tower. But as for you, you want to make everyone equal, treating both Gu Masters and the mortals equally, causing law and order to be established in the whole world. Such ambitions and ideals are too big and also very heavy," Tie Xue Leng's words were filled with experience.

"But father, this so-called law, fairness and justice. If we don't treat everyone equally, what meaning do they have? If the young don't have ambitious dreams, then how could they be considered young? I believe it's all a matter of our own efforts. As long as I give my best, it might not necessarily be impossible to achieve!" Tie Ruo Nan spoke excitedly, her two eyes filled with hopes for the future.

Tie Xue Leng was silent for a good while, "There will be a day when you will understand. But, this is good too, young people should walk their paths by themselves. Setbacks will make you mature. Father won't interfere anymore. I only hope you can live the life you want!"

He then took out a letter and gave it to Tie Ruo Nan.

"This is....?!" Tie Ruo Nan tore open the letter and was immediately overjoyed.

This letter was from Jia Fu and it recorded every information regarding Jia Jin Sheng's case, including how Fang Yuan obtained the Liquor worm by rock gambling, how the bamboo gentleman was used to interrogate Fang Yuan, and even Fang Yuan's bidding prices at the second caravan visit where he showed business talent and received Jia Fu's recruitment offer.

Tie Ruo Nan reread the contents of 'Fang Yuan's bidding prices' multiple times; her gaze turned brighter and brighter.

"This Fang Yuan is not only fierce in his methods, but also has cruel nature and is even able to scheme deeply. My intuition tells me he is very suspicious. If he is really the killer, then he should be somewhat afraid. But the bamboo gentleman showed no changes to his lies, how did he do it?" Tie Ruo Nan muttered to herself.

"What are you preparing to do next?" Tie Xue Leng asked.

"It has been a long time since Jia Jin Sheng's death. Everything is fishy and filled with mysteries. Till now, his corpse has not been found and even the place of his death hasn't been deduced. This case is too clean, giving me no clues, except that Fang Yuan is the biggest suspect. Although the clues from Wang Er has been broken, there are no evidences to prove he is the killer. However, because there are no other clues, I can only rely on my intuition to investigate this Fang Yuan!" Tie Ruo Nan enthusiastically replied.

"You feel that Fang Yuan is suspicious?" Tie Xue Leng asked.

"Extremely suspicious!" Tie Ruo Nan immediately said, "This Fang Yuan is clearly only a C grade aptitude, but why is his cultivation speed faster than Fang Zheng's? One could say he had the help from the Liquor worm and the Relic Gu, but this speed is still very fast. Gu Yue clan might not have sensed anything wrong, but this is a case of 'those closely involved can't see as clearly as those outside'. This is the first suspicious point."

"Besides this, there is another suspicious point; his luck. He rock gambled for the first time in his life and bought six purple gold stones, but was able to get two live Gu; a mudskin toad and a Liquor worm. Isn't this luck way too much?"

Tie Xue Leng nodded, "Yes, continue."

"This Fang Yuan looks ordinary, but if we look into him, we will find that the mysteries surrounding him are like the thick fog covering the mountain. Many things that were inadvertently revealed makes one ponder. For instance, his rock dissecting technique; he actually used the Moonlight Gu to dissect rocks and did it without damaging the core. Such delicate control is really unimaginable for a student....wait!"

Tie Ruo Nan paused. She had discovered something as her eyes let out bright and sharp light!

Her gaze landed on a line of words in the letter, and the more she looked at, the more her gaze brightened.

"I found it. This Fang Yuan has a huge problem!" After a long while, she suddenly raised her head and excitedly spoke. ...

The fragrance of the tea in the cup rose with the steam and spread in the study room.

Fang Yuan held the tea cup, then blew the floating tea leaves and drank the hot tea. After that, he leisurely let out some turbid air.

Upon seeing the leisurely attitude of Fang Yuan, Gu Yue Mo Chen did his best to endure and felt the veins in his forehead bulging.

Previously, Fang Yuan had asked for a huge price and he had angrily chased the latter out of his house.

But today, he had no choice but to re-invite Fang Yuan.

All this was simply because circumstances are more powerful than men. Yao faction had been pressuring him from everywhere and the matter regarding his drop to Rank two was going to be revealed sooner or later. Mo faction was in imminent danger; it urgently needed an elder to serve as son-in-law and stabilize the situation.

"This bastard is too vile, making such sky-high demands. Does he really think my Mo faction is bathing in gold?" Gu Yue Mo Chen cursed inwardly, while outwardly putting on a warm smile and speaking in a negotiating voice, "Elder Fang Yuan, your price is too much, it greatly exceeds what my Mo faction can support. Can you decrease it?"

Fang Yuan glanced at Gu Yue Mo Chen. This old man who knew when to give and take was worthy of respect.

In fact, his current situation was also becoming messed up.

The Tie father and daughter were forcing him into a corner. Once it was found out that he killed Jia Jin Sheng, Gu Yue Clan would definitely hand him over to appease the Jia family's anger and simultaneously be able to continue trading with the Jia family caravan every year.

It was almost the crucial moment now, so Fang Yuan softened his tone, "Then we will decrease it by thirty percent. But there is a condition, you need to show me your sincerity by paying forty thousand primeval stones in advance. Also you must hand over a Pig Iron Gu and an Afterlife Grass Gu."

Gu Yue Mo Chen couldn't help but massage his brows when he heard this. He replied in a sunken voice, "Pig Iron Gu will be handed to you, but my Mo faction's warehouse doesn't have any Afterlife Grass Gu. We can't also give the forty thousand primeval stones at once, they will be given to you in installments."

Fang Yuan knew this old fox wasn't speaking the truth, but he was very clear that being too overbearing could instead produce the opposite result.

"That's okay. I will wait for you to send them first, then we can talk about marriage. Before that, I can't guarantee my allegiance." Fang Yuan left these words before walking away.

The study room was silent once more.

A long while later, Gu Yue Mo Chen suddenly said, "You can come out."

A hidden door was pushed open and a young girl walked out. There were tear stains on her face and her eyes were red from the crying.

"Grandpa." She paid her respects; she was Gu Yue Mo Yan.

Gu Yue Mo Chen sighed, "You are also clear on the family's situation. Mo Yan, our family needs your sacrifice, can you understand?"

"Yes." The young girl sobbed and lowered her head.

No matter which world, there is no such thing as a free lunch. Even Fang Yuan contributed a lot of strength to the clan as a clan elder. The only difference is that the amount one pays or obtains, differs from person to person.

Even those kids with golden spoons also cannot freely enjoy the privileges. By receiving the family's nurturing, they needed to have the resolve to sacrifice.

And this resolve was already present in Gu Yue Mo Yan.She didn't have the least bit of feelings for Fang Yuan, even feeling hatred and disgust towards the latter. But she knew, she had to marry him for the sake of her family, becoming his wife!

Chapter 177: Brother, how can you do this to me?!

Living Steel Gu is a Rank two Gu, looking like a charcoal briquette, fist-sized and black all over. On the surface, there were numerous holes.

Fang Yuan injected his primeval essence and this Living Steel Gu started floating, rotating on its own, black smoke pouring out from the holes on it.

Chainsaw Golden Centipede coiled around Fang Yuan's leg, its dark-gold colored armor full of injuries, the two rows of razors on its sides tattered and damaged.

But when the steel smoke came over and covered these wounds, they gradually healed.

The black smokey steel essence continued to be used, as the two rows of razors on the Chainsaw Golden Centipede could be seen growing at an observable rate.

Healing Gu varied in a few types. There were some that healed Gu Masters, some that specialised in certain injuries, and those that healed Gu worms.

To the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, the Living Steel Gu is its healing Gu worm.

An hour later, the Living Steel Gu became smaller and smaller. It went from a fist-sized charcoal to a pearl size, eventually vanishing.

It was an expenditure-type Gu.

But its sacrifice brought about the recovery of the Chainsaw Golden Centipede.

At this point, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede was good as new. Its two rows of razors were shiny as new, glowing with a sharp and cold flash. On its dark gold exoskeleton, the injuries were mostly healed, and only five to six light scars remained.

But this was nothing to worry about. In about a few weeks, these scars would vanish through the natural recovery of the centipede.

However, if not for the Living Steel Gu and just relying solely on the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, it would take at least half a year for the razors to fully grow back.

The Chainsaw Golden Centipede was more strong than it was flexible. Although it used little primeval essence and had great attacking power, its weakness was a lack in the healing aspect.

All living beings are equal, in this world there is no all-rounded Gu, there has to be weakness and advantages. Even Rank six or seven Gu and above followed this natural law.

"This way, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede's battle strength is completely recovered..." Fang Yuan stretched out his hand, touching the cold exoskeleton of the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, his face slightly pale.

On his pale face, cold sweat was forming."Damn it, it had to come at this time..." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, his left hand subconsciously pressing his stomach.

His mind entered his aperture, only to see that the white silver Primeval Sea was still, the entire aperture filled with an oppressed feeling.

All the other Gu had been suppressed to one side. Only above the sea, within the aperture, the Spring Autumn Cicada was glowing with a yellow and green lustre.

At this time, the Spring Autumn Cicada not only had both wings recovered, but its main body also recovered much of its energy.

Just like an object falling from the sky, the closer it gets to the ground the faster it falls, and the Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery rate was the same. After the initial difficult period, as time passed, its recovery speed accelerated.

Thus, the problem came.

The Spring Autumn Cicada was Rank six, while Fang Yuan was only a Rank three Gu Master. His aperture was gradually unable to hold the Spring Autumn Cicada.

Back then, when the Spring Autumn Cicada was weak, the burden on the aperture was not as huge. But now that the Spring Autumn Cicada gradually recovered, regaining its Rank six ability, it caused this tiny temple of Fang Yuan's to be unable to hold this high god.

"If this goes on, I might even die from the Spring Autumn Cicada before the Tie family father and daughter find out the truth! Truly, when your roof has a hole it just has to rain non-stop for days....."

The best solution was to raise his own cultivation level. When he gets to Rank six, the aperture will have the capacity to store the Spring Autumn Cicada again.

But this method takes too long. In his previous five hundred years of life, he also used more than four hundred years to attain Rank six.

He was now a C grade talent with Rank three cultivation. To cultivate to Rank six, he had a severe lack of time.

Other than that, there was another way to solve the problem.

It was to take the Spring Autumn Cicada out of his aperture and raise it outside his body.

But that act had great disadvantages.

Firstly, the Spring Autumn Cicada was not a battle-type Gu, so it could not protect itself. Keeping it in the aperture was safer. Secondly, when a Rank six Gu appears, it would interfere with natural laws and cause a mirage at the location it is at.

Fang Yuan was now at the village where there were many people, and the Tie family father and daughter was on to him as well. Once this Spring Autumn Cicada leaves his body, everyone would find out.

Therefore, he could only feel troubled."The Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery is getting faster. At this rate, I don't have much time. Once I get the forty thousand primeval stones from Gu Yue Mo Chen, I'll take the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus and leave this place. As for the Tie family father and daughter, I can resolve it at a later time."

Fang Yuan sighed.Tie family father and daughter's matter was something that he could only put off and delay. But now, the Spring Autumn Cicada was not giving him time to stall.

He was at his wits end. As time urged him, wasting every minute and second is reducing his lifespan.

A Gu Master being killed by their own Gu worm was not uncommon. Many Gu Masters who forcefully activate their Gu get a backlash from their Gu worm's power and lose their life. Such incidents were everywhere. Gu Yue Qing Shu was the prime example, buried not far away.

...

"Six purple gold stones, each fist-sized. With Fang Yuan's cultivation, he actually opened five on the spot. How could he have so much primeval essence at that time?" Tie Ruo Nan stared at the information on the letter, laughing smugly.

Tie Xue Leng nodded, "You finally found this suspicious point. Indeed, only when you are meticulous can you discover what normal people cannot see. But what can you derive from this suspicious point?"Tie Ruo Nan closed her eyes, activating the Intuition Gu secretly.

In the darkness, she felt an enlightenment in her mind, and she opened her eyes abruptly. "Instinct tells me, Fang Yuan must have had the Liquor worm from long ago!"

"But instincts are sometimes wrong, they cannot represent truth," Tie Xue Leng reminded.

"Isn't it easy to get evidence? Hehe, as long as he has the Liquor worm, he has to feed it. If he feeds it, there has to be evidence." Tie Ruo Nan's mouth curled into an arc, "Let's go! We'll find Gu Yue Fang Zheng, Fang Yuan's brother once again. As the little brother, he has to be the most familiar with Fang Yuan."

...

"You're asking about brother's actions back then?" Fang Zheng showed a complicated expression.

He sighed, recalling, "Back then, brother was a very outstanding individual. Since young he constantly displayed his talent, making many poems, causing the entire village to put their attention on him. Back then, I admired him and held him in awe. In my heart, he was like a tall mountain that I couldn't climb. Maybe because he was at such a high point, when he tumbled down, the despair was greater. Afterwards during the awakening ceremony, he was tested to have only C grade talent, thus he became discouraged for a long time, sleeping in class and not returning to the hostel at night, buying wine and getting drunk all the time. From that moment on, I realized, brother was also human..."

"Wait you said, buy wine?" Tie Ruo Nan heard this crucial phrase and caught on to it, squinting.

"Yes, for a period of time, he was dead drunk. Sigh, maybe reality was too harsh. He only had C grade talent, but his brother turned out to be A grade, and he could not accept the truth. Actually, if I was in his shoes, I would understand his feelings and emotions as well," Fang Zheng said.

"Wait let me ask you, from that moment on, Fang Yuan would buy wine to drink every few days?" Tie Ruo Nan asked again.

"Yes, from that moment on, brother fell in love with alcohol, spending a lot of money for wine. For a time, he was in love with the bamboo wine, which is our clan's speciality, a very expensive wine. He snatched primeval stones from his classmates in order to buy wine to drink. This is an overbearing act, thus not a single student liked him. Why, is there a problem?" Finally, Fang Zheng asked in confusion.

"There's a huge problem. I suspect that your brother's Liquor worm wasn't obtained from the gambling rocks, but he had it long ago. Your brother's drunkard act was merely a performance. His real motive was to conceal the fact that he had the Liquor worm, and was feeding it," Tie Ruo Nan replied solemnly.

"WHAT?!" Fang Zheng hearing so, jumped from his seat in shock.

This was shocking information!

"What you just said made me even more suspicious. Where did your brother buy wine normally? I need to investigate." Tie Ruo Nan stood up as well. she was racing against time, moving quickly to solve the case.

"In our entire village, there is only one place selling Bamboo wine, it is that sole inn."

"Then I'll take my leave." Tie Ruo Nan turned around and left.

"Wait, I... I'll go with your guys!" Fang Zheng hesitated, chasing after them.

An hour later.

Tie Ruo Nan walked on the stone pavement, concluding, "Earlier the innkeeper already told me everything, and the situation is clear as day. Fang Yuan buying so much wine, his true motive is to feed the Liquor worm. After that, he purposely went to gamble rocks, and that is to expose the Liquor worm logically in front of everyone. All this, is according to his plans."

On one side, Fang Zheng appeared a little distraught, his face looking a little lifeless.

He did not expect that the truth was really like this!

Long ago, he had once looked down on Fang Yuan, thinking he was a loser, giving up on himself. From that moment on, he felt that the tall mountain was no longer so hard to scale.

But the truth was, everything was Fang Yuan's disguise, his performance, his scheme!

The surrounding people were played by him like fools, believing his lies.

Even he Gu Yue Fang Zheng was no exception!

Looking at it now, his disdain and despise towards his brother back then, was like a giant mockery of a joke.

"Brother... in your heart, what place do I hold? In those eyes of yours that pretended to be drunk, was I a huge joke? Brother! You are such a scheming fox, in your heart, was I childish enough for you to sneer at?!" Fang Zheng screamed in his heart.

He was humiliated, he was furious.

He felt that he was played by Fang Yuan. From the start, he was a clown putting on a childish and laughable act.

He felt the disdain Fang Yuan felt towards him.

"Brother, how can you treat me like this?!"

"If not for lady Tie, I would still be in the dark. How long do you intend to lie to me, and to the clan? You killed the innocent, taking lives as you wish. Deception and lies, indifferent and inhumane, is that the real you?"

Chapter 178: Black White Grey

Long ago, in Fang Zheng's heart, Fang Yuan was like a tall mountain, so tall he could never scale.

Long ago, Fang Zheng thought that the shadow of this tall mountain would enshroud him his entire life.

But life gave him an unexpected twist.

Fang Yuan being dispirited, let Fang Zheng see his weakness. The tall mountain that he resembled, instantly collapsed.

And yet—This was actually all brother's performance, an act?

The collapsed mountain in his heart became enshrouded in a layer of mystery.

"Brother, exactly what kind of person are you?"

Fang Zheng realized at this moment that he knew nothing about this blood related brother of his.

Fang Yuan's heart was full of scheming, he had too deep of a shrewdness. With his acting skills and the indifference towards taking human lives, Fang Zheng felt infinitely distant towards him.

Along with this distant feeling, there was also a feeling of fear that Fang Zheng did not want to recognise.

This goddamn feeling was back, creeping into his heart.

He tried his best to shrug off this feeling of fear, causing him to subconsciously follow after Tie Ruo Nan's footsteps.

"Lady Tie, thanks for letting me find out the truth and seeing my brother's true side. Helping you is akin to helping myself, so just ask away, I will tell you everything I know," Fang Zheng said earnestly.

Tie Ruo Nan nodded, but then shook her head quickly, "What I need to know, I already understand now. The problem now is, where did Fang Yuan get that Liquor worm from?"

"You are right, this matter is suspicious. During brother's situation back then, he had not inherited our parent's assets, and at the same time was only a C grade, beginning his cultivation. Where did he get the Liquor worm from?" Fang Zheng frowned.

"In this situation, there's only two causes. One is outside help, and the other is an inheritance legacy. But who would invest in a C grade talent? If it is an inheritance, which is it?" Thinking of this, Tie Ruo Nan stopped in her footsteps.

Inheritance legacy... inheritance legacy...

In her mind, this phrase kept appearing.

She fell into deep thought.

"If it was an inheritance legacy, everything would fall into place. Firstly, the Liquor worm's origin can be explained. Secondly, the reason for killing Jia Jin Sheng is also established!" Tie Ruo Nan thought excitedly.

What perplexed her the entire time, was the killer's motive.

There has to be a reason to kill.

Fang Yuan showed the Liquor worm, and Jia Jin Sheng wanted to buy it. But the value of the Liquor worm is too low to establish a motive to kill.

But what if, Jia Jin Sheng who refused to give up, adamantly wants to buy the Liquor worm from Fang Yuan, thus following him all the way and discovering an inheritance legacy ground...

What would Fang Yuan do?

"Hehehehehe." Tie Ruo Nan laughed.

Fang Zheng showed a perplexed gaze.Tie Ruo Nan looked back, "I want to inspect the Gu Yue clan's history records!"

Fang Zheng shook his head, waving his hand, "The history is kept in the clan's forbidden grounds, how can an outsider inspect it?"

"Then can you get in?"

Fang Zheng shook his head, "Only clan elders."

"Is that so... then what can we do now?" Tie Ruo Nan frowned.

"Lady Tie, maybe I can help." From the shadows, a crippled old woman walked out.

It was none other than Gu Yue Yao Ji.

She was still the medicine faction family head, but when she stepped down from the medicine hall elder's position and was replaced by Gu Yue Chi Zhong, also losing an arm, her former authority had almost fully vanished.

But the pursuit of authority was already ingrained in her soul. She understood deeply that collaborating with Gu Yue Chi Zhong was only a temporary solution. The only way was to devour the Mo faction. Only then would she have the ability to take back her medicine hall elder's position.

To absorb the Mo faction, all she had to do was to eliminate their hope.

And this hope was naturally Fang Yuan.

"Divine investigator Tie, to speak the truth, I've been observing both of you for some time. Come with me, I'll bring you into the clan's forbidden area. Hehehe, normally that place would be heavily guarded. But coincidentally, right now I am in charge of protecting the forbidden grounds," Gu Yue Yao Ji laughed sinisterly.

She obviously hoped to harm Fang Yuan indirectly, but if he was innocent, she could definitely slander him using her wicked methods.

In the underground tunnel inside a hidden room, Tie Ruo Nan looked at the Gu Yue clan's historical records.

From the first generation onwards, after Gu Yue clan was built until its golden age, and then its decline, the records contained the information for the last few hundred years. All events, big and small, were recorded in detail.

"This first generation clan leader has a mysterious origin, creating the Gu Yue village singlehandedly. He's most likely a demonic cultivator!" Tie Ruo Nan flipped the first few pages, saying something shocking.

"That's nothing much. Many demonic cultivators, after getting sick of roaming, would choose to spread their bloodline, and establish a clan. A few hundred years later, they would be wiped off their demonic origins, and the descendants would become righteous cultivators. Such situations are actually very common, it is nothing strange." Beside her, Tie Xue Leng said.

"Then all his previous wrongdoings, will it all be spared like that?" Tie Ruo Nan had an indignant expression. "These demonic cultivators caused all those crimes, but when the time is ripe and they feel tired, they would settle down and enjoy their old age. Isn't this too good for them?"

Tie Xue Leng sighed deeply, "Ruo Nan. When I was young, I felt like you too, thinking that this world is in black and white. But after you see more of the world, you will find out that this world is actually grey. Many times can black turn to white, and white can turn to black. Some white can also be more devious than black, and even bear greater sins."

"And demonic cultivators also have their own grievances. Righteous Gu Masters control the cultivating resources, while demonic Gu Masters are all alone, only able to rely on their extreme methods. Those like the first generation clan leader who are able to change their ways, that is the best solution. At least he will no longer cause harm to others. Turning from black to white, he can contribute his strength towards the righteous path."

Tie Xue Leng explained and consoled, but the young girl Tie Ruo Nan did not seem to be convinced.

She shook her head, saying adamantly, "Father, it is not right for you to sympathize with demonic Gu Masters. White is white, black is black. They should be punished for making a mistake. Breaking the law, they should face judgement. If not, where would justice lie, where would fairness lie, where would the law stand?"

"This is not sympathy. Anywhere where there's people, there are interests involved. Places that involves interests will have crime. As long as people exist, crime would never end. My child, you will find out eventually, a person's strength is too insignificant." Tie Xue Leng's voice was experienced and wise, but also sorrowful, "Nevermind. To the current you, it is still too early to say such things, you should concentrate on solving the case."

"Yes, father," Tie Ruo Nan pouted, not agreeing with Tie Xue Leng's pessimistic outlook.

When people are young, they tend to think they can change the world. But after they grow up, they will eventually find out that a person being able to retain their sense of self, and not being changed by the world is already a great success.

As the girl continued to flip, her hand suddenly stopped.

"Fourth generation clan leader... Flower Wine Monk? Li... Liquor worm?" Her eyes shone!

...

Electric currents flowed as the sharp teeth edges cut like blades, shining with a cold light.

A frenzy lightning wolf pounced towards Bai Ning Bing, its wolf claw drawing a shadow in the air.

Bai Ning Bing did not have any movements. As the frenzy lightning wolf's claw became larger in his eyes, he did not have any inclination to dodge.

Suddenly, a white rainbow shot out from his aperture.

The light rainbow burst, and white light shot down like rain. In the light rain, the elegant white snake appeared, its long whiskers bringing about a fairy-like atmosphere.

Towards this Rank five snake Gu, the arrogant frenzy lightning wolf immediately withered, wanting to retreat.But the white form immortal snake opened its mouth and shot out a cloud smoke.

The white smoke looked slow, but quickly enveloped the lightning wolf.

The frenzy lightning wolf's vision was obscured by the smoke, and it quickly moved back. But no matter how it moved, the white smoke followed it like a shadow, always engulfing its surroundings and not giving it any chance to escape.

White form immortal snake's ability was this lump of smoke. After being enshrouded, one cannot tell their directions, as their vision is dyed in a white smoke.Wild beasts like lightning wolves relied on their strong vision and had weak hearing. The frenzy lightning wolf was the same, thus its most useful sensory organ being blinded caused it to howl in panic. In its struggle, it broke many trees and mountain rocks as it became more agitated.

HOWL!

It suddenly opened its mouth and shot out a blue thunderbolt.

The thunderbolt shot towards Bai Ning Bing, but he had no plans to dodge.

Crack!

The thunderbolt hit Bai Ning Bing on the chest, penetrating it.

Bai Ning Bing lowered his head and saw the huge hole that the thunderbolt had made, allowing him to see through to the back.

But quickly, the huge hole began to freeze. Layers of white ice covered the injury and the ice slowly melted, turning into flesh.

"This is the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique's true strength. I am ice, and ice is me. Fatal injuries to ordinary Gu Masters can be recovered in just a few seconds for me," Bai Ning Bing thought, as he slowly raised his right arm.

His right arm was ordinary broken, but relying on the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique, it had already recovered fully.

"The white form immortal snake Gu also sensed the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique, thus it entered my aperture. The Northern Dark Ice Soul physique can attract water-type Gu worms to join me! Such great strength, yet so brittle!"

Bai Ning Bing sighed at the heavens.

These days, he did not suppress his cultivation. The Northern Dark Ice Soul physique was getting stronger, but he felt that death was approaching him even faster.

"Great immortal hasn't done anything?" At this time, Bai clan leader came over, asking in concern.

Bai Ning Bing shook his head, "This snake Gu does not recognise me, it is merely attracted by my Northern Dark Ice Soul physique and moved from the clan's spirit spring into my aperture. Only when I am in mortal danger and in a death situation would it come out and protect me."

But the white form immortal snake was not refined by Bai Ning Bing, thus this protection also had its limits.

Like earlier, the frenzy lightning wolf's thunderbolt was too fast, and the white form immortal snake could not react in time, thus Bai Ning Bing was hit head on.

After all, the white form immortal snake was not a defensive Gu.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, Jiang Fan and the River Swallowing Toad was the same. Although Jiang Fan had its assistance, he was still assassinated by a Gu Master.

Bai clan leader sighed. He felt intense regret and pity towards this, yet there was nothing he could do. He had already done what he could.

"Right, the three clan's negotiation results is out. Xiong clan preserved more than half of their strength, we cannot underestimate them. Eventually the three clans came to a decision that there shall be a three-clan tournament. And the compensation will be decided by the results of the competition. Only Gu Masters aged thirty and below can enter the tournament."

"I understand." Bai Ning Bing nodded, "I can already sense it, my life is coming to an end. Having a competition at the end, I am really happy. Thank you, lord clan elder."

"No no, this is also for the sake of the clan." Bai clan leader's expression was embarrassed. It was his suggestion in the first place, and the biggest reason for it was to squeeze out the last remaining value that Bai Ning Bing possessed.

But Bai Ning Bing's gratitude, came from the bottom of his heart.

The white form immortal snake was unmoved, meaning that he was not fated to receive the first generation ancestor's inheritance. But life and death are bound to occur, what fear could he have?

Bai Ning Bing had already found his path, he no longer feared. There was only one lingering battle that he could not let go of.

"Fang Yuan, the three-clan tournament, will you attend it? Don't disappoint me, because right now, I am really really strong..."

Chapter 179: History is written by men

"The Flower Wine Monk begged for mercy on his knees. The fourth clan head was merciful and kind, intending to spare his life. Yet the Flower Wink Monk suddenly launched a sneak attack, and the clan head flew into a rage, killing the Flower Wine Monk on the spot. However, due to the heavy injuries from the sneak attack, he passed away not long after. Alas, demonic path members were indeed treacherous and unworthy of kindness...."

However, as Tie Ruo Nan read through this content, her eyes gradually dimmed down.

"What a pity, this Flower Wine Monk died on the spot and couldn't leave behind an inheritance. If he could leave an inheritance, that would be perfect to explain everything," The young girl sighed inwardly.

Yet she didn't give up and continued to flip through the Gu Yue clan records, until the time was up and Gu Yue Yao Ji rushed them out.

Fang Zheng welcomed the Tie father and daughter outside of the clan pavillion, "Were there any discoveries?"

Tie Xue Leng was silent whereas Tie Ruo Nan gave a bitter smile and shook her head.

Fang Zheng continued, "I just thought of something which might be of help. Brother and Chi faction worked quite closely, and the Chi faction's elder Gu Yue Chi Lian had once defended him in front of everyone. Lady Tie, do you think this Liquor worm could have been secretly handed over by elder Chi Lian to my brother?"

"Chi faction?" Tie Ruo Nan frowned.

"Yes. Chi and Mo faction were the most influential factions of our Gu Yue clan before the wolf tide," Fang Zheng explained.

How was Fang Yuan involved with Chi faction? Tie Ruo Nan reflected on this.She started feeling a headache; this was her first case and she had been full of confidence at first but when she actually started doing it, she felt that it was filled with difficulties.

When she had seen her father solving the cases, it was as if success was guaranteed; all the mysteries were solved with methodical and orderly arrangement. However, she realized how truly difficult it was to solve a case when it was her turn.

There seemed to be no trails sometimes whereas all kinds of weird clues seemed to emerge, causing Tie Ruo Nan to be at wit's end.

It was like she was covered in a dense fog and she didn't know how close or far she was from the truth.

Would this clue regarding Chi faction be of any use?

Tie Ruo Nan couldn't help but feel at a loss, and she subconsciously looked at her father.

"Father should have already discovered some clues, right?" At this moment, the admiration in the young girl towards her father deepened further.

"If it was my father, this case should have already been solved. I am still far away from father's level. But even if I fail, as long as father is here, the truth will come out and the killer will be punished." Tie Ruo Nan felt ashamed but also a sense of pride.

With Tie Xue Leng here, she had no worries that the criminal could get away.

But the young girl quickly shook her head, getting angry. The anger was towards herself.

"Ruo Nan, you are worthless. Didn't you think of surpassing father? How can you surpass him if you have the mentality of always relying on him!?"

"Ruo Nan, cheer up, you can do it!" The young girl pursed her lips, inwardly encouraging herself.

Her spirit boiled up again.

She decided to overthrow her previous conjectures and start over.

"If Fang Yuan didn't obtain the Liquor worm from an inheritance and got it from other people, then this Chi faction would be the biggest suspect. However, why would Chi faction take notice of a C grade aptitude ordinary student and secretly give him the Liquor worm?"

"What does Fang Yuan have that Chi faction felt it worthy to invest in him? Because he is Fang Zheng's brother? No, that is almost negligible. Wait a second, it might not be Chi faction taking the initiative to invest in him. There is another possibility, and that is because Fang Yuan blackmailed them!"

"If it is truly so, what did Fang Yuan have on them to make them hold their nose and obediently compromise with a student that had yet to be a Gu Master?"

Tie Ruo Nan racked her brains and an answer seemed to gradually emerge in her mind.

But this answer was blurry like the light behind a paper window. Tie Ruo Nan could feel its existence but she couldn't grasp and understand it.

"Father." The young girl suddenly raised her head and looked at Tie Xue Leng, "I would like to borrow the Cactus Pointer."

Tie Xue Leng replied in a relaxed voice, "The suggestion given by Cactus pointer is based upon the information the user has. It only speculates on behalf of you and might not be accurate. Are you sure you want to use it?"

The young girl nodded.

Cactus pointer was a seed.

Tie Ruo Nan buried it in the ground then used her palm to press on the soil, transferring her white silver primeval essence to it.

After several breaths, she withdrew her hand. Soon, they could see the soil loosening up, and a young sprout grew out of it.

The newborn sprout was a translucent green, and looked very fragile. It quickly grew, becoming bigger and bigger, and its color changed from fragile greenish yellow to verdant green, then finally to dark green.

Its appearance was similar to a cactus. It had thick flesh, the surface covered with sharp black thorns and was lush green all over.

Within moments, a flower bud appeared on its top part.

The white flower bud gradually grew, becoming charming and delicate. The main body of the cactus, however, was shrinking as if its moisture was being squeezed out.

Tie Ruo Nan stretched her fingers and gently plucked this flower bud. The moment the flower bud was taken out, the cactus started turning grey and completely died after a few seconds.

The cactus pointer was a Rank three consumable Gu.

Tie Ruo Nan carefully opened the flower bud.

The flower bud, however, was not wrapped up with layers of petals, instead appearing similar to a ball of paper.

When Tie Ruo Nan completely opened it, it formed into a neat and square white paper.

There were only one word written on the white paper —'Aptitude'.

This word would mean nothing to others and might even sound ridiculous. But to Tie Ruo Nan, it was a very important tip.

The cactus pointer was used just like this; it gave insights to the Gu Masters who had racked their brains but couldn't advance forward. It pierced the paper window and let the Gu Masters see the light.

"Right, it is aptitude!" Tie Ruo Nan shouted.

She immediately took out the letter which recorded all the intels collected by Jia Fu.

There was something written in this intel which described the details on when and at what price Gu Yue Chi Lian had bought the Cleansing Water Gu.

"It's this! I only briefed through this earlier and neglected it, not considering the underlying meaning. But the cactus pointer speculated on my behalf and gave me the answer. This Cleansing Water Gu only has one use and that is to cleanse the foreign primeval essence auras from the aperture."

"Why did Gu Yue Chi Lian need it? Hehe, this situation is too common and happens a lot in many clans. He should have bought this for Chi faction's inheritor. Chi faction's inheritor should have a bad aptitude, so Gu Yue Chi Lian poured his primeval essence to raise the former's cultivation. The Cleansing Water Gu is necessary to remove any after-effects from this action. By some chance, Fang Yuan found this secret and used it to blackmail Chi faction, thus forcing them to compromise and give him the Liquor worm."

Tie Ruo Nan kept on mumbling out her conjecture.

"Lady Tie, you are amazing. You could deduce so many things with just this word! But Gu Yue Chi Cheng clearly has B grade aptitude," Fang Zheng said.

"B grade aptitude? Hehe, does that mean it can't be fake? It is very simple to prove this. We only need to examine Chi Cheng's aperture and the truth will be out." Tie Ruo Nan's gaze was burning as her mouth slightly curved upwards.

"That's inappropriate." Tie Xue Leng, however, shook his head disapprovingly.

If this truth was found out, it would be a great blow to Chi faction, leading to turmoil among the Gu Yue village's higher-ups and causing political conflicts.

Tie Xue Leng said, "We came here to solve a case and not to wreck havoc. In the end, we are outsiders and unless it is absolutely necessary, we can't meddle in other clan's politics."

Tie Ruo Nan nodded, "Father is right. Besides this, there are also other ways to prove it. I remember that clans use a Photo-audio Gu to record every important sacrificial ritual. This is a traditional practice and I believe Gu Yue clan isn't an exception. I want to refer to the Awakening Ceremony's image!"

...

"Divine investigator Tie, you have constantly been on the move for so many days and have gone through a lot of trouble to solve the case, please come have tea. As for the image you want to look into, it is stored in the secret room inside the underground cave which is among the clan's restricted areas. It would be inconvenient to let you two enter, but I have already sent someone to get it. It will be here in a short while," Gu Yue Bo spoke with a smile.

"I have troubled the clan leader," Tie Xue Leng politely said.

Tie Ruo Nan and Gu Yue Fang Zheng were standing on the side.

"Divine investigator Tie, if I may be so bold to ask a favor...." Gu Yue Bo suddenly said.

Tie Xue Leng. "Oh? Please speak, clan leader."

"This is our Qing Mao Mountain's internal affair. My clan, Bai clan and Xiong clan have always been in a deadlock but that changed due to the wolf tide. Xiong village evaded the wolf tide with malicious intentions and tried to take advantage of the wolf tide to weaken the other two clans. The negotiation earlier for compensation with them ended up in nothing. Hence, our three clans decided to hold a three-clans tournament. Only Gu Masters at age thirty or below can participate in it, and it will decide the future strength of each clan."

Upon saying this, Gu Yue Bo sighed, "Actually I have already felt that something was strange with Fang Yuan long ago, but couldn't look into it properly because of the wolf tide. If he really is the killer, my clan absolutely won't shield him. But I hope Divine Investigator Tie can delay this for a few days, since the three-clans competition is hosted on the day after tomorrow."

Fang Yuan killed old Wang's whole family, but they were just mortals and it was not worth investigating. What if he killed them? It wasn't a big deal.

However, if he really killed Jia Jin Sheng, then that would change everything.

If Gu Yue clan still protected Fang Yuan, that would mean becoming enemies with Jia family and losing the chance to trade with Jia family caravan again; it would even result in Jia family's retaliation.

Organizations protected their inner members, but if benefits were endangered, the organization could easily give up one or two members for the greater good.

The organization's earliest form came from ancient times. Human clans assembled together for their survival, borrowing each other's strength to gather more food and dividing up their work to hunt more successfully.

Any organization's essence was obtaining maximum benefits.

If one or two members obstructed the organization's path to benefits, then sacrificing them was a natural thing.

Thus, even if there were very few elders in Gu Yue clan right now, if there came a time when they had to abandon Fang Yuan, the clan leader would have no hesitation.

However, the day after tomorrow was the three-clans competition. The results of this competition would decide their future for the next few years as well as the benefit allocation of Qing Mao mountain. As a Rank three Gu Master, Fang Yuan was a vital fighting force for the Gu Yue clan.Just like Bai clan's clan leader, Gu Yue Bo also wanted to squeeze out Fang Yuan's maximum worth.

Chapter 180: Watching the Awakening Ceremony again

"It's about time, I can't wait any longer."

As the night fell, Fang Yuan opened his eyes in a dark room.

He already took off his Gu Master uniform and was now wearing a black gown which covered his legs. Matched with his long black hair, he would appear like a specter as he moved in the dark.

He was already used to having long hair in his previous life. Some Gu worms needed long hair to show their abilities, like the Black Hair Gu, Steel Hair Gu and so on.

Having long hair was quite convenient as well. You could just cut it short if there came a time where you had to alter your appearance. But for short hair, to grow it in a short period, one needed to rely on specific Gu worms.

Not long ago, he had made an agreement with Gu Yue Mo Chen. Right now, he had already received the Pig Iron Gu and all forty thousand primeval stones. The only thing remaining was that healing grass Gu.

"I can only forget about the healing Gu now. How can everything go as one wishes, reality is full of helpless choices...."

Fang Yuan sighed, then stood up and lightly opened the door before using the Stealth Scales Gu and disappearing into the night.

He was forced by the circumstances to make this move.

Tie father and daughter were drawing in closer, and his plan to be an envoy to Xiong village had been stopped too.

Xiong village was able to preserve most of their strength; Bai clan and Gu Yue clan didn't dare to be overly forceful, thus the compensation talk ended in failure. The three sides then decided on holding a three-clan competition.

Mo faction might have intentionally recruited Fang Yuan, but this move caused Fang Yuan to be in the middle of the political struggle and draw every elder's hostility.

Also adding in Bai Ning Bing who was growing stronger as he approached his death, the whole situation was becoming more unfavorable to Fang Yuan, forcing him into an impasse.

Even if Fang Yuan was an old fox, he still needed strength to support his schemes. Facing such a situation, despite him already using up all his efforts and strength, making much faster progress than he did in his previous life, his Rank three initial stage cultivation was still not enough to overturn the situation.

"The situation is dire, I can only take a risk and bet on this method!" Fang Yuan thought hard, placing his hopes on the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.

As long as he plucked the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, the spirit spring in the underground cave would be wasted. The clan was sure to madly investigate, but what else besides the investigation?

The spirit spring would already be disabled, and even if they got the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus and destroyed it or put it back into the spirit spring again, the spirit spring would not recover.

What could the clan do to survive then?

There was only one thing: that was to seize a new spirit spring!

However, there were only three spirit springs in Qing Mao mountain and each were occupied by one of the three clans. If one was destroyed by Fang Yuan, then Gu Yue clan had only one choice—to make a choice between the two.

This choice was war, a war with either Bai village or Xiong village.

Only by seizing one of the spirit springs could Gu Yue clan have the foundation to continue its existence.There was no need to talk of Gu Masters being able to support their cultivation without the support of spirit spring.

This move was too dangerous, though. But Fang Yuan had no other choice as the Spring Autumn Cicada was recovering so fast that his aperture was already starting to feel a burden. He didn't have much time, so he could only fight back for a sliver of chance at survival and seek life in death. ...

The hall was bright with all the lights.

A Gu Master had already delivered the Photo-audio Gu, but this Gu was currently in Gu Yue Bo's hand."Divine Investigator Tie, what did you think about my request?" Gu Yue Bo asked smilingly.

Tie Ruo Nan lightly snorted.

Tie Xue Leng ruminated for a while before agreeing, "Alright, if Fang Yuan really turns out to be the killer, I will leave enough time for him to participate in the three-clans competition.""Father...." Tie Ruo Nan's eyes flashed with a strange light; this was not her father's style.

"Hehe, Divine Investigator's words are worth a lot and he never breaks his promises. This humble one fully trusts you and also thanks you for understanding." Gu Yue Bo's smile became more gentle, however he coldly hummed inside.

Gu Yue Yao Ji had secretly brought the Tie father and daughter into the underground cave and let them look through the clan's official historical records. How could he as a clan leader not know of this?

But he had to restrain his anger because of the approaching tournament and also the complicated political struggles in the clan.

Tie Xue Leng might be a powerful Rank five expert, but he had no way to appease the dissatisfaction in Gu Yue Bo's heart.

"Fortunately, the genuine contents are all recorded in the clan's secret records and only the successive clan leaders can hold them. That official history is for the outsiders to look." Gu Yue Bo was secretly feeling smug.

Gu Yue clan's historical records were divided into official records and secret records.

Official records were hidden in the secret room in the underground cave and its contents were to brainwash the later generations and was a fake, in fact.

But the secret records recorded all the genuine details without any fake details. There were even records of some secrets that could never be divulged.

For instance, the ritual for summoning the Blood Guillotine Gu which could never be recorded in the official records, but was recorded in detail in the secret records.

"Gu Yue clan leader, my father has agreed to your request, now show us the image." Tie Ruo Nan's tone showed her bad mood.

"Even if Divine Investigator Tie hadn't agreed, I would have fully cooperated with your investigation," Gu Yue Bo gently clarified, then he lightly pinched his fingers, smashing the Photo-audio Gu.

Although the Gu broke into pieces, it instead formed into a ball of seven-colored smoke which contained all sorts of noise.

Gu Yue Bo lightly blew on it; this smoke floated into a wall, but didn't pass through.

Like an ink drop falling into water, a colorful imprint began to appear on the spotless wall.

The imprint grew larger until it formed into an image of the former Awakening Ceremony.

Within this image, Fang Zheng quickly found himself and also many other familiar faces.

All these faces held looks of excitement as they looked all around the cave, their faces full of the immaturity of young. They were like young chicks who had just learned to flap their wings and fly out of the nest.

"That is Fang Yuan....." Similarly, Tie Ruo Nan soon found Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was walking within the group, and although he was looking all around like the rest, his gaze was tranquil and detached. In the group of similar ages, he was like a crane within a group of chicken. If one didn't specifically pay attention to him, normal people wouldn't find any differences between him and the rest.

However, the group in the hall right now were all concentrating on him, exposing this peculiarity.

"Eh? This Fang Yuan is really strange." Right now, even Gu Yue Bo couldn't help but reveal a slightly surprised expression.

The scene on the wall changed to when the group of youths reached the sea of flowers.

The Awakening Ceremony began, and each of the youngsters stepped in the underground river and walked towards the sea of flowers on the opposite bank.

The light of the Hope Gu rose and fell.

There were also the elders' voices which could be clearly heard.

The scenes appeared with such clarity that it felt like one was really there.

First, it was Gu Yue Mo Bei who was found to have B grade aptitude, causing an uproar, then Gu Yue Chi Cheng was also tested to have B grade aptitude.

"It really is strange, this Gu Yue Chi Cheng looks too nervous. His body movements are stiff and his skin color is also not normal, it is just that the light in the underground is dim. But if one carefully looks into it, they will find that something has been applied on his body and that is what is attracting the Hope Gu. Hehe, this is clearly a cheat." Tie Ruo Nan was confident as she observed this.But in the next moment, she immediately frowned.

It was Fang Yuan's turn. He stepped into the river and started moving towards the opposite bank.

The light from the Hope Gu wasn't vigorous. The higher the hope, the greater the disappointment, and the sighs from the youths and the elders could be heard by everyone in the group.

Everything seemed normal, but Tie Ruo Nan's frowns got even deeper. Because Fang Yuan's expression was calm all along the way.

At that time, his back was facing the elders and the youths; they couldn't see his expression. However, as Tie Ruo Nan observed as a spectator, she saw that Fang Yuan's expression didn't change at all, indifferent and cold.

It was as if, as if.....he already knew this would happen!

"This is impossible! If it was me in his place, a fifteen year old with everyone's expectations on me, but was tested to only have C grade aptitude, how could I not feel the least bit of frustration, disappointment and discouragement? How can this be, how can this be!?" Tie Ruo Nan's frowns were almost forming a knot.

Huge doubts and suspicions covered her mind, even stifling her breaths.

Her heart was beating loudly at this moment as all her thoughts flashed through her mind.

What is going on?

How could this be?

"Wait a moment, aptitude.... Could it be?!" Tie Ruo Nan suddenly raised her head. Her intuition had activated and an extremely bold and crazy conjecture formed in her mind.

Light and shadow reflected upon Fang Zheng's face.

The Awakening Ceremony had been the most important turning point in his life.

Before the Awakening Ceremony, he was living a low and insignificant life; a nobody. After the Awakening Ceremony, however, his life was completely changed. He was basked in the lights and his confidence also burst out.

In his memories, the Awakening Ceremony was a picture of blurriness; he had passed through it without even realizing it.

Right now, as he observed this as a spectator, complicated emotions rose up in his heart which he couldn't explain with words.

Fang Zheng looked at himself when it was his turn. He remembered how inferior and weak he had felt at that time.

Soon, he saw how he had tumbled down into the river and struggled to get up, and was pulled up by his brother Fang Yuan, how he had cut out a sorry figure.

A smile appeared on his face—this was the former him, the one who was ridiculed by many!

Then he saw himself walking absent-mindedly towards the opposite bank, and saw his body being enveloped by the lights of the Hope Gu along with the shocks and admiration of many.

That time was a moment of glory, a moment of miracle!

An A grade aptitude, his life would no longer be the same from that moment!

"Fang Zheng, I have a question." Tie Ruo Nan suddenly spoke, breaking Fang Zheng's recollection.

"What is it? Please ask. I will definitely answer everything I know," Fang Zheng turned around with a smile.

"It's about your brother. When your brother pulled you up, I saw his mouth moving, but there was too much noise in the surroundings. What did he say to you, could you tell me the exact words he told?" Tie Ruo Nan asked with a bright gaze.

"His words....." Fang Zheng tried to recall, "He seemed to have said... road?"

"Right. It was road." Fang Zheng's eyes brightened, "I remember it. He said to me, 'The road to the future will be interesting'. Huh? Strange, I didn't think anything of it at that time, but now that I recall it, I think brother's words contained profound meaning... as if, as if he already knew I had A grade aptitude!""No, he didn't mean the A grade aptitude, but something else." Tie Ruo Nan's body trembled, her expression complicated as she let out a breath of turbid air.

Chapter 181: By an odd twist (Long chapter)

"Lady Tie, what do you mean?" Fang Zheng did not understand.

Tie Ruo Nan stretched out her finger, pointing at the wall, "Look at him, Gu Yue Fang Yuan! Don't you think he looks way too calm? When finding out that he has C grade talent, while his blood related brother has A grade talent, normal people would definitely have some reaction to it. But him? Not a trace of emotion! The surrounding praises and mockery cannot move his heart. Don't you find this strange? Throughout the process, he is too calm."

Tie Ruo Nan's words, attracted everyone's gaze.As this scene replayed, all the gazes on the wall landed on Fang Yuan's silhouette.

Fang Yuan stood among the crowd, standing alone, upright. A dark shadow engulfed half his body.

And this scenario, was a huge contrast to the other side.

His own brother, Gu Yue Fang Zheng, was moving step by step, his body bathed in the Hope Gu's pure white light.

At this moment, the elder and younger brother had a swap of identities. The former fell from grace, falling to the lowest point in his life, engulfed by shadows. The latter being blessed by fate, shining in brilliance, climbing his way to the top.

"A fifteen year old youngster, going through such a catastrophic change in his life. But yet, on his body there is no trace of disappointment, perplexity or jealousy. Only calmness, he stood among the crowd, silently watching like he was an outsider, like he was watching a show," Tie Ruo Nan's voice came appropriately.

Yes.

Fang Yuan watched silently.

As the shadows engulfed half his body, his face was expressionless, except the pale colour of a youngster's skin.

Gu Yue Bo stared at the wall, solemn.

Fang Zheng felt a strong chill emerging from deep within his body.

Brother, what in the world are you...

"Even if he had a prediction towards the Awakening Ceremony's results, his heart would definitely feel a change in emotions, and he definitely won't be as calm as this. I used the Cactus Pointer earlier, and always thought that the word 'aptitude' was referring to Gu Yue Chi Cheng. But now that I think about it, it might not refer to Chi Cheng, but most likely Fang Yuan!" Tie Ruo Nan said.

"Lady Tie, what do you mean? I don't understand it at all?" Fang Zheng was more confused.

Tie Ruo Nan raised a finger. "Only one type of situation would cause Fang Yuan to be so calm. That is, he has a trump card that no one knows. Only one situation would cause him to not be jealous, and that is because he has something greater. If two people walked together and one person finds a primeval stone, only if the other finds ten or a hundred would they not be jealous, and have a calm emotion. Fang Yuan is like that."

"You are saying, Fang Yuan cheated and concealed his true aptitude? He is not a C grade talent?" Gu Yue Bo understood Tie Ruo Nan's words, "But if he is A or B grade, why would he not display it outright?"

"Fang Yuan had great wisdom since young!" Tie Ruo Nan's lips curled, her expression confident as she radiated utter confidence. "These few days, I've read some of his poems. With such visions and aspirations, even father was full of praise for him. Such a genius, he naturally has his own schemes."Gu Yue Bo shook his head, "Just with this alone, it still doesn't confirm anything. Concealing aptitude and revealing his aptitude gives two completely different treatment. Even if Fang Yuan didn't know this, after a year in the academy, he should be clear of it."

"Of course he knew, that's why he did not dare to reveal it." Tie Ruo Nan did not beat about the bush, saying confidently.

"What do you mean?" Gu Yue Bo was also lost now.

"Gu Yue clan leader." Tie Ruo Nan turned around, looking at Gu Yue Bo solemnly. "Do you know about Ren Zu's ten children?"

Gu Yue Bo was first stunned, before he immediately reacted, understanding Tie Ruo Nan's true meaning.

HE WAS SHOCKED!

His iris expanded, his mouth agape, not having any of his clan leader disposition.

This was the first time Fang Zheng saw Gu Yue Bo in such a state.

Ren Zu's ten children, eldest son Verdant Great Sun, second daughter Desolate Ancient Moon... the ten children's aptitude defied heaven, thus heaven was wary and did not give them a long lifespan. In the Gu world, the ten children also represented the top ten most extreme aptitudes!

That is—the ten extreme physiques!"Ren Zu's ten children died one by one, and Ren Zu was about to die of old age. But at the end, Ren Zu gathered the corpse of his ten children and sacrificed himself, all going into the stomach of the Derivation Gu. Derivation Gu's stomach burst, exploding and countless life spreading across the land, creating the first batch of mortals. These mortals did not have Ren Zu or the ten children's talent, but they could cultivate after awakening their aperture. Humanity thus grew and developed, forming today's size. Of course, that is all a mythological story."

"But according to the story, every one of us has Ren Zu and his ten children's bloodline in us!" Tie Ruo Nan continued, "The only thing is that most people have diluted bloodlines, or due to intermarriage, restricted each other and caused it to remain dormant. But some people when born have stronger bloodlines, and as they aged or cultivated, they would start going towards the extreme, with one bloodline dominating the rest. When it appears, that is the ten extreme physiques!"

"What is this ten extreme physique?" Fang Zheng asked.

"Don't tell me, Fang Yuan has one of the ten extreme aptitudes?!" Gu Yue Bo was stunned.

"Very likely so! Only the ten extreme physique would cause Fang Yuan to be so calm, and does not have much need for cultivation resources. And only the ten extreme physique that dominates the A grade talent can cause Fang Yuan to not have a hint of jealousy or envy, and only the ten extreme physique can cause Fang Yuan to not reveal his aptitude, as he fears being killed earlier, thus choosing to conceal the truth!" Tie Ruo Nan spoke quickly.

Even Tie Xue Leng would not think of rebirth. Not to mention the young girl. Under all sorts of coincidences, she managed to conjecture a conclusion that was completely the opposite of the truth.

Hearing so, everyone was dumbfounded.

Tie Ruo Nan's analysis had proof and evidence, causing others to believe it. If not for this reason, what other explanation is there?

"Yes, yes! The ten extreme physiques, ten extreme physiques... It has to be the Ancient Moon Desolate Yin physique!"Gu Yue Bo's heart was in turmoil, so excited that his body shuddered.

Others might not know this, but he had the clan's secret history and knew many ancient secrets.

Hundreds of years ago, the first generation ancestor established the village at this spot and named it Gu Yue village. The truth is, the first Gen was not named Gu Yue at all!

Why did he pick the name 'Gu Yue'? It was a mystery.

But before Gen 1 died, he once sighed, "The bloodlines shall be passed down, there will be a great plan of centuries, Ancient Moon Desolate Yin, the world shall shudder!"

He left behind those parting words, and in his will, it predicted that the Gu Yue clan would one day in the future produce a Gu Master with one of the ten extreme aptitudes, the Ancient Moon Desolate Yin body! He would cause the world to tremble and bring the Gu Yue clan towards a new golden age! He also mentioned to his descendants that if one day such a physique appeared, they had to be brought into the blood pond graveyard.

As the clan leader, Gu Yue Bo knew the weakness of the ten extreme physiques, but he had studied this will deeply, and found that the first generation ancestor seemed to know a method to curb this weakness. And this method was kept in his coffin in the graveyard, in an eternal slumber with him.If the Ancient Moon Desolate Yin physique really appeared, bring him to the coffin...

"To think that Gu Yue Fang Yuan is that prophesied genius—the Ancient Moon Desolate Yin physique!" Gu Yue Bo screamed in his heart.

"This cannot be. Under everyone's watchful eye, how can brother cheat under everyone's gaze?" Fang Zheng was completely taken aback, shaking his head, unable to accept this theory.Tie Ruo Nan looked at him in pity. "If even Chi Cheng could cheat, why couldn't Fang Yuan? The ten extreme physiques have endless potential, unlimited possibilities. Maybe Fang Yuan awakened early, and maybe he deceived the bamboo gentleman, due to the ten extreme physique. Or maybe Jia Jin Sheng was killed by Fang Yuan, because he found out this secret of Fang Yuan's."

"Tie family young lady, speak with caution." Gu Yue Bo's expression was unhappy, speaking in a low tone, "Words cannot be spoken mindlessly. Whether Jia Jin Sheng is killed by Fang Yuan, that is not confirmed yet. Fang Yuan is my clan's member, and even if he did commit the act, how we are going to answer to the Jia family is also our matter. You are only here to investigate the case."

Gu Yue clan leader's attitude had changed 180 degrees.

Before, he had thought Fang Yuan was a C grade talent with no possibility of investment. But now, Fang Yuan was the Ancient Moon Desolate Yin physique?!Once it involved the first gen's prophecy and will, his value completely changed.

He had to be protected, and even if the Jia family was offended, there will be no regret!

"Oh crap. This Gu Yue clan leader just turned on his words. How shameless is he, changing his attitude so quickly! I should not have revealed the truth of the ten extreme physiques so soon. The ten extreme aptitudes rule over the A grade talent, so it seems the Gu Yue clan leader wants to protect Fang Yuan now. This will bring great obstruction to solving the case. What do I do now, father?"Tie Ruo Nan's heart sank, and gritting her teeth, she subconsciously looked for her father's figure.

"Eh, where's father?" The young girl was stunned.

Divine investigator Tie was still around earlier, but in the blink of an eye he was gone.

This discovery caused Gu Yue Bo to tense up.Where could Tie Xue Leng have gone at this time? Gu Yue clan leader naturally related it to Fang Yuan.

"Fang Zheng, I am going to look for your brother. Go inform the other clan elders, and quickly assemble to look for me!" Leaving behind his instructions, Gu Yue Bo activated his Gu worm and flew out from the window.

Tie Ruo Nan snorted, running out of the room towards Fang Yuan's residence.

In the entire hall, only Fang Zheng was left.

"How... how can this be?!"

Fang Zheng's current state was not optimistic. His face was pale, his body on the verge of falling over, his spine devoid of all strength.

He felt that his world was covered in darkness.

He felt his world collapsing!How could it become like this?

"Brother's aptitude is the ten extreme physique? My A grade talent is nothing compared to him, a complete failure compared to him!"

As he thought and thought, Fang Zheng's tears fell down.

At this moment, all of his spirit was dampened.

All this time, his greatest achievement was beating Fang Yuan in aptitude. All his confidence was built upon this. But right now, he was told this cruel fact—his aptitude was nothing compared to his brother!

His proudest and most confident area had been suppressed by Fang Yuan.

The confidence he had built up after so long, collapsed in an instant.

"BIG BROTHER!" He raised his head, allowing his tears to flow like a river.

He screamed in his heart, "From start to end, you've been watching a show all along! Seeing me jump up and down, looking at my clown-like performance?"

The corners of his eye looked at the wall again.

The images turned and moved, and people moved all over the place with countless voices praising Fang Zheng's performance. However, Fang Yuan alone stood among the people, his face calm as he watched.

Peacefully watching just like that...

Fang Zheng suddenly felt that in this image, he who was covered in this light of hope, was so childish, so eye-piercing. In his heart, Fang Yuan's calm dark irises showed a divine expression.

His image was gradually enlarged, getting taller and taller until he was unable to climb over, as high as a mountain reaching into the clouds.

Those calm eyes looked at him from that mountain high up in the sky, staring at Fang Zheng's pathetic appearance who was at the foot of the mountain.

Those eyes were like they were saying—Fang Zheng, my laughable little brother, you won't do, you won't do, won't do...

Like the echoes in a valley, reverbing in Fang Zheng's heart.

He felt a strong depression.

Unimaginable depression, suppressing him until he could not breathe properly.

He thought he had gotten rid of this feeling, but to think that that today this feeling assaulted his heart again.

In fact, it was more intense than before by a hundred times!

"AHHHHHH! I'm going to die, I'm going to die!" Fang Zheng's face twitched, veins popping on his forehead. He was drowning in his delusions, gripping his own throat tightly.

With a plop, he fell onto the ground kneeling.

Because he lacked oxygen, his face went red and his tongue stretched out, his eyes gradually popping out.

"No! I don't want to die, I really don't want to die!!" His other hand grabbed the tile on the ground, but as he used too much strength, even his nails broke and blood bled. The intense pain increased Fang Zheng's desire to live!

His body had no injuries, but in his heart, he had received a fatal injury.

He could not get up, for the pride sustaining him had already shattered.

He felt that he did not have the face to see anyone; he was unable to face up to reality, to his older brother. He had become a huge joke, an ironic clown.

He was heart was like dying ash, but this ash still had small embers burning.

"So what if he is the ten extreme aptitude? Brother, you did something wrong. You killed someone, you should not have done so! Right, that's right! You have to pay for your sins of murdering, brother, Jia Jin Sheng was killed by you right? You walked on the wrong path, you did something wrong, so what if your aptitude is better than me?!"

Ring... Something seemed to have sounded off near his ear.

A lump of fire started to burn in Fang Zheng's heart.

The dying ember resurrected!The hand gripping his throat, gradually let go.

Fang Zheng's body was covered in sweat as he kneeled on the ground, one hand sustaining himself as the hand was full of injuries from grabbing the tile.

Droplets of sweat flowed down his face and nose, and onto the file.

His distorted horrifying face had gradually calmed down.

A gust of wind blew along the door and windows, into this hall.

The cold wind of the night sky stimulated his body as he shuddered."HEHEHEHEHEHEHE..." Fang Zheng half laid on the ground as he laughed, his voice shrill and eerie.

The light of the fire danced around his face along with the wind. As it shone on the young man's face, it was not of warmth and brightness, but it resembled the devil's dance.

Chapter 182: Blood pond graveyard

"There's no one here!" Turning the house upside down, Gu Yue Bo did not find Fang Yuan anywhere. A huge rock weighed on his heart. With Fang Yuan and Tie Xue Leng's sudden disappearance, it easily caused him to relate them together.

"Speak, where is Fang Yuan?" Gu Yue Bo's face was grim like water, as he screamed at Tie Ruo Nan who just arrived.

"How would I know where Fang Yuan is?" Tie Ruo Nan's attitude was tough. Even against a Rank four expert, she did not relent.

"Hmph, why did Tie Xue Leng go missing? Tie family's young lady, can you give me an explanation?" Gu Yue Bo said as he got closer to Tie Ruo Nan.

The young girl's expression was slightly stunned. The truth was, this matter had been very peculiar from the start.

The original plan was that her father and her would come here next year. Back then, Tie Xue Leng was solving another case when a white crane suddenly descended from the sky.

The white crane carried a letter, and passed it to Tie Xue Leng.

After seeing this letter, Tie Xue Leng changed his plans and put down the case at hand, heading immediately towards Qing Mao mountain.

If not for the letter, the Tie family father and daughter would not have gotten here so early.

As his daughter, Tie Ruo Nan knew her father well. Normally, only exceptional cases would cause Tie Xue Leng to make such a decision.But, what caused her to not understand was that this Qing Mao mountain case was only about Jia Jin Sheng's death.

Although Jia Jin Sheng's death involved the asset struggle of the Jia family, its severity level was merely average, and was far below the point where the divine investigator has to put so much emphasis on.Towards this, Tie Ruo Nan was always doubtful.

And now, Tie Xue Leng mysteriously disappeared, not even telling his own daughter.

Where did he go? What did he do?

"Father, you have an injury, please take care of your body." Tie Ruo Nan was worried.

This situation had happened several times before. Every time, it was when Tie Xue Leng was fighting against a strong foe and could not distract himself to protect Tie Ruo Nan, thus choosing to battle alone.

His injuries right now were caused by a strong foe under such circumstances previously.

"Although father is injured, he is after all a Rank five expert. Ordinary Rank four Gu Masters are not his match. Father, I believe in you, I will wait for you to return!" Tie Ruo Nan's eyes shone with light as she encouraged herself.

Gu Yue Bo got closer as the young girl raised her head, staring right at the Gu Yue clan leader. "Explanation? You want an explanation, but does it mean I need to give you one?"

Gu Yue Bo's face grew even grimmer as he said, "Little wretch, you sure talk tough, it seems I can only take you captive and use you to exchange for our clan's Fang Yuan!"

"Hehehe." Tie Ruo Nan laughed instead. "Gu Yue clan leader, would you really dare to do such a thing? My uncle is the current Tie clan leader, do you want to cross swords with my Tie family?"

Gu Yue Bo stopped in his tracks.

He was anxious and almost forgot.

Tie family!

It was but a super clan, having thousands of years of legacy, standing strong even today. Standing tall in the Tie clan mountain fort was the Demon Suppression Tower, imprisoning countless demonic Gu Masters, the symbol of the righteous faction.

Gu Yue clan was only a slightly average clan, and was smaller than Jia clan. But Jia clan was also merely a young clan, unable to compare with the Tie clan.

Even in the entire Southern border, the Tie clan is a first class powerhouse, a large clan with strong foundations!

Tie Ruo Nan's words softened. "Gu Yue clan leader, I am not here to be enemies with you. But please believe in my sincerity. I do not know where father went, but I will not leave or secretly run away. The Tie family only dies in battle, there are no cowards that run from battle. Not only will I stay here, I will also arrest the criminal that killed Jia Jin Sheng!"

"Fang Yuan might not be the murderer!" Gu Yue Bo frowned, showing a fierce expression."But he might be!" Tie Ruo Nan stared, her heroism overflowing; at this point she was refusing to relent.

Both sides stared for a long time.

Tie Ruo Nan continued, "Fang Yuan went missing, so it is very likely that he is escaping for his crimes, thus he has greater suspicion. But I will definitely not malign an innocent party!"

"Hmph, I hope so." Gu Yue Bo swung his sleeve and left.

Fifteen minutes later....

Gurgle gurgle.

The spirit spring's whirlpool moved violently as a lotus image flickered above the spring water like an image.

Pieces of primeval stones were thrown in by Fang Yuan, causing the appearance of the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus to become clearer.

"Earlier at the classmate gathering, they gave me around ten thousand primeval stones. Together with Gu Yue Mo Chen's forty thousand, I've already thrown them all in. Why is it that this Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus still hasn't shown its true body?"

Fang Yuan stared intently through the crystal walls, glaring at the center of the spirit spring, feeling uncertain.

The Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus was very precious. After continuous advancing and reaching Rank six, its value would be no less than the Spring Autumn Cicada.

Even in his previous life, Fang Yuan had only heard of it, and never interacted with it.

Thus right now, it was his first time seeing one, and so he was slightly unsure.

But he soon calmed himself, laughing, "Around fifty thousand primeval stones, it's more than enough. Why am I worrying over nothing here? So what if the refinement fails? Hehehe."Thinking so, he no longer hesitated. Taking in a deep breath, he jumped up, knocking onto the crystal wall.

This wall was formed by the Moat Gu.

When Fang Yuan knocked onto it, it was like jumping into the water. There was a ripple in the walls as he was instantly swallowed up.

Water surrounded Fang Yuan from all directions.

Fang Yuan opened his eyes, but he could not see the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.

The Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus could only be seen through the water crystal walls before extraction.

Fang Yuan knew this well, and was not surprised. He had already estimated the distance, and even accounted for the refraction of the light due to the water, and grabbed according to his memory.

This grab, was like grabbing out of thin air, conjuring a lotus.

The lotus was blue and white, its petals closed, looking like a lamp filled with a holy aura. But it had its own consciousness, and even though it was grabbed by Fang Yuan, it resisted.

But that was nothing!

Just by leaking a little of the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura, this Rank three flower Gu was instantly refined.

Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus obtained!

In the spring water, Fang Yuan's lips curled into a smile.

He willed, and the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus turned into a white blue light, shooting into his aperture.

Without the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, the numerous whirlpools in the spirit spring vanished. The spring water that was filled with vitality turned into a puddle of still water without any signs of life.

"The spirit spring is no more. This place is no longer safe, I have to leave as soon as possible." Fang Yuan's expression turned serious, and just as he was about to leave, something suddenly happened!

Deep in the spirit spring, a blinding blood colored light shot out.

A large suction force suddenly appeared. Caught off guard, Fang Yuan was sucked deep into the water.

The spring water turned red, becoming blood water, wrapping around Fang Yuan completely, dragging him down.Sky Canopy Gu! Thunderwings Gu!

In the moment of crisis, Fang Yuan screamed in his heart and a white armor appeared on his body. At the same time, a pair of large lightning wings appeared behind his back.

Thunderwings spread, giving Fang Yuan an upward force. But the blood water came endlessly, and its suction force became greater and greater; there was no way to oppose it.

Puff...

Hearing the water all around him, Fang Yuan was dragged by the currents, along the tunnel, heading straight down.

Just when his breath was used up, the surrounding pressure vanished.

Fang Yuan took a deep breath. At least he did not die of suffocation, but he found that he was falling from a high spot.

He subconsciously activated his wings, but the Thunderwings Gu was in bad shape.

The originally strong wings, were tired and soft.

Fang Yuan's heart sank. He tried his best to maintain his balance in the air, slowing his descent.

This was an area underground. It was not dark, but filled with red light. Fang Yuan was falling from about fifteen metres, and below him, was a pond.

But this underground pond was not of the transparent colour; it was red, like blood water.

No, it IS blood water!

The piercing blood stench assaulted Fang Yuan as he continued to fall.

This situation was weird no matter how he looked at it, so for safety, Fang Yuan did not want to land in this bloody pond.

Chainsaw Golden Centipede!

He activated the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, his palm entering the centipede's mouth and swinging it like a whip.

The golden centipede's body stretched to the longest, and its tail stabbed into the mountain wall at the side.

Fang Yuan willed with his mind, and the golden centipede's body constricted. This way, it brought his body to the side of the mountain wall.

These walls were slippery and did not have a good landing spot. But as Fang Yuan relied on the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, he managed to find an uneven area and placed his feet above.

"Where the fuck is this?" Stabilizing his body, Fang Yuan immediately observed the surroundings.

According to his estimations, this should be in a place deeper underground, even below the underground cave.

"How can there be such a place?" Fang Yuan was shocked. In his previous life, he was not strong enough to learn about the secrets of the higher-ups.

The truth is, this was the blood pond graveyard, the forbidden grounds that buried the first generation's coffin. Even among clan elders, only one or two knew this secret.

Fang Yuan looked down. This blood pond shone with a bloody radiance. Its circumference was even larger than the village, emitting an eerie and scary aura.

At the top of the cave, there was up to a hundred holes that had water gushing down, bringing the shells, turtles, snakes and fish from the river with it.

Swoosh swoosh... Streams of water continued to pour down from the holes, entering into the blood pond.

The blood water was turbulent as numerous seafood moved around, entering the pond. However, in a few breaths, all the blood in their bodies were sucked out. They turned into dry corpses and floated on the surface of the water, appearing and disappearing as the waves moved them about.

The blood pond's redness only intensified.

As Fang Yuan looked on, his iris shrunk a little. If he had landed in this pond, even with the Sky Canopy Gu's protection, he would not be in good shape.

He continued to observe, and other than fresh dry corpses, there were also some bones in the water.

Some were fish bones, bear bones, and even human skeletons.

This was a giant burial ground; it was creepy, and bloody.

The ripples and waves in the blood pond raged on and swept into the surrounding walls, the bright red and glowing blood water entering the surrounding soil. This caused the soil to all turn into a bright red color, turning into red soil.

Chapter 183: Blood Sea Ancestor

"Wait a second, red soil?"

Fang Yuan's mind jolted at the sight.

He stretched his hand out and grabbed the wall beside him, taking out a lump of red soil.

This red soil was very soft and emitted a faint red light. Fang Yuan merely pressed it lightly, but it crumbled down.

"So, it was like this." He seemed to have come to a realization.

The first time he had entered the secret cave inside the rock crack, he saw that the secret cave was full of this red soil which emitted faint glow; there was no need for any other lighting source.

He had felt it weird at the time because Qing Mao mountain's soil was blue-black in color. He had thought this was arranged by the Flower Wine Monk, but now it seemed that the source was this strange blood lake.

Fang Yuan felt even more wary; his five hundred years of experience had almost become an intuition.

"This place is not only strange, but also dangerous. I don't have the time to dilly-dally, I need to think of how to leave here." Fang Yuan raised his head and looked at the cave walls, where hundreds of holes were in the top part of the wall; which was the one connected to the spirit spring?

Fang Yuan hesitated for a moment.

Water could flow down here, but it didn't mean that the passages were wide enough for a human to pass through.

"And...." Fang Yuan looked grave as he tried shaking his two wings.

However, he couldn't control these thunderwings perfectly like before, and the originally clear blue thunder was now stained with some scarlet; it gave off a contradictory feeling of power and weakness existing at the same time.

The Thunderwings Gu had become unreliable, it was very possible for it to screw up and drop Fang Yuan in the middle of flight.

Swoosh....

An inexplicable undercurrent surged up from within the blood lake, giving off the enormous aura of Rank five gu.

"That is...." Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk; a long shadow gradually appeared in the blood lake.

Its length surpassed forty meters and its width over six meters.

This was an enormous python; it dwelled in the depths of the blood lake, but now that it had smelled out the scent of flesh on Fang Yuan, it came out to begin the hunt!

"Damn it....." Fang Yuan felt a pressing urge in his heart.

Right now, he was relying on the Chainsaw Golden Centipede to puncture the wall, barely managing to hang onto the soft red soil. And with his long hair and black gown, he looked like a black ant compared to the enormous blood lake.

Hundreds of black dots appeared in the blood lake and rose up, just like a travelling shoal of fish.

Whooshhh.....

They were much faster than the giant python and flew out of the blood lake within moments, revealing their appearance.

These were not fish, but bats.

These blood colored bats had two long pointed ears with two pairs of wings. The main pair of wings were rather big, whereas the secondary pair of wings was on the smaller side and was below the main wings.

They didn't have claws, but the edges of the two pairs of wings were as sharp as steel blades.

"Rank three—bladewing blood bat Gu?" A name immediately appeared in Fang Yuan's mind.

These bladewing blood bat groups were directing their intense murderous aura towards him, but the first thing that appeared in his mind was 'that' image.

In the image from the Photo-audio Gu, the Flower Wine Monk's whole body was covered with blood, with severe injuries to the point of being near death.

Moonshadow Gu was not able to cause such injuries, but these bladewing blood bats were a different matter.

"Could it be that the Flower Wine Monk had come to this place and was injured by these bladewing blood bats?" Fang Yuan's thoughts revolved rapidly.

Flower Wine Monk's death had been shrouded in riddles. Now, it appeared extremely likely that it was due to this place.

"Bladewing blood bat...." Fang Yuan murmured. In fact, this Gu wasn't a stranger to him.

Even though this Gu was a Rank three Gu, it was very easy to feed, its food being blood.

In his previous life, he had established the Bloodwing Devil Sect, and the symbol of the sect was precisely the bladewing blood bat. The resources from the devil sect were more than enough to support close to ten thousand bladewing blood bat Gu, allowing the sect to establish a terrifying might and spread terror.

More precisely, he owed his success to bladewing blood bats.

After over four hundred years in his previous life, he had accidently obtained an inheritance from the Blood Sea Ancestor. With the colonies of bladewing blood bats and his own Rank five cultivation, he became an overlord of a region.

This Blood Sea Ancestor was a Rank seven demonic path Gu Master who took lives as easily as cutting grass, and his evil reputation was such that it resounded throughout the world, having his name recorded in history.

At the beginning, he was just a mortal, but through luck and destiny, he became a Gu Master of demonic path. He started out from the lowest of levels and rose up in ranks, before becoming an authority of demonic path after eight hundred years.

He didn't have high aptitude, thus he had limited primeval essence in his aperture. Therefore, he had a crazed interest towards researching the fusion of Gu worms.

Wild Gu worms possessed their own will and could absorb the natural primeval essence in the air by themselves. However, after a Gu worm was refined by a Gu Master, its willpower would be dominated by the Gu Master, and it would lose the ability to absorb the surrounding primeval essence. It would be able to only absorb the primeval essence in the Gu Master's aperture.

Blood Sea Ancestor had invested a lot of efforts in researching Gu which could absorb natural primeval essence even after being refined by a Gu Master.

The righteous Gu Masters were very afraid of this. They were extremely worried that the Blood Sea Ancestor would succeed in his research. As a result, they organized countless traps before moving in for the kill.

In the end, Blood Sea Ancestor wasn't able to succeed, but it also wasn't a complete failure.

He succeeded in producing the fusion recipes of bladewing blood bat, blood guillotine and blood frenzy Gu.

Rank three bladewing blood bat Gu was his first accomplishment. It was very easy to feed, but it still needed the Gu Master to provide primeval essence. The colony of bladewing blood bats was very special; a Gu Master just needed to control a male bat, and they could indirectly command all the other female bats.

Blood frenzy Gu was his second accomplishment. This Gu was formless; as a ball of blood essence, it survived by attaching itself to other beings. It was a Rank four Gu and had a very unusual ability. Every Gu worm infected by its aura could absorb natural primeval essence every now and then. But it had a great disadvantage—the Gu worms affected by the Blood frenzy Gu would gradually leave the control of the Gu Master and would turn into a pool of blood after a period of time.

Blood guillotine was the Blood Sea Ancestor's last accomplishment. This Gu was a Rank five Gu and was no doubt more advanced than the previous two. Its usability and feeding were fused into one. Usings wars to sustain itself, it multiplied by swallowing Gu Master's blood. It didn't need the Gu Master to provide it with any primeval essence.

Unfortunately, after the Blood Sea Ancestor created the blood guillotine, due to the many battles and the entrapment by the righteous path, he was defeated.

He suffered from fatal wounds that could not be healed, and he carved out a bloody escape from the layers of entrapment.

The righteous path figures were worried about his final counterattack which could endanger themselves, so they didn't have any inclination to chase after him and looked on as he made his getaway. Since then, these righteous path figures would regret the moment every time they recalled it; they regretted that they let him get away.

The Blood Sea Ancestor knew his death was a sure thing, so he started setting up a large scale inheritance. In the limited time before his death, with the strength of his Rank seven cultivation, he unexpectedly set up hundreds of thousands of inheritance grounds; his inheritances extended everywhere from the Middle Continent to the Southern Border and other places.

Right before his death, he smiled devilishly, "The blood path is not alone, the legacy will continue for all eternity!"

This statement was not in the least false, for countless Gu Masters benefited from his inheritances, and thus the demonic path flourished greatly.

No matter the bladewing blood bat Gu, the blood frenzy Gu or the blood guillotine, they were all very easy to raise and multiply. Maybe in some unremarkable valleys, at poor villages, at no-man deserts, or beside some mountain paths, you might find two or three Gu left casually by the Blood Sea Ancestor.

These Gu were easy to raise and didn't have a high demand for primeval essence, thus they could easily be used by Gu Masters with ordinary aptitudes.

Survival was a difficult thing in this world, so which Gu Master wouldn't thirst for stronger powers? The Gu worms left by the Blood Sea Ancestor represented a whole new strength; this strength was a quick and easy way to rise in power, and it became more welcomed than other Gu worms.

Power itself had no sins; it became good in the hands of good, and evil in the hands of evil. But in the world, how many people could have a resolute mind after a sudden increase in strength?

A man who got money would often become fickle. A sudden rise in strength would certainly nourish ambitions that weren't there before.

As a result, many Gu Masters that obtained the Blood Sea Ancestor's legacy would become a devil that massacred everything. Even many righteous path figures had changed their sides.

The inheritances of blood Gu brought great turmoil and danger towards the whole world.

In each inheritance of the Blood Sea Ancestor, there were often only two to three Gu. However, these inheritances were like a spark of fire that could cause a prairie fire if left alone!

There would be demonic path Gu Masters who would come into possession of the blood Gu every so often and cause chaos. Some of them would fail; killed away in some villages. Some would succeed temporarily and become a huge figure, harming a whole region.

No matter if they succeeded temporarily, or failed, at the moment of their exhaustion, they would also leave behind new blood inheritances.

Thus, the blood calamity continued endlessly. Not only did it not end with the death of the Blood Sea Ancestor through the combined strength of the righteous path, it instead thrived even more greatly with the foundations left behind, unable to be eliminated as it continued for eternity.

It was to the extent that the righteous path figures would frequently curse, "These accursed Blood Gu Masters! We have already killed waves upon waves of them. But if we become even a bit careless, we will see a new one coming up from nowhere!"

By now, the Blood Sea Inheritances were already publicly recognized as the most popular in the whole world, with the greatest number of inheritances. There was no competition!

In the strictest sense, Fang Yuan had received a favor from the Blood Sea Ancestor.

"In my previous life, only after over four hundred years, I found a blood sea inheritance and was then able to begin my rule. Now, if I can subdue these blood bats, it will be like completing four hundred years of effort."

Blood bats charged at him but Fang Yuan was not afraid.

He had the Spring Autumn Cicada, so these bats would submit without question in front of the Rank six aura. The only problem was the Rank five Blood Python that was still concealed, hiding within the blood lake.

"But this situation is somewhat fishy. The Blood Sea Ancestor's inheritances normally only have two-three Gu worms. How come this place has hundreds of bladewing blood bats? Could it be... that rumor is true?"

The rumor said that the Blood Sea Ancestor's hundreds of thousands of inheritances were diversions, and the true inheritances were only a few.

In these few inheritances, the Blood Sea Ancestor was said to have concealed his best Gu worms, or research insights or fusion recipes.

"Could this place be a true inheritance ground of the Blood Sea Ancestor?" When Fang Yuan thought of this, his heart started to beat loudly.

His thoughts moved like lightning and although he thought of many things, only a little time had passed in reality.

Bladewing blood bats charged at him one after another; Fang Yuan was calm, his long hair and black gown fluttering in the air as he climbed up the wall and was going to summon Spring Autumn Cicada.

But right at this time, there was a sudden change!

"As expected, this place is hiding the blood calamity!" A deep and firm voice, loud like the clash between iron and stone, came from the top of the cave and echoed within the blood lake.

Divine Investigator Tie Xue Leng!